<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>30</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/class/smuggler/sergeant_klewer.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice working with you, Captain. Stay alive out there, yeah?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574295" id2="17" version="1065353216">And Republic Customs thinks you have full diplomatic access to the planet. That'll keep the heat off you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574297" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here are the supplies Beryl Thorne needs delivered. Take them to the camp at these coordinates. They're for an engineer named Ovold.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck out there, Captain. Try not to get dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Help me with those scavengers, and I'll handle Republic Customs. That's the deal, yeah?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574306" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the captain, yeah? I'm Sergeant Klewer. Risha says &quot;hello.&quot; I hear you two are in business together.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574308" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to square you with Republic Customs. Agent Soganti is watching your every move, but I can fix that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="574309" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a law-abiding citizen.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Relax, Captain. I'm a friend. Your partner and me go way back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="574312" id2="17" version="1065353216">He doesn't scare me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't underestimate Agent Soganti. The man never sleeps more than three hours a day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="574315" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is an obvious trick.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me some credit. If I was trying to trap you, would I be this blunt about it?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574318" id2="17" version="1065353216">Risha expressed some concern you might not be able to leave Taris with what you came here for--not unless Republic Customs lays off.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574320" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can give you temporary diplomatic immunity. Republic Customs won't be allowed to search you or your starship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="574321" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="574322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only temporary immunity?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your credentials will hold up until Agent Soganti can run a full background check. That will take several days. By then, you'll be gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574325" id2="17" version="1065353216">The thing is, I need you to scratch my back while I scratch yours. We've got a problem with scavengers raiding our supply lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="574327" id2="17" version="1065353216">And what do you want from me?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574328" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm looking for professional help dealing with some nasty scavengers. They're making a lot of trouble for our supply lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574330" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need you to convince the scavengers to relocate. When that's done, you'll be off Republic Customs' radar. It's a deal, yeah?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="574331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, it's a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="574332" id2="17" version="1065353216">I deliver the supplies first.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Funny thing... I've lost track of Beryl Thorne's supplies. I'll probably find them by the time you handle this favor for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="574335" id2="17" version="1065353216">No way.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't make me be unpleasant, Captain. If you won't do this favor for me, you won't get Beryl Thorne's supplies.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574338" id2="17" version="1065353216">The scavengers have been coming from these coordinates. They probably have a camp there. Make life extra unpleasant for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574340" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you get back, I'll have diplomatic credentials and the supplies you came for ready to go. Have fun out there, yeah?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="574344" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enjoy Taris. Try to keep your head attached to your body, yeah?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
