<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>65</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/world/escape_and_evade/captain_labe.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714125" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Eighty-third Platoon will always be at your service, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714126" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm grateful for your help, sir. I trust you'll keep the details of our mission classified.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714127" id2="17" version="1065353216">You performed admirably for the Empire. You should consider a career in the military.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714128" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm grateful Lieutenant Herral and his men didn't die in vain. Thank you for recovering that stolen data card.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714131" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Labe, Eighty-third Platoon. I'll do my best to serve, my lord, though my resources are limited.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714133" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Labe, Eighty-third Platoon, sir. Unless this is an official visit, I'll have to ask you to wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714135" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Labe, Eighty-third Platoon. I don't normally work with mercenaries, but I'm willing to pay for some extra eyes and ears right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714137" id2="17" version="1065353216">You there. I'm Captain Labe, Eighty-third Platoon. I could use your assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714139" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of my squads disappeared while returning from an important mission. I'm mounting a search-and-rescue operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714140" id2="17" version="1065353216">A holorecording from your squad leader directed me here, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714140" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Herral sent me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714141" id2="17" version="1065353216">Holorecording? I don't understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714143" id2="17" version="1065353216">The situation is under control, Captain. I finished the mission your men started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714143" id2="17" version="1065353216">I already did their job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714144" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finished? You don't even know the details of our mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget the search and rescue. The mission's over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714146" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need for that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714147" id2="17" version="1065353216">How would you know that? Our mission is classified.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait... that data card you're holding. I recognize those markings. That's the security codes the traitors stole.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714151" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sent Lieutenant Herral's squad to recover that. They're... they didn't make it, did they?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714152" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were ambushed and slaughtered by a Republic patrol.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714152" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, they didn't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714153" id2="17" version="1065353216">They fought bravely, but they were outnumbered by Republic forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714153" id2="17" version="1065353216">It wasn't their fault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714154" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic troops made short work of your crack team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714154" id2="17" version="1065353216">Obviously not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714155" id2="17" version="1065353216">I served with Lieutenant Herral for six years. This must not stand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714157" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time to burn every Republic outpost to the ground. Show those dogs how the Eighty-third Platoon avenges its fallen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714159" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll organize what's left of my command and drive those scum off Balmorra by myself, if I have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714160" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hatred will win this war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714160" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes--to battle!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714161" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I tell the men, we'll have all the hate we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Herral stood his ground when he should've retreated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be a fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Herral was one of the best I've served with... but you're right. We need a solid plan of attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714166" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good you retrieved that data card. If the resistance had cracked our security codes, their saboteurs and commandos could've struck where we're most vulnerable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714167" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the resistance had any courage, they'd face us in open battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714167" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those cowards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714168" id2="17" version="1065353216">They don't have the spine for that. Neither does the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714170" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps this data card might be safer with me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714170" id2="17" version="1065353216">It sounds quite useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714171" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's, ahem, very probably true, my lord. However, I've already signaled central command to come get it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714173" id2="17" version="1065353216">The resistance will certainly make another attempt to steal this data card.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tighten your security.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714174" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't get another chance at the security codes--I'll see to that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spare me the pretty speeches. I did this for the reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714176" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care about that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714177" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. You're a mercenary, after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714179" id2="17" version="1065353216">I always protect the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714180" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done the Eighty-third Platoon--and the Empire--a great honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714182" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your thanks isn't enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714183" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything my unit can spare is yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714185" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish I could offer a greater reward, but I'm afraid this will have to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714187" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've inspired us to take action, my lord. Those Republic scum will suffer for what they've done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714188" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd better start gathering my men, sir. I think a frontal assault might take those Republic dogs by surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714189" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd invite you to join my men assaulting the Republic outpost, but this is a score we need to settle personally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714190" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me, but I need to rally the men. We've got a score to settle with the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714191" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should file a report with central command. I appreciate your wise counsel, my lord. Good day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714192" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to request reinforcements from central command. Thanks for the strategic advice, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714193" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a head for battle strategy, mercenary. Thanks for helping me keep mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714194" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate all your help--and your advice. Stay safe out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714198" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me, my lord, but I'm overseeing a vital mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714199" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apologies, sir, but I'm busy directing a classified operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714200" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're looking for work, we're not hiring any mercenaries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714201" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me, but I'm monitoring an important mission.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
