<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>13</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/operations/republic/operations_terminal.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1112206" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Republic by completing Operation: Scum and Villainy in any difficulty mode.

[Operation: Scum and Villainy]
Defeat Dread Master Styrak (Any Difficulty Mode)</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1112207" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Republic by completing Operation: Terror From Beyond in any difficulty mode.

[Operation: Terror From Beyond]
Defeat The Terror from Beyond (Any Difficulty Mode)</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1112208" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --

A large cache of Isotope-5 is being held by renegade mercenaries in the courtyard of Toborro the Hutt's palace. They've got a massive Isotope-5 droid posted on guard duty at all times--our forces haven't been able to put a dent in the thing. We need you to take that droid down.

-- END --

[Operation: Toborro's Courtyard]
Defeat Golden Fury (Any Difficulty Mode).</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1112210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Republic by completing Operation: The Eternity Vault in any difficulty mode.

[Operation: The Eternity Vault]
Defeat Soa, the Infernal One (Any Difficulty Mode).</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1112211" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Republic by completing Operation: Karagga's Palace in any difficulty mode.

[Operation: Karagga's Palace]
Defeat Karagga the Unyielding (Any Difficulty Mode).</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1112212" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Republic by completing Operation: Explosive Conflict in any difficulty mode.

[Operation: Explosive Conflict]
Defeat Warlord Kephess (Any Difficulty Mode).</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1112720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Republic by defeating dangerous, high-priority targets on planets across the Galaxy. Surviving an encounter with these enemies will require a large, coordinated Operations group.

Defeat three Heroic World Bosses:

Target List
-----------------------
Trapjaw (Tatooine, Level 30)
R4-GL (Nar Shaddaa, Level 32)
Ulgo Siegebreaker (Alderaan, Level 35)
Rogue Cartel Warbot (Quesh, Level 38)
Snowblind (Hoth, Level 44)
Primal Destroyer (Belsavis, Level 44)
Gargath (Hoth, Level 49)
Nightmare Pilgrim (Voss, Level 50)
Dreadtooth (Section X, Level 50)</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1125571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Republic by completing Operation: The Dread Palace in any difficulty mode.

[Operation: The Dread Palace]
Defeat The Dread Masters (Any Difficulty Mode).</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1126869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Republic by completing Operation: The Dread Fortress in any difficulty mode.

[Operation: The Dread Fortress]
Defeat Dread Master Brontes (Any Difficulty Mode).</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193721" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Republic by defeating the following enemies in any difficulty mode.

[Operation: The Ravagers]
Defeat Captain Coratanni (Any Difficulty Mode).</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Republic by defeating the following enemies in any difficulty mode.

[Operation: Temple of Sacrifice]
Defeat Revan (Any Difficulty Mode).</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid in diminishing the former Sith Emperor's power by defeating the following enemies in any difficulty mode:

[Operation: Heart of Ruin]
Defeat the Colossal Monolith (Any Difficulty Mode)

Defeat the Worldbreaker Monolith</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1228507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid in the suppression of emerging threats on Iokath by completing Operation: Gods from the Machine in any difficulty mode.

[Operation: Gods from the Machine]
Defeat IZAX, The Destroyer (Any Difficulty Mode).</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
