<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>152</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/manaan/republic/theron_shan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126781" id2="17" version="1065353216">...I just think it might put everyone at ease if you ditched the lightsaber.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get down to that lab and see what's happening. I'll stay in contact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127151" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey. I just called Tee-Three to have him find you, but it looks like you were already on the way. That's impressive timing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127152" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you doing here, Theron?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127153" id2="17" version="1065353216">Digging, just like I said I would. Let me show you what I've got so far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127154" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey. I just called Tee-Three to have him find you, and he said you were already on the way. That's some impressive timing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127155" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are we here, Theron? What is this all about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's run through what I've got so far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel Darok commanded our strike on Korriban, supposedly to gather valuable intelligence data--none of which has been turned over to the SIS.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127160" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the Sith you spoke to on Tython: Darth Arkous. Member of the Dark Council, organizer of the attack on the Jedi Temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127161" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've found a connection between them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127162" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes--they've both been paying visits to the same genetics lab, in an underwater facility here on Manaan. They're headed down there again as we speak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127163" id2="17" version="1065353216">How quickly can you arrange transportation? We can catch up to them and find out the truth before any more lives are lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'll catch them both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it some kind of medical treatment facility? Experimental research? Something else?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the lab.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127165" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no documentation for the lab's purpose, but traffic in and out is mostly freight, not passenger. Probably research--which fits my other findings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127166" id2="17" version="1065353216">How long were you planning to wait before you contacted me? This is a major threat!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127166" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should have called sooner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127167" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wanted more than just circumstantial evidence. And I got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127169" id2="17" version="1065353216">With Darok and Arkous working together, the timing of the attacks makes perfect sense. They weren't really attacks at all--they were robberies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127170" id2="17" version="1065353216">Robberies? What do you mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127171" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imps hauled something out of the Jedi Temple just before you got there. A few security holos were still working, so I got a shot of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darok's top guy, Commander Jensyn, grabbed something similar on Korriban. I ran the images through some databases--they were pieces of ancient Rakata technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any technology that the Sith would keep under lock and key must be bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127175" id2="17" version="1065353216">As in, technology from the ruthless empire that conquered the galaxy before the founding of the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127175" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakata tech?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. You can understand my concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ancient technology, galactic conspiracies, secret labs... should we get our heads checked?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127178" id2="17" version="1065353216">This gets crazier every minute.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127179" id2="17" version="1065353216">I probably wouldn't believe it either, if I hadn't seen all of the evidence for myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127181" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm pretty sure Darok and Arkous have brought their Rakata tech to the lab, but you're going to have to go in to figure out exactly what they're doing with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127183" id2="17" version="1065353216">There. I've arranged transport to get you in, but security will probably come after you with more than smiles. Don't let them slow you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127185" id2="17" version="1065353216">While you're searching the lab for Arkous and Darok, I'm going to meet with one last contact. I think she might have some interesting intel for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127186" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;She&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127187" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wouldn't believe me if I told you. Good luck down there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127681" id2="17" version="1065353216">There you are. Our first few interviews with Jakarro's &quot;friends&quot; went well, believe it or not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127683" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're going to start with some antique smugglers from the Exchange, see if the Revanites have gone for any other Rakata tech.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you found any traces of Colonel Darok or Darth Arkous?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything from Darok or Arkous?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not one. Apparently the Revanites know a thing or two about staying hidden.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127687" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to see you're still in one piece. It's a good look for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127687" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] It's good to see you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127688" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I was starting to wonder if it was Lana you had your eyes on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127692" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still think working with a Sith is more trouble than it's worth. We can handle this on our own, Theron.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127692" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can do that without Lana.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127693" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're good, I know that. And I'm not so bad, either. But I still think we're better off spreading the work--and the risk--around a bit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127695" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Revanites did manage to take us out... at least there will still be someone else going after them, even if it is a backstabbing Sith and a murderous Wookiee.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127697" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;The Order of Revan&quot;. Hmph. My family has even more pull than I thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127698" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're related to Revan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127698" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're related to Revan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127699" id2="17" version="1065353216">You never heard that story? Bastila Shan, Revan's great Jedi love? The name made it all the way down to me, even if the Force didn't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127701" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look: Revan was a wild card, and his crazy cult of followers is bound to be the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Highly-trained bravado aside, we're up against some long odds here. Are you sure you still want to be dragged into all of this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127704" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Revanites are a danger to the entire Republic. We can't afford to ignore them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127704" id2="17" version="1065353216">This threat must be ended.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127705" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you keep going up against impossible enemies, it's going to turn into a habit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127706" id2="17" version="1065353216">I follow the will of the Force. As long as I'm needed, I'll help--it's as simple as that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127706" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force guides me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just like Master Zho always said.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127709" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not fighting odds, we're fighting people. And people can always be taken down, no matter what the numbers say.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127709" id2="17" version="1065353216">Odds don't mean anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127710" id2="17" version="1065353216">You make it all sound so easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127711" id2="17" version="1065353216">I figure, the longer the odds, the better the payout. And I love a good payout.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127711" id2="17" version="1065353216">Definitely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127712" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess that's one way of looking at it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127714" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not going anywhere, Theron. You can count on that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127714" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127715" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teams aren't my usual style, but I think I could get used to this one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127717" id2="17" version="1065353216">They tried to kill me. I'm not going to let that slide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127717" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't quit without payback.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127718" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and Jakarro will make a great team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127720" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, I'd better get back to Lana and Jakarro before they... do... anything. I'll get in touch as soon as we get something concrete--stay safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that really necessary? Surely I'm not as intimidating as you imply?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127724" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can understand our concern, I'm sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127724" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to play coy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127725" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I'm sure you can understand mine. I've come to help, and I can hardly do that without my weapon of choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your mastery of the Dark Side is plain enough--but I also sense your intentions. You mean no harm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127727" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sense the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron mentioned that you were quite perceptive. I'm Lana Beniko.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127730" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've earned a little trust so far--I'm sure you wouldn't mind earning a bit more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127730" id2="17" version="1065353216">Convince me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127731" id2="17" version="1065353216">As pragmatic as described. I'm Lana Beniko.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127733" id2="17" version="1065353216">After the day I've had, one Sith lord isn't worth getting worked up about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127733" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't scare easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127734" id2="17" version="1065353216">You see, Theron? We'll get on just fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127736" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we just spent some time together, I'll bet we could come to an understanding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127736" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Maybe so, maybe not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127737" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm confident we'll be seeing a lot of each other in the days to come.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127739" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko: dedicated Imperial citizen and fully-armed Sith lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127741" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you don't need to worry about that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith can't be trusted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deception is one of the key weapons in the Sith arsenal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith lie. It's in your nature.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127747" id2="17" version="1065353216">You trust him, and lying is the core of his profession. Couldn't &quot;Lana Beniko, terrifying lord of the Sith&quot; earn the same trust?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arkous manipulated her and her people, same as Darok did to us. She's already shared a lot of good intel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Based on your work in the lab, we know that Arkous and Darok are working together, manipulating both sides for some third party.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127753" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're Revanites. Members of the Order of Revan, a secretive cult that's had its claws in the Empire for many years. It seems they've pierced the Republic now, as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127754" id2="17" version="1065353216">How large is this cult? What kind of resources do they have?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me more about them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127755" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given what you uncovered in the lab, they're much larger and better funded than we'd ever guessed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127757" id2="17" version="1065353216">I helped pull Revan out of the Maelstrom Prison. I heard he died not too long afterward... was that incorrect?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127757" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127758" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not as far as Lana or I know. But dead men can be even better cult leaders than live ones.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127760" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure I've ever heard of this &quot;Revan&quot; person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127761" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure Theron could tell you all about him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127763" id2="17" version="1065353216">He was a Jedi, then he was a Sith, then he was a Jedi again, all about three hundred years ago. I'll send you a history file.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127765" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't be so secretive once we tell everyone what they've been doing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's expose them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127766" id2="17" version="1065353216">All of the physical evidence went down with the lab. How would we convince anyone?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127768" id2="17" version="1065353216">We know the Revanites have highly-placed moles in both the Republic and the Empire. That means we have no idea who we can really trust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127769" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then it's up to us to stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1127770" id2="17" version="1065353216">Droid! Tell them this is boring and I don't care about any of it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh... my master, the incomparable star captain Jakarro....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127773" id2="17" version="1065353216">...Is more interested in action than discussion. And this is his translator, C2-D4.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127774" id2="17" version="1065353216">...Has a short attention span. And this is what's left of his translator, C2-D4.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Former interpreter for Her Imminence, Queen Lina of Onderon!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127777" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, we got that earlier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127779" id2="17" version="1065353216">All of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1127781" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you understand me, then understand this: the Pub and Imp left me to die--twice! I won't rest until I've tasted their blood!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127783" id2="17" version="1065353216">I saw your list of known accomplices earlier--quite impressive. Could any of them help us find where these traitors might be hiding?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1127785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course! But I do the talking, understand?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Superb! Then if Theron agrees...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go ahead and get the ship prepped. I'll cover our tracks and catch up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well. It's been a pleasure meeting you. May the Force ever serve you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127793" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd better travel separately. If the Revanites put a tail on us, they won't know which to follow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127794" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think these cultists realize who they're up against.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127794" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thinking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suits me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127797" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Revanites realize their trap didn't work, won't that make things worse?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127797" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should we lay low?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127798" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think it's better if they do see you. They'll have to alter their plans to compensate--and that's when they'll make mistakes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana isn't our ally, Theron. She's going to betray us, sooner or later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127800" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't trust a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127801" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're probably right. But for now, she can be useful--the Revanites are just as dangerous to the Empire as they are to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127803" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're going to need allies, even if they aren't as trustworthy as we'd like. But that doesn't mean we have to let our guard down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127805" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd better get moving. Watch your back out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127809" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not all you've discovered, is it? You've found something else, something they've already done....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127809" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's more, isn't there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127810" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Colonel Darok is working with the Imps, we need to move on him right away, before he can do any more damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127810" id2="17" version="1065353216">So Darok is a traitor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127811" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't even gotten to the good part.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127813" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've flown with some pretty nasty characters--didn't mean we were buddies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could just be a coincidence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127814" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127820" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're going to get to the bottom of all of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold up--there's more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I'll do my best to stay that way.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
