<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>54</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/trooper/bothan_resistance_3.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc to resistance. Come in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, Major, nothing yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074598" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. I'm going to report in, but keep looking. We wouldn't want to leave without any souvenirs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075094" id2="17" version="1065353216">Raven Squad to central: Strike confirmed. Tell the pilot he did some nice landscaping.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075096" id2="17" version="1065353216">Copy, Raven. Proceed immediately to reinforce objective six. Firefall protocol has been initiated. Repeat, Firefall is go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075098" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood, Raven out. Blast it....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075100" id2="17" version="1065353216">No souvenirs today, friends--need to move out right away. Sholl, you take point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Found her!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Found him!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075106" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major! Are you alright? We couldn't really see what happened. Do you need some water? Get the major some water!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, Rylo, I'm still kicking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1075107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks, I'm fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075109" id2="17" version="1065353216">Raven Squad called in the air strike... their commander is a major named Varis. What do we know about them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1075109" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was an Imperial squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075110" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get out of the way, Rylo. We have work to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1075110" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will you shut up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075112" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some Imperial commandos were searching the wreckage--I heard them say something about &quot;initiating Firefall protocol.&quot; It sounded urgent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075113" id2="17" version="1065353216">No....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075115" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Firefall&quot; is a scorched ground retreat. The Imps are falling back, but they're destroying everything they possibly can on the way out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075116" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the tactical assessment of this bunker? What will we need to drive the Imps out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1075116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the bunker.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075118" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every man the Empire sends out to vandalize farms is a man we don't have to face in Liah'starn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1075118" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let them waste their time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075898" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Firefall&quot; denotes a retaliatory strategy employed during an Imperial retreat. It calls for total annihilation of all civilian resources: homes, crops, equipment and people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey there. Still in one piece?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077462" id2="17" version="1065353216">There you are--slow movements, now. Make sure everything is in place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077464" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew it! No craven Imperial bombing could fell the commander of Havoc Squad!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077466" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're still alive, too? Remind me not to buy stolen Imp bombs anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun rejoices to find you safe and whole, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master! Oh, it's such a relief to find you intact!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observation: You are very difficult to kill, master. I will note this in my memory banks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here they are!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commando unit. One of the best. Bit of a loose-cannon reputation, but I still figured they'd be fighting with the main Imperial force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our scouts confirmed it. A few Imperial squads are already out burning fields, and hundreds more are gathering at bunker 496, a few clicks from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077479" id2="17" version="1065353216">This one's even more secure than the last one. We have to mobilize the resistance and attack in force!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077481" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to gather every able-bodied fighter we've got and hit that bunker right away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1077481" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ready everyone to attack!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. We have to drive them back before they can cause any more damage!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077484" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't expect my people to stand by while their homes and livelihoods are destroyed!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077486" id2="17" version="1065353216">If hordes of resistance fighters storm an Imperial bunker, they'll realize we're a threat. We can't risk that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077488" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's an Imperial artillery battery not far from bunker 496. Havoc could capture the artillery and use it to destroy the bunker while the Imps are still getting prepped inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me where to find the artillery, and we'll send the Imps packing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1077489" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make it happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got the coordinates right here. The place isn't a fortress, but there are still plenty of sentries posted--watch out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Major. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surely an orbital strike or another bombing run from Dagger Wing could settle this faster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1077493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aren't there other options?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Retasking the Daggers or one of the warships in orbit could take hours--we need to act now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077496" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is war--damage is inevitable. I say we ignore the bunker and move against Liah'starn right away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1077496" id2="17" version="1065353216">The bunker isn't a priority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you lost your mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077499" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not going to let the Imps hurt these people any more than they already have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077501" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find the artillery battery here. It's not as heavily guarded as the bunkers, but stay sharp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1078510" id2="17" version="1065353216">After the explosion, I saw them searching the wreckage. But then they were called away, something about &quot;initiating Firefall protocol.&quot;</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
