<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>35</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/trooper/bothan_resistance_2.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1027331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc to resistance: Cache two secured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1027332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Copy, Havoc. Please hold position until retrieval team arrives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074780" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major! Rylo here. Wanted to get some quick shots of you helping the resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074782" id2="17" version="1065353216">While we're at it, why don't you talk a bit about the situation. How's it feel to be helping the Bothans win their freedom?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074783" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm proud to be helping our allies finally drive the Empire off their world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1074783" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's an honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aiding in guerrilla warfare is just part of being a SpecForce soldier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1074784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just doing my job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074785" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe you had the dispatcher keep me here just to do another interview.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1074785" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're starting to annoy me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you in danger? I heard you say the area was secured. It's important to get your thoughts in the moment; it adds realism.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075857" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, grabbing a quick image after a battle is one thing. Putting an entire operation on hold is something else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps this discussion could happen a bit later, when we aren't in the middle of an operation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075860" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't want to hear my thoughts, pal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun apologizes for interrupting, but this discussion seems poorly timed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075862" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I may say so, I'm not sure this is the ideal setting for an interview....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Protestation: This discussion is an utter waste of our time, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, look, just one more question, then: How do you think the Bothans will do when the battle for Liah'starn begins?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075871" id2="17" version="1065353216">I promise, this is the last question: How do you think the Bothans will do when the battle for Liah'starn begins?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075878" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Bothans have been preparing for this for years. I'm sure they'll fight bravely when the time comes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1075878" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll do great.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075879" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no way to know how new soldiers will do in battle until they actually face it for real.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1075879" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't bother me in the field again, Rylo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1075880" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is over. [Leave]</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075881" id2="17" version="1065353216">But--Major! Major?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075883" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure with your leadership, they'll do just fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075884" id2="17" version="1065353216">A vote of confidence from the Republic's finest!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075886" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, thank you for your time, Major. Rylo out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077167" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well spoken, sir! The Bothans are truly fortunate to have one of the Republic's finest soldiers fighting for their freedom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great, great. Let's see, what else....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077171" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the war against tyranny, all useful tactics must be employed!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077173" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Helping the helpless fight back,&quot; great stuff. Now, what else did I have....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077175" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on, are we actually playing along with this nonsense?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077177" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, yes, one last question: How do you think the Bothans will do when the battle for Liah'starn begins?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
