<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>75</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/trooper/dagger_wing_pilot.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074132" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc on deck!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074134" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a pleasure to see you again, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blasted good to see you again, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074138" id2="17" version="1065353216">We really owe you. After all that time locked up on Belsavis, we've finally gotten a chance to prove we aren't a bunch of sickos bombing civilians for kicks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074139" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear you're the ones getting me to the surface for this bunker assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1074139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074140" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's affirmative. And it's going to be quite a ride.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074142" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been looking forward to seeing what you can do behind the stick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1074142" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to have your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074143" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won't be disappointed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074145" id2="17" version="1065353216">After everything I had to go through to wrangle you people, one op isn't nearly enough payback.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1074145" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think this makes us even?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell you what, we can argue about who owes who more when you see what we're pulling to get you down to the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074148" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your objective, Imperial bunker 227, is the central command post for infantry and anti-aircraft defenses throughout the region.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074150" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your target is Imperial bunker 227: heart of the regional infantry and anti-aircraft defense grid, and all-around tough nut to crack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074152" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what's the plan--you fly interference while we shuttle in? How close can we get?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074154" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is the maximum effective coverage? How close will you be able to deploy us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074156" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials can hide behind as many cannons and shields as they like--they won't stop us!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074158" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think you can get us anywhere close to the place, or should I go get dressed for a nature hike?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074160" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're dropping you right on their heads. We'll be making a full-speed bombing run over the bunker--and you'll be inside one of the bombs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074161" id2="17" version="1065353216">The higher the wall, the greater its weight--and the more cracks appear in its structure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074163" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were able to find a few gaps in the grid--but fancy flying is going to be our best defense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observation: The effectiveness of anti-aircraft cannons is greatly reduced by the application of orbital atomic bombardment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074167" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think the Bothans might get touchy about us making that big of a mess. But we'll definitely be laying down some pain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, dear... I should have upgraded my internal stabilizers. This is sure to be a turbulent landing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074171" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah! Your droid knows our style.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our plan is to hit 'em with a full-speed bombing run--with you riding down inside one of the bombs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Orbital drop pods are one thing... not sure I've ever seen it done with a starfighter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1074174" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a new move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074175" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, you're gonna get a front-row seat!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074177" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the best plan I've ever been a part of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1074177" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sold!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad you approve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074180" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bombs aren't exactly known for soft landings, people. Have you lost your minds?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1074180" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're insane.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074181" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, don't worry so much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074183" id2="17" version="1065353216">The bomb has been specially modified to ensure a rapid, but safe, landing. You'll take the enemy completely by surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074185" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've modded the bomb with repulsorlifts that kick in right before impact--you'll be fine, and the Imps will be too busy to notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074187" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll be dropping a few hundred tonnes of HE munitions on the bunker, too--should keep most of the guards busy while you charge the command center.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074188" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've thought of everything. When do we begin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1074188" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074189" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's just one last thing to sort out--your reporter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074204" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe I'm saying this, but... this could actually work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074206" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't mind seeing the safety certifications for this... device... but the principles seem sound enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074208" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have the utmost faith in the capabilities of Republic technicians!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we start deploying for all of our missions this way?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074212" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun sees no reason such a device couldn't work, and looks forward to examining its components more closely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074214" id2="17" version="1065353216">Approval: I do enjoy seeing a look of surprise in an organic's face before disposing of him. This plan practically guarantees it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074218" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not going to lie--I'm still a bit nervous about this plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1074218" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're sure this will work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074219" id2="17" version="1065353216">The tech's been through plenty of tests. It's as safe as dropping someone out of a supersonic starfighter and into open combat can be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074221" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's one other matter: the reporter, Rylo Kann. He asked us to discuss our service history with the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074223" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, one last thing--Rylo Kann asked us to do some interviews, talk about our &quot;history of noble service&quot; to the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074225" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're only giving this crazy plan a shot because it's going into Rylo Kann's broadcast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1074225" id2="17" version="1065353216">Showing off for the cameras?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074226" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think we want to show off for that runt? Please.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074228" id2="17" version="1065353216">He thought it'd be a great idea to interview us after the mission is over, talk about our &quot;history of noble service.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074230" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this guy aware that we were locked up for bombing Imperial civilians? Sure, we were duped into it, but that doesn't make it a happy, patriotic story.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074231" id2="17" version="1065353216">The point of this publicity campaign is to show everything. Don't hold back--tell him exactly what you went through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1074231" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talking about the bombing and Belsavis would only shake people's confidence. Make up something else--understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1074232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lie about your past.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074233" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood. We'll think of something when we get back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074235" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got orders to cooperate with Rylo, but you don't. Ignore him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1074235" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't talk to him at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074236" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you think that's best. We'll take care of it after the mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074238" id2="17" version="1065353216">All pilots--board your fighters and prepare for takeoff!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074240" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so, Major. We'll sort it all out when we get back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074242" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, everybody, enough chitchat! Get to your fighters and prep for takeoff!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074244" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your ride's ready whenever you are--just hop in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077092" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been asked to provide an interview once the mission is over, discussing our service history with the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077094" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077096" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077098" id2="17" version="1065353216">With pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1081817" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a pleasure, sir.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
