<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>32</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/trooper/imp_artillery_cannon.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074797" id2="17" version="1065353216">Longspear, this is Raven Squad, cease fire! Cease fire! You're destroying our own bunker, what are you--ugh! You again?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075138" id2="17" version="1065353216">That bunker is going to be a smoking ruin any minute now. No more burning down farms and crops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1075138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time for you to fall back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, I'm just not that easy to kill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1075139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surprised?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075140" id2="17" version="1065353216">You dropped a bomb on me, so I'm dropping some artillery shells on you. Seems fair enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1075140" id2="17" version="1065353216">Payback time!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075141" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, what's one little air strike between friends?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075143" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, you've already won this round--we're falling back to Liah'starn on the double. Think you could lay off the cannons while we evac our wounded?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075145" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just want to get these boys and girls home alive. You've taken them out of the game, there's no need to keep firing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075146" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll give you three minutes. Get your wounded people out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1075146" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. [Cease fire]</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075147" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't enjoy killing, but I have to make sure your people back off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1075147" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, but no. [Keep firing]</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075148" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I have the chance to kill some Imps, I take it. And you're next on my list.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1075148" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad. [Keep firing]</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075737" id2="17" version="1065353216">My commanders happen to agree with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075739" id2="17" version="1065353216">You burn people's homes to the ground, and then ask us for a time-out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075740" id2="17" version="1065353216">What assurances can you give that we can trust you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nonsense! No mercy for Imperial scum!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075742" id2="17" version="1065353216">This gal's got some serious nerve. I like her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun would gladly embrace an alternative to further death, but... how can we trust these words?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075744" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would certainly be a very honorable thing to do, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rejection: A wounded foe is a job half-finished. I was not programmed to leave jobs half-finished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Much obliged. Next time I see you, I might just shake your hand before I start shooting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075748" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast it... win or lose, I'm finding you again before this is over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075750" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you don't find me before this is all over, I'm going to be very disappointed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075752" id2="17" version="1065353216">The plan worked! The Imperials are double-timing it toward Liah'starn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1075754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Transmitting rendezvous coordinates now. Meet up with us, and we'll plan our own entrance into the city. Balkar out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077513" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's fine--I like a challenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Burning people's houses down wasn't my idea--no sport in it. I don't even care about this planet, honestly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077524" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't care less whether the Empire keeps this rock or not, all right?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
