<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>104</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/trooper/ship_holo.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069312" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad to General Garza. Ready for mission briefing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Acknowledged, Major. As we discussed earlier, your team will be part of a joint task force working to liberate Bothawui from Imperial forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Correct. Your assignment is to work with local resistance forces to capture the Empire's strategic headquarters, located in the city of Liah'starn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069317" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be assisted by an SIS agent code-named &quot;Graybeard,&quot; who's already made contact with the Bothan resistance. He'll help you ready them for the assault on Liah'starn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069319" id2="17" version="1065353216">What can you tell me about the Bothans? I don't know much about them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1069319" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not familiar with Bothans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do the Bothan forces have what it takes to keep up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1069320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope these people can fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069321" id2="17" version="1065353216">They haven't engaged in open combat operations for some time, but I think you'll still find them quite motivated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069327" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's an odd code name. What else do we know about this person?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1069327" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Graybeard&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your first objective is to neutralize an Imperial command bunker that oversees infantry patrols and anti-aircraft systems in territories approaching Liah'starn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given the bunker's heavy defenses, getting you into position for the assault will be difficult. The pilots of Dagger Wing will be assisting with your deployment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069334" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be a pleasure to finally see the Daggers at work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1069334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069335" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't heard from the Daggers since Belsavis. Have they been fully reinstated?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1069335" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is Dagger Wing's status?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Officially, no, but their roles and responsibilities are largely the same as before their imprisonment. Conrad Gall continues to lead them expertly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes--they were all reinstated with formal apologies. Tobin Harlan has adapted to his role as commander, though there were some initial difficulties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dagger Wing isn't necessary--I've got my own ship and plenty of good soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1069340" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069341" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your ship isn't nimble enough to evade the bunker's defenses--Dagger Wing's fighters are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069343" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your SIS contact will be monitoring the bunker's comm traffic--once you've seized the command center, use the holoterminal inside to signal him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069345" id2="17" version="1065353216">The reporter... I think we're finished here. Dagger Wing's officers will be waiting to discuss your assault on the bunker. Good luck--Garza out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069346" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Chancellor has made this a priority, so it's our job to see it through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1069346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing we can't handle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069347" id2="17" version="1065353216">I disagree--I think it's the duty of every soldier to reflect the best ideals of the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1073561" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have to be honest--I'm with the general on this one. That reporter is going to be nothing but trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1073562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. If done well, this could really inspire people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1073564" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess it's happening no matter what, so we might as well get used to it. I'll bring the guy aboard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1073565" id2="17" version="1065353216">We didn't get much choice in participating in the Chancellor's plan, but I'd still like to hear everyone's thoughts on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1073565" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the rest of you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1073566" id2="17" version="1065353216">You two are nuts. Maybe you like having every move you make recorded, but I prefer a bit of privacy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1073568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Public relations are not our responsibility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1073568" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1073572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major, great to see you again!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1073574" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't tell you how excited I am about this project--the audience is going to be completely amazed. The true stories of Havoc Squad!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1073575" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to have you, Rylo. Make yourself comfortable, and let us know if you need help or any special equipment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1073575" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome aboard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1073576" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, no need to worry about me. I'm used to working on the run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1073578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since you're going to be working with me and my crew, I'd like to know more about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1073578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1073579" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me? I'm nothing special. City kid from Coruscant, always loved the news, always loved hearing people's stories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1073580" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to make this clear, Rylo: The missions come first. If you interfere in any way, we're going to have a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1073580" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just stay out of my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1073581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course! I'm here to document, not to participate. You don't have to worry about a thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074066" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing, frankly. I've been assured that the agent in question is one of their best. We'll know soon enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fur-coated bipeds, and longtime members of the Republic. Their resistance has focused on sabotage and espionage rather than open conflict.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074070" id2="17" version="1065353216">You obviously made an impression on them on Belsavis--they volunteered for this operation with no hesitation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074072" id2="17" version="1065353216">As my own operations have proven, increased morale can significantly enhance military effectiveness. This is a superb opportunity!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074074" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a fantastic opportunity! We will inspire our allies and strike fear into our enemies simultaneously!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun concurs. The transmission waves of Rylo Kann's broadcasts flow prosperously.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074078" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assessment: Notoriety can have a useful psychological effect on organic targets. But documenting our capabilities only assists our enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074080" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nonsense. The benefits far outweigh the risks. Done tastefully, I think this could be very educational for the public.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074081" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for speaking your minds, people. Let's bring him in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074083" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a real privilege, you know? I get to see and hear so much, and then share it with the whole galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074085" id2="17" version="1065353216">But hey--you've got a giant Imperial bunker to assault, and I need to get set up so I can record every minute of it. Go ahead, I'll be fine!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1074086" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be all set up in just a few minutes--go on with your work! I have a feeling this bunker assault is going to be a real crowd-pleaser.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc to General Garza. Mission complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076534" id2="17" version="1065353216">So I've heard. The Chancellor and I are both very impressed--the liberation of Bothawui was handled flawlessly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chancellor Saresh is preparing a special victory ceremony aboard her flagship as we speak. You've been invited as a guest of honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076537" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be an honor to attend and represent Special Forces at the ceremony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1076537" id2="17" version="1065353216">With pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will there be food at this thing? Drinks? Anything fun at all?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1076538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there going to be a party?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does a guest of honor have any choice about being a guest or not?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1076539" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076543" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, I'm afraid not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations again, Major. Come to the Resolute as soon as you're able. Garza out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076547" id2="17" version="1065353216">A party thrown by the most boring people in the Republic isn't really a party.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076566" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not every day you get invited to an official ceremony with the Supreme Chancellor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1076566" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a privilege.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076567" id2="17" version="1065353216">Garza said I was invited; she didn't say anything about bringing you along.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1076567" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who said you're going?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those boring people are also busy--maybe it will be short. Let's go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1076568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get this over with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077090" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm very sorry to interrupt, master, but Rylo Kann has arrived. He requests permission to come aboard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1078418" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Navy reports that all Imperial bunkers have been neutralized--all without a single Republic casualty. Truly excellent work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1078420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps after the ceremony. It's not the kind of thing I'd be told about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1078422" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's fine by me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1078424" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pipe down, no one asked you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1078425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your opinion is noted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1078426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah. I doubt the rest of us are lucky enough to get out that easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1078428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thing you don't speak for anyone, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1078429" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;The rest of us&quot; will be honored to attend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1078430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Homeworld of the Bothans. Planet's a big-time farming center, and it's on a strategic hyperlane. Several battles over it in the last war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1078432" id2="17" version="1065353216">A major agricultural center, if memory serves. Homeworld of the Bothan people, and site of several major battles before the Treaty of Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1080146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our troops have already raided almost all of the remaining Imperial bunkers, and captured thousands of enemy prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1081807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given the success of the operation, I take it that Rylo Kann didn't interfere in your duties more than necessary?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1081808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rylo was very professional the whole time. No trouble at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1081808" id2="17" version="1065353216">We worked great together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1081809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rylo interrupted me a few times, but it wasn't anything I couldn't handle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1081809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some problems, nothing big.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1081810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rylo repeatedly interrupted my missions to ask stupid questions and make pointless recordings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1081810" id2="17" version="1065353216">He was constantly annoying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1081811" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing less than expected, then. Fortunately, documenting Bothawui was the extent of his contract.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1081813" id2="17" version="1065353216">In any case, you've given the Republic an incredible victory to celebrate, and the Chancellor all the publicity she could ask for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1081818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. The less interruptions we have, the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1081824" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you were able to keep the situation under control. Having a reporter along could've been disastrous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1081865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guest of honor at the Chancellor's special party--quite an accomplishment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1081872" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're prepared to depart on your command, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1081873" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ship's ready whenever you are, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1081875" id2="17" version="1065353216">Navicomputer's loaded and ready, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1081878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coordinates are loaded, sir.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
