<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>53</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/voss/world/imperial/gormak_infestation/commander_dasim.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536124" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've recovered a shipment of weapons for the research outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536125" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent! We lost almost everything in the last attack. This is a stroke of good fortune.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536126" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll deal with the rest of the Gormak. Thank you again for everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536128" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak leaders are dead. Hopefully they have the intelligence to retreat and regroup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536129" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak leaders are dead. You can deal with the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536130" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, my lord. I promise you, we won't waste the opportunity you've given us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536132" id2="17" version="1065353216">My part's done. The rest of the Gormak are all yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536133" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're better than an entire squadron. Thank you, hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536135" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attack when ready, Commander. The Gormak leaders won't bother you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent work! Thank you! I'll make sure Imperial Command hears of your part in this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536138" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll mobilize these worthless Voss and my remaining men and see if we can't mop up any of the beasts still lurking nearby.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536140" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll prepare my troops to attack on your go-ahead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536143" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been plagued with complications from the start of this mission. And the Voss are not helping.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Things are starting to look up; you're the first people I've seen in days who weren't Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536147" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, I'd welcome you to the research outpost if these idiot Voss had managed to hold on to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536149" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a welcome sight, hunter. I was afraid our reinforcements would be more Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536151" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's nice to see someone from civilized space again. I'm sick to death of Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536153" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is so good to see someone who's not a blasted Voss!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536155" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't imagine why we're courting an alliance with these freaks. They can't spit without a prophecy telling them when and where.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536157" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak struck while we were helping to build the research station. The unfinished defenses were rubbish, and we only had a few men. We had to fall back here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536158" id2="17" version="1065353216">You let yourself be overrun by savages? What kind of officer are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="536158" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's pathetic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536159" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak savages are far more resourceful than the Voss. Though that's not saying much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536161" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have enough men left to hold this position?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="536161" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many survived the attack?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536162" id2="17" version="1065353216">Short answer: no.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="536164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me handle the Gormak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536165" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, you honor us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="536167" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killing Gormak might be fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah... thank you, my lord. That's very kind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="536170" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can clean up your Gormak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536171" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to see a professional show up out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="536173" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could try to help out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. We're in dire need of some experienced fighters out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536176" id2="17" version="1065353216">The attack cost me most of the men who could tell which end of the blaster went first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536178" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak leaders are the dangerous ones. If you eliminate them, I can lead what's left of my men to clear the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536179" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait here, I'll return when the leaders are dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="536179" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="536180" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like a plan with action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536181" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm deeply in your debt. I'll be waiting for you to give the all-clear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536183" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any grunt could do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="536183" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do it yourself. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536184" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. I'm sorry to have wasted your time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536188" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, thank you. You've saved my men from the hopeless incompetence of the Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536190" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done! Thank you, hunter. With only the idiot natives searching for them, I considered these hopelessly lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536192" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where did you find these? Well done! The blasted Voss can't locate their backsides with both hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536194" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're under fire by the Gormak almost constantly. Fresh weapons will make all the difference to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536195" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought this was a research outpost. It looks like a refugee camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="536195" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why defend this dump?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536196" id2="17" version="1065353216">How long have you been under attack? Where's your support?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="536196" id2="17" version="1065353216">There should be guards here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="536197" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're welcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="536198" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where are our reinforcements? I'm growing sick of listening to these Voss whine.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
