<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>20</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/daily_area/ziost/ambient/sanctuary/b7g2_and_hmc10.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152559" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen thousands drop dead from Tarisian Toxic Flu. Watched cities vaporize from proto-isotope bombs. Nothing like this. Thought it would be dead silent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152561" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Humanitarian crisis,&quot; says the Republic. But what about us droids?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152562" id2="17" version="1065353216">My field of expertise is in the biological sciences. Yours?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hazardous services. Approved for Class Nine unstable isotopes and species-neutral catastrophic pathogens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152566" id2="17" version="1065353216">You aren't carrying any of those things around with you...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152568" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have the clearance for that information. Hey, you know anything about what's going on here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152570" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like I'd tell you if I did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152573" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about us? Need a spinal upgrade there, professor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152575" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know about you, but I'm not serving any purpose standing on the outskirts of a war zone. I'll be shot to scrap, and what good will that do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152577" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me a good laugh, at the very least.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152579" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're awful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152582" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's this bacteria in my databanks--connects all its hosts into a single mind till there's nothing left for it to infect. Then it dies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does it say what happens to the life forms?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152586" id2="17" version="1065353216">They don't die, but they don't really know they're alive anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fascinating. I'd like to study them sometime.... I don't imagine what happened to them is what we're seeing here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. This is... something else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152593" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've surveyed virtually every landscape imaginable in search of life. There's always something to hear--sometimes agreeable, sometimes not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should look for transport. Nothing of use left for either of us to do here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152597" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm staying. It's not entirely dead here yet, and I'd like to conduct research.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1152599" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know death. What's out there--it's not life, I'll tell you that. But if you insist on sticking around, I can wait.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
