<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>54</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/manaan/shared/transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126677" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Lana. Darth Arkous isn't far--I can sense him. We have to learn what he and the Selkath are doing down there and confront him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126679" id2="17" version="1065353216">To have your run of the place, you'll need to shut down the security grid. You have the coordinates now. I'll stay in touch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126682" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've met our potential ally, who's already proved quite resourceful. He's learned of a prisoner in the security hub who's been scheduled for disposal by experimentation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126684" id2="17" version="1065353216">This &quot;Jakarro&quot; sounds like someone you might want to talk with--as soon as you contend with the head of security.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126687" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to see you've made a new friend--or friends, as it were. But a warning....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126689" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're about to encounter members of the Order of Shasa--Force-sensitive Selkath who are neither Jedi nor Sith. Their complicity here does not bode well for us....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126695" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been slicing the facility files, and I keep finding references to the Order of Shasa--some pack of Force-using Selkath. They aren't Jedi or Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126699" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting. I'm seeing records of a prisoner here--someone named &quot;Jakarro&quot;. I'll bet he could share some interesting stories with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron here. I'm patched into the lab's tracking systems--looks like Arkous and Darok are still inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126708" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hi. You don't know me, but I'm here with Lana. She's meditating, using her connection to Darth Arkous to pinpoint his location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126710" id2="17" version="1065353216">She wanted you to know if I found anything, and I did. Energy readings from Gorima's lab. Rakata technology's firing up like crazy in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126712" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't know for sure what's going on, but I can pretty much guarantee it's got to be stopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126714" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings! We haven't met in person, but your associate asked me to contact you while he's busy with his scanning equipment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126718" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello again. I'm afraid that all of the emergency pods have been ejected, and all hatches leading back to the facility entrance are sealed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me again. Darok and Arkous ejected all the emergency pods. No going back the way you came.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126721" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good news is I slaved one of the pods. Got it on remote pilot, headed for a docking hatch nearby. You should have the coordinates by now. Get moving!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127315" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a security checkpoint ahead that can grant you access to the rest of the facility. Transmitting coordinates now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127318" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like my contact's here. The chief of security is just ahead of you--watch your step.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127321" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm still not sure how they tie into all of this, but I imagine you're going to run into them... be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently, he's picking up powerful energy readings from Gorima's laboratory. Readings consistent with Rakata technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127325" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron and I agree that this is a dangerous sign. Whatever is going on in that lab, please do your best to stop it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fortunately, I... &quot;procured&quot; a small watercraft for just this eventuality. The autopilot should have it docked at a hatch near your location shortly. Please hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128941" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take that thing out quick!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128946" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep at it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128948" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's it! Don't let up!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128949" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're doing it! You're doing it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana said you were tough. C'mon, let's see it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128951" id2="17" version="1065353216">There you go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128953" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128954" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gonna have to breathe water if you don't get going here...!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meaner than it looks!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better get your act together...!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thing's almost out of juice, now finish it off!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great work! Now let's get you out of there!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128961" id2="17" version="1065353216">That thing just keeps going!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128963" id2="17" version="1065353216">Getting readings from their alpha cyborg. That thing's serious--and it's coming right for you! Stay sharp!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128970" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done it. Excellent work. Now let's get you back to the surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128971" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's finally faltering. Strike the beast down!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let it gain the upper hand!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128973" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's on the offensive...!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Steel yourselves!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Its power is incredible...!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128976" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're bound for a watery grave if you don't watch yourself...!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128977" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the way!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show it you will not back down!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128980" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep going! You can do this!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good! Don't let up!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your time is short. Be merciless!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their cyborg champion is after you. I can sense its power from here... it's considerable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our ally just made note of strange power signatures in your vicinity. He believes they may be emanating from Rakata technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that...? I'm registering some tech near you that reads like it's from the Rakata.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128990" id2="17" version="1065353216">See if you can't open up the network for me. I'll slice in and take a look.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128993" id2="17" version="1065353216">It warrants a closer look. Tap into a nearby console so we can investigate.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
