<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>45</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/voss/bronze/imperial/history_is_what_you_make_it/sergeant_darrst.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss should have a minor groundquake soon. Localized at the statues.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant. Your path is clear. The statues are real.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85995" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was afraid of that. If the Voss discover these statues... hmm, even a small seismic event might destroy them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85997" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll look into it. Your assistance is appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are the ruins clear? We must reach the statues before the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86002" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're all headed for the shrine, stop a moment. We have trouble that way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86004" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, a moment? Normally I wouldn't presume, but we're in a difficult spot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86006" id2="17" version="1065353216">You there! Yes, you! I have need of a mercenary, if your prices are reasonable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Officer. Wherever your post, I'd like to commandeer you for a special mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Darrst, Imperial Reclamation Service. We've found disturbing evidence of an ancient link between the Jedi and the Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi iconography--statues, to be exact--found in Voss ruins. If authentic, they could make the Voss sympathetic to the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surely the Voss can see the Jedi's weakness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="86013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Over some statues?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86014" id2="17" version="1065353216">They have no interest in ideology. Only the Jedi's resemblance to the Mystics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86016" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi don't have the wit for deception.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="86016" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must assume they're real.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86017" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the Republic hasn't the stomach. Still, we shouldn't rule out the possibility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bunch of statues? You're kidding, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="86019" id2="17" version="1065353216">You worry too much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86020" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss have an unseemly interest in the Jedi, despite the Jedi Council's disapproval of their entire way of life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86022" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Voss alliance would guarantee a Republic victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="86022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unacceptable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Precisely. That's why we have orders to inspect these ruins before the Voss do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="86025" id2="17" version="1065353216">How so?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Simple logic. The argument for an alliance is stronger with proof of an earlier one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="86028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't affect me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86029" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the Voss, the Republic could win this war. We can't let them gain more favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86031" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we could confirm the statues' authenticity, we could determine how best to handle the situation and the Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, the local natives have overrun the area. Gormak, I think they're called. Ghastly, savage creatures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroy the ruins. Blame the Gormak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="86034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wipe them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86035" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak have no interest in Voss ruins. Suspicion would fall on us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="86037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get to the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="86038" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a coward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86039" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're scientists, not soldiers. We've lost several scouts to them already.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86041" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you could cut a path through the Gormak, you could examine the statues yourself and report back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86043" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the statues are fakes, they'll be exposed. If real... we'll do what's necessary to protect the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="86044" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like your outlook.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="86045" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86046" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am authorized to offer hazard pay. The amount will be equal to the task.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86048" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few of our scouts managed to send back coordinates of the ruins. You'll find the statues inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86050" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak won't make it easy, but examine them as best you can. I'll be waiting. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="86052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Far too busy. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86053" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can only hope someone else volunteers before the statues are discovered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86055" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, another time. The data from these ruins must be analyzed.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
