<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>86</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/the_streets_of_cademimu/republic/master_satele_shan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="514249" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514251" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele, this is Carrick Station reporting. What's the situation on Cademimu?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514252" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better than we hoped, thanks to you. Governor Chornarov was captured, and his separatist allies are surrendering to our forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514253" id2="17" version="1065353216">Considering all the elite guards I had to fight, I'd expect the number of prisoners to be low.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514253" id2="17" version="1065353216">There can't be many left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514254" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry you were forced to commit such violence, but your efforts saved lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514256" id2="17" version="1065353216">We won't have to worry about further violence. That's good for everyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514256" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad the fighting is over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514257" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people of that world have suffered enough--and you spared them from more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514259" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do the Republic a favor. Skip the expensive show trial. We know they're guilty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514259" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lock them up for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514260" id2="17" version="1065353216">That decision is not mine to make, but take heart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lock up that politician and his lackeys extra tight. People that slimy slip out of cages real easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make sure no one escapes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514263" id2="17" version="1065353216">A maximum security prison frigate is already on its way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514265" id2="17" version="1065353216">That war criminal you wanted brought in made the mistake of trying to stop us. General Ortol won't be hurting anyone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514265" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Ortol is dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514266" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd have preferred putting him on trial, but at least he didn't escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514268" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic needs to make an example of the governor and those separatists. We don't want other worlds getting ideas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Execute them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514269" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mercy encourages loyalty more than the threat of death. Do not let talk of revenge spoil our victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not only did you liberate Cademimu, you thwarted an Imperial invasion. We detected an enemy fleet dropping out of hyperspace at the system's edge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514273" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Imperials saw we commanded Cademimu's missile defenses, they retreated. Had they captured that world, dozens of systems would've been threatened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe the governor planned to join the Empire?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514274" id2="17" version="1065353216">They might have been invited.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chornarov would never have turned over power, but it's possible his separatist friends had other plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514277" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never heard of the Empire running from a fight before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514277" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our enemy ran away?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514278" id2="17" version="1065353216">They couldn't risk the attack. They knew what our missile batteries would do to their vessels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514280" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be some time before Cademimu's government is restored. Until then, we'll maintain the peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514282" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm tired of talking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514283" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enjoy your respite from the fighting. I'll be in touch. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="514285" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514287" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Carrick Station on Emergency Response Corps priority frequency. Master Satele, do you read us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent--you've arrived just in time. The people of Cademimu are being held hostage by a criminal despot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Governor Chornarov was under investigation for corruption. He was about to be arrested by Republic officials when he declared his planet's independence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514291" id2="17" version="1065353216">What crimes was the governor being accused of?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514291" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like he's guilty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Extortion, blackmail and fraud are the least of his offenses. His government abused its power thoroughly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514294" id2="17" version="1065353216">Politicians usually need the voters on their side for something like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514294" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the people agreed to that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514295" id2="17" version="1065353216">The governor enacted emergency powers and imposed martial law. The people of Cademimu have no say in this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514297" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's certainly a creative solution. If his world is beyond Republic law, he's safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514297" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's one way to evade arrest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514298" id2="17" version="1065353216">If nothing else, it settles the matter of his guilt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514300" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chornarov was able to seize power because of the Republic's missile arrays stored on his world--and the criminal army he's amassed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514302" id2="17" version="1065353216">After separatist forces were crushed on Ord Mantell, Governor Chornarov secretly offered their leaders and surviving troops asylum on Cademimu.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Angral had a secret listening post on Ord Mantell. I got to see the civil war there up close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514303" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've met the separatists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you know what separatists are capable of. Unfortunately, they aren't our only concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive my ignorance, Master, but I'm unfamiliar with Ord Mantell's political situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the separatists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514307" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ord Mantell is fighting a civil war against violent separatists funded and trained by the Empire. But that isn't our primary concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514309" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad had a mission to wipe out those separatists. I intend to see it through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514309" id2="17" version="1065353216">My orders are clear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before we can deal with separatists, we must clear a path to the surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514312" id2="17" version="1065353216">Separatists. I've hated those guys ever since I landed on Ord Mantell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514312" id2="17" version="1065353216">That filthy scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514313" id2="17" version="1065353216">From what I understand, they're no fan of yours, either. But we have larger problems to deal with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514315" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's been smuggling separatists onto his world for months? How did we not notice that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514315" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did he manage that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514316" id2="17" version="1065353216">We did notice. We simply underestimated the number he brought in. Separatists were the least of our concerns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514318" id2="17" version="1065353216">The governor conspired with enemies of the Republic. He signed his own death warrant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514318" id2="17" version="1065353216">All traitors must die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514319" id2="17" version="1065353216">This mission is not about revenge. We have larger concerns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514321" id2="17" version="1065353216">The missiles produced on Cademimu are supposed to supply planetary defense batteries along the Celanon Spur, a major trade route. Those worlds now lie vulnerable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Governor Chornarov has commandeered enough Republic planetary-level weapons that a large-scale invasion is impossible. The missile arrays would destroy our capital ships in orbit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514324" id2="17" version="1065353216">A lone strike team could slip past those planetary defenses. That's why we're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514324" id2="17" version="1065353216">A small ship could get inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514325" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have no way to remotely shut down those missiles? That's just bad design.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514325" id2="17" version="1065353216">There isn't any fail-safe?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514326" id2="17" version="1065353216">There were deactivation codes, but the governor's slicers disabled them. He'd clearly been planning this for some time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514328" id2="17" version="1065353216">That one man could bring the Republic to its knees is inexcusable. The SIS should've assassinated Chornarov before it got this far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514328" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should've killed Chornarov.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killing elected officials is the Empire's way, not ours. We'll assign blame later. Our only focus should be ending this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514331" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need you to restore the planet's defenses to Republic control. That will mean defeating Governor Chornarov's elite separatist guards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514333" id2="17" version="1065353216">A stealth-equipped assault shuttle is standing by. Your landing zone will be Cademimu's capital industrial sector, close to the missile arrays.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514334" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're on our way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there a secondary target?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't make things too easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514337" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is one last detail. Governor Chornarov is merely a corrupt politician. His private army's leader, General Ortol, is a mass-murderer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ortol sent thousands of innocent Ord Mantellians to their deaths. If you encounter that war criminal, bring him to justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514341" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry to Cademimu before the remaining missile defenses come online and our window of opportunity closes. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514342" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start Veteran Mode]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="514343" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1112099" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start Master Mode]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
