<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>33</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/bronze/republic/live_specimen/dr_parren.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317829" id2="17" version="1065353216">My research will be the greatest scientific advancement Alderaan has ever known.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, yes! What a magnificent specimen! Yes. This one will do quite well.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317834" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you'll find this to be adequate compensation. I have ample funds available now that I no longer have to pay my assistants.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just take your credits and go. I have important work to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317840" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't continue my research until you bring me a live Killik specimen.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are you bothering me? Do you have any idea what I'm working on?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317845" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait. You're a Jedi. Maybe you can help me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317847" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait. You look like a capable sort. Yes. I think you can help me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hopefully you'll fare better than my previous assistants... may they rest in peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="317850" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happened to them?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317851" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were devoured by Killiks. A nasty way to go, though I suppose it's an unavoidable peril of this project.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="317853" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm nobody's assistant!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. What if I said we were partners? I'll even give you an acknowledgment when my papers are published.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="317856" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you working on?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317857" id2="17" version="1065353216">The details of my research are far too technical to get into. But the basic concept is simple: I want to domesticate the Killiks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317859" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe we can learn to coexist with them. But I need a live specimen to continue the project. Something my previous assistants failed to deliver.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="317860" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sent them to their deaths!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317861" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't want them to get eaten. I gave them all the necessary equipment to complete the job before I sent them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="317863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aren't Killiks too dangerous to try and capture alive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="317863" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you catch a Killik?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="317864" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Killiks can't be tamed!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every great scientific breakthrough must endure the scorn of ignorant convention. Wouldn't you rather be on the cutting edge of progress?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317867" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've developed a neutralizer specific to one of the Killik hives. It temporarily turns a weakened Killik docile.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317869" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can use it to subdue a weakened Killik and lead it back to me. I'll see you are well compensated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="317870" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sent your assistants out into Killik territory and they were slaughtered! Doesn't that bother you at all?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="317870" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your assistants died for you!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317871" id2="17" version="1065353216">An unfortunate but acceptable loss. The Killiks slay hundreds each month. Imagine how many lives will be saved once I finish my work!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="317873" id2="17" version="1065353216">I certainly hope so.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317874" id2="17" version="1065353216">My research could be worth millions. I'll be sure you're amply rewarded if you bring me my specimen.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take this neutralizer. Use it to subdue a weakened Killik, then lead the specimen back here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="317878" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're insane! [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317879" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. Spit in the face of scientific advancement. But when my work is complete, you'll regret passing up this opportunity!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quit bothering me! You're impeding the progress of science!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
