<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>52</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/jedi_knight/multi/bengel_morr.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings again. I have searched for news of your battles with Darth Angral, but found nothing. I hope your hunt goes well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639104" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I left Tython, I promised our enemies would fear your name. I'm keeping that vow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639106" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was in a cantina on Hutta. Some filthy Mandalorians were bragging about how many Jedi they've killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639108" id2="17" version="1065353216">I took one's head for a trophy. Told the rest of those scum you were coming for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639110" id2="17" version="1065353216">The terror in their faces... I wish you could've seen it. I haven't felt this good in years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639112" id2="17" version="1065353216">Goodbye, for now....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, my friend. The HoloNets are filled with stories of your victory on Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639118" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything you achieved on Tython was only a prelude. You are becoming the greatest weapon the Jedi will ever know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639120" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you executed Darth Angral's son, I hope it was with the lightsaber I taught you to build at the Great Forge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639122" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remain your most loyal comrade. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639659" id2="17" version="1065353216">My comrade... I'd almost lost hope. So much time passed without news from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639661" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard whispers you had died at the Emperor's hands. I shouldn't have believed it. Forgive my lack of faith in you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639663" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know now that you are alive and defending the Republic against Sith and the weak-willed Jedi who have shown their true natures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639665" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic and Empire have gone to war on Corellia. I hope to see you there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victory is at hand. Be strong. May the Force be with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639673" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope this message finds you well. I tried to see you when you were on Tython. The Council kept everyone away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, the temple hallways are filled with rumors. Some say you fell to the dark side and are seeking redemption.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Others say you never fell, that you captured a Sith Lord and are using him to hunt down the Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639679" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the truth is probably a lot more complicated. Honestly, all that matters to me is that you're alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639681" id2="17" version="1065353216">For a while, everyone assumed you were dead. When I heard that, I felt like I'd lost an old friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639683" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to know that was just a rumor. May the Force be with you. Bengel Morr out....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640222" id2="17" version="1065353216">My comrade... the Jedi are weakening. You and I are the only true warriors among them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640224" id2="17" version="1065353216">A master and her Padawan tried to capture me. Told me I was sick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640226" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were so trusting. I tricked them easily. Fed their corpses to a hungry beast. No less than they deserved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640228" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you destroy the Empire, we must begin exterminating the weak among our Order. Only the strongest should be Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640230" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wherever you are now, know that I remain your loyal comrade. Bengel Morr out....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640234" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apologies that I did not contact you sooner. I am far on the Outer Rim, my comrade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640236" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are secrets and treasures buried here--things that are rightly yours. I will see you have them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your victory over Darth Angral has fed the flames of my dedication. My purpose is clear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640240" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will end the Sith forever. The Emperor himself will fall before you. I've foreseen it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640242" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force is with you--with us. Victory is coming....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello again. It's Bengel Morr. I hope you'll forgive me for sending another message.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640250" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Masters say talking about my feelings is good. Whether or not you watch these recordings, making them fills me with peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640252" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I prefer talking to you because you saw me at my worst. You understand better than anyone what I became.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640254" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remember the rage I felt when you killed my student, Callef. He was the only true friend I had, back then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640256" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see now that his death was my fault. I led him to the dark side and forced you to kill him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640258" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a hard thing to live with, but I have to try. I owe you that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640267" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings. This is Bengel Morr. The Council permitted me to send you this message. I needed to say some things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640269" id2="17" version="1065353216">I owe you a debt. No, more than that. I owe you my life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640271" id2="17" version="1065353216">You saved me. When I think of the dark things I did here on Tython... I fell so far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640273" id2="17" version="1065353216">My greatest regret is that I never apologized to Master Orgus before he died. He was a good teacher. I miss him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640275" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Masters tell me I'm making excellent progress. My connection to the light side grows every day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640277" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope to repay the gift you've given me, somehow. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="980048" id2="17" version="1065353216">[View Message 2]</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="980052" id2="17" version="1065353216">[View Message 1]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="980073" id2="17" version="1065353216">[More...]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="980074" id2="17" version="1065353216">[View Message 1]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="980077" id2="17" version="1065353216">[View Message 3]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="980078" id2="17" version="1065353216">[View Message 4]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="980079" id2="17" version="1065353216">[View Message 5]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="980089" id2="17" version="1065353216">[View Message 2]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="980090" id2="17" version="1065353216">[View Message 3]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
