<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>34</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/macrobinoculars/roth/multi/shroud.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104067" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've actually found me? I'm impressed!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's make this a battle for me to remember you by!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Become the worthy challenge I know you can be!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104070" id2="17" version="1065353216">You thought me a mere spy, but I'm so much more!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104071" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that the best you can muster? You disappoint me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104072" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even as you strike me down, I endure!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104075" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe I've already found my next challenge. Too soon to look ahead? Perhaps. But, frankly, I'm bored now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104077" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's probably because you've been cheating--using my former lieutenant and my own equipment to come after me. Hardly impressive. Tell Evie Bo I say... hello.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104078" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's probably because you've been using an SIS agent and my own equipment to come after me. Deena Riss has given you a leg up, cheater.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104081" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's official: you've gotten on my nerves. Congratulations. You must be so very proud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Know this: when the galaxy sees my plan in all its glory, and that you tried and failed to stop it, you'll become a corpse. And I'll remain a legend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104086" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've recently taken to reading some heavily-encrypted reports. You've been busy. Made powerful friends, powerful enemies. I've underestimated you. It won't happen again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104088" id2="17" version="1065353216">However--know that no matter how deep you dig and how much you find, you won't stop me. But you will make your most powerful enemy yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104091" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever your cause in all this, you should know that it means nothing to me. What I do, I do to prove that I can--without being caught.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104093" id2="17" version="1065353216">If my threat before was too subtle, understand this: anyone who's ever tried to capture me has met with a most violent end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104096" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're surprised to hear me on a secured channel, then it's clear you have no idea who you're dealing with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104098" id2="17" version="1065353216">I strongly suggest you stop looking into my affairs. Or keep looking, I suppose. You won't get far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104102" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not in my employ. How very curious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104104" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did anticipate outside interference--but nothing quite so meager. It would appear I've concerned myself over nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104106" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well. I won't keep you from... whatever it is you believe you're accomplishing. Carry on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104896" id2="17" version="1065353216">So that's the Shroud. Can't believe he actually spoke to you. He's not exactly the type to poke his head out....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104900" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was him on holo. The Shroud. Didn't expect him to be onto us so soon-- Ah, don't matter. Just gotta work faster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, this is telling--your transmission contains a structural assessment of government installations on Coruscant. That's certainly in line with what we've learned so far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104904" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have my people check on those locations. Meanwhile, I've got a list of relay points these files passed through. That'll help us get at more data. Updating coordinates....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see what you scored us. Old dossiers, old invoices and... an Imperial report: &quot;Dromund Kaas Structural Integrity Assessment.&quot; Gotta be the inspiration for his attack on Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got relay specs connecting it to other files. That's it--we're on the scent. Got the new coordinates plugged in. Good hunting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, hello. I suppose you think you've got me, now that you've made it into my facility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, think again. It's a very large facility--with an even larger welcoming committee!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111638" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is most unfortunate--for you, I mean.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111640" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm the only one who's ever stood in this control room without being carried out in pieces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111642" id2="17" version="1065353216">That said, I do hope you like the place. You may even get to watch my plan come to its fruition--if you survive that long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111646" id2="17" version="1065353216">After all you've been through, did you really think I wouldn't have a surprise or two waiting for you here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111647" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, no--you don't want to bother with that....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111648" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh--now where will you go, hmm?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
