<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>12</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/uprisings/denova/trench_runner/barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1218080" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander, if you take out those artillery bunkers we can send Alliance air support onto the battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1218081" id2="17" version="1065353216">Brace yourself, Commander. General Rike is sending in reinforcements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1218082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look to the skies, Commander--enemy air support coming your way!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1218083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get ready for another wave, Commander. This time Rike's sending in air support and ground troops!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1218084" id2="17" version="1065353216">With those artillery bunkers out of the way, we can send in Alliance air support. Just give the word when you want the bombs to start falling!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1218085" id2="17" version="1065353216">These mines belong to the Republic--your Alliance stole them. But what else could I expect from your kind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1218086" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've never faced firepower like this before!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1218087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now you'll see what real Republic soldiers can do!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1218088" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impossible odds are no reason to surrender. To the death!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1218089" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even though I fall, others will rise against you...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1218116" id2="17" version="1065353216">My colleagues may be willing to make peace with the enemy. Some have even defected to your side. But I remain loyal to the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1218118" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will fight with everything I have to restore our former glory... including this prototype hover tank. Ha ha! Bey'wan didn't warn you about that, did he?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
