<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>30</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/dromund_kaas/world/flashes_in_the_dark/captain_jeelg.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676504" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have the respect I deserve around here again. Thanks for your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676505" id2="17" version="1065353216">A-ha! A holocommunicator with Kubaz markings on it. This will shut up those fools calling me paranoid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676507" id2="17" version="1065353216">With this, I'll finally prove there are spies all around us. My superiors can't ignore this kind of evidence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676509" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done a great service for both me and the Empire, my friend. Take this, and my thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676511" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you come back from the jungles with a Kubaz holocommunicator, I'll finally be vindicated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676512" id2="17" version="1065353216">I used to be respected, you know. My word carried weight. One tiny mistake, and suddenly no one trusts me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676514" id2="17" version="1065353216">My troops were acting strangely--plotting something. Obviously, they were traitors; all the warning signs were there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676516" id2="17" version="1065353216">The smart move was to kill them all. How could I know they were planning a surprise party for my promotion?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676517" id2="17" version="1065353216">You killed all the troops under your command?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="676517" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676518" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was under a lot of stress at the time! I've got my wits about me now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="676520" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't even know your name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, I've been in the jungle too long. Forgot my manners. I'm Captain Jeelg with Imperial Reconnaissance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676523" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure it was an honest mistake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="676523" id2="17" version="1065353216">These things happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676524" id2="17" version="1065353216">My men did a good job of keeping me in the dark. Too good, the blasted idiots.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676526" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have to listen to me. This time, I'm not being paranoid. This time, I've identified a major threat to Imperial security.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676528" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are Kubaz spies all over the jungle, and they're invisible. You can only see them when lightning flashes disrupt their stealth technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676529" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are &quot;Kubaz&quot;? Are they our enemy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="676529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kubaz?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those long-snouted mercenaries work for whoever pays them--but the Empire would never contract them to spy on Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those long-snouted alien freaks spy for whoever pays them--but the Empire wouldn't contract them for surveillance on Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676534" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can these alleged Kubaz make themselves invisible?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="676534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stealth technology?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676535" id2="17" version="1065353216">They must have powerful stealth field generators. If not for the electrical discharges in the atmosphere, I'd never have noticed them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="676537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ridiculous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just like my superiors--dismissing me because of a simple, past mistake. You have to believe me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676540" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's enemies are up to something. The Kubaz are here assessing our strengths and weaknesses for them, I just know it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scour the jungle, watch the lightning flashes and strike when you see a Kubaz! Kill the snouted scum and bring me proof.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="676544" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find proof... I'll find it in the lightning... somehow....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
