<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>41</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/bronze/imperial/nowhere_to_run/captain_zender.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234952" id2="17" version="1065353216">Area secure. Another district the enemy won't be able to retreat to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234954" id2="17" version="1065353216">The turrets no longer pose a threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent teamwork out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234957" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard the screams of terror from here, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now I'm curious how much damage I could do if I could tote that much non-regulation equipment around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234961" id2="17" version="1065353216">A perfectly executed operation, glad to have had you aboard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234963" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent, excellent. That couldn't have gone better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234965" id2="17" version="1065353216">The turrets went out of commission so quickly, we barely suffered any casualties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that that last pocket of resistance is gone, we have complete control of this district. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234969" id2="17" version="1065353216">My boys aren't afraid of a few gun batteries; we'll hold their attention as long as it takes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234972" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, a pleasure, have you come to lead the final assault?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, did Command send you to gauge our progress? We're preparing for another assault as we speak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234976" id2="17" version="1065353216">The smell of fear bring you running, bounty hunter? Good instincts, I could use you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to the end of the line, the last stand of the desperate scum hiding in this district.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234980" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've cornered a sizable resistance force, trapped them like rats. I was afraid they'd realize the hopelessness of the situation and surrender, but they're feeling sporting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234982" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a stalemate at the moment. They can't escape, but their position is well fortified.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234983" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Sith expects results, Captain, not excuses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234983" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suggest you fight harder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234984" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will not fail, my lord. We're just below force to achieving a sweeping victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234986" id2="17" version="1065353216">You enjoy giving them just enough hope of escape to make them struggle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toying with them sounds fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your approval is a great honor to me, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234989" id2="17" version="1065353216">I might be available to offer a solution. What are we looking at?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's talk business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234990" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find my definition of &quot;well fortified&quot; does not include improvised barricades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234990" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be the judge of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234991" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand, sir. I assure you, if that were all that was standing in our way, we'd already have them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234993" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's tripping you up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234994" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have the support of the entire Imperial war machine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bring out heavier firepower.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cleanup operations are low priority for ordnance. Anything bigger than man-portable is being put to use on the front lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234997" id2="17" version="1065353216">The resistance has shown remarkable ingenuity. They've cobbled together a number of repeating blaster turrets to block our advance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234999" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've tried hitting them from several angles, but they've been quick to redeploy their defenses. I could use a hand outmaneuvering them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I look like a charity?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Logistics authorized bounty funds for resistance members turned over. This seems like a good use for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235004" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need a heavy hitter to flank the resistance position and take out those turrets while my force mounts a direct assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235006" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't dare redeploy the turrets away from our attack, so you won't have to worry about them being turned on you before you can destroy them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just handle it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood. We'll manage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235011" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy is inventive, I must give them that.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
