<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>7</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tatooine/heroic_weekly/imperial/mission_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Officer Vengo has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Infinite Dessication sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Officer Vengo may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Reskin has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jundland sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Captain Reskin may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Cibinel has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jundland sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Captain Cibinel may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana Corrs has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Mos Ila sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Lana Corrs may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180208" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gezda has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jundland sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Gezda may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180209" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vuk Dimitrius has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jundland sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Vuk Dimitrius may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Marcus has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jundland sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Commander Marcus may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
