<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>251</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/smuggler/master_sumalee.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1021784" id2="17" version="1065353216">That farmstead is the only lead we have on those gangsters. Be careful down on Bothawui.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1021786" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd like to help, but I'm coordinating a planetary invasion. Excuse me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1026599" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you and your crew, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1027715" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is outrageous! How does a criminal gang come to possess a superdreadnought that threatens our security?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037494" id2="17" version="1065353216">I read you, Risha. Captain--it's been too long. Republic High Command still talks about your defeat of the Voidwolf. Jealously, I might add.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037495" id2="17" version="1065353216">All they have to do is single-handedly take down an Imperial flagship, and they can join my club. I'll cut them a discount on membership dues.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037495" id2="17" version="1065353216">They should be jealous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037496" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it hadn't been for you, I'd still be wandering around Corellia looking for a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037496" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were a big help to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037497" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm the one who's jealous. They see you all the time, but you never call me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037497" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Hello, gorgeous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037500" id2="17" version="1065353216">You see what I have to put up with, Sumee?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037504" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could arrange for you to be shot out the air lock together. Then you'd see her for the rest of your life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037506" id2="17" version="1065353216">The holo chimes on both ends. Try it and see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037507" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not here for a reunion. Risha says you can help me find some people I want a chat with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get down to business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037513" id2="17" version="1065353216">He must be worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037518" id2="17" version="1065353216">I regret we never got a chance to team up. Always stuck behind a desk--no place for a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still humble and generous. I've missed you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037523" id2="17" version="1065353216">How romantic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037533" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been reviewing reports about the attack on Port Nowhere. Whoever ordered it must face justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037785" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire claimed Bothawui in the Treaty of Coruscant. With that peace broken, we're taking it back. Things were going very well until recently.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does this end with you asking me to save the planet? Because I charge a lot for that--and I'm available.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037786" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need a job done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037787" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've committed a sizable force, but we'll take all the help we can get. The Republic needs this world's agriculture.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037789" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's so special about this place that's worth fighting over?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is Bothawui important?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037790" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is an agrarian world. High-yield farming communities, vineyards and ranches. Resources we desperately need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037792" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire has adopted a &quot;scorched ground&quot; policy as it retreats. Anything you can do to prevent that here is greatly appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037794" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not here to help the Republic win the war. Are you gonna help me find the people who hit Port Nowhere, or not?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037794" id2="17" version="1065353216">Skip to the Womp Gang.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course--but it wouldn't hurt you to return the favor. The Republic desperately needs this planet's food resources intact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037797" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Fenn Traw'lurr of the Bothan resistance intelligence network. He has information for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, bountiful Captain. Master Sumalee provided only the barest details of your situation. May I ask what your interest is in the Womp family?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037883" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just want to ask a few questions, but I won't lie--I'm not optimistic about the answers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037883" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on an investigation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037884" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, good. You already know they are unpleasant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037886" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's this about me being &quot;bountiful&quot;? Is that how you ask for bribes?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037886" id2="17" version="1065353216">What did you call me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037887" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me--a colloquialism, born of millennia spent tending farmlands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037889" id2="17" version="1065353216">I plan to fill them with tiny holes. Is that a problem?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037889" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want revenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not for me, but they might feel differently.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037892" id2="17" version="1065353216">My network has heard of these people you seek: an extended clan of common criminals and lackeys, noted mainly for petty thievery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed. Our spies now report a large group of Womp gangsters have taken over a farmstead. To what purpose, we don't know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037895" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suspect the only digging the Womps do is when they're burying bodies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037895" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt they're farming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are the previous owners of this farmstead still around?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who used to own the place?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037897" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need to know anything but where they are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just give me coordinates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038974" id2="17" version="1065353216">They have vehicles, but nothing for tilling soil.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038976" id2="17" version="1065353216">The original farmers were members of the Sut'valris family-clan. Good native Bothans, dragged off to an Imperial internment camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038978" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you wish, but take care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038980" id2="17" version="1065353216">The farmstead is guarded by heavily armed speeders. The gangsters shoot at any air traffic that comes near.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038981" id2="17" version="1065353216">You guys won't mind if that farm burns to the ground, right? Hypothetically?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1038981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Things may get blasty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Obviously, we would prefer you leave as little of our world in smoking ruin as possible. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always nice to meet a fella who thinks his way around trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1038983" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] You're a useful man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, I think! A lot. See if you can guess what I'm thinking now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful--you're gonna make Bowdaar jealous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038994" id2="17" version="1065353216">My expertise will remain at your disposal should the need arise. Best of luck to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038995" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's my most sincere pleasure to serve you. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038996" id2="17" version="1065353216">A pleasant stroll in the countryside, huh? I've heard that before. Alderaan, Tatooine, Taris....</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1038996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds too easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bothawui puts those worlds to shame, trust me. Good hunting to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038998" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't my first frontal assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1038998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't tell me my job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apologies. I meant only to serve you with the best intelligence I could gather.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay in touch, Captain--and remember it's a war zone. Don't lose your head down there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reassurance: I remain eighty-percent functional when my head is removed, master--in case that ever comes up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039005" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're here to claim heads, not lose them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1039007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pulled the head off a gundark, once. It kept fighting. Stupid beast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reminds me of the time on Ord Mantell when I snuck up behind a separatist and... never mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for that lovely mental image as we race toward certain death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, the captain can still function without it. And thank goodness for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, Captain. I'm doing all I can to help you find the people who attacked Port Nowhere, but the Republic has its hands full.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039970" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's just say the scum provoked me. The rest is my business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1039970" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll ask questions, not you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039971" id2="17" version="1065353216">A personal grudge, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039973" id2="17" version="1065353216">They hurt a lot of good Republic citizens. They won't get away with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1039973" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm here for justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039974" id2="17" version="1065353216">After so long under corrupt Imperial law, it's a pleasure to be reminded of the Republic's high principles.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039976" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Common&quot; and &quot;petty&quot; aren't words I'd use to describe anyone who nearly destroyed a space station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Petty criminals can't afford war speeders. I'm beginning to think you're on the right course, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039981" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't recommend a direct approach. Best you arrive outside the speeders' weapon range and go in on foot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, are you quite sure I should be accompanying you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039986" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're closing in on Bothawui, and I have good news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039988" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the persons responsible are on Bothawui, I may know someone who can help. Meet me at my office on the station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, one of our supply fleets is missing. Nearly two dozen bulk freighters en route here just... vanished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me, Captain--duty calls. I requisitioned a private shuttle you can land near the Womp Gang's farm. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044788" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, I just received an update from the Bothan resistance. Something about you invading Camp Shatter and needing my help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044789" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm doing just fine all by myself--but if you've got any bright ideas, I'm listening.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044789" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't turn down an offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044790" id2="17" version="1065353216">Traw'lurr exaggerated. Everything's under control. How are you--missing me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044790" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] I just want to talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should I remind you that I never miss?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044793" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a brave man to let me carry a blaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Terribly--which is why I'd like to keep you alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044797" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't suppose you have a few good soldiers handy? Promise to give most of them back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044797" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sister, can you spare a squad?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Traw'lurr underestimates me, but you should know better. I don't need rescuing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Help is the last thing I need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044801" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want these criminals brought down as much as you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044803" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Na'tog owes me a favor. He'll dispatch a commando team to cut off enemy reinforcements and secure your position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044819" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wish I could do more, but it's one emergency after another. Someone just raided our fleet's refueling depot. Millions of liters stolen. No survivors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044820" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let me keep you--I have a whole bunch of people to shoot. I'll try to leave some for your reinforcements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044820" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll let you go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044821" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm starting to wonder if all these random attacks aren't connected. Maybe our gangsters are better organized than we think?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could the Womps be involved?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044822" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never heard of a gang taking out a military refueling depot, but you might be onto something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep in touch--and may the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you're in the market for a new supplier. I might know someone--for the right price.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Want to buy some fuel?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044826" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a fine line between opportunism and callous greed. Good luck, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056481" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're good at making extra trouble. Let's lighten that load.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060236" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've repeatedly killed our people, stolen vital resources and escaped justice. Their leader just demanded one hundred trillion credits to end these raids. I need a solution!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060237" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep yelling like that, and you'll burst a lekku. Relax. It's all under control, Madame Chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060237" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm down, Saresh. I'm on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chancellor, I believe you're acquainted with the captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060240" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course I am. The Voidwolf's defeat is the only reason I can ignore being referred to as &quot;Madame Chance.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060242" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course I am. Your success on Makeb bought you considerable leeway with me--but &quot;Madame Chance&quot; is pushing it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060244" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you're in the middle of something. I'll come back later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060244" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this a bad time?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060245" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't you dare. Er, the Supreme Chancellor needs your input.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would you pay fifty trillion credits if I made your problem disappear?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060247" id2="17" version="1065353216">How much to kill him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060248" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm funding a war, not a bounty hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060250" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to the captain's efforts, we know our enemy's name--and forced him to reveal his secret weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060252" id2="17" version="1065353216">Traw'lurr informed me that the dreadnought previously belonged to a Hutt named Barabbula. I've heard him mentioned in history lessons. He was Supreme Mogul of the Cartel three centuries ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060253" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not much to go on--but then again, when is it? My people will run a search on this Barabbula. We'll find something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060253" id2="17" version="1065353216">My crew will investigate this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060255" id2="17" version="1065353216">Risha, I'm putting you in charge. Get me a lead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060256" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on it. See you back at the ship. Sumee....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060257" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get to the ship and tell Risha to start researching. She knows all the wrong people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060258" id2="17" version="1065353216">I live to please you, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060259" id2="17" version="1065353216">Acknowledgment: I will deliver your message with extreme authority, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060260" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any day I get to order Risha around is a good one.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1060261" id2="17" version="1065353216">Red Mane will find answers. She's good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060262" id2="17" version="1065353216">She never met a scoundrel she didn't like. On it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, I'm sort of an underworld expert, too! All right....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Risha? I need everything on a former Hutt Supreme Mogul named Barabbula. I want friends, enemies, tail measurements--got it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Barabbula sounds familiar. I'm on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060268" id2="17" version="1065353216">How does a bigshot Hutt drop off the face of the galaxy in his private superdreadnought without us knowing about it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't you know anything else?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060269" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic was fighting the Jedi Civil War when this happened. We've asked the Cartel for help, but they're a little distracted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for stealing my thunder, lady. I'll just let you and that loudmouthed Bothan handle this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060270" id2="17" version="1065353216">So much for my surprise news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me. The truth is, that's all I know. We need your underworld expertise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060273" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, your crew could assist the investigation. I'll alert them to this opportunity to please you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suggestion: Your organic crewmates could earn their keep by investigating this lead, master. I will motivate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Risha enjoys boasting about her underworld knowledge. I'll get her started researching.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1060276" id2="17" version="1065353216">Red Mane has good luck. I will tell Risha about this Barabbula.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060277" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know who needs something to do? Risha. I'll get her started on this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060278" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just had a great idea. Instead of saying something stupid in front of the Supreme Chancellor, I'll go get the crew busy investigating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060279" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know I've heard the name Barabbula before. I'll go back to the ship and do some digging. Catch you later, Sumee.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060280" id2="17" version="1065353216">I took the liberty of contacting Risha. She's gathering whatever information she can find on Barabbula.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060282" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, I'll put this plainly. The Republic's in no position to defend itself from random assaults by criminal thugs with their own dreadnought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060284" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will not pay that ridiculous ransom. I'm granting you full authority to deal with this. Find that ship and eliminate those gangsters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060285" id2="17" version="1065353216">I use a very literal interpretation of the word &quot;eliminate.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060285" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm planning to kill them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060286" id2="17" version="1065353216">So do I.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave those crazy Womps to me. You go beat up the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything for the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060289" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060291" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll play along until my losses exceed the potential profit. After that, all bets are off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060291" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm in this for the credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060292" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's more potential profit in a Republic that survives, than a galaxy dominated by the Empire. Consider that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060294" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't suppose this &quot;full authority&quot; comes with a fancy identicard and one of those spiffy security uniforms?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060294" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I have a law badge?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060295" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm in no mood for jokes. My people are dying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060297" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want my help, keep the speeches to yourself and let me decide how this plays out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060297" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't boss me around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060298" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you wish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060300" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've kept your survival on Bothawui a secret. Given how badly the Womps want you dead, that seems best. You'll have room to maneuver.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060302" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always a pleasure, Madame Chancellor. Well... here we are again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060303" id2="17" version="1065353216">My good looks, luck and brilliance combined with your... Jedi-ness... those Womps will never know what hit them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060304" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was wondering when I'd finally get you alone. Does this office door have a lock?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060304" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Just the two of us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060305" id2="17" version="1065353216">Risha's under the impression you two have an exclusive relationship. And she's my friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Risha seems taken with you. I don't think I can betray an old friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060307" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're telling me you two never shared anything before? I know better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060307" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] Risha won't mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060308" id2="17" version="1065353216">She told you? That was a long time ago. We were different people then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060310" id2="17" version="1065353216">You enjoy tempting death. Risha told me your Mandalorian crewmate is much more than a friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060311" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't your Mandalorian friend be jealous? Risha seems to think you two are more than friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060312" id2="17" version="1065353216">Technically, she's an ex-Mandalorian. And we have an open relationship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060312" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] Akaavi won't mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060313" id2="17" version="1065353216">How progressive of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Risha's told me a lot about you. She says you're incapable of sustaining an emotional attachment. Luckily, so am I.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isn't it wonderful when two people find each other in this crazy old galaxy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060316" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad we're of like minds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop talking and get the lights.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060318" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I miss a memo, or have Jedi standards on romance gotten a lot more relaxed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060318" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the Jedi Code?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grand Master Satele Shan lifted the Council's ban on romantic relationships. We still can't form attachments, but... I don't think that'll be a problem with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060321" id2="17" version="1065353216">It isn't too late to back out. Are you sure want to do this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop asking questions you already know the answers to. I've wanted you since before Corellia. You feel the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060322" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] I want you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060323" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to regret this--but not for a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060325" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is one office I'll never look at the same way again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's do this more often. I don't know about you, but I feel ready to take on the whole galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060326" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] This was fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060327" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm hoping we won't have to. Fight the whole galaxy, I mean--not the other thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060329" id2="17" version="1065353216">You alright? I haven't just driven you to the dark side, have I?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you still feel like a Jedi?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060330" id2="17" version="1065353216">For a moment or two. I'm over it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060332" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was wonderful, but let's keep it to ourselves. No reason to upset Risha.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Risha can't know about us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060333" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll change your perspective on all sorts of places, but let's keep it quiet. Akaavi wouldn't appreciate what we have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Akaavi can't know about us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060334" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was so wrong. I regret this immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060336" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm leaving to organize a fleet of scout vessels. We'll see if we can't catch that dreadnought in a hyperspace scanning net. Long shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060338" id2="17" version="1065353216">See what your crew's found on Barabbula the Hutt. He's our only link to the Womp Gang. One last thing? This never happened. Goodbye, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060339" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's just an office. Don't get all dreamy on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060339" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm done here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060340" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're in the clear on that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060342" id2="17" version="1065353216">My gut just sent me a message that this is a terrible idea. Let's quit while we're ahead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060342" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, it'll end badly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060343" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your instincts talk to you? Interesting. Maybe you're Force sensitive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060345" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer you as a friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060347" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just remembered I have this important thing to do--save the Republic, blah, blah. Besides, you and I work better as pals. Right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's just be friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060348" id2="17" version="1065353216">All engine and no thrust, hmm? I understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060350" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've both faced worse odds alone. Together, we'll be more than enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060350" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chin up, Sumalee.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060351" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll have to be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060353" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here you are again. I've got a ship to catch--do whatever you want.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060353" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm leaving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060354" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not planning to sit around here, if you're wondering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060356" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll organize a scout fleet to scan for the dreadnought, but it'll be like hunting for a pebble in an asteroid field.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060358" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope your sources know a quicker way to find the Womp Gang. May the Force be with us, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1067601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Sumalee, I expect you to coordinate all efforts with the captain. Do not fail either of us. Saresh out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1093524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember Master Sumalee, that nice Jedi who helped us beat the Voidwolf on Corellia? She's here. I called ahead to get her working for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1093525" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remember Master Sumalee. She'll definitely come through. Pretty sure she has a crush on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1093525" id2="17" version="1065353216">She'll do anything for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1093526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good old Master Sumalee. Always nice to have her on the payroll.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1093526" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like this plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1093527" id2="17" version="1065353216">All the Jedi I've met blur together. Is she the one who carries a lightsaber and moralizes at people?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1093527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't say I remember her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1093528" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll remind her you're spoken for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1093529" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can snap your neck like a twig.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1093531" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear rumors the Jedi have loosened up on the whole &quot;no romance&quot; thing. You might actually have a shot there, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1093533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best part is, she works for free. I love altruists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1093534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Close enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1093535" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't want Jedi mixed up in this. Our hands might be getting extra dirty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1093535" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't need her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1093536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use her for information. Sumalee and I go way back--she knows when to mind her own business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1093538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sumee, you there?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
