<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>118</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/smuggler/the_twins.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1021797" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want to join our gang, you gotta survive the Inflictorator!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, it is possible I left something cooking aboard your vessel. Perhaps I should go check?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Paradox: My motion sensors detect nothing nearby, but my alertness matrix is running hot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry. I have a bad feeling about this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1053622" id2="17" version="1065353216">My neck fur itches. Bad luck is near.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053624" id2="17" version="1065353216">If anything's on the other side of that door, me and Mabel are ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053626" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is usually the time when something terrible happens. I shouldn't have said that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053628" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like this. Where are the gang's reinforcements?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Light 'em up, Pertie! Let's see what these wermos are made of!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053642" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's about time. Huntster, free the new recruits. They pass the test.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053646" id2="17" version="1065353216">A party, for me? I love it! Fry those guys some more. That's entertainment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1053646" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, all! Glad to be here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe we oughta just shoot him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Frying your own gangsters? That's the classy behavior I've come to expect from the Womps. Why would you do that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1053649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice way to treat your gang.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053650" id2="17" version="1065353216">We only keep the toughest outlaws. We're gonna pillage our way across this galaxy. You could've been smart and joined, but no.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053652" id2="17" version="1065353216">Big mistake, not killing me when you had the chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1053652" id2="17" version="1065353216">You people are all dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053653" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't get to die easy. Not after what you did to my sweet boy Rance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053655" id2="17" version="1065353216">He was Pertamunk's husband-to-be. You took him from her. Now she's taking things from you. Starting with your teeth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1053657" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pertie, all the meet-up details are on this datapad. I don't want you missing the last shuttle because you got lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056414" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sure we shouldn't have just killed her while she was out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not only are you a bunch of Bothan-eating, Republic-raiding lunatics, but you marry your own relatives? That explains so much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056416" id2="17" version="1065353216">You people are twisted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056417" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were seventh cousins! Who are you to judge?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hang on, I just realized: Either you're twins, or somebody lost a bet. Which is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you brothers or sisters?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056420" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and me are about to have some private time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations. You idiots are going on the Republic's &quot;most-wanted&quot; list. Maybe I'll get them to pay me for wiping you out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056422" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galaxy will want you dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tough talk from a wermo strapped to an Imperial &quot;inflictorator.&quot; You're not going anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056429" id2="17" version="1065353216">Huntster! We're not supposed to put that stuff in writing!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056431" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got a terrible memory. Besides, the datapad's encrypted. We need to be off this rock when Operation Toxic Payback goes off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056432" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd love a bedtime story. How about &quot;Operation Toxic Payback and the Last Shuttle.&quot; Will you do all the voices?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056432" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me all about your plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056433" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're one of the nicest families I've ever met--psychotic behavior notwithstanding. Too bad none of you are leaving Bothawui.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056433" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admire your family loyalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056434" id2="17" version="1065353216">You drop that datapad and run along, ugly. I'll catch up when I'm done with your sister.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056434" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right, leave us alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut your mouth!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't take too long with this. C'mon, recruits! We're off to the space mansion!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now it's just you and me. We're gonna have us some fun. Rance would've wanted that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056440" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is probably a good time to tell you that my outfit is lined with detonite.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056440" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] I'm rigged to explode.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056441" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're lying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056442" id2="17" version="1065353216">That shock you just gave me almost set off these pants. Good thing it didn't--my gear could level this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056444" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm trying to imagine the look on your brother's face when he finds out we blew up together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056445" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll cut that fancy gear right off you....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056446" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know why you keep referring to Rance in the past tense. He's still alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056446" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] Rance is alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't lie to me! Kashtinn and Greyetta saw what happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056448" id2="17" version="1065353216">They didn't see the medical team that kolto'd your betrothed after I shot him. He's recovering at a field hospital.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, when I turn up dead, the Republic will probably just execute him....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait! I... I'll let you go... but I'm keeping your friend until I get my sweet boy back. You go free Rance right now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056452" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got some bad news for you, Pertie--Rance wasn't faithful. There was some Mirialan floozy with him in that farmhouse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056452" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] He cheated on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056453" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? You blasted liar!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056454" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just telling you what I saw. They seemed happy together--and who could blame them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would Rance... why would any man.... want you when he could have a real woman?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut up! I'll take you apart the old-fashioned way!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056463" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, you will be pleased to know my personality matrix remains intact after that unexpected shutdown.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Request: Please permit me to ease my embarrassment at being deactivated, master. Deleting this hideous troublemaker should do the trick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056467" id2="17" version="1065353216">They hit us with heplara-3 nerve toxin--the same gas the Imperials used against my clan.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1056469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only cowards fight with gas! This insult will not stand!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Last time I got knocked out that hard, it was Skavak. You look fresh-eyed, as usual. Figures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, we're not dead! Is that what hit us? Was it some sort of breath attack?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nerve gas... I'll have a headache for days. On the bright side, not dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Sumalee, we found her. She's uninjured, and Camp Shatter is secured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057336" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had everything under control--but I appreciate the assist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1057336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice of you to drop by.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Sumalee, we found him. I repeat, we found him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1057339" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have big news to share.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057341" id2="17" version="1065353216">An army, for me? You really do care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1057341" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Sumalee, my hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057344" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're going to need their protection.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057346" id2="17" version="1065353216">She sent them for me, darling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything for you, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057349" id2="17" version="1065353216">Typical Republic army--showing up after the party's over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1057349" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for nothing, slowpoke.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057351" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess what? The Womp Gang attacked your refueling depot and supply convoy. They're planning something nasty for Bothawui, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057354" id2="17" version="1065353216">These criminals have declared war on the Republic. Whatever they're planning for Bothawui, we can't let it come to pass.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057355" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was after that scum first, Jedi--and I'll have their heads no matter what happens to this lousy planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1057355" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care about Bothawui.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057356" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't mean we can't use each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057358" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you say, Master Jedi? Ready to team up with a living legend and save the galaxy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1057358" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can handle them together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057359" id2="17" version="1065353216">How could I refuse such a generous offer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057361" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm happy to pitch in, but my contract with the good people of Port Nowhere stands as-is. That money's all mine, got it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1057361" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;We&quot;? I'm not sharing my fee.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057362" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't dream of coming between you and your money.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057364" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only chance I've got of catching these bad guys is locked on this datapad. I need a way to access it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1057364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you decrypt the datapad?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057365" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wouldn't even know about these people if it wasn't for me. Let's settle on my fee before this goes any further.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1057365" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make me an offer to stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057366" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be rewarded for bringing the Womp Gang to justice. I've never met anyone with such a gift for capitalizing on conflict.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057368" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on my way back to Bothawui. Head to the Republic's forward camp. Our best slicer--Corporal Frisk--will be expecting you. He'll decrypt that datapad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057370" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll take care of the prisoner, Captain. Anything we need to know about her?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057371" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had to hit her pretty hard. Have a medical droid check her over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1057371" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take her for healing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Throw her in the strongest prison you can find--preferably one with bad food.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1057372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send her straight to a cell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1057375" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's dead. [Kill her]</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057377" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's ready for burial.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057378" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh, right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1057380" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll want to take that encrypted datapad to our forward base. The fighting's bad up there--be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait! I... I'll let you go... but I'm keeping your fancy droid until I get my sweet boy back. You free Rance right now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait! I... I'll let you go. I can't live without my sweet boy. You go free Rance and bring him back here right now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1067608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get those boys to the meet-up. Kashtinn needs replacements. Those hits on that Republic refueling station at Enarc and the supply convoy over Farstine cost us muscle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1067609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bad enough you hit Port Nowhere. Attacking the Republic's a whole new level of stupid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1067609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurting the Republic was dumb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1067610" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only fool here is you. Shot up our gang, killed our blood... my sweet boy....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1067612" id2="17" version="1065353216">You knocked over those Republic marks? That took some asteroids. I'd be impressed, except that I hate you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1067612" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admire your ambition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1067613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Feeling's mutual. We've got big plans--too bad you won't be around to see the Womps on top.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1067615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Us Womps are leaving a real nice present for all the scum-suckers here on our way out. You don't live happily ever after. The End.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1067616" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can see why Kashtinn hates you. Got a real big mouth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1067618" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got an encrypted datapad with info on the Womp Gang's rendezvous--and maybe something called &quot;Operation Toxic Payback.&quot; Unfortunately, my prisoner isn't talking.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
