<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>372</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/smuggler/trawlurr.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1021809" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Bothan resistance network is at your service, Republic friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1025335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fire the flares at the coordinates I've provided. Hope to the stars we aren't too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1027666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Camp Shatter is your best bet to find the Womp Gang's rendezvous point. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040418" id2="17" version="1065353216">Were you addressing me, master? I was calculating next week's dinner menu.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Conjecture: These troublemakers may be smarter than they look, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040422" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only one here who knew anything was Rance--and he won't be telling.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1040424" id2="17" version="1065353216">Writing down a secret plan is bad luck. Stupid, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040426" id2="17" version="1065353216">These folks are slippery as Adegan eels--and not just 'cause they don't bathe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040428" id2="17" version="1065353216">These people don't strike me as the &quot;write things down&quot; type. That requires literacy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Criminals smart enough to cover their tracks? What's the underworld coming to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040432" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won't find any trail to follow here, Captain. We taught the Womp Gang that compromising information is best stored up here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like the Bothan resistance knows more about the Womps than you've let on, Traw'lurr.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040433" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;We,&quot; huh? That's not good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apologies for arriving too late to be any assistance--though you acquitted yourself admirably.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040435" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm terrible with names and faces after a shootout. Are you friend or foe?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040436" id2="17" version="1065353216">Friend, most definitely. Fenn Traw'lurr of the Bothan resistance network. I provided the intel that brought you here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your hands where I can see them. Any sudden moves and you'll join these creeps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Twitch wrong, and I shoot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040438" id2="17" version="1065353216">I mean you no harm. Fenn Traw'lurr, Bothan resistance? I spoke with you and Master Sumalee by holo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040441" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you wanted my help, you could've just asked. I might've given you a discount for being cute.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040441" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Next time, be honest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040442" id2="17" version="1065353216">I deeply regret my error.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040456" id2="17" version="1065353216">We believe the Womp family switched sides to the Empire... and we're right. This datapad details a contract to hunt my agents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040458" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire will pay these gangsters to slaughter my entire spy network.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would the Empire work with this family? For that matter, why would the Womps kill your spies?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040459" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a strange alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040460" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire knows they're beaten. They've offered a staggering sum to anyone who can punish us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do these lowlifes know enough about your operation to deal that kind of damage?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can they actually do it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040463" id2="17" version="1065353216">My condolences. Let me know where to send the flowers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040463" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's bad news--for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040464" id2="17" version="1065353216">This concerns you as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thing you're a spy and not a tourism ambassador, because you're really putting me off Bothawui right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't manipulate me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040468" id2="17" version="1065353216">To be fair, this was the only lead I had on our mutual enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040473" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're not expecting my understanding, because right now, all I'm thinking about are creative ways to shoot you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040473" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should blast you for lying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040474" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand your anger, but hear me out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040476" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Womp Gang knows our secrets, but my agents know theirs. We possess the information to help you hunt down this filth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040492" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to make an example of those gangsters? The resistance will give you that chance--but only if you save my agents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040493" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I save your precious spy network, you're going to owe me a lot more than just information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040493" id2="17" version="1065353216">You work for me, now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040494" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll be honored to serve you--but time is short.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040496" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're chasing a threat to the Republic that has allied with the Empire. Help our resistance survive, and both our causes benefit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040497" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a slick one. I'm just gonna agree before you talk me into buying beachfront property on Tatooine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, okay! I'm sold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040498" id2="17" version="1065353216">The beaches here are much nicer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040500" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seek to profit by eliminating these gangsters. My agents can ensure your success, but only if they're still alive. It's just good business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spies! Can't trust 'em, can't shoot 'em on sight. I'll help you--but don't go thinking we're friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040501" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll work with you, for now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040502" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll settle for colleagues.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything for you, handsome. You can owe me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040504" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Of course I'll help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040505" id2="17" version="1065353216">She means credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever it takes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040509" id2="17" version="1065353216">A debt I'll happily repay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you hear that? My meter's running. You've hired me, so talk fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, but I'm charging extra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040512" id2="17" version="1065353216">I bet you can tell me everything about the Womps. Start talking, or this conversation ends with my blaster down your throat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040512" id2="17" version="1065353216">No deal. All I need is you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040513" id2="17" version="1065353216">The kind of knowledge you require is only available in the minds of my field agents--the very ones whose lives are in danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warning my network requires more than a comm signal. The Empire tracks our holotransmitters, so we've adopted more primitive communications.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040517" id2="17" version="1065353216">My agents deliver emergency signals using flare pistols. Fire one where it can be seen, and my people will run for safety.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040518" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this is the only way to find the Womp Gang, well... I've done crazier things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040518" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything that high-profile is bound to get noticed by the bad guys. I'll be painting a target on myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Flares draw trouble, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Correct. That's why you should always be on the move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shooting a few flares shouldn't pose much risk to someone like you. Let me know when your people are ready to talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great--you go do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040523" id2="17" version="1065353216">There isn't time to warn everyone if I'm working alone. I need you on the other half of the sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use a Republic holofrequency to call me once you've fired the flares. I'll tell you where to meet my agents. Be safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040922" id2="17" version="1065353216">I owe you a confession. My network had an &quot;understanding&quot; with these gangsters. Their smuggling and sabotage were useful to our cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040924" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the Womp family recently broke ties with us, and I fear the worst. That's why I sent you here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040925" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've worked with them for years. They can summon us to a private meeting and murder whoever shows up--or force them to talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1041937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Five percent, tops. You ain't that cute.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1041938" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right. Why clean up your own mess when you can get someone else to do the dirty work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1041938" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fair enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1041939" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did my research, Captain. You may be the single best marksman on Bothawui right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1042067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Traw'lurr, come in. I shot all the flares.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1042068" id2="17" version="1065353216">My agents are evacuating, but the one who knows most about the Womp family hasn't reported in. I'm headed to her enclave now. Care to join me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1042069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like the Womp Gang got to her first. I've questioned corpses before. They're really tight-lipped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1042069" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's probably dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1042070" id2="17" version="1065353216">My missing agent knows all the network's escape routes and hideouts. I suspect our foe will try to interrogate her. That buys us time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1042072" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't let you walk into certain death alone, handsome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1042072" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] I'll meet you there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1042073" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are talking to me, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1042075" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I walk in with you, my odds of survival rise dramatically.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1042077" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this lady's the expert on the Womp family, I don't want her getting shot until she answers my questions. Maybe not even then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1042077" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1042078" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get what I need from your other agents. Where do I find them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1042078" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll work without her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1042079" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't understand. The missing operative knows our retreat plans. If the Womp Gang breaks her, there'll be no one left alive to question.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1042081" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm transmitting our enclave's coordinates. It's an underground cavern. Quite beautiful, but with many ambush zones. Be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1042083" id2="17" version="1065353216">My agent's name is Ror'sunn. If you get to her first, keep her alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043285" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no intervention like the timely variety. These animals really would've made soup out of us. And now that we've established my gratitude... who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043286" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm taking down the Womp Gang, and Traw'lurr says you're the expert on them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043286" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043287" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Expert&quot; may be exaggerating, but I'll gladly oblige your questions if it means less riffraff polluting my homeworld.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043289" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm figuring out the Womp Gang's power structure. What do you know about &quot;Hur-Hur&quot; and his friends?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043289" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about these guys.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Frawnk and Hubrick were Unnur's sons. They weren't merely gangsters--they were all members of the Womp family.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your gratitude. Tell me everything you know about the Womp Gang--or I'll be cooking fried Bothan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Work for me, or you're dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043293" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another fan of the culinary arts. Very well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043295" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Womp family rooted themselves on Bothawui before the Empire seized control. A pack of petty thugs scraping out a wretched existence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043297" id2="17" version="1065353216">Long ago, the resistance caught the Womps burying toxic waste on our planet. Rather than neutralize them, we turned the situation to our advantage by sabotaging the Imperial-run farms.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043298" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the sabotage part--poisoning the Empire's food supply--but how did you get away with charging the Womps to bury toxic waste?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043298" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain your operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our agreement was straightforward: Pay us for disposal sites and protection from the Empire, or take up permanent residence in their own dumping grounds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043301" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you say &quot;toxic waste,&quot; I assume you don't mean what the Womps generate naturally. Where were they getting it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043301" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where'd this waste come from?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043302" id2="17" version="1065353216">You deliberately poisoned your own planet? Remind me not to eat in your restaurants.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043302" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's disgusting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043303" id2="17" version="1065353216">We only poisoned the farms growing crops for the Empire. Our own food supplies remain safe to consume.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043305" id2="17" version="1065353216">We never learned the offworld source of the gang's toxic waste, but there was no shortage of it. It was profitable business for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043307" id2="17" version="1065353216">But since the family patriarch died and his eldest son Kashtinn took over, they've grown increasingly uncooperative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043308" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard something about a &quot;space mansion.&quot; That mean anything to you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043308" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seems they have a new home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043309" id2="17" version="1065353216">First I've heard of such a thing. I couldn't begin to speculate what he meant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pretty sure I chatted with Kashtinn by holo. I'm not a fan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043310" id2="17" version="1065353216">I met the new head Womp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043311" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's a boorish, self-aggrandizing, deluded buffoon--and I'm not convinced he's truly in charge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043312" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds to me like the Womp Gang has every reason to hate the resistance. You should've seen this attack coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043312" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you blame them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043313" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were always such cowards. Their newfound confidence--not to mention firepower--caught us off guard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043314" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm cutting off all the branches on that family tree, but I need to know where they're gathering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043314" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're dead once I find them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fortunately, Unnur loved to talk. I believe I can help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank the sun and seasons you're alive. Apologies for being late again, Captain. Took the scenic route evading a stubborn Imperial patrol.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Caught a parting shot, but I'll live. I hope Ror'sunn is providing useful intelligence on our mutual enemy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043320" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's telling me all about your operation. Toxic waste dumping, extortion... who knew spy work was so glamorous?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043320" id2="17" version="1065353216">And revealing your shady work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043321" id2="17" version="1065353216">You flatter us. From what I've heard of your exploits, we're amateurs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Poor baby, looks like you could use a woman's touch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043323" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Need some healing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043324" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure he can afford a medical droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043326" id2="17" version="1065353216">A lovely offer, but my wounds can wait. Justice cannot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043328" id2="17" version="1065353216">We just wrapped up a history lesson, but I still don't get what this gang is after. Seems like they're hitting things at random.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me what the Womps want.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043329" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Womp family we knew was a pack of impoverished imbeciles. Somehow, they've become a genuine threat--obsessed with avenging past indignities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043331" id2="17" version="1065353216">If all you're gonna do is stand there and bleed, at least be quiet about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043331" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need to hear from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043334" id2="17" version="1065353216">While he was interrogating me, Unnur indicated the Womp Gang has taken over Camp Shatter. The Empire granted them the facility as a temporary base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Camp Shatter was one of the most brutal detention centers on Bothawui. Impossibly well-defended.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ever heard of Belsavis? I busted in and out of there like it was the Galactic City Public Library.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing is impossible for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there anyplace else I can go? Maybe something that's only &quot;possibly&quot; well-defended?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we have another option?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043339" id2="17" version="1065353216">From what I overheard, the Womp Gang has abandoned its old hideouts. Camp Shatter is the only certain lead I can offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043341" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not like Imperials to hand over a base to a bunch of crazy criminals. What's the catch?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043341" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why'd the Empire give it up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043342" id2="17" version="1065353216">The valley it occupies was overrun by Republic forces. The Empire retaliated by flooding the area to destroy its tactical value.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043344" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our enemies clearly intend to wreak more havoc on Bothawui before they depart. Considering what they did to Port Nowhere, I fear the worst.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043346" id2="17" version="1065353216">The resistance is in shambles. The Republic military is engaged with the Empire. You're our best chance at stopping the Womp Gang.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043347" id2="17" version="1065353216">No offense, but I couldn't care less about Bothawui. I'm just dealing with a business rival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043347" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no hero, but I'll fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever your reason, we'll be pleased when you win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043350" id2="17" version="1065353216">Saving planets is a hobby of mine. So's blasting bad guys, come to think of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043350" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043351" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isn't it wonderful when work and play coincide?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043353" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not doing this for the warm feelings or revenge. It's just a job--a profitable one, hopefully.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043353" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope this war pays well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043354" id2="17" version="1065353216">A certain degree of professional detachment is acceptable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know how often I'm someone's &quot;best chance&quot;? I'm starting to think this galaxy would fall apart if I wasn't around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone always says that!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043357" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best never to test that theory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043359" id2="17" version="1065353216">I love making new friends, especially the appreciative kind. I'm doing a lot for you people. Now it's your turn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1043359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Repay me by swearing loyalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rebuild your spy network and take over the black market. Basic goods are in short supply, and your people will pay whatever we ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043363" id2="17" version="1065353216">My crew will provide the goods. You handle the distribution. I take eighty percent of the profits. Understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clear as a summer sky. You'll always have friends on Bothawui--assuming you eliminate the competition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043366" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll escort Ror'sunn and the others to safety. Take care, Captain. I don't envy you assaulting an impregnable enemy base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1043385" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not misunderstand: Delivering these signals is dangerous. The Empire watches the skies. They will hunt us both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044831" id2="17" version="1065353216">They have an expansive list of grievances and are machinating toward inflicting great trauma on many.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Translation: A big family of losers is bent on revenge, and when they finally get organized, we're all in trouble. So let's prevent that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044832" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd better stop them quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you get your kicks from making people consult a dictionary when you talk?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Restate all that in Basic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044834" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Womp Gang is powerful, dangerous and gathering strength. Whatever their plans are, we don't want them succeeding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044836" id2="17" version="1065353216">How big is this family, anyway? Starting to wonder if I brought enough ammo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044836" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many Womps need killing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044837" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm embarrassed to admit we never fully charted the Womp family line. They breed like gizka.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044840" id2="17" version="1065353216">He killed Rance... this little person killed my brother! Who am I going to play sabacc with now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shh... Mother's here. I'll make it all better, I promise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044843" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you'd like a shot at revenge, I'll clear my schedule. Just tell me where to meet up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's settle this in person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044844" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want a dance? I've got moves. I'll step all over you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044846" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't normally compliment people trying to kill me, but you look amazing for someone old enough to have grown-up children.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mother? But you're so young.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044847" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't talk to my wife. You're not worthy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044849" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want the hurt to go away, I recommend swallowing a thermal detonator. It's quicker than what I'll do to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kill yourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044850" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm talking to a corpse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shh... he'll get what's coming to him. This whole galaxy will be on its knees before we're done. Goodbye, Captain--we'll be in touch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044855" id2="17" version="1065353216">They fried the console. There's no data on where these Womps are or what they're planning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1059163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to see you in one piece, Captain. I'm relieved to report the Womp Gang's plan to poison my world failed thanks to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently, the dreadnought that fired on you has been causing the Republic considerable trouble elsewhere. Master Sumalee was summoned away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060364" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll assist your interrogation in her place. How may I help you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060365" id2="17" version="1065353216">Traw'lurr, does your spy network know which branch of the Womp family tree &quot;Chuckles&quot; here fell out of?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060365" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the prisoner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060366" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just stand there and look handsome while I work. I'll get back to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060366" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] We'll find something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get back to him with what? A drink order? I'll have a Harmon Kizzlebrew--hold the toxic waste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060369" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps we should shift focus to your prisoner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060371" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm suddenly eager to see this interrogation concluded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get some answers. Back my play, whatever it is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Follow my lead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060374" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well, but it's easier to improvise when you know what you're working with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060376" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need your help beating answers out of this idiot. Just arrange my business like we agreed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060376" id2="17" version="1065353216">Serve me, business partner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060377" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people are handling the details. I'm more useful to you here, I think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060379" id2="17" version="1065353216">This one is Narnish Womp. He's Kashtinn's fifth cousin. Considering what transpired at the grain storage complex, I'm guessing they aren't close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060381" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can't shut up, step outside. I'll handle this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060381" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay out of my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060384" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't bother asking me questions. Already lost my family. You can't take anything else from me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060385" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're looking at this all wrong, Narnie. Can I call you Narnie? Anyway, my point is you're a blank slate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060385" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can give you a new start.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060386" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060387" id2="17" version="1065353216">As far as the galaxy knows, you're dead. You don't have to be a Womp anymore. You could start over with a new name, on a better planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060388" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always liked Nar Shaddaa....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060389" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good idea. I might even be willing to throw in some startup funds to get you on your feet--but only if you talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060390" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have family here on Bothawui. What's the big girl's name from Camp Shatter? Lurchy? Hurtie?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060390" id2="17" version="1065353216">You still have Cousin Pertie.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pertie?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060392" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's her. She's being held nearby. Nice girl, recently lost her betrothed. Probably feeling a lot like you right now. Lonely... unappreciated... tired of people trying to kill her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pertie's a sweet girl.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060394" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then take care of her. Tell me what I need to know. I'll arrange a family reunion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060395" id2="17" version="1065353216">My Bothan friend here is a highly trained spy. He knows lots of ways to make you talk. Isn't that right, Traw'lurr?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Traw'lurr, be my &quot;bad cop.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060398" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's true. I have a jar of... lung beetles. Highly unpleasant. They lay eggs in your respiratory system.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooh, that sounds bad. I would hate to be you right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060400" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't do that. You're Republic. You have to follow the rules!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060401" id2="17" version="1065353216">Traw'lurr's a local. He makes the rules here, not me. But if you start talking, I'll keep him off you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060402" id2="17" version="1065353216">Traw'lurr, step outside and make sure we're not disturbed. I need to ask some questions with my fists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060402" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right. Time for a beating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060403" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your privacy is guaranteed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060405" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't do this! It's against the law!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since when have you cared about the law? Talk, or I'll finish rearranging your internal organs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060409" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to know about that ship Kashtinn hit us with? That all started before I was born.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060411" id2="17" version="1065353216">Decades ago, this Hutt--Barabbula--offered my family credits to bury his toxic waste. He sent droid-piloted shuttles full of it every month.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060412" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the hardest-working criminals I've ever met. Not sure whether to respect you or point and laugh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060412" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's quite a family business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your employer's name doesn't ring any bells. Give me the short version.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about Barabbula.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060414" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know any version. He's a Hutt, he's rich, and he was paying us. That's all we cared about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060416" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a bunch of nobodies. How'd this Hutt even know you existed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why'd the Hutt approach you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060417" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Womp family used to be huge. We ran half this blasted galaxy. Barabbula respected that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060419" id2="17" version="1065353216">When we were old enough, Kashtinn and me got sent to meet the Hutt's shuttle and pick up the monthly waste shipments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kashtinn and the shuttle droid got friendly. One day, the droid slipped how Barabbula flies around the galaxy in a giant space mansion--alone!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me guess: Your family suddenly developed an interest in real estate?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060422" id2="17" version="1065353216">You decided to steal the ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060423" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do realize there's no such thing as &quot;space mansions,&quot; right? It's a dreadnought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060423" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not a mansion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060424" id2="17" version="1065353216">You say that because you've never been inside. You could eat off the floors in there. It's gorgeous!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds relaxing. I can't tell you how many times I've thought about firing my crew and going solo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Solitude must be nice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060427" id2="17" version="1065353216">But who would cook meals for you, master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060429" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confession: Were I not programmed otherwise, I would also embark on a solitary rampage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060431" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wouldn't last a day. You crave attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1060433" id2="17" version="1065353216">A lone warrior's days are few in number.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060435" id2="17" version="1065353216">We love you, too, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060437" id2="17" version="1065353216">It does get pretty loud on the ship at night. Bowdaar snores.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060439" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a common fantasy, trust me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060441" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kashtinn started working on how to upload a slicer code to the droid. Reprogram it to take over Barabbula's ship. Spent years on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turns out Kashtinn isn't dumb--just slow. Few weeks ago, he finally uploads the code. Now that space mansion belongs to him. Well, him and Greyetta.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060444" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been in the market for a new ride. I think I've found the perfect one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060444" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be taking that ship back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your cousin and... whatever she is... took over that dreadnought. Now what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060445" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do they want?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060446" id2="17" version="1065353216">Womp family has about three-hundred years of scores to settle. Kashtinn's working through the list.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060448" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume the ship's original owner went out the air lock?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did they kill the Hutt?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060449" id2="17" version="1065353216">No idea. All I know is, somebody else is moving into my quarters. It's not fair. They had a window.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060451" id2="17" version="1065353216">You people might as well give up. That space mansion's bigger than most stations. You'll never stop it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060453" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's everything I know. You promised to set me up with a new life on Nar Shaddaa. Can I go?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060454" id2="17" version="1065353216">A deal's a deal--but don't even think about contacting your relatives. Wouldn't be healthy, understand?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060454" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're free to leave, Narnish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060455" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't. Kashtinn would kill me for surviving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060457" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll arrange a believable story to cover his impending escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060459" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know anything else. When can I see Cousin Pertie? She doesn't do well without family around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like this planet's full of toxic waste thanks to your family. I'm putting you and Pertie on hazardous material cleaning duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060460" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and Pertie clean Bothawui.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060461" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't we just go to prison? Maybe share a cell?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060463" id2="17" version="1065353216">I told you everything. We're even now, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060464" id2="17" version="1065353216">From what I've heard, there's an awful lot of toxic waste buried on Bothawui. I think you should dispose of it appropriately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060464" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll clean up Bothawui.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about prison, first. What would I have to do there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060467" id2="17" version="1065353216">That wasn't offered as an option. Besides, I find the captain's suggestion highly entertaining.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060469" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been a bad boy, Narnie. There's a place for people like you, but my ship's full. I'm sure the Republic can find you a nice private cell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060469" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sending you to prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060470" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? That's not fair--I cooperated! Wait, you said private cell? I won't have to sleep with twenty other people?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060472" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have all the solitude we can provide. Now do shut up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060474" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expect you'll be leaving soon. Might I interest you in some local cuisine before you depart? Interrogations always leave me hungry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060475" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] A meal sounds perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060477" id2="17" version="1065353216">No thanks--this is business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, it's been a pleasure assisting you. Please let me know if you require anything else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060480" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a Hutt dreadnought controlled by a crazy family of inbred gangsters out there. If I don't handle this mess, who will?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060480" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060481" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I've heard since I got here is how good the food is. It'd be a crime to not try it before I go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060481" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Join me for a meal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060482" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll return to your ship and inform the crew that you are dining without them, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis: Your posture, vocal inflection and core body temperature indicate you desire to be left alone with this man. I shall comply.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060484" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've had Bothan food. Too rich. Enjoy yourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1060485" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have to say it. Bowdaar knows the routine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060486" id2="17" version="1065353216">I ain't hungry. You need me, you know where to find me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three's a crowd, Captain. I'll head back to the ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060488" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds great! I can't wait to try... oh. I wasn't invited, was I? Right. See you at the ship....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060489" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll head back to the ship. Wouldn't want to be in the way....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060491" id2="17" version="1065353216">More for us to share. I know just the place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060492" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know just the place. Come--let me show you Bothan hospitality.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060494" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was delightful. I hope we'll do it again someday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060495" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of my crew is the jealous type. It's probably best if he doesn't find out about us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060495" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure, but don't tell Corso.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060496" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a spy--we're trained in discretion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060498" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I'll be spending lots of time here when this Womp Gang business is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060498" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to see you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. My world has much more to offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060501" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm one of those people who's always moving forward, but you never can tell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060501" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll see if I have time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060502" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope is the water that nourishes the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060504" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you'd told me Bothans only eat uncooked root vegetables, I wouldn't have stuck around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060504" id2="17" version="1065353216">The food here is awful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060505" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry if you were dissatisfied.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just get busy setting up that little enterprise we discussed. This captain needs a new pair of boots.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060507" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I need is your business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Profit before pleasure--understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060510" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you got the wrong idea about us. We're just friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, but you're not my type.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not even good friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apologies if I have offended you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Sumalee was summoned back to the orbital station. Perhaps she can assist your hunt. Bountiful harvest, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Sumalee was summoned back to the orbital station. I recommend you consult with her. It appears there's nothing more to learn on Bothawui.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060517" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no telling what kind of trouble these inbred gangsters will make with a Hutt dreadnought. Goodbye, Traw'lurr.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060517" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060518" id2="17" version="1065353216">May your harvest be full.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's hoping your planet gets back on its feet soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for all your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that the Republic is here and the Empire is not, that much is certain. Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell your people I expect Bothawui to be turning a profit for me within the month.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember our deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060522" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm certain we'll reap a bountiful harvest from our partnership. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for all your brilliant advice. I can take it from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060523" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm done with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best of luck. Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Traw'lurr, I think our ugly friend here needs to have an accident while trying to escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to die, scum. [Kill him]</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Happens all the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060528" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? No, you can't do that--I told you everything!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060529" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060532" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll explain things to the Republic authorities. Obviously, you had no choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Sumalee returned to the orbital station. I recommend you consult with her. The trail here has gone cold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060535" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll expect to hear from your people soon about our business partnership. Time is money--don't waste mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't forget our deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060536" id2="17" version="1065353216">I look forward to achieving our mutual prosperity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060538" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you tell the Republic how &quot;Chuckles&quot; got dead, omit my name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for handling things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060539" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Womp Gang has many rivals. It won't be difficult to redirect the blame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060541" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Womp Gang can wait. Trails aren't the only thing that interests me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060541" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] What about you and me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget about hurting my feelings--how do you flirt with another man while there's a dead guy in the room?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please excuse me, Captain, but I have a murder to cover up. Perhaps we'll meet again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pleasure working with you, Trawlie. Let's do it again someday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060546" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been a real pal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should you ever return to Bothawui, please let me know you're coming in advance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060549" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been fun, but I need to go look at people who don't remind me of herding banthas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1060549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Goodbye, hideous freak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bothawui will be greatly diminished by your departure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1060552" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell, Captain. May you find what seeks you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1067619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shh... she'll pay for what she did, I promise. This whole galaxy will be on its knees when we're done. Goodbye, Captain--for now.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
