<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>58</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/world/imperial/shock_doctrine/lord_malichose.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491036" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Organas continue to spew venom about House Ulgo. So much for their virtue of forgiveness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491037" id2="17" version="1065353216">My scouts tell me you have succeeded, and the Organa frequencies are jammed with angry rhetoric.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any reasonable voice, including the Jedi, is being drowned out in their hatred of House Ulgo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491041" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is too much to hope that they will come to blows, but this revulsion will serve us well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491042" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did what you wanted, but you don't sound pleased.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Satisfied?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491043" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is how I express elation. It is something my colleagues get used to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491045" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was repulsive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be comforted that any violation you feel is felt by the Organas and Jedi ten times over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491048" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I like to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your pride is deserved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491051" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will monitor the situation as it degenerates. If the fear and hatred last, we will add this to our roster of tactics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491053" id2="17" version="1065353216">The longer they forget about House Thul, the more time we have to maneuver. Then the endgame can begin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491055" id2="17" version="1065353216">Horrify them. Burn the atrocity into their brain so they report every detail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491058" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Lord Malichose. I was told you were coming and was given some background information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Collectively, you are powerful, but I require determination as much as combined firepower.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your exploits prove you are capable, but I require... more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491066" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Organas have sent spies and several Padawan Jedi here to scout the Ulgo's fortress. I need the Organas dispatched.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do the Ulgos work for them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are we defending Ulgos?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491068" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Ulgos, like the Organas, believe they can fight one another under the pretense of rules, which both nobly adhere to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491070" id2="17" version="1065353216">So put down some mines and check back in a week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this worth my time?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491071" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would be short-term progress. You must understand--Alderaanians, especially Organas, adhere to a code of conduct in war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491073" id2="17" version="1065353216">With pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quantity of casualties is secondary. You will assault the pride of the Alderaanians. They believe warfare can be conducted civilly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491078" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is why the Organas must be shocked into hating the Ulgos more than the Empire or House Thul. Disgust is our weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491080" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Ulgos will not provide a sufficient outrage, a sufficient atrocity, we--that is, you--must do it for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491081" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt they will cleave to their precious rules once their opponents do not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491081" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like where this is going.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly. Your assignment is to kill the Padawan Jedi and scouts of the Organas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491084" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fakery does not hold up well in the long run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491084" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt this will work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491085" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fakery, no. Visceral reaction is my plan's strength. You must kill Organa scouts and Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491087" id2="17" version="1065353216">How would I do that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491088" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need you to kill Organa scouts and whatever Padawan Jedi you can find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491092" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ultimate goal is for the Organas to exhaust themselves bringing war to the Ulgo's doorstep. Revulsion is the first step in this plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491093" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it serves us strategically, I will do this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491093" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can stomach it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491094" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you see the benefit. Now, we have concocted a kit of common implements carried by Ulgo troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491096" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will give you atrocities. In abundance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491096" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was born for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491097" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enthusiasm is good, but I do not suggest... improvisation. We have here a kit containing common implements Ulgo soldiers carry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491099" id2="17" version="1065353216">These items will give the act the... homemade authenticity needed to convince a skeptical observer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491101" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kill the Jedi. Kill the Organas. Use the tools provided and return here. It is not so difficult if you have the will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491105" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can you just stand there and ask me to commit war crimes?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491105" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is wrong. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491106" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would you rather I pace back and forth?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491110" id2="17" version="1065353216">These mountains crawl with Organas, and worse, Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491113" id2="17" version="1065353216">In seriousness, however, hesitation is normal. Once you have seen how House Thul needs us, I think you will reconsider.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491115" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then desecrate the remains. The Organas will find them and blame the bodies on the Ulgo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491116" id2="17" version="1065353216">There were notable successes, but I remain unclear on your tolerance for... psychological assignments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491117" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have ascended from the low-born based on merit, but I require... commitment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491119" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your specific deeds are classified to me, so I do not know the... moral nature of your assignments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491121" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are a professional, but most professionals have limits. What I propose may exceed them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764842" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no emotion, there is-- ahh! The Elysium! They're at the Elysium! The old meeting place...ahh!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764844" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Elysium is full of history...it's the old meeting place of the houses. The Padawans are there to study, not to-- ahh!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Padawans are protected by some of Organa's strongest troops...and a Jedi Master. You won't get away with this...ahh!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
