<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>60</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/open_worlds/class/jedi_knight/multi/captain_maddox.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry to trouble you, Master Jedi... but when it comes to Sith Lords, seems we're pretty useless on our own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088611" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's all right, Tefani. I'm a soldier, and this is how soldiers go--even semi-retired ones.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088612" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're going to make it, Captain. Just lie still and let Doctor Kantos help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088612" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not letting you die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know why Legius's men attacked you? What did they want?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me what happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088614" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have time for last words. I need to know where Darth Legius went.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088614" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're wasting time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088615" id2="17" version="1065353216">The man just told you he's dying, and all you care about is finding Legius?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088617" id2="17" version="1065353216">They took the planetary shield codes for the New Uphrades evacuation colony. Guess the civs here are lucky they missed the boat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every civilian we've saved is in that colony now. Legius wants to make another statement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legius wants attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is there a shield around the colony? And how did we end up with the codes?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088619" id2="17" version="1065353216">What shield codes?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088620" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Supreme Chancellor hears, she'll send the entire fleet to the colony. Legius won't get within fifty parsecs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088620" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's got no chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get this intel to Republic command. Maybe they can evacuate New Uphrades before Legius gets there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alert the authorities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088625" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are millions of innocent people on New Uphrades. Aren't you the least bit worried about them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Morale? Seriously?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legius is one Sith, with one army, and no support from the Empire. He can't destroy New Uphrades by himself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088626" id2="17" version="1065353216">You overestimate him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088627" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll contact the Supreme Chancellor's office. Single cruiser like yours can reach Legius a lot faster than the fleet, so say your goodbyes now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088630" id2="17" version="1065353216">You turned from war and chose a life of peace. I can't promise I'll never fight again--but I intend to try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088630" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll honor your memory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088631" id2="17" version="1065353216">There will always be men like Legius. If I don't stop them, who will?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088631" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not that simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legius has destroyed countless lives. Killing him won't be enough. Killing his men won't be enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088632" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire must pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088851" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imps had him cornered. He held them off for a while, but when the shock troops got in....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088853" id2="17" version="1065353216">His internal injuries are too severe. If the Imperials hadn't destroyed half my supplies....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088855" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have to answer, Captain. I can give you a sedative if you're in pain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never mind, Audra. If I have to die... I'm going to die useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088862" id2="17" version="1065353216">They came in hot. Perimeter guards were dead before they could sound the alarm. We got the civs behind forcefields just in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once the Imps were in, they went for the computers. Sliced past our security, uploaded something to Legius. Didn't see what, but I have an idea....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like what? &quot;I've lost my mind?&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088867" id2="17" version="1065353216">State-of-the-art protection for the Supreme Chancellor's pride and joy. We had the codes so we could send refugees there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088869" id2="17" version="1065353216">New Uphrades has plenty of defenses besides the shield. Legius will never get past them before a Republic fleet arrives.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1088871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Legius = lost Project Sever // Darth Legius = expects to die?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088873" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dark Council wants Legius dead anyway. Maybe he wants to go out with a bang.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088875" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dark Council's gonna kill him anyway, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088877" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dark Council wants Legius dead. He's got nothing to lose now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088879" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legius failed to recover Project Sever. His life is forfeit regardless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speculation: Legius has been condemned by the Dark Council. Self-termination may be a preferable alternative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088883" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would rather be deactivated by the Republic than the Dark Council, master. Perhaps Darth Legius had the same thought?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088885" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said the Jedi got Project Sever... if that's true, Legius is done for anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088887" id2="17" version="1065353216">If he's planning a suicide run... he could bombard the colony until he's out of torpedos, transfer life support to his ship's engines....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088888" id2="17" version="1065353216">The big picture's my job. Saving lives is theirs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even if he's willing to die trying?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088897" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's all you can do. All any of us can....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088898" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's your life, master Jedi. Not theirs....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088899" id2="17" version="1065353216">But where does it end? Where does it....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088901" id2="17" version="1065353216">The... body?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better get moving. Supreme Chancellor wants you in the air and on Legius's tail. Master Satele will be leading reinforcements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1097248" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll need us on New Uphrades if things go wrong. Let's get the body in cryo and the civilians to a safe location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1097252" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll move out with the fleet. When you find Legius, I hope he gets everything that's coming to him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099535" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's already got a head start. If Legius destroys New Uphrades, it would be the biggest blow to morale since the Sacking of Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099536" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi have such power. To waste it on more death... you're better than that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at all we've done together. Serving the Republic, doing your duty... doesn't have to mean war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't grow old fighting battles, like I did. After Legius is gone... let him be the last.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
