<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>6</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris_imp/heroic_weekly/mission_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173119" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lya Charrel has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Brell Sediment sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Lya Charrel may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173120" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intelligence Report No: 97-213. Clearance Level: 4.

The old Tarisian government lives. Approximately three centuries ago, the leaders froze themselves in carbonite within Transport Station 5.

Intercepted transmissions confirm the Republic's elite Ember Squad was dispatched to recover the frozen leaders. If revived, their knowledge will accelerate Taris's reconstruction by three thousand percent.

Darth Gravus orders immediate action. Stop Ember Squad's thawing mission and eliminate the frozen Tarisian leaders. Hazard fee payable on completion.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173121" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Bourom has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Sinking City sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, General Bourom may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173122" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Komo has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Republic Resettlement Zone sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Lord Komo may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177084" id2="17" version="1065353216">Praetor Nollus has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Tularan Marsh sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Praetor Nollus may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177085" id2="17" version="1065353216">From the desk of Darth Gravus: 

The Republic rats have fled underground. An entire battalion rallies in Gadon's Superhighway, a massive swoop track beneath your very feet.

The scum unite under Taren Vor, a Jedi commander descended from old Taris. He aims to build a subterranean supply network. If successful, the Republic will infest the planet for decades.

Stop this mockery of Taris's ruin, and your valor will be repaid. Crush the Republic's highway, bury their army and annihilate the Jedi leader.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
