<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>33</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/bronze/inside_man/watcher_eight.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719596" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be sure to report your excellent work to my superiors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent Veld was able to relay a message to me. Your assistance is appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719599" id2="17" version="1065353216">As are these code cylinders you gathered. Rest assured, we will find them most useful. Again, my thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still no communications from Agent Veld. Are you having difficulties?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good day, Cipher Nine--yes, I know your identity. You may call me Watcher Eight. I have a mission for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pardon me. Watcher Eight, Imperial Intelligence. Your rise with the Sith has been well documented. Might you have a moment to assist me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your reputation precedes you. Watcher Eight, Imperial Intelligence. I'm authorized to hire anyone I need, and I need the best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good day. Watcher Eight, Imperial Intelligence. I've heard of your successes. I need a team that's capable and discreet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent Veld, my top field operative, has failed to check in. Instead, I received some garbled distress signal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719614" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will not abandon Agent Veld. I need him found.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever prompted the distress signal, Veld could already have fallen victim to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="719615" id2="17" version="1065353216">He may be dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your expert opinion notwithstanding, he's survived worse missions without a scratch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knowing Agent Veld's task could be the key to finding him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="719618" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's his mission?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719619" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't risk exposing the details of a field agent's mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you should consider writing him off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="719621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Veld sounds useless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719622" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather not discard an excellent operative at the first sign of trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719624" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can give you Agent Veld's last known position, near the Republic's main landing field. But the rest would be up to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719625" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you know my designation, you know I can cope without backup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="719625" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not a problem, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Both Agent Veld and his mission are in good hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="719626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719627" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll ensure your agent is safe, and his mission completed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="719627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave it to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="719628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds dull, but all right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to hear it. His distress signal was sent from these coordinates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719631" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll send him an alert to watch for you, but it may not get through. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your Agent Veld will have to cope on his own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="719633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719634" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see. Perhaps someone else will be willing to rescue a man in need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="719636" id2="17" version="1065353216">No distractions, please, I have an important matter to consider.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
