<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>46</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/war_world/quesh/bronze/republic/venom_cleanup/jedi.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70792" id2="17" version="1065353216">The swamps of Quesh are teeming with unique and fascinating life-forms. I look forward to being able to study them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="70795" id2="17" version="1065353216">The tanks are destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="70796" id2="17" version="1065353216">I destroyed the tanks. But some of the nearby creatures were exposed to the toxins, and I had to kill them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70797" id2="17" version="1065353216">I grieve for their loss, but putting them out of their suffering was a mercy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70799" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will take many moons for the Empire's venom-processing operations to recover. Hopefully by then, we will have driven them from Quesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for all you've done.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70805" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Imperial processing facilities are not destroyed, the environmental damage will be irreparable.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well met, fellow Jedi. It reassures me to know there are others in our order who have taken an interest in this world.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70811" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well met, noble Captain. Always an honor to meet one so dedicated to defending the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well met, friend. Always an honor to meet those who have chosen to aid the Republic here on this world.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70815" id2="17" version="1065353216">My name is Goonawaro. I wonder if I could be so bold as to ask of you a favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="70816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi need to stick together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="70816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="70817" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would never turn my back on another member of the order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="70817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="70818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always happy to help the Jedi out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="70818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fire away.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70819" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your willingness is appreciated. I will get right to the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="70821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this the kind of favor that could get me killed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="70821" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Favor&quot; is pretty vague.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70822" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will not mislead you. There is an element of danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="70824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do you need my help?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70825" id2="17" version="1065353216">We Ithorians are not warriors. I came to study the impact of recent events on the unique ecosystem of Quesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="70827" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it isn't critical, I'm out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70828" id2="17" version="1065353216">What could be more important than preserving the ecosystem of an entire planet?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70830" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you are no doubt aware, both the Republic and Imperials are extracting Quesh venom from beneath the planet's surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70832" id2="17" version="1065353216">However, unlike the Republic, the Imperials are employing dangerous methods that are poisoning the world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="70833" id2="17" version="1065353216">How terrible.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their callous disregard for the natural order is an affront to all I believe in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="70836" id2="17" version="1065353216">This whole planet is one giant, toxic swamp. How could it get any worse?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="70836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quesh is already poisoned.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quesh sustains life. Plants and creatures have adapted to survive in this environment. But the Imperials are disrupting the natural balance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="70839" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are the Imperials doing that's so bad?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="70839" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of methods?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Instead of slowly siphoning Quesh venom from the ground, the Empire carves deep wounds in the earth and processes the reserves in great tanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70842" id2="17" version="1065353216">The tanks release noxious clouds into the environment. Eventually, their operations will kill all natural life on Quesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="70843" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we stop them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="70844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expect to get paid.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70845" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did not expect a Jedi to be so obsessed with material wealth. But I will pay you if necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="70847" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expect to get paid.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh. I see. Among my culture, such a brazenly mercenary attitude is rare. But I will pay you if necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70850" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use these explosives to destroy the tanks where the Imperials store their Quesh venom. This will cripple their production capabilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful. Detonating the explosives may cause clouds of concentrated toxins to be expunged from the tanks. Avoiding exposure would be wise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="70854" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70855" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand. I appreciate your time, and I apologize for bothering you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70859" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperial factories are poisoning this world.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
