<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>112</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/excavation/roth/republic/master_cedral_gend.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104671" id2="17" version="1065353216">The seeker droid is yours to keep. It may prove useful elsewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back. I'm prepping a rocket that will fire the Seeds of Rage into a nearby star. Rather excited about that, if I'm honest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you brought the devices? I expected to feel their presence. That much dark side energy is difficult to miss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104679" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't feel them because they're no longer a threat. They were just machines. Take them apart, and they aren't so bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104679" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've been neutralized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104680" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have difficulty believing technology that evil can be repaired like some malfunctioning droid. You should have consulted with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104682" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least the planets that were endangered by the Seeds are safe. We'll have to hope that technology never resurfaces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep the seeker droid--it may be needed again. Please excuse me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104685" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't want those things on my ship. I blasted them to bits in deep space.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104685" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] I destroyed the Seeds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104686" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd hoped to oversee their destruction personally, but I'm glad to know they're gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104688" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appear to have wasted my time on the rocket, but that's a small price to pay for the lives we've saved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104690" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was stopped on the way here by SIS. They had official clearance from the Supreme Chancellor to seize the devices. You didn't know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104690" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] The SIS took them away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104691" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? That's completely unacceptable! How did Saresh even know about the Seeds?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104693" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is deeply troubling. I've had concerns about the Supreme Chancellor's ambitions. Perhaps I was right to worry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104695" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for everything you've done. Please, keep the seeker droid. You may find it handy elsewhere. Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104701" id2="17" version="1065353216">Today marks a great victory for the Republic. Not only have you saved many lives, you've deprived our enemies of terrible weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104703" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could sense the dark side power in the Seeds even before you arrived. I'm launching those devices into a nearby star.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104704" id2="17" version="1065353216">The sooner we're rid of these things forever, the easier I'll breathe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104705" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's why I can't rest until every last bit of Sith technology has been eradicated forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104707" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Seeds were dangerous enough in the ground. How do we know it's safe to &quot;bury&quot; them in a star?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure that's wise?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104708" id2="17" version="1065353216">I already thought of that. Even if the Seeds miraculously survive being incinerated, no one will ever get close enough to suffer their effects.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104710" id2="17" version="1065353216">You shouldn't destroy the Seeds without taking one apart and understanding how it works. You never know when that knowledge might come in handy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104710" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to study them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104711" id2="17" version="1065353216">I respectfully disagree. The fact that the Emperor never deployed these weapons himself tells me everything I need to know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104713" id2="17" version="1065353216">My work has taken me many places in this galaxy, and I've discovered a fair number of exotic items. I share them whenever possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104715" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please accept this gift--and keep the seeker droid, too. I hope you'll find them useful. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104723" id2="17" version="1065353216">You found one of the Seeds! Take care handling it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104724" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Seed! Thank the Force you found it in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104725" id2="17" version="1065353216">A planetary population saved, thanks to you. Get that Seed offworld quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Outstanding! That's one less Seed to worry about. Keep up the hunt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done! You've saved untold lives from that awful device. Stand by... receiving a transmission... blast!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104729" id2="17" version="1065353216">My spy reports the Dread Masters are attacking the Arcanum facility to steal everything there! The only good news is, we have Arcanum's coordinates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104731" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't let our enemies escape with the evil technology stored there. Fly to the Arcanum facility and put an end to this madness!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104736" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're entering the Arcanum facility. There's no telling what evil is waiting for you. Be cautious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104737" id2="17" version="1065353216">There! That Sith up ahead! My spy reports he leads the Dread Masters' forces!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104738" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the last of the enemy forces. We've won, but my spy reports the Imperial Ninth Fleet is headed to Arcanum. Best be leaving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104740" id2="17" version="1065353216">Besides, we have new leads on other planets where the Seeds of Rage are buried. I'm transmitting you fresh coordinates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep up the search--those worlds are in terrible danger. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done! The Seeds are growing in power the longer they operate. We must find the others quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104748" id2="17" version="1065353216">You found it! We may not be able to undo the Seed's damage, but you've ensured an end to the suffering. Continue the search.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent! You've gathered more Seeds than I dared hope we'd find, but we haven't uncovered them all yet. Keep hunting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104750" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've saved another world and uprooted another Seed. The Force is with us, but this isn't over yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104751" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done it again! I knew I could count on you to find these terrible machines. Now press on--there's no time to lose!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104752" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect! That's the last Seed we had coordinates for, but I think we know where the rest of them are being kept.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104754" id2="17" version="1065353216">My spy reports the Imperial traitor has just revealed the location where the Dread Masters' thieves coordinated their raid on Arcanum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104756" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sending you the coordinates. Bring these servants of evil to justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104761" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've entered a den of very powerful thieves. Be ready for anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104762" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish we'd been able to take one of them alive. Their leader must have escaped with any remaining Seeds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104764" id2="17" version="1065353216">My spy reports the Empire's traitor just perished during interrogation. We're at a literal dead end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Search the databanks there for any leads. It's up to you to end this. May the Force be with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104771" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's it--you've recovered all the Seeds! Return to me, and we'll deal with those devices once and for all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Head to the coordinates I've provided and use that seeker droid until you've located all of the Seeds. I'll remain in contact via transmissions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just in time. The threat is escalating faster than I feared. I've spent my life rooting out dark side corruption, but this is the most insidious form I've yet encountered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104777" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you heard of a facility code-named &quot;Arcanum&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104778" id2="17" version="1065353216">The name isn't familiar.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104778" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, I haven't heard of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider yourself fortunate. It is a place of powerful evil.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104781" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever it is, I doubt it belongs to the Republic. Sounds right up the Sith Empire's alley, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104781" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it an enemy stronghold?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your instincts serve you well. Good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104784" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not here for a lecture on obscure galactic lore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get to the blasted point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104785" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not offering one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arcanum is a vast repository of dark side technology created for the Emperor. Presently, it's controlled by a member of the Dark Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104789" id2="17" version="1065353216">My spy in Imperial space reports that the Dread Masters' forces have raided Arcanum and stolen Sith devices called &quot;the Seeds of Rage&quot;.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104790" id2="17" version="1065353216">Judging by their name alone, I'm guessing these things were better off locked away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104790" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't sound good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104791" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're fortunate the Sith have a weakness for melodramatic titles.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104793" id2="17" version="1065353216">You placed someone in the Empire with that much access to enemy secrets? Impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104793" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a spy on the inside?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104794" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't common knowledge, but Imperial Intelligence is all but destroyed. The Republic has begun to exploit this opportunity with great success.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104796" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did these people get inside a Sith stronghold, much less escape with anything?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who were these forces?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104797" id2="17" version="1065353216">They recruited one of Arcanum's trusted guardians. By the time their theft was discovered, they were already halfway across the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104799" id2="17" version="1065353216">According to my spy, the Seeds of Rage are devices powered by Sith alchemy. The machines stimulate madness and violent impulses in living beings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104801" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters have secretly buried the Seeds of Rage across the galaxy to destroy entire populations. We must find and neutralize these devices.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104802" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Sith believed the Seeds were dangerous enough to be kept locked up, we should be worried.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104802" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104803" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire is as desperate to recover the Seeds as we are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104805" id2="17" version="1065353216">If these things have been buried in secret, I doubt the Dread Masters left us a handy map to follow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find them with what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed not--but the Empire is aiding our search without realizing it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104808" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're machines buried in the ground. How much damage can they do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104808" id2="17" version="1065353216">How bad can they be?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104809" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Seeds were locked away for good reason. Unless we act, entire worlds will be thrown into chaos by dark side power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104811" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arcanum's caretaker, Darth Acina, captured one of the thieves. As her interrogators discover the burial sites, my spy will intercept that information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once we have a general location, you'll have to use one of my seeker droids to find and extract the Seeds. The dig sites will almost certainly be extremely hazardous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104814" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have experience dealing with hazards. Remind me to tell you about Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104814" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi is always prepared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your confrontation with the Emperor is a tale I most definitely wish to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uncovering knowledge in dangerous places is a hobby of mine, Master Gend. I'll manage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104817" id2="17" version="1065353216">It wouldn't be the first time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104818" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you'll succeed, Barsen'thor. That's why I wanted you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104820" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad doesn't do milk runs. We'll uproot the Dread Masters' little gardening project and leave scorched ground behind us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104820" id2="17" version="1065353216">My team will be ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104821" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's probably for the best, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, I will almost certainly be extremely well-armed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104823" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can handle any hazard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Proving once again you're the right Captain for this mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104826" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are seeker droids? How do they work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain seeker droids to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104827" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're Class Five units programmed for excavation. Once activated, seekers tunnel beneath ground level and return with whatever they find. Hopefully, those infernal Seeds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104829" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're planning to stay here drinking caf while I risk my life performing manual labor, guess again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104829" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd better be coming along!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104830" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd like nothing more than to handle this myself--but this is the only secure location to receive messages from my spy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104832" id2="17" version="1065353216">My spy intercepted coordinates that we believe are Seed burial sites. The Empire is recruiting retrieval teams of its own. Let's beat them there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take the seeker droid. I'll transmit updates as we learn other coordinates. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello there.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
