<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>84</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/star_fortress/theron_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176466" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're in a service duct over one of the main observation towers. Should find a lift system in there that'll get you deeper inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176468" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I'm in. Now, what happens when I pull out this line of code...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep me plugged in for a few, I'll get this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176470" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've got a rotating cypher algorithm. Miot, give me a hand here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176471" id2="17" version="1065353216">See if we can't shut this thing up once and for all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176474" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know the drill: get to the system data center and take EPHEMERIS out. We'll be in touch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got a ways to go to reach the EPHEMERIS control center. Better get to it. We're here and listening.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Setting a course for Alderaan. You think I'm stuffy, Miot, you're in for a treat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Navicom locked on Belsavis. Planetful of convicted psycho killers, here we come.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176491" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't exactly have clearance on Nar Shaddaa anymore, but... we'll make it work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Plotting a course to Tatooine. I do not like Tatooine, but I do like saying Tatooine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good call. We don't want the Eternal Empire gaining influence over anyone on Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Miot, be sure you got your parka. We're going to Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176495" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, we're going after that sun reactor. I'm with Miot, ready to help in any way we can. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great, you're in. Once you set that reactor to blow, we'll need you to hightail it out of there before we're all, you know--incinerated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176500" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coming out of hyperspace. Miot, stealth maneuver thirty-six. Get us in nice and close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176501" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, Commander, we're here. Get ready to be dropped off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176502" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eyes on the target. Ready for infiltration when you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Star Fortress in sight. Let's get you inside so you can knock them down a peg.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure what's at the heart of this thing. Keep your guard up. I'll be in touch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like you found a hub of activity. Stay on your toes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Getting some big power readings from the levels below you. Should look into it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Must be where all those Skytroopers are coming from. Try not to wake anything up down there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope they don't start mass-producing those things. Great work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Miot says the power source is just a bit below you. Couple levels, maybe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, you're in power central now. We need to do something about EPHEMERIS. See if you can patch me into its data cores.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice work, Commander. Now we'll bypass that shield and--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't get at the shield. Something remote, have to rethink this. Miot, get a lift open!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shield's down, reactor's dead ahead. Get in there and do what you do best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Made it this far, just a bit more to go. Few more explosions and we'll have liberated a world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be your best friend if you can shut that EPHEMERIS up for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176641" id2="17" version="1065353216">EPHEMERIS data cores right ahead, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176646" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great job, Commander! Now move before that thing blows!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice takedown! Get out of there so we can go somewhere less explode-y!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176648" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll congratulate you soon as we're outside the blast radius. Hope that works for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hopefully, they'll sleep easier tonight planetside. Miot, get ready to haul out of here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176651" id2="17" version="1065353216">That ought to set them back a good while. Nicely done. Let's blaze a trail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176658" id2="17" version="1065353216">We hurt them and they know it. More to be done, we'll figure it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176659" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't over yet. We'll finish it. But right now it's time to get out of here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admiral Aygo, you sly Bothan....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Military codebreaker's coming in handy....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176673" id2="17" version="1065353216">That Hylo Visz knows a brilliant slicer or two....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trying a little something from the seedier side of the HoloNet....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Sana-rae....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Slicing codes from a Force user. Multi-talented....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176681" id2="17" version="1065353216">With a tip of the hat to Doctor Oggurobb....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176682" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see what our resident Hutt concocted for us....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176718" id2="17" version="1065353216">There you are--beating heart of the whole station. Hope you brought some kind of sun shade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176720" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can get around that Exarch we can deal with the stabilizers. After that, be ready to run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Readings coming out of there are pretty intense. Don't get fried.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176726" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I know you and labs, could be you're about to come across some horribly dangerous experiment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176728" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm seeing here the Eternal Empire's placing locals into forced conscription. Not much you can do I guess, thought you should know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176733" id2="17" version="1065353216">Been getting a look at their armament logs. I know world governments that can't match what they've got in these things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176734" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like their resource harvesting includes the local wildlife. Probably arena fodder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176735" id2="17" version="1065353216">More of those blasted Skytrooper pods. Arcann loves those things, doesn't he?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander, you're breaking up! Losing contact!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176739" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lost you for a minute there, glad you were just unconscious. Looks like they've got you in detention. Going to have to get creative to break out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176743" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're back! Great! Not that I was panicking. Quiet, Miot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good going, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every little bit helps....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice find. Thinking about keeping it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176747" id2="17" version="1065353216">You showed them!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176748" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander--eyes open!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Incoming on your position!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176750" id2="17" version="1065353216">Try not to blow yourself up, too, okay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, if you wanted a sense of the scale of this place... there you go....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176752" id2="17" version="1065353216">Huh. Bet the Alliance can make use of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176753" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was close. That was maybe too close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think I know someone on Odessen who could use that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176755" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, they didn't see that one coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Power spike near your location!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176758" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176759" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176760" id2="17" version="1065353216">There we go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Connection secured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176764" id2="17" version="1065353216">No good. Bet Aygo knows some people....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Strange configuration. Maybe Oggurobb can make something of it....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seen a cipher like this before on the black market....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Out of ideas here. Could use one of Sana-rae's visions about now....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast it all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177125" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut out. No go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177126" id2="17" version="1065353216">I swear I'm getting worse at this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177134" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I'm reading this right, EPHEMERIS beamed its core computing into one of those units. Interesting move--little creepy, but interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Might give us a tactical advantage, actually. Taking it out could disrupt system protocols for a bit.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
