<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>33</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/bronze/republic/tech_diagrams/corporal_fabel.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195891" id2="17" version="1065353216">SIS is talking about building our own Arc Emitter--give the White Maw a taste of their own medicine.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow! I heard the blast from here. That Arc Emitter must've gone up like a rocket!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks. We found some Anomid stuff while we were investigating 'em; take anything that catches your eye.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember: Find a diagnostic pad, calibrate it at a control point, then take the pad to the Arc Emitter. Else this won't work.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you believe this? My lieutenant said those White Maw pirates were dumber than concussed mynocks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195899" id2="17" version="1065353216">But, seems the pirates hired some Anomid tech geniuses to do their thinking for them. If this report's right, we're in a world of trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="195900" id2="17" version="1065353216">There must be plenty of salvaged ordnance and starship cannons for them to work with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="195900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are they making weapons?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Weapons. Wish it was that simple, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="195903" id2="17" version="1065353216">The White Maw are dangerous enough, without superior technology at their command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="195903" id2="17" version="1065353216">This does sound worrying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="195904" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pirates are nothing if not adaptable, Corporal. Keep that in mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="195904" id2="17" version="1065353216">You underestimated the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195905" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know, sir, but no one saw this coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="195907" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'd be easy enough to stop those techs; just make them a higher offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="195907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't the Republic hire them?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195908" id2="17" version="1065353216">I dunno. It's like they see this as a challenge, not a job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="195910" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not that familiar with that species.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="195910" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are Anomids?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195911" id2="17" version="1065353216">They wear these weird masks because they can't talk. Kind of stuck-up, but their tech is amazing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="195913" id2="17" version="1065353216">If a few engineers can tip the balance, the Republic's worse off than I thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="195913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why? They're just technicians.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195914" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Anomids are building something called the Arc Emitter. Destroys any equipment that runs off a generator--they can cut off everyone's heat and power just like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195916" id2="17" version="1065353216">But, they've only got lousy White Maw equipment to work with. Might be a way to trick that Arc Emitter, if you can get close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="195917" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count me in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="195918" id2="17" version="1065353216">The White Maw's probably protecting the Arc Emitter, and anyone working on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="195918" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd need to be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195919" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best plan would be making that emitter target itself. Boom! No salvage left for the White Maw.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195921" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Anomids working the Arc Emitter use these diagnostic pads, to set its targeting right.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get hold of one, calibrate it at a control point, and jam it into the emitter. Wonders of technology will do the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="195925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not me. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195926" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, but if your heaters suddenly go dead, you'll know who was behind it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="195928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stupid White Maw, making my life difficult....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
