<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>45</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/bronze/imperial/black_boxes_white_ice/yunaali.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197213" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Victor Squadron pilots were born for the cockpit. Looking over their flight data... it's inspiring.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197215" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have the flight recorders from Victor Squadron.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197216" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, good. Hope the Republic didn't give you too much trouble. They can be possessive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197218" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have my people start going over the data immediately. We'll pass on our findings as soon as we find something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looking forward to getting a peek at those flight recorders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197223" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Sith? My, these frozen wastes produce such... interesting guests. But please, stay awhile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197225" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. You don't have the cut of an EDF officer. Joined the Imperials, then?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197227" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must be freezing. Please, stay awhile. Warm yourself up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197229" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must be cold, coming all this way. Stay awhile, I insist. Warm yourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197231" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Captain Yunaali, Hammer Squadron. Call sign's &quot;Blue Mother.&quot; Organizing a joint training op for our pilots.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197233" id2="17" version="1065353216">Been digging through these old hulls for research material. Slow going, but I want our people learning from the best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197234" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even if our people train together, don't delude yourself into thinking we're equals, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197234" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember who's in charge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197235" id2="17" version="1065353216">How could I forget, my lord?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197237" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can learn much from the dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197237" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like your methods.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or their ships.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197240" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you should spend less time scrounging and more time flying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197240" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quit rifling through junk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197241" id2="17" version="1065353216">Running combat maneuvers will only take you so far. We need to understand how the enemy thinks, how they fly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197243" id2="17" version="1065353216">No shortage of abandoned spacecraft on Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197243" id2="17" version="1065353216">You picked a good spot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197244" id2="17" version="1065353216">Precisely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197246" id2="17" version="1065353216">Smart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Joint training? Sounds risky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, there'll be the usual swaggering and chest-thumping, but we all know who the common enemy is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197250" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm particularly interested in Victor Squadron. Finest pilots the Republic ever produced. Nearly took half the Imperial armada down with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197252" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our scouts have located what's left of their ships. Fighters are mostly scrap, but some of the internal components are still intact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197253" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised the cold didn't ruin everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197253" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not all frozen?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197254" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thing we're only after the flight recorders. Those things are built to withstand anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197256" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think there's something of value in those ships?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197256" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of components?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197257" id2="17" version="1065353216">Information. It's likely the ships' flight recorders are functional.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197259" id2="17" version="1065353216">Internal components? Boring.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197260" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most of the parts are useless or boring, yes. But the flight recorders--those are the real prize.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those recorders contain a detailed log of Victor Squadron's missions. Analyzing that data could give us valuable insight into the Republic's flight tactics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, the Republic has already mobilized to recover the flight recorders. Someone needs to beat them to the punch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197265" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't you do it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197267" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not authorized to engage the Republic directly. If there's any blood to be spilt, it can't be on Chiss hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197269" id2="17" version="1065353216">The crash site isn't far. Recon has confirmed a Republic presence already in the area, so watch your tail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't be me. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197272" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you'll reconsider. We may not get a chance like this again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Marvelous planet, this. A frozen monument to one of the greatest space battles ever.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
