<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>11</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/bonus_series/imperial/mission_terminal_new.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185457" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

Since we know the Republic is taking action against former Regulator forces on the planet, we have an opportunity to provide them with &quot;proof&quot; that the Empire is not mining isotope-5. 

Obtain clean environmental samples from Frinn Mesa and pair them with a shipping manifest claiming that these samples were from the drilling mesa, and intended to be tested for contaminants. Leave the package at a Regulator camp for Republic forces to discover.

END MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185458" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

The Empire's experiment leading to Makeb's present state remains in full evidence at the abandoned mining site. 

To lessen the chance of anyone uncovering the true extent of our involvement here, rig the catwalks so that the first time anyone attempts to explore the mine shaft will also be the last time. 

The explosives stored at the site should provide ample incentive to stay away.

END MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185459" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

It appears that the Hutt Embassy's archives computer is still connected to the Hutt Cartel's offworld network. A virus uploaded into the computer could seriously cripple the Republic's new allies--but the Embassy is being kept under lockdown by abandoned mercenary forces. 

To gain entry, you will need to either sow chaos somehow or find an access card. If you choose the former route, be sure to use mercenary ordinance so that our involvement remains hidden.

END MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185460" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

It is in the Empire's interests to frame the mercenaries remaining on Makeb for our isotope-5 mining operations. 

Find a way to dose mercenaries at the Hutt Strongholds with trace elements indicative of the mining of isotope-5. Be sure to take their ID tags, as you will use that information to add them to a database of known smugglers.

END MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185461" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

One of our scouts has spotted an opportunity: former Regulators occupying a communications tower on Aboro Mesa are in a prime location to shell the nearby artillery bunker of another group of mercenaries. 

Use one of the Regulators' hovertanks to fire on the bunker, as it will foment hostilities between these groups, saving us the trouble of dealing with them ourselves.

END MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185464" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

Some residents of Talaos City have refused to leave their homes, even when given the opportunity to evacuate by the Republic's Protectors. We need to convince these people it's truly time to go. 

Pick up some &quot;thumpers&quot;, baradium charges and ion wave charges. By simulating a powerful groundquake and power outage in concert, we ought to scare those residents right out of the city--and, hopefully, off the planet.

END MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185465" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

Before they fled the planet, Republic operatives temporarily slowed the pace of Makeb's destruction by powering down the Cartel mining mesa's drills. 

If we were to reactivate those drills in a particular configuration, it would create a dissonance wave that we can use to convince the forces still on Makeb that its destruction is once again imminent.

END MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185466" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

A group of former Regulators has buried caches of isotope-5 in the caverns surrounding Stronghold One. Their intention is to smuggle the energy source offworld, which we most certainly cannot allow. 

Recover the isotope-5 from the Volcanic Mesa--and discourage any future smuggling for good measure. After you've finished, prepare the isotope-5 for our transport to pick up.

END MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185467" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

An Imperial scouting party sent to investigate the presence of isotope-5 powered prototype droids at the Tarlam settlement has not returned. We would send more forces to investigate, but many of the landing pads are shielded against invasion. 

Install remote shield disruptors at the landing pads; then clear a path to the last known location of our missing soldiers.

END MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185469" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

Our scientists have determined that a sizeable isotope-5 deposit exists beneath the Westwater settlements. If we're to drill there, we'll have to evacuate the area without signaling our intentions. 

If you were to induce a groundquake, it would convince any stragglers that their homes are no longer safe. You'll also need to contend with any former Regulators still lording over the settlements.

END MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1186867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mission terminals located at shuttle pads across the planet will provide various missions you can undertake to aid in Imperial Objectives.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
