<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>26</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/bonus_series/imperial/undermoff_bensen.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent work. Better than I would've done, I have no doubt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most of the mercs have been recalled to the volcanic base. Our forces can deal with the remainder so you won't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do away with some of those mercenaries and we'll have room for our forces to land.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103705" id2="17" version="1065353216">A whole bunch of Jedi got called over to the Archives. They're about to find everything you planted there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103708" id2="17" version="1065353216">That data you planted at Telemur has got the civilians spooked. They think the mercs will flatten another mesa. We'll need to coax them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103709" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're going to coax those civilians out, you'll have to thin the mercenary herd first. Not that you'll mind, I'm sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103712" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect. These mercenaries are doing exactly what we framed them for at the Hutt stronghold!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103714" id2="17" version="1065353216">Access a terminal and patch it into the network. It'll leave a clear trail, sell our deception all the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103718" id2="17" version="1065353216">That dissonance wave you made at the mesa drill is really going to sell these thumpers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103719" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to really sell the danger from the thumpers. Place some charges in the nearby gorge--that ought to do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mercs are being recalled to the Fingers mesas. You're all clear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103723" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm intercepting chatter. Heavy merc activity at the next platform.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103725" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mercs have control of the platform. You'll have to get the blasting caps from them to fire the drill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103728" id2="17" version="1065353216">It appears the mercs are looking for sources of isotope-5 to plunder for themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103730" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad for them you destroyed that abandoned mining drill. Good on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103731" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll need to wipe any record of that abandoned drill platform or they might get wise to our operations here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103735" id2="17" version="1065353216">The records you planted at Frinn Mesa should now be here as well. Let's make sure they've propagated through the network.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Brilliant. Simply brilliant. It's truly an honor to be working with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103739" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sewed that one right up. Fabulous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103740" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you do it? Fantastic. Really.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Took care of that, didn't you? Great work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that was impressive. You make it look so easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103792" id2="17" version="1065353216">Again--brilliant. We are so close now. Just one final task. Bit of a doozy, but I know you'll manage. Updated coordinates for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect! That was perfect. We're not quite out of the woods yet, however. Got a few more tasks, if you please.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bang-up job! But, listen--now the mercs are trying to get their paws on some isotope-5. Can't allow that. Sending coordinates now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104862" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's it. That's the lot of it! Oh, good show. You can come on back up now--at your leisure, of course.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
