<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>71</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/world/imperial/gearing_up/captain_habbaz.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553455" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's talk that some of the Rattataki are wanting to join us, and the rest are giving us a wide berth. Well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553457" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's done--the machines, the Rattataki leadership, all of it. I took care of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553458" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. I knew you were the perfect person for the job. I should have sent a holo crew to record it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553460" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Rattataki will give us a wide berth after your little demonstration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553461" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't had a fight like that in a while. Maybe I should pay Rattatak a visit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553461" id2="17" version="1065353216">The attack went perfectly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, of course. Thank you for your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553463" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those savages are still trying to figure out what happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553463" id2="17" version="1065353216">The attack went perfectly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553464" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm saddened that I couldn't watch it personally. Thank you for you help, you're an inspiration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone in my place would have done the same thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553465" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did what had to be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553466" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps, but without your flair. In the future, you should take more pride in your work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553467" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm done with the Rattataki.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. Thank you for helping us this time; because of you, we'll be able to handle it ourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553470" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're just resupplying--as long as the Rattataki have the machinery to create weapons, they remain a threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553471" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're only half-done. The leaders will just repair the factory if you don't kill them. We must break them utterly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553472" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Republic unit was destroyed as well, sir. No survivors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553474" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was hoping they'd wipe each other out. Notify me if you hear anything else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Operative Bator tells me you've done pretty well against the Rattataki before; well, they're back, and this time they've gone too far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent, I don't have to look for you. The local Rattataki--the former prisoners, not you--need to be taught a lesson.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad you're here. The Rattataki--the wildest alien prisoners in the Republic's little zoo--have finally overstepped their bounds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553482" id2="17" version="1065353216">The savages have claimed the planet for themselves, call it New Rattatak. They say they'll kill everyone, Republic and Empire alike.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553483" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're no match for Imperial troops. They can't hold out for long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hardly a serious threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553484" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've taken a factory and started making weapons--what they lack in skill they make up for in initiative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553486" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is why they don't take prisoners on Rattatak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553486" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's my species, all right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553487" id2="17" version="1065353216">These aren't normal Rattataki--whatever happened here turned them into psychotics, and now they've captured a weapons factory to arm themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone willing to kill Republic troops can't be all bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553489" id2="17" version="1065353216">They could be a valuable ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553490" id2="17" version="1065353216">They aren't looking to negotiate; they're looking to commit genocide. They've taken a factory and are arming themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553492" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd think they'd have learned their lesson by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553492" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're still around?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553493" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've learned, all right--learned they need weapons. They've taken a factory and started arming themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553495" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I care why?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553496" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're a threat to everyone on Belsavis. They've converted a factory, and they're using it to make weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right now, they're content to slaughter the Republic, but once they've stockpiled enough armaments we'll be next on their dance card.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553499" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know how they think. I'll take care of this situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553499" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take care of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553500" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're all yours, but don't confuse your loyalties--these savages only want more bloodshed. You'll find their factory on the upper grounds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553502" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Rattataki need to be put in their place--I'll take care of them myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553502" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see to this personally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553503" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm certain it will be terrible to behold. You can find their factory in the upper grounds of the compound.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553505" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are they arming themselves with?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553505" id2="17" version="1065353216">About these armaments....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553506" id2="17" version="1065353216">Crude blades mostly, but they scavenge weapons off their victims, too. They're masters of ambush--they don't fear us or the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553508" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is why you sought me out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553509" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need someone who can deal with them in terms they understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553511" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Rattataki only respect strength and ferocity; areas in which I understand you excel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553513" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Rattataki feel safe, feel confident. They need to learn that the Empire can reach anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553515" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Rattataki think their leadership is untouchable, that nothing can stop them. They need to be proven wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553517" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need someone to kill their leadership, wreck their little factory and put those aliens in their place. I respectfully request your assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553518" id2="17" version="1065353216">They will regret their arrogance. Leave this to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553518" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be my pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their weapons will not defend them from my wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553519" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be my pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553520" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the same tricks they know; they won't be a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553520" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle it myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553521" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do whatever you want if the payoff's high enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553521" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be my pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553522" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't underestimate the Empire ever again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553522" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be my pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553523" id2="17" version="1065353216">I look forward to seeing your methods in action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553525" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it, but I'll need a squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553525" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll need troop support.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Command has ordered against a frontal assault--the Rattataki can resist that too easily. You'll have to go alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553528" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll need to take out both the leaders and the machines in the factory--there can be no chance of them rebuilding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go yourself. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, it was foolish of me to interrupt you. I simply thought you might enjoy the pleasure of handling it yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553533" id2="17" version="1065353216">The prisoners are taking out their vengeance on the Republic. The mynocks are coming home to roost, and we get front row seats.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
