<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>51</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/world/republic/containment/general_skylast_holo.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on back. I want to thank you in person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706844" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recon droids are still picking up Esh-kha activity. Get down there and stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706849" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made it. Good. Now listen up--got a possible lead on that &quot;World Razer.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Skylast here. Got another crisis brewing in your neck of the woods. Top priority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello? This thing still work? This is General Skylast, Republic Infantry. Got a crisis brewing in your sector that requires your immediate attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706857" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recon droids picked up a large contingent of Esh-kha headed for the prison bowels. Elite soldiery, very dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Led by none other than the Esh-kha's patriarch, Gore Claw. If that maniac's involved, it's a sure bet they're up to something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706860" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think this has something to do with the World Razer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doubt it's a coincidence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't think of anything else that would rally the Esh-kha like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Must be something important down there. Question is, what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever it is, must be big.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Couldn't say. Still plenty of Esh-kha sealed away in the lower vaults--other nasties, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you've run into this Gore Claw before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706866" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706867" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's killed dozens of my men. Wants nothing more than to lead the Esh-kha on a galaxy-conquering spree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Call me when you've got something more concrete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706869" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're just speculating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706870" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's just a hunch, but a man can either trust his gut or get plugged in it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706872" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Esh-kha are gonna need one heck of a trump card if they want off this rock. My money's on the World Razer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706874" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've intercepted a few Esh-kha transmissions. Keep hearing references to something called a &quot;World Razer.&quot; Whatever it is, they're trying to awaken it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dug up some records on the thing. Very apocalyptic. Saw phrases like &quot;destroyer of planets&quot; and &quot;eater of stars&quot; more often than I'd like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706877" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to keep that thing as far away from the Republic as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706877" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't let it escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706878" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there's one thing Belsavis is good for, it's keeping the galaxy's scum out of the Republic's hair.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hard to believe a creature of such destructive power could exist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706880" id2="17" version="1065353216">A dangerous find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seen a lot of weird things in my time, but a planet-eating monster takes the cake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706883" id2="17" version="1065353216">A target that big calls for some serious ordnance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706883" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not equipped for that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706884" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you want me to stop it with my... blaster?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706884" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll need a bigger gun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706885" id2="17" version="1065353216">The entire Republic fleet may not have the firepower to take that thing down. That's why we keep it here, imprisoned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706887" id2="17" version="1065353216">What could the Esh-kha possibly gain by releasing something like that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706887" id2="17" version="1065353216">So why free it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706888" id2="17" version="1065353216">They have two things on their minds: escape and genocide. Seems the World Razer will facilitate both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't suppose you've found anything on how we destroy this thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me how to kill it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing substantial yet. I suspect killing it is out of the question, but we may have other options.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Overheard some Esh-kha comm chatter... something about disabling a &quot;failsafe.&quot; Could be our ticket to stopping all this nonsense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706895" id2="17" version="1065353216">The transmission came from a nearby cave. Lots of Esh-kha assembling there. Going to need you down there to see what this failsafe is all about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever the Esh-kha are up to, I'll put a stop to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706896" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see this through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706897" id2="17" version="1065353216">What am I supposed to do once I get there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706898" id2="17" version="1065353216">See this through to the end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706900" id2="17" version="1065353216">This mission will take you deeper into Belsavis than anyone's gone. It's a dangerous world down there, but the Republic--heck, maybe the galaxy--is counting on you. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely not. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706910" id2="17" version="1065353216">That World Razer could wake any second.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="763658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not much of a choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="763659" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, if I must.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
