<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>30</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/class/jedi_knight/accellerite_console.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469239" id2="17" version="1065353216">General, the chemical plant is ours. The Sith never finished their bomb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469240" id2="17" version="1065353216">After all our time together, I never expected anything less.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469242" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your Jedi army sent the Empire packing. Every weapon factory in the sector is now ours, and we're turning those munitions against the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469244" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even better, there were no casualties among your people. It's a rock-solid victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469245" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad my people are safe. I know this must have been hard on them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469245" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's wonderful news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469246" id2="17" version="1065353216">They looked pretty green when they first arrived, but they're gaining confidence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469248" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish your Jedi army was so successful. They took back Thrakus's corporate headquarters, but the enemy looted all her weapon factories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469250" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire is now better armed, plus you lost a full Jedi squad on this mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469251" id2="17" version="1065353216">The man directing our enemy is still at large.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469251" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to find Master Braga.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469252" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people will root out Master Braga's hiding place. We just need more time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469254" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expected we'd lose people, but not so quickly. What happened?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469254" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did they die?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469255" id2="17" version="1065353216">From what I hear, that headquarters was a maze. Your Jedi split up and wandered into an ambush.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469257" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our goal was to kick the Empire out of Labor Valley completely. Can you do it or not, General?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469257" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we control this sector?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469258" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the head start your Jedi gave us? Absolutely. Don't expect overnight results, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469260" id2="17" version="1065353216">Considering the firepower the Empire escaped those factories with... I don't know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic forces have just engaged the Empire in the Axial Park sector. The fighting is heavy, and SIS reports plenty of Sith activity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe we'll find your missing Jedi there. Worth a shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, we know Master Braga isn't here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tol Braga surely has a hand in that battle. We should go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Large battles require strong leaders. There's a good chance your target's there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469274" id2="17" version="1065353216">I already have people in Axial Park at these coordinates. I'll alert the other Jedi to meet you there. Var Suthra out....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691715" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations. You saved all my weapon factories, at the expense of my company's assets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691717" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire stole all our precious resources. My company lost billions to those scum. Farewell, Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your forces performed splendidly. They drove the Empire from my headquarters before it could loot any precious resources.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691721" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trust you'll find my gratitude as generous as promised. Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="935755" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Braga = hiding in Axial Park? // Jedi + T7 = find him</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
