<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>68</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/class/jedi_knight/captain_rikdine.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555304" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Var Suthra's camp is in the Labor Valley sector. Good luck, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555308" id2="17" version="1065353216">I broke the bottleneck trapping our forces here. We have access to the Labor Valley region.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555309" id2="17" version="1065353216">The all-clear just came in moments ago. We're already establishing beachheads all over that sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555311" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we don't break the Empire's hold on this sector, our offensive will be over before it's begun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555312" id2="17" version="1065353216">All Jedi reinforcements are present and accounted for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reports say you broke the Imperial blockade. We're establishing beachheads all over the Labor Valley sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555318" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Var Suthra is requesting you on a priority channel. Patching him through now....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, my old friend. I understand you're supreme commander of the Jedi forces here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555321" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see you're back in the thick of things. What can I do for you, sir?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="555321" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to see you, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555322" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a Jedi Master helping the Empire destroy Corellia. I need to find him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="555322" id2="17" version="1065353216">My mission is critical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele has asked me to assist your mission however I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555325" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why, were you hoping to be in charge?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="555325" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that a problem for you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commanding regular troops is hard enough. Wouldn't dream of ordering Jedi around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele has informed me you're looking for a Jedi Master helping the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555330" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm placing my resources at your disposal. I have a base camp in Labor Valley. Bring your people to my position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555332" id2="17" version="1065353216">You go on ahead. I will guide our forces there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="555334" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make sure everyone gets on the next transport. You don't need to wait for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555336" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see you soon, my friend. Var Suthra out....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555340" id2="17" version="1065353216">We still haven't broken the Imperial blockade in this sector. The situation's getting worse every moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555342" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Aves is leading forces to break the Empire's stranglehold. He needs your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555344" id2="17" version="1065353216">These young Jedi are unprepared for what lies ahead. Those of us with battlefield experience will share our knowledge while you're gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="555345" id2="17" version="1065353216">These reinforcements have no battlefield experience. We'll prepare them to face the enemy while you clear the path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555346" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be back as soon as I've broken that blockade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="555346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems to me an army of Jedi could break this blockade easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="555347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't we do this together?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555348" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must manage our forces carefully. This situation requires more than brute force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555350" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's right. The general requested a crack squad for this mission, not a full company.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="555352" id2="17" version="1065353216">From what I've heard about this blockade, we're more likely to get everyone killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555354" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's right. The general is looking for a crack squad to handle this, not a battalion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some reinforcements. I'd be better off with a shipload of battle droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="555356" id2="17" version="1065353216">I may as well be alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555357" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must make do with what we have.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="555359" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Jedi will be better than droids when we're done training them. I promise you that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find Corporal Hartke. He'll introduce you to the general. And good luck....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555374" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last transport of reinforcements is docking now. There's still Jedi on the planet not accounted for, though. Hope you find them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555375" id2="17" version="1065353216">Transports from Kinyen and Duro brought more reinforcements. We're still waiting for others. Keep up the search for your people already here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555376" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reinforcements from Orto and Rodia have arrived. You should keep searching for your people out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555377" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your reinforcements will arrive soon. The rest of your people are somewhere in this sector. When you find them, send them here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555378" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want those shield generators online yesterday! Move it, privates!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555379" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Rikdine? Master Satele Shan sent me. I'm the new Jedi commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555380" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made it--thank the skies. The Empire controls so much of Corellia, we can barely establish a landing zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555382" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy has us under constant bombardment. We're in a blasted bottleneck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555383" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll deal with that once I've rallied the Jedi on the ground. Master Satele said you could help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="555383" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need the other Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555384" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've sent more of your people home in body bags than I want to count. There aren't many of you left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555386" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like our first order of business is knocking a hole in the Empire's forward lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="555386" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can we break out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555387" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll want to speak with Corporal Hartke about that. My job is to organize your forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555389" id2="17" version="1065353216">There has to be a better spot than this. Hasn't anyone looked?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="555389" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find another landing zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555390" id2="17" version="1065353216">We lost ten thousand men securing that spaceport. We pull out, we'll lose ten thousand more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555392" id2="17" version="1065353216">The shuttles bringing your reinforcements will arrive shortly. In the meantime, you should gather the few already here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555394" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have coordinates to the last known locations of your fellow Jedi. That's the best I can offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555395" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done well. I'll take it from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="555395" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555396" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not here to pick up corpses. I need to know if these people are alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="555396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are the Jedi alive or dead?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even if I could make that assurance now, things change moment to moment out there. That's how bad it is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555399" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should know better than to expect anything useful from you people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="555399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Typical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Between the bombardment and enemy patrols, it's chaos out there. We're doing the best we can.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="555402" id2="17" version="1065353216">This location is the rallying point for your forces. As the reinforcements arrive, they'll come here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555404" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take the intel on the Jedi you're looking for. I hope you find them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="555406" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't engage the enemy until we break out of this sector.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
