<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>55</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/class/jedi_knight/doctor_godera.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455792" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't recommend you waste any time. Those turbolasers will be complete soon. Hurry to the assault shuttle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Haven't seen you since Darth Angral became a cloud of random molecules. Glad you joined the festivities. This gathering is long overdue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455796" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't a celebration. People are dying out there, doctor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455796" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a war, not a party.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455797" id2="17" version="1065353216">As long as it's the right people dying, that's not a problem for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Godera, this is a war zone--are you trying to get yourself killed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455799" id2="17" version="1065353216">You shouldn't be here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Honestly, who's going to target a science museum? Besides, the general's best men are guarding me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455802" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seem familiar. Have we met?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455802" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455803" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've put on a little weight since Taris, but... Doctor Godera, remember?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455805" id2="17" version="1065353216">My probe droids have been hunting for your Master Braga. They've found enemy activity in two buildings bordering Axial Park.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teams of Sith under Master Braga's command are setting up turbolasers in the buildings' topmost floors. They're camouflaging the weapons from view.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever they're planning, it's designed to be a surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a sneak attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is Master Braga personally overseeing this operation? Can I get to him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is he with them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455810" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith are only taking orders via holo, but I'm closing in on the source of those transmissions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send artillery to level those structures. Threat eliminated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bomb the buildings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455813" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admire your plan's simplicity, but both buildings contain thousands of civilian inhabitants.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455815" id2="17" version="1065353216">The turbolasers are code-named &quot;firestorm.&quot; An adaptation of the technology from Darth Angral's superweapon. Lethal and focused.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those turbolasers will make Axial Park a literal inferno. There would be no survivors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455818" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor wants to inflict maximum fatalities here. We need to take out those weapons fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455818" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the enemy's goal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455820" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt the enemy soldiers on the ground have been notified of this plan by their Sith masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455820" id2="17" version="1065353216">And a lot of dead Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems the Empire's left claw doesn't know what the right claw is doing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455823" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we took control of those turbolasers, we could incinerate the whole Imperial army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455823" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could use those weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455824" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fires created would be too intense. They'd spread out of control and consume whole sectors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455826" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Var Suthra wants those turbolasers destroyed. As I'm currently standing in the line of fire, I'm inclined to agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Demolitions and transport have been secured. All we need is a small commando group. I'm told you can provide that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just point us at the targets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't we just enter these buildings from the ground floor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455830" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need a transport?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455831" id2="17" version="1065353216">The structures are thousands of meters high. You'd be exhausted before you reach the enemy positions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just like old times. The Republic finds a problem, and I have to go fix it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't I always?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doing it the opposite way never seems to work out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic military transports can't get off the ground here, but there's an Imperial assault shuttle on display at a starship museum nearby.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455838" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy doesn't know the Corellians have it. They'll mistake the assault shuttle for one of their own. You'll fly directly to your targets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive plan, doctor. Let's put it into action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455840" id2="17" version="1065353216">You say the transport is in a museum. Does it actually fly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455840" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're sure the shuttle works?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellians love starships even more than museums. The assault shuttle is in pristine condition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455843" id2="17" version="1065353216">After we hit the first turbolaser, the enemy will be onto us. They'll start gunning for our transport.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455843" id2="17" version="1065353216">And blow our cover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never said the plan was foolproof. You're a Jedi. Fly recklessly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455846" id2="17" version="1065353216">One last thing... I've modified some proton torpedos into explosive charges. Drop one down a turbolaser's barrel and you'll fuse it shut. Weapon neutralized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get to the shuttle. Stop the Sith before they turn this park into a giant cookout. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455850" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do me a favor when you leave. Kill every Imperial and Sith you see.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="455853" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will secure fuel for the shuttle and prep it for takeoff. It will be ready to fly when you meet us.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
