<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>84</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/class/jedi_knight/erris_wyum.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494368" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back, General. My scouts say they've never seen such a decisive victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494369" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wonder if there's room on the cruiser for my office? I'd much rather be up there than down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494370" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me get this straight... not only did you save millions of lives, but you and your strike team seized an Imperial battle cruiser.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nope. Doesn't sound any less incredible when I say it out loud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494374" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rogue Jedi you were after--did you catch him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494375" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Braga is no longer under the Emperor's control. He's returning to Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494375" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's on his way to Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494376" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure how I feel about him going free. At least he isn't our problem anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494377" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Braga was beyond redemption. I had to kill him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494377" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494378" id2="17" version="1065353216">A lot of people will sleep better knowing he's gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494379" id2="17" version="1065353216">I convinced Master Braga to switch sides. He's attacking Imperial positions as we speak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494379" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's fighting for us, now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494380" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's still classified as an enemy combatant. We can't guarantee his safety. Hope that won't be a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494381" id2="17" version="1065353216">The general should be here. What's his status?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494381" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where is General Var Suthra?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494383" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi Council asked me to keep that to myself. What matters is, he's no longer a threat to Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494383" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] That's top secret.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494384" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Jedi weren't famous for their honesty, I'd think you were giving us the brush-off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494389" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got the Empire running. Their command-and-control network is in shambles. These Jedi troops performed brilliantly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494391" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm recommending this brave Jedi army for the Republic's top military honor. You've all earned it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494392" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi Order is grateful for the recognition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494392" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi don't serve in the hope of recognition. We do it because we must.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Medals aren't necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494394" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, I don't award medals to make myself feel better. I do it because I must.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494396" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's nice to see the Republic military finally acknowledge the Jedi Order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, we did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494397" id2="17" version="1065353216">There have been too many hard feelings since your people left Coruscant. It's time we put that behind us and work together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494399" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you can't stay, but Corellia needs the rest of us. This battle isn't over by a long shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494401" id2="17" version="1065353216">I promise I'll take good care of your people here. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494404" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish I had good news, but the general's mission was not successful. He didn't have the forces he needed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494406" id2="17" version="1065353216">They put up a good fight, but the enemy had superior numbers. There were no survivors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494407" id2="17" version="1065353216">All those soldiers and Jedi, gone. The cost of this battle was too high.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494407" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's horrible news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494408" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those soldiers and Jedi saved Corellia. They kept the enemy busy so I could complete my mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494408" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a noble sacrifice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494409" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll be recognized for their service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494411" id2="17" version="1065353216">It could've been worse. We could all be dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494411" id2="17" version="1065353216">War happens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494412" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose, when you look at it that way....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494414" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's still plenty of fighting to be done. The Empire is down, but it's already regrouping.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494416" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd ask you to stay, but I get the feeling you've already got one foot out the door. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494418" id2="17" version="1065353216">Want to hear something sad? I'm not allowed to retreat. Hope you shut down those reactors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494419" id2="17" version="1065353216">The general has been waiting for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494420" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're here to check something out, the librarian is dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your friend offered to stay and fight. I figure one Jedi is still better than none.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="494425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia has become a Jedi graveyard. After all our sacrifices, I can't abandon it. I have to see this through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494426" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm leaving Corellia in good hands. Be careful out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494426" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="494427" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force guide and protect you, Supreme Commander. Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494428" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm placing you in charge of all Jedi forces on Corellia until Master Satele says otherwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494428" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're supreme commander, now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="494429" id2="17" version="1065353216">Considering I'm the only Jedi left, that isn't much of a promotion.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="494431" id2="17" version="1065353216">It has been an education serving under you--one I will not forget. Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="494432" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are so few of us left. I do not think that promotion will be necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="494434" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you. Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494435" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won't last long without me to watch your back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494435" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't expect you'll survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="494436" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no death; there is only the Force. Farewell, Supreme Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your strike team volunteered to stay and fight. We won't turn down the offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="494439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia has become a Jedi graveyard. After all our sacrifices, we can't abandon it. We have to see this through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494440" id2="17" version="1065353216">If not for cannon fire from the cruiser, the general would be dead. His entire platoon and one of your Jedi squads didn't make it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494441" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm thankful General Var Suthra lived. He's a great leader.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494441" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least the general survived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494442" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's a tough old man, I'll give him that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494446" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back, General. My scouts tell me your people had it rough out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494448" id2="17" version="1065353216">We took down several command-and-control centers. Might be the edge we need to win this sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494450" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were aided by some timely cannon fire from that cruiser. Your doing, I assume? Much appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494452" id2="17" version="1065353216">But casualties were high. I lost half my platoon and two squads of Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494454" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll recommend everyone who gave their lives today for the Republic's highest honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494455" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are dead Jedi the only ones who qualify for medals?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494455" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the rest of us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494456" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, no--of course not. You've all earned the recognition.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="494458" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will stay and fight. I owe it to the men who died for me aboard that cruiser.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494459" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi here will need a leader. I can't think of anyone more qualified than you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494459" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're supreme commander, now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="494460" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is a great honor--and an even greater responsibility. I won't let you down. Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494461" id2="17" version="1065353216">With your strike team joining us, I feel a lot more confident of victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="494463" id2="17" version="1065353216">It has been a great honor serving with you. I feel ready to take on the whole galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494464" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume that cannon fire from the cruiser was your doing. Good timing. Saved my skin.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="494466" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is good to see you alive, Supreme Commander. Did you find Master Braga?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="494467" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was able to use the cruiser's weapons and aid the general, but... my teammates died protecting me from an enemy counterattack.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="494469" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope their sacrifice wasn't in vain. Did you find Master Braga?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
