<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>223</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/class/jedi_knight/general_var_suthra.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="468445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Godera... the Sith killed him. Damn them!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469028" id2="17" version="1065353216">The doctor was a brilliant man. He served the Republic with loyalty and dedication.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469028" id2="17" version="1065353216">My condolences, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469098" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't know him well, but I think he'd rather we keep fighting than stop to mourn him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469099" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish the people who believe we can make peace with the Empire could see this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469125" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please give Master Satele my regards. Today, the Jedi saved Corellia three times over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469126" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be right behind you. We'll keep the Empire's forces off your back long enough to reach that turbolift. Good luck, my old friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="469129" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're at the point of no return, my friend. Win or lose, this is where we'll make our stand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469131" id2="17" version="1065353216">Erris Wyum is with Corellian Intelligence. He's just learned our job here is even harder than we thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469133" id2="17" version="1065353216">My reconnaissance teams just picked up an energy surge coming from the reactors on that Imperial battle cruiser.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469135" id2="17" version="1065353216">We believe the cruiser's reactors are being overloaded--building to detonation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Braga sabotaged his battle cruiser. He's using it to destroy this whole sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469136" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a suicide attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469137" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why not simply crash it into the surface?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get a message to the Imperial officers aboard that cruiser. Tell them what's happening.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warn the ship's crew.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469140" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've tried. No response from them--not even insults. For all we know, the command crew is dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469142" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've stopped his other plans. A suicide attack is the only option that idiot has left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469142" id2="17" version="1065353216">Braga is a desperate fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469143" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Master Braga wants to destroy his own ship, why not crash it into the surface?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469145" id2="17" version="1065353216">A reactor detonation at its present altitude won't just flatten this sector. The radiation released will kill people for hundreds of kilometers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469147" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good news is, there's a secure turbolift connecting the cruiser to the government buildings. They use it to send troops there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your strike team will use that to get inside the cruiser, shut down those reactors and deal with Master Braga.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469150" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will be different. Usually, I run away from exploding enemy cruisers....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469150" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope it's that easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469151" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have absolute confidence you'll survive this. If I'm wrong, we won't live to regret it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469153" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Master Braga sees me coming, he might detonate the reactors early.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469153" id2="17" version="1065353216">Frontal assaults are risky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469154" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a plan to distract him and buy you the element of surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't wait to see the their faces when I arrive with all my friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469156" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should take my army, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469157" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't take the enemy by surprise with an army of Jedi--but don't worry, your people will have plenty to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469159" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm commanding a platoon of Republic troops. With your Jedi squads backing us, we'll hit enemy command-and-control centers all over this area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469161" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll keep the enemy's attention off your strike team and retake Capitol Square for the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without all these Jedi, I'd say you were crazy to even try it--but you just might pull this off, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469164" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people won't let you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469164" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force is with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469165" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish there were more Jedi for this mission. It would improve your odds of success.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469166" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people are battle-hardened and ready for anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469166" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll be enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469167" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm counting on that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469169" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's rare to see a general charging into battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should you be going out there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469170" id2="17" version="1065353216">None of us can afford to play it safe. This is all or nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your goals realistic. All I need is for you to clear my path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be a hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469173" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do that, and then some.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469175" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is it, friends. May the Force be with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469177" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it too late to go back to Balmorra?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better yet, may it not be with the bad guys.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469179" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough platitudes. Let's end this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469180" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victory or death! For the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="469181" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi + Force + T7 = unstoppable combination // Onward!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469190" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Godera meant well, but the weapons he designed nearly destroyed the Republic. Some might say we are safer without him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469190" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is neither good nor bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469191" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some might say he's the only reason the Republic survived this long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469193" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll burn his name into every enemy I kill here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469193" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll avenge him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469194" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know he'd appreciate the gesture.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469196" id2="17" version="1065353216">All enemies accounted for, General. I found Doctor Godera's work. Looks important.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469198" id2="17" version="1065353216">He was tracking Master Braga's holotransmissions. He found... signals coming from an Imperial battle cruiser hovering above Capitol Square.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469199" id2="17" version="1065353216">He found Master Braga. I need to get inside that battle cruiser right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469199" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's where I'm going.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469200" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would the Empire bring a warship down to the planet surface?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469200" id2="17" version="1065353216">It isn't in orbit?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469201" id2="17" version="1065353216">We assumed it was to intimidate us. Maybe it's something worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469203" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Braga's gone insane, and now he has a warship at his command. Blow them both out of the sky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469203" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shoot it down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469204" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would inflict massive civilian casualties in the heart of Corellia. We need a better plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469206" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic troops established a small forward base in the government district. Gather your people and meet me there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469208" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senator Zackin sends his regards. Your Jedi troops freed all his Corellian &quot;citizens&quot; with no casualties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meanwhile, those Imperial murderers who slaughtered our wounded are laughing all the way back to Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469211" id2="17" version="1065353216">My mission here is to save lives, not take them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469211" id2="17" version="1065353216">I made the right choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469212" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll never understand you people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469214" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they're not on Corellia, they're no threat to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469214" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least they're gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469215" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the next planet those killers are sent to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469217" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's only a temporary reprieve. Someday, they'll pay for what they've done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469217" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll get theirs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469218" id2="17" version="1065353216">They should have died today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your Jedi troops caught the Imperials off guard. Wiped out every one of those murdering scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469222" id2="17" version="1065353216">You lost a squad in the battle, but they went down fighting. Their sacrifice meant something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469224" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for doing the right thing. I found you some top-of-the-line advanced combat gear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469225" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll put this gear to good use. I'd better get going.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469225" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Colonel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469226" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kick those Imperials into the nearest sun, Supreme Commander!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469227" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad I don't have to remind you about our agreement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469227" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you'd forgotten.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469228" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd never cheat a Jedi. It's bad luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469229" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a little underwhelmed, Colonel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469229" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469230" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were all out of heavy artillery walkers. Best I could do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469232" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll transmit the coordinates of our forward base to all your people and have them meet you there. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469276" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you doing here? The Sith are preparing that chemical bomb. Get to the factory!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469278" id2="17" version="1065353216">General, I've shut down the chemical pipelines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stand by. Agent Helver is collating the data. Did you run into much trouble out there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469280" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toxic smoke, killer droids, enemy patrols. The usual.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469280" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could say that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469281" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it me, or have you grown a sense of humor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469283" id2="17" version="1065353216">There were a few troublemakers who soon saw the error of their ways.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469283" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing I couldn't handle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469284" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgot how much fun it is to work with you....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469286" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is asking stupid questions one of your core competencies, General?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469286" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you think, idiot?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469287" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgot how irritable you can be....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469289" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hang on, we're getting something.... One of the chemical plants was siphoning accellerite. We've found our Sith bomb makers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469291" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sending the coordinates to you and your strike team now. They'll meet you inside. Hurry!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469293" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut down those chemical pipelines so we can find the Empire's forces. Hurry!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469295" id2="17" version="1065353216">General, my forces are on the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469296" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to hear it. An agent with SIS is bringing us the latest intel on Master Tol Braga.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469298" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the meantime, we should form a battle plan to drive the Empire from this sector. It's running riot here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469300" id2="17" version="1065353216">Magremme Thrakus is one of the chief suppliers of the Republic's war effort. She owns half the facilities in Labor Valley.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469302" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire &quot;appropriated&quot; my weapon factories. They're stealing billions of credits worth of firepower.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469303" id2="17" version="1065353216">My forces will retake this entire sector, starting with your factories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not for long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469304" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope so. They've been in my family for generations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469306" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sort of armament is the Empire taking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469306" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of weapons?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469307" id2="17" version="1065353216">My factories produce everything from personal blasters to capital ship torpedoes. The Empire is looting all of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469309" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should be easy to defend a munitions plant from hostile takeover. Everything you need is there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469309" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you're letting them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469310" id2="17" version="1065353216">I manufacture weapons, not soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469312" id2="17" version="1065353216">I recommend devoting all Jedi forces to removing the enemy from those weapon factories. We certainly need munitions more than the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469314" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a priority signal from the Supreme Chancellor. Excuse me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469316" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is more to this than weapons, you know. The Empire also seized my company's base of operations. I want it back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469318" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you were to allocate forces toward liberating my corporate offices, I'd be extremely grateful--and I do mean personally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi aren't for hire, and the general believes your weapon factories are more important.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469319" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure about this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469320" id2="17" version="1065353216">The general doesn't see the big picture. My company possesses many valuable assets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would the Empire raid your corporate offices?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469322" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's your motive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469323" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never trusted Corellia's banking system. I convert all my company's monetary reserves into precious resources. Many are hidden beneath the offices.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469325" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire hasn't found my resources yet, but given enough time, they will. There's no telling what they could do with all that wealth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469327" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate personal gratitude, assuming it's actually worth my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make a specific offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469328" id2="17" version="1065353216">I run a multi-trillion credit corporation. If you help me, you won't be disappointed with your reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469330" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone is here and ready to face the enemy on your command. May the Force be with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="469331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your forces are ready for duty, Supreme Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Kiwiiks, I haven't seen you since Coruscant. That's an impressive bunch you've brought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never seen this many Jedi in one place. Blasted impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469337" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we're going to retake those weapon factories, your people need to go now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469338" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're on it, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469340" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want those weapon factories cleared of all Imperial forces. Don't let the enemy escape with any munitions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469340" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose you're right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469341" id2="17" version="1065353216">New information has come to light, General. I believe Thrakus's corporate offices is the more important objective. I'm sending all forces there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469341" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, we're saving the offices.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469342" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't understand. That office building has no strategic value.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469344" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I have my company, I can build more weapons. It's business, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="469346" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will communicate your orders to the others.</text>
		<text bitflag="7489" id1="469347" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll deliver the orders at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469349" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Var Suthra... we've learned the Jedi traitor Tol Braga has sent a strike team to destroy Labor Valley.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469350" id2="17" version="1065353216">What could destroy this entire sector?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469350" id2="17" version="1065353216">That requires quite a weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469351" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tol Braga is a good man. Whatever he's doing, it's not of his own free will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469351" id2="17" version="1065353216">He isn't a traitor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469352" id2="17" version="1065353216">With all due respect, I couldn't care less why he's trying to kill us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469354" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I can get to Master Braga, I'll end these threats for good. Where is he?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know where Braga is?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469355" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're tracing his holomessages, but there's too much chaos on the comm frequencies to get his location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469357" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith have invaded a chemical refinery to create an improvised bomb. The explosion will release a massive toxic cloud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469359" id2="17" version="1065353216">That cloud will kill everyone here and drift into the adjacent sectors. Potentially millions of fatalities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469360" id2="17" version="1065353216">Point me to this chemical refinery. I'll handle the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469360" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'd better move fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469361" id2="17" version="1065353216">A weapon that indiscriminately kills friend and foe alike. The Sith are on a suicide mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Including the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps they're as deluded as Executor Krannus was on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469364" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather put them out of our misery personally. How do we do that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469366" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send a general retreat. We don't want to be anywhere near this bomb when it goes off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469366" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to pull back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469367" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll never evacuate everyone in time. Besides, there are civilians to consider.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469369" id2="17" version="1065353216">We still don't know which chemical refinery the Sith have, but we do know which chemicals they're gathering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469371" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shutting down all the chemical pipelines feeding the refineries won't stop the Sith. However, it will give away their location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contact me when it's done. May the Force be with you all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469375" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have to wait. I'm in the middle of something.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="469378" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have coordinates to the turbolift. We'll keep a low profile, split up and rendezvous there quietly. The enemy will never know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469380" id2="17" version="1065353216">All due respect, General, a platoon of normal soldiers and two squads of Jedi won't be enough to accomplish that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469381" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great victories have been won with less. Don't give in to fear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469381" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is always hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469382" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wasn't planning to give up. Not my style.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469384" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're getting battle reports from your Jedi forces. They're wrapping up their missions now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469386" id2="17" version="1065353216">You lost a squad fighting those Imperials that slaughtered our soldiers--but no enemies survived. I call that a victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469388" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your people took out almost all the Imperial scum who were killing our wounded soldiers. Looks like you lost a squad, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469390" id2="17" version="1065353216">You lost another freeing the Corellian &quot;citizens&quot; from the slave camps. The Senator offers his condolences.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469394" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cost you a squad, but your people taught those Imperials a lesson. The ones who aren't dead know better than to attack wounded soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469396" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rest of your people freed the Corellian &quot;citizens&quot; without any trouble. The Senator offers his warmest regards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469398" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another Jedi squad died while freeing the Corellian &quot;citizens.&quot; The Senator offers his condolences.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469402" id2="17" version="1065353216">The squad you sent after the Corellian &quot;citizens&quot; freed a couple before having to retreat. The Senator isn't happy, but who cares?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469403" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wish you'd sent more people after those Imperials who slaughtered our wounded soldiers. Most of that scum got away, and you lost a squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469405" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sent more than enough to free the Senator's Corellian &quot;citizens.&quot; No casualties reported.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469407" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the Senator offers his thanks for freeing the Corellian &quot;citizens.&quot; No casualties there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even worse, you lost another one freeing the Corellian &quot;citizens.&quot; The Senator offers thanks--and condolences.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469412" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wasn't much point in sending a lone squad to attack those Imperials. Your people barely made a dent in that murdering filth before retreating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469414" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meanwhile, the Corellian &quot;citizens&quot; were all freed without incident. The Senator offers his warmest regards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469415" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate the status report, but I'm needed elsewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for the update.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469416" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to know my forces are making a difference out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469416" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people do good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469417" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy is taking notice, that's for sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469419" id2="17" version="1065353216">If these losses continue, I won't have much of an army left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469419" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're losing too many Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Next time, put all your people on the same mission--and bet on the sure thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469422" id2="17" version="1065353216">I committed forces to your mission. You promised me advanced combat gear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469422" id2="17" version="1065353216">You still owe me gear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469423" id2="17" version="1065353216">I requisitioned the best combat gear I could get you. It's not much, but it's yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469431" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did lose a squad, though. Too bad you didn't have more forces to commit. Probably would've made a difference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469433" id2="17" version="1065353216">No casualties on your end either. It's a good day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your Jedi gave us a boost, but odds are still fifty-fifty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469437" id2="17" version="1065353216">The news isn't so good on this end. We drove the Empire from a few weapon factories and saved Thrakus's corporate headquarters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469439" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I'm afraid your losses were heavy. Two Jedi squads died in the fighting. I'm sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469440" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have to use my squads more carefully from now on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469440" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's almost half my people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469441" id2="17" version="1065353216">The hardest part of leading troops is learning to focus on what's most important. Dividing forces leaves both halves vulnerable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dozens of pipelines run through this sector. We can't expect one Jedi to shut down all of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469445" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Outer Rim Jedi have left, but the rest of us could form a strike team.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="469447" id2="17" version="1065353216">I already sent out our main forces, but we can search with you. We'll be your strike team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469449" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll divide the chemical pipelines among all of you. Shut them down, and we'll pinpoint the Sith's location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Half of my forces will push the Empire out of those factories. The rest will liberate Thrakus's corporate offices.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="469451" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Save both objectives.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469452" id2="17" version="1065353216">That office building has no strategic value whatsoever, but it's your call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="469454" id2="17" version="1065353216">My company's survival is at stake. The Jedi understands this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="469457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Supreme Commander, we'll deliver Master Kiwiiks's body to the nearest medcenter and wait for orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="469458" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done, Supreme Commander. We'll sweep this area for surviving Sith and then rendezvous with our main forces.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
