<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>40</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/class/jedi_knight/master_satele_shan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691814" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, I've landed on Corellia. From what I saw flying in, the fighting here is intense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia is in a state of total war. The Republic and Empire aren't holding back anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691817" id2="17" version="1065353216">The losses are staggering, and not just military. Thousands of civilians die every hour.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691819" id2="17" version="1065353216">And each death brings the Emperor closer to his goal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which is why we cannot retreat. If the Republic pulls back, the Empire will exterminate every being here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our enemy doesn't need a planet-destroying device. The war itself will deliver what he needs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="691822" id2="17" version="1065353216">War is the Emperor's weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691823" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor doesn't distinguish between his people and ours. Every Imperial and Sith we kill adds fuel to his ritual.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="691823" id2="17" version="1065353216">But fighting won't help us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. He's planned for every contingency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck. This planet's population numbers in the billions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="691826" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would take forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691827" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperial war machine is efficient. They'd need a week, at most.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Tol Braga is aiding the enemy. He knows how to hurt us--block our efforts to save this world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691831" id2="17" version="1065353216">Removing Master Braga from the Emperor's control is the key to victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691832" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a big world. He could be anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="691832" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have to find him first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691833" id2="17" version="1065353216">He commands legions of Imperials and Sith. He cannot do that from hiding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691835" id2="17" version="1065353216">After my experience with Warren Sedoru, I don't have much hope for Master Braga.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="691835" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if I can't save him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope is all we have now. The alternative is death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691838" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't leave a fellow Jedi enslaved to that monster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="691838" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the right thing to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691839" id2="17" version="1065353216">After prolonged exposure to the Emperor's influence, Master Braga may be difficult to free--but we must try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our fallen master is many things, but &quot;brilliant military strategist&quot; isn't one of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="691841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Braga is useless to the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691842" id2="17" version="1065353216">His wisdom and knowledge are great. In the enemy's hands, they are terrible weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691844" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only a handful of Jedi remain alive on Corellia. I'm sending reinforcements from the Outer Rim, but they're inexperienced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691846" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need strong leadership to win this battle. I'm naming you supreme commander of Jedi forces on Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691847" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll resolve this crisis with as few casualties as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="691847" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do my best, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691848" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't find Master Braga if I'm herding troops from one battle to another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="691848" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I already have a job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use them. If nothing else, they might clear your path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691851" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't trust anyone else with the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="691851" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I should be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shock troops. Excellent. They will make finding your enemy easier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia must not fall. Your mission is twofold; direct our forces to aid the Republic military's efforts, and personally find Master Braga.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691856" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until reinforcements arrive, rally those few Jedi already on the surface. My contact, Captain Rikdine, will help you locate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="691858" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sending his coordinates. May the Force be with you.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
