<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>16</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/jedi_consular/chapter_2/multi/shuuru.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641567" id2="17" version="1065353216">The... fight on Corellia must have been so harrowing. I hope you're alright.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641568" id2="17" version="1065353216">So it comes down to Corellia. Either we win, or... no, we must win!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641569" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't lose a friend to the enemy, Jedi, not again!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641570" id2="17" version="1065353216">A shame I can't come on the mission... but it's all right, I'll be cheering for you!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you think those Voss would tell my fortune?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Strange. I keep wanting to ask Grell's advice about all this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641573" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what was Republic security doing when Grell was captured? What do we pay our taxes for?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi, I'm still not sure recruiting these &quot;Esh-kha&quot; is a good idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641575" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, Jedi, we'll conjure up an army in no time!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641576" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't think Blaesus told the Emperor anything about me, do you?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641577" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi, what's going on? Did something happen to Blaesus?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck, Jedi. Show those pirates who's in charge!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641579" id2="17" version="1065353216">You saved dozens of Selkath lives on Attis Station. I'll never forget this, Jedi, never.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641580" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph! There was no Republic rescue when my world was bombed! I suppose ocean planets are expendable.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hijacked ships, a Jedi Master whose feet are barely wet... This is going to be a disaster!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="641582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Manaan... I wonder what's changed since I left.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
