<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tatooine/bronze/imperial/shields_down/teek.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me. I must finish my reports.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your device worked well. The droids are destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616365" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course it worked well! Do you think you're dealing with some fourth-tier apprentice?</text>
		<text bitflag="7489" id1="616367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now here. It turns out they gave me a budget for testing after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616369" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few weeks from now, every soldier in the Imperial Army will be fitted with one of these.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616373" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's valuable technology I gave you! Don't just drag it around; go test it on the droids!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616374" id2="17" version="1065353216">No! No! No! This will not do at all. I wanted expendable testers. I made that very specific on my order form.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616376" id2="17" version="1065353216">What good does a Sith do me? If I break you, someone's going to slice my head off.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616378" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bounty hunters cost much too much to replace. Didn't they have any slave gladiators or something?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616380" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone spent a lot of money to get you outfitted. They probably won't like it if I break you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616382" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go. And bring me back someone who no one will miss if they die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616383" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of Neimoidian orders around Imperials?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616383" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616384" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you talking about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616385" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a joke.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616386" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Teek! I am a tier-six inventor of Research Corps Eight of the Imperial Science Bureau!</text>
		<text bitflag="7489" id1="616388" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have just designed a portable oscillator to strip the natives' droids of their shielding so the slightest blaster hit will destroy them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616390" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once I test it under field conditions, it can be mass manufactured and distributed to every soldier on the planet!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616391" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this technology is valuable, it should go first to the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616391" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can test it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616392" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, as long as you don't break it. Uh, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616394" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is fortunate we met, scientist. I will test your device against these droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616394" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can test it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hrmph. Well, I suppose with the oscillator, you shouldn't come to any harm....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Were you planning to pay your lab rats anything?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have a test budget?</text>
		<text bitflag="7489" id1="616398" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course not! But if you guarantee that you will return the device unharmed, I might be able to scrounge up a stipend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616400" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm always interested in trying out the latest technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Allow me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616401" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect! Maybe when we're done, I can interest you in a helmet that lets you hear alien comm signals as a constant buzzing in your left ear....</text>
		<text bitflag="7489" id1="616403" id2="17" version="1065353216">But, right! The droids....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616405" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about this device.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616406" id2="17" version="1065353216">It collects solar radiation and oscillates it at the precise frequency to... never mind! You're no scientist. All you care is that it works, not how!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616408" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once it's powered at a solar receptor, the oscillator is what you call &quot;point and shoot.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616410" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will give you the location of both the power station and the droids if you truly wish to test it for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616414" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616415" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you find any widows or orphans, send them my way....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not interfere with the process of science!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
