<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>117</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/world/imperial/taming_trandoshans/captain_vandorn.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707439" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew those Trandoshans were hiding something. I hope you found the Republic's storage facility full of surprises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707442" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were right about those Trandoshans. Much more effective without shock collars weighing them down. Thanks for breaking them in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707443" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Trandoshans are responding to slavery quite well. Thanks to you, we'll secure this wing shortly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reform the Trandoshans. Show them your superior strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707445" id2="17" version="1065353216">The alien inmates are right where we want them--bruised, broken and terrified of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707447" id2="17" version="1065353216">But if I know criminals, they'll be back to their old tricks soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707449" id2="17" version="1065353216">We better ensure their wounds stay raw. But we don't have the manpower that disciplinary action takes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find the meanest gang of aliens, then deputize them. They'll keep the rest in line.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recruit some of the prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707451" id2="17" version="1065353216">A repugnant idea--which, I'm afraid, is the only way out of this mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707453" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's stopping you from flooding this wing with Imperials?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't you deploy more troops?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not enough resources. There's only one solution--a revolting one. Recruit aliens to enforce order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707456" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want these inmates broken, look no further.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707456" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm all the manpower you need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707457" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate the offer, but we need permanent enforcers. I hate to say it, but that means recruiting prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707459" id2="17" version="1065353216">The aliens here are mostly slack-jawed brutes, except the Trandoshans. They follow a strict warrior's code of honor and competition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707461" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fools even worship a goddess--some &quot;Scorekeeper&quot; they think rewards honor. Devotion's carved them into fanatics. Now they roam this wing, hunting dangerous prey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707462" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Trandoshans owe their freedom to the Empire. It's time they repay us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707462" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will draft them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707463" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't volunteer peacefully, my lord. You'll have to appeal to their appetite for competition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707465" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must break the Trandoshans' spirit. Then they'll respect their new master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707465" id2="17" version="1065353216">They will lose their faith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707466" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree, my lord. But you'll have to prove your strength to the scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707468" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time we introduce these Trandoshans to civilization. They'll repay us with servitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707468" id2="17" version="1065353216">How quaint... and exploitable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707469" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must be clever. Appeal to their base nature.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707471" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Trandoshans are that gullible, they'll come around. They just don't know it yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707471" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make them volunteer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recruitment should be simple. Just appeal to their competitive side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707474" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Trandoshans are useless if they won't swear loyalty to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707474" id2="17" version="1065353216">But are they dependable?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707475" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll honor an agreement, but standard diplomacy won't work. We must appeal to their thirst for competition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707477" id2="17" version="1065353216">So they're insane. That's bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707478" id2="17" version="1065353216">As vile as they are, we can win them over. All it takes is a little competition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trandoshans can't resist a worthy foe. They'll fear you, but the chance to kill a mighty Sith will prove too tempting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trandoshans can't resist a worthy foe. And it's not every day a top Imperial operative comes knocking. They'll be compelled to fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trandoshans never turn down a worthy foe. They'll recognize you as a fellow hunter. And they'll be compelled to prove their strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trandoshans never shy from worthy prey. And they don't come any more impressive than you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Challenge their leader to a duel. Demand that if you win, his entire pack serves as the Empire's enforcers. They'll be honor-bound to obey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707489" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Trandoshans will soon obey the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707490" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Trandoshans laugh in my face, I'm killing every last one of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707490" id2="17" version="1065353216">This better work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry--they'll bite. I mean, well, you understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure. Why not?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you! The sooner we lock this wing down, the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't forget my price.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. I'll take care of everything once the contract's fulfilled.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707499" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Trandoshans built their fortress inside a vault. Storm the place and challenge their leader. Make the scaly thugs bow to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707502" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those alien gangs will think twice before attacking the Empire again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707503" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you kicked a few of them while they were down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707505" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blasted aliens don't know who they're messing with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Vandorn? Commander Calum sent me to assist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707512" id2="17" version="1065353216">Operations Group Four's honored, my lord. I'm happy to report that our prisoner release program's on schedule.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Operations Group Four welcomes you, sir. I'm happy to report that our prisoner release program's going brilliantly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Operations Group Four welcomes your services, mercenary. Our prisoner release program is already underway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Operations Group Four. Our prisoner release program's gotten off to a marvelous start.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707520" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've hit only one hiccup, really. The prisoners here--they're gangs of rabid aliens. Formerly members of some Republic experiment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707522" id2="17" version="1065353216">The gangs attack the Republic as planned, but they're also tormenting our boys. Now there's a large number of berserk aliens between us and the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707523" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care how ferocious these prisoners are. I'll reach the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aliens won't stop me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even if you find the Sith Lords, we need this area secure for their escape. My team's instilling order now, and--excuse me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707526" id2="17" version="1065353216">A prison break needs a clear escape route.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then how will we get them out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not to worry. Operations Group Four's on the job. We'll have those aliens killed or back in their cells in no--excuse me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I detect a hint of repulsion towards non-humans, Captain?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have a problem with aliens?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only the criminal element. I'd never lump someone of your caliber in with these--excuse me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707532" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't your lucky day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707533" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have everything under control. Operations Group Four's clearing out the aliens, and--excuse me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707537" id2="17" version="1065353216">One more step and I'll--! Oh... so sorry. Thought you were a prisoner. Please accept my apologies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis isn't safe to travel alone. But if you got this far, maybe you could help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to see friendlies so far from home base. Stay a moment. You're about to walk right into a battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707543" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Captain Vandorn, head of Operations Group Four. We just unleashed enough vicious alien prisoners to keep the Republic busy for months.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we hit a hiccup. The alien gangs went berserk, attacking Imperial and Republic alike. We need to restore order, ASAP.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send your operations group into the field. Knock some alien skulls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lay down the law.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707547" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on top of it. My team's already out there, rounding up the inmates and--excuse me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707549" id2="17" version="1065353216">The longer these inmates run loose, the more Republic meat they chew.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707549" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the rush?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707550" id2="17" version="1065353216">These aliens are more lethal than expected. Operations Group Four's fighting to slow their advance and--excuse me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707552" id2="17" version="1065353216">A mob of prisoners shouldn't be too hard to control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707552" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't handle a few aliens?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Operations Group Four can handle anything. My team's out there now, beating the bushes and--excuse me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707555" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Vandorn speaking. Dead? All of them? No--that's impossible! Well, stop blabbering and--Sergeant? Sergeant?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707557" id2="17" version="1065353216">The alien gangs have wiped out Operations Group Four. We've lost control of this wing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707558" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where the military falls, Captain, a Sith will triumph.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707558" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will take it back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis twisted these aliens into savage killers. Your lightsaber's just what they deserve!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707561" id2="17" version="1065353216">So the aliens developed a taste for Imperial blood. I know just the cure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707561" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take it back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, my lord. Only Sith can bring such brutal degenerates in line!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707564" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time these aliens taste Imperial justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707564" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707565" id2="17" version="1065353216">These criminals are bloodthirsty lunatics. Discipline's just what they need!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707567" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bringing these aliens in line will cost you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707567" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could help, for a price.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707568" id2="17" version="1065353216">If credits will bury them, so be it. But be careful. Belsavis twisted those aliens into brutal lunatics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707570" id2="17" version="1065353216">A child could see the danger of unleashing hordes of frenzied aliens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707570" id2="17" version="1065353216">You screwed up, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707571" id2="17" version="1065353216">I--I followed Commander Calum's orders exactly. Still--this can be fixed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't shed a tear over them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707574" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right. But my entire outfit... gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707576" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew these aliens were brutal--that's why we released them. But they've crossed a line!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Carve up their top gangs and make the aliens fear us. Then we'll be able to evacuate the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707579" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to show them who's in charge. Carve up their most aggressive gangs, and you'll give the alien filth a reason to fear us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707580" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay here and secure the outpost. Leave the prisoners to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707580" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll thin out the aliens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch an expert at work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. Gun for the Gamorreans, Anomids and Gand. They're the fiercest scum of the bunch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kill enough members of each gang, and they'll learn to respect the Empire!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count me out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please reconsider. We can't free the Dread Masters until this wing's secure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707588" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't let this alien scum run us out. Let me know if you change your mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Operations Group Four has everything under control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="755766" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose someone has to.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
