<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>52</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/rishi/hub_1/making_a_mark/shared/holoterminal.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133010" id2="17" version="1065353216">The job's done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent news, but it's only our first step.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133012" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of the Nova Blades mentioned a slave camp. Somewhere remote. We should strike there next.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1133012" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a suggestion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good call, actually. I ran across some chatter about that place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone called Margok is in charge of the Nova Blades. He'll get us closer to the Revanites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1133015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's go after Margok.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, he will--but he's safely inside his headquarters. We must set his operations into a state of disarray, send his forces scattering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you have something in mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1133018" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's next?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133019" id2="17" version="1065353216">I intercepted some chatter about a slave camp--well, more like a slave island.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133020" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard one of their lieutenants mention it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133021" id2="17" version="1065353216">Basically, anyone in Raider's Cove who doesn't give the Nova Blades a slice of their action or whatever gets locked away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some get put into hazardous labor--like mining--but most are sold as slaves to visitors from offworld. It's a lucrative business for the Blades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1133024" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mean &quot;was&quot; lucrative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133025" id2="17" version="1065353216">You got that right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me the coordinates and I'll get started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1133027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where is the camp?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133028" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not that simple; we don't actually know where the slave island is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133030" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, just like their supply cache, if I destroy the assets they're left with nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1133030" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't sell a dead slave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoa--if you're suggesting what I think you are...!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133033" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you said yourself, these slaves are assets. They're also enemies of the Nova Blades, which makes them all the more valuable to us alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133035" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have to slip in with one of the Nova Blades' cargo shipments. I'm sure the island's heavily guarded, so try not to get killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133041" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe Theron means to say he's concerned for your safety--as am I. May the Force serve you well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron, do you read me? The supply cache has been destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron? Our task is complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc to base. Objective complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey there. I don't know if you guys have heard, but the Red Hulls just completely trashed a Nova Blade supply cache.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134913" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand the main suspect is being described as &quot;skilled and extremely attractive.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134916" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe one more assault on the Nova Blades' holdings should be enough to solidify our &quot;pirate feud&quot; and disguise our true goal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134917" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of the Blades mentioned a slave camp. Do you know anything about it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134918" id2="17" version="1065353216">We do. You remember me saying that the Nova Blades basically run things around here? For the most part, they're pretty hands-off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134920" id2="17" version="1065353216">But if someone stands up to them, or fails to pay their &quot;fees&quot; to live here? The Blades grab them and ship them off to the slave camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134922" id2="17" version="1065353216">The slaves are a substantial part of the Nova Blades' income, both through their labor in hazardous mines and as merchandise for offworld slave traders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134924" id2="17" version="1065353216">According to our information, the slaves are kept on a remote island under heavy guard. Do you think you can manage to free them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134925" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one should have to suffer in slavery. I'll take care of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134925" id2="17" version="1065353216">It would be my pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134926" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really aren't like other Sith, are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134926" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] An interesting suggestion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134927" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like to think I'm my own woman.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this some kind of trick?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith do not free slaves. They kill them, or capture them for their own use. What's your game here, Lana?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134932" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're joking. A Sith who wants to free slaves? You expect me to believe that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134933" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is not some kind of elaborate deception. Freeing them contributes to our goals. It's that simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since we don't know the island's exact coordinates, your best bet is to stow away in one of the shipping containers the Nova Blades take out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you reach the slave camp, you can catch them by surprise, break up the security, and free as many as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134939" id2="17" version="1065353216">All in a day's work for a noble Jedi, yes?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just another day for the hero of Havoc Squad, yes?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134941" id2="17" version="1065353216">Certainly nothing a daring star pilot can't handle, yes?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
