<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>94</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/rishi/hub_1/making_a_mark/shared/jakarro.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132891" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must be the one Lord Beniko and Agent Shan have brought to assist us!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop calling her Lord, droid! You know she hates that!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132895" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm showing respect, Jakarro. You could learn to do the same once in a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132897" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you could learn to properly introduce us!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132899" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? Oh--you are now in the presence of renowned illicit-transport specialist Jakarro. I am his translator, Ceetoo Deefour.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132901" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are here under the direction of Lord--of Miss Beniko and Agent Shan--to assist you in your exciting campaign against the Nova Blades!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132902" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, then--what are we waiting for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get started.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132903" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have been waiting for you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132905" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jakarro says he is pleased to get things underway!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132906" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you, local pirates or something?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132906" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're their source?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not compare me to the sorry pirates on this backwater dump!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jakarro wishes me to convey that we do not, in fact, live here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132910" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have me confused with someone who needs assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132910" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132911" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you have me confused with a Wookiee who cares!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132913" id2="17" version="1065353216">While Jakarro recognizes your obvious prowess, he would nevertheless prefer to lend a hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132914" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understood every word he said.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank goodness! I hate having to reword his every foul utterance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132917" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch it, droid! I can still drop what is left of you into an active volcano!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132919" id2="17" version="1065353216">What Jakarro lacks in manners, he makes up for in heart, and he would very much like revenge on the Revanites, who hired and then betrayed him. As would I.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132921" id2="17" version="1065353216">To that end, we plan to start by taking apart the Revanites' allies by firing from Jakarro's ship on the targets of your choosing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132924" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's you! It's really you! I can hardly believe my optical circuits!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jakarro and Deefour. I was hoping I hadn't seen the last of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to see you two.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132926" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is good to see you, too, Sith!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Rishi, my lord. Not exactly the paradise we'd hoped it would be....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132930" id2="17" version="1065353216">The chumps who pass for pirates in this place are a joke! I like the bird ones, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132932" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is good to see you, too, bounty hunter!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132934" id2="17" version="1065353216">And may I thank you for not taking advantage of yet another bounty on our heads.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132936" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could make some serious credits if any of the chumps who pass for pirates in this place have markers on them! Easy pickings!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132938" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is good to see you, too, spy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, just broadcast it, why don't you! Big lug. Do you not know what &quot;undercover&quot; means?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132942" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would not worry--the pirates here barely understand anything about anything!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132944" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had a feeling Lana and Theron were talking about you when they said they had help. A bad feeling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132944" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not you two....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always willing to put down others--I like you! The chumps who pass for pirates in this place, on the other hand....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132947" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jakarro, I don't think I can take any more flapping out of that synthesized yap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132947" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut him up.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132948" id2="17" version="1065353216">The droid keeps me from becoming too relaxed on this boring backwater. He stays on!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132950" id2="17" version="1065353216">All bluster aside, this planet's inhabitants are not to be trifled with. The Nova Blades in particular are a powerful and organized group.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132952" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is why we intend to depower and disorganize them by firing from Jakarro's ship on the targets of your choosing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132953" id2="17" version="1065353216">They see me causing trouble and word gets out that the Howling Tempest Gang is coming for the Nova Blades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132953" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132954" id2="17" version="1065353216">Precisely! It's nice to not have to explain everything for a change.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch it, droid!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132958" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we're using a ship, we could take out their entire depot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why be so precise?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132959" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you are to be implicated as the perpetrator of these acts, you must be seen flagging their assets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132961" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you miss, you make me look bad. Don't miss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't you dare fail me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132962" id2="17" version="1065353216">With your guidance, we couldn't possibly miss!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here. The sooner we finish making a mark with the Nova Blades, the sooner we can get at the Revanites!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132966" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd wish you good luck if I thought you'd need it. We'll keep in touch!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1134451" id2="17" version="1065353216">At last! You should know by now that it isn't wise to keep the mighty Jakarro waiting!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Must you complain so loudly, master? There could be ruthless pirates or hungry wildlife all around us! Hearing us! Smelling us!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134454" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to see you're still helping us out. We need all the allies we can get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134454" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to see you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1134455" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got that right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134457" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should watch out for cannibals, too. Apparently that's actually a problem around here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch out for cannibals, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134458" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, I think I'm safe on that account, at least. Hopefully.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134460" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was sure that Theron and Lana would have gotten rid of you by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not you two again.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1134461" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha! They would be long dead without my wisdom to guide them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134463" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is my life....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1134467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron and Lana got the little Jedi they were hoping for! Now we can finally get to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1134469" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must be the soldier. From all of Theron and Lana's talk, I thought you'd be taller at least.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1134471" id2="17" version="1065353216">At last, a star captain of some reputation! The rest of this planet's scum are amateurs at best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Allow me to present my master, the noted transport specialist Jakarro! And I am Ceetoo-Deefour, former translator to her majesty, Queen--</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1134475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut up, droid! Nobody cares about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134476" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're pretty short on allies right now. I'll be glad to have your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pleasure to meet you both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134477" id2="17" version="1065353216">You see, Jakarro? There are people with manners on this planet after all!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134479" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you two get mixed up in all of this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why help us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134480" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Revanites hired us for a job, then betrayed, tortured, and threatened to kill us!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134481" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that why you're... in pieces?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1134482" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, that was for speaking out of turn. Always.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1134484" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to see the Revanites ruined as much as you and your other tiny friends do. Now can we get on with it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134485" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're an... interesting pair.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134485" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't even know what to say.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134486" id2="17" version="1065353216">How kind of you!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1134488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, are we going to destroy these Revanite-loving scum-eaters, or are we going to stand out in the heat all day?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron and Lana said you'd have a plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1134490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. You will mark targets in the supply cache. I will be circling in my ship nearby. When a target is marked, I will blast it to bits!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134492" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mean... we don't have to go charging in face-first this time? We're staying in the ship? Oh, thank you master, thank you!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1134494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quit blubbering, droid! Don't forget the rest!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, yes... please make sure it's clear that this was the work of the Red Hulls. We need to keep up appearances, after all!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well. Let's get started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood. Ready to move?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure thing. You two ready?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1134500" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes! Good hunting!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
