<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>53</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/world/republic/survivor/cedin_kavil.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666977" id2="17" version="1065353216">The doctors say they should be able to clear up his head wound. He'll be right as rain in no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666978" id2="17" version="1065353216">You there. Where's my ship? Need to get back up there. Battle won't win itself, you know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666980" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh, the battle? Oh--I see! The Battle of Hoth. Of course. Uh... that's fine. Let's get you checked up first. All right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for taking me seriously and going out there. Even though he does seem a bit... confused.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="666983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad I could help out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666984" id2="17" version="1065353216">He probably sustained a head wound when his ship went down. And he's been out there a long time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="666984" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not surprising.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666985" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose. He's with us now, though. That's the main thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="666987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey--I'm the best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems like a lot of trouble for one man, I know, but he's a hero. He deserved more than being left to freeze to death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666992" id2="17" version="1065353216">The medics will check him out. You never know--he might actually fight again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666994" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should hurry. The reports say a fierce storm is on its way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you the group giving the Empire a hard time? I was told you might pass through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi! Finally! I was told you might pass through the outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain. I was told you might pass through, but I was starting to lose hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me. Are you the freelancer who's been giving the Empire a hard time?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank the stars! I was told you might pass through the outpost, but I was beginning to lose hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667007" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Cedin Kavil--communications officer. I need your help to rescue a war hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pilot First Class Darkil Aro was shot down during the Battle of Hoth. He's been lost for years out there in the wastelands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667010" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did this pilot manage to stay alive? This is one of the harshest planets in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667010" id2="17" version="1065353216">And he survived?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667011" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't say I know his name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who was he?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rescuing soldiers isn't really my job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, my mission is urgent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darkil is no ordinary soldier. He single-handedly took down an Imperial battle cruiser. Saved us from losing the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667015" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been doing a grid-by-grid search of the ice fields in my spare time, searching for wreckage. It's... sort of a hobby.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667017" id2="17" version="1065353216">I located an emergency beacon broadcasting Darkil's digital tag and active life signs. I've told Command, but they say we can't spare the resources.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667018" id2="17" version="1065353216">It does sound like he might still be alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667018" id2="17" version="1065353216">You might be onto something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667019" id2="17" version="1065353216">He is. And we need to bring him back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667021" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're putting a lot of effort into this. Is he family?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667021" id2="17" version="1065353216">This seems... personal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667022" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. My father was a pilot. Killed in action. I... didn't have the skills to follow him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667024" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a lot of effort for one man, no matter how special you think he is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Command is right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667025" id2="17" version="1065353216">No--you're wrong!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667027" id2="17" version="1065353216">This man destroyed an enemy no one else could, and we left him on this planet for years... we owe it to him to attempt a rescue!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667028" id2="17" version="1065353216">This pilot deserves full honors for taking part in that battle. I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667028" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your words are wise, Cedin. This pilot is an example to us all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667029" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667030" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darkil deserves every effort to find him. No matter what Command says, I'll rescue this pilot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667030" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count me in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667031" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've spent my fair share of time chasing credits. Guess I can help someone else out for a change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667031" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667032" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, fine. I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you! If I had even half the skills of my father, I'd be out there with you. But... I guess you help out where you can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here are the coordinates. Good luck, and be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't help. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I'm sorry for wasting your time. I suppose he'll just have to stay out in the wastelands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please--don't disturb me. I'm collating some search data.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
