<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>56</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/war_world/quesh/bronze/imperial/adrenal_appropriation/captain_franges.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71436" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those adrenals were more than satisfactory, I--our troops will benefit greatly from their synthesis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71437" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have the formula samples? Oh, please tell me you have them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71438" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold on, this isn't free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71440" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I--uh....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71442" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't expect anything else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, yes, next time--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here. My command's entire recreational spending allocation. Please excuse me, I--I should really see to securing these.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71447" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would advise capturing those adrenals before the Republic moves them, or worse, uses them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finding Quesh to your liking? It's an acquired locale.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71450" id2="17" version="1065353216">If your group is on a tour of the facilities, you should sample what luxuries this planet has to offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71451" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, may I suggest sampling what luxuries this planet has to offer while you're here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71452" id2="17" version="1065353216">My sole luxury here will be grinding the Republic under my heel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71452" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not here for pleasures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent, my lord. I know just the place where you can do just that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71455" id2="17" version="1065353216">How very helpful. What do you recommend?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71455" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intelligence taking an interest in what this planet has to offer? If you don't mind mixing business with pleasure, I can make some recommendations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71457" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're suggesting dereliction of duty, that's an executable offense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71457" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're setting a poor example.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71458" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are certain fringe benefits to being stationed on a Hutt-controlled planet; you should try the local fare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71459" id2="17" version="1065353216">I avoid letting the Hutts get their hooks in me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spice isn't my thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71460" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not talking about anything so crude as spice. Quesh is the new center of the galaxy's adrenal industry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, point the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71463" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I'll pass.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71464" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not suggesting anything against regulations, of course, it's just that Quesh now produces the highest grade adrenals and stims in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71466" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can find all the latest adrenal formulas available right here in our civilian markets... but, if you're interested in something truly cutting-edge....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71468" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've heard of the Three Families? The rebellious Hutts who've chosen to ally with the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fill me in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71472" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Three Families broke all ties with the Hutt Cartel to corner the market on adrenals. They've allied with the Republic for protection.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spit it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71475" id2="17" version="1065353216">We intercepted a communication from the Three Families indicating that they've moved an experimental formula to Attis Station for final testing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71477" id2="17" version="1065353216">Industry rumors about the formula's effects are nothing short of miraculous. Heightened awareness, near immunity to fatigue or exertion, mild euphoria. It's perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71479" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to acquire some samples for synthesis, to distribute it among our troops, after I've tested its safety, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71480" id2="17" version="1065353216">These delusions of grandeur pale before the power of the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71480" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a crutch for the weak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71481" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, my lord, but it would bestow impressive benefits to those of us who lack your natural ability.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71483" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd be interested in sampling this wonder of yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds worth a try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71484" id2="17" version="1065353216">As would I, my lord, and its impact as a force multiplier would be astronomical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71486" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could look into getting this formula, if it's worth something to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you making an offer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, it most definitely is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Taking it would deprive the enemy of a combat enhancement if nothing else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71489" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a dangerous advantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71490" id2="17" version="1065353216">My thoughts exactly. If the Republic were to distribute this to their local forces, they'd have an army of supersoldiers at their disposal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71492" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't see us capturing the formula through conventional assault. The army would be most appreciative if you acquired this formula for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, fine, I'll handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71495" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find Attis Station nearby. It's a Republic research facility disguised as a simple outpost, so it'll be better protected than it appears.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Liar. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find someone else to feed your habit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71500" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ahem, merely a suggestion. If I may be of service, I'll be here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugh, these stims my adjutant brought are absolute rubbish.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
