<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>44</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/bronze/republic/frozen_assets/aza_gundo.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lot easier for Organa to fight without worrying about those CryoBan weapons. Thanks again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318025" id2="17" version="1065353216">CryoBan weapons. Those Thul soldiers are empty-handed now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dead, too, from what I hear. Good work. Not like they were going to hand them over by asking nicely.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318028" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make sure Organa knows what you did. And these'll go in the first trash compactor I find.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318030" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better get moving. House Thul keeps those CryoBan weapons, and we'll all end up icicles.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318033" id2="17" version="1065353216">First squad I've seen around here not fighting for their lives. Got a minute?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait. There's no kind of tech that could take a Jedi down. Could use your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant. Glad to see one officer not limping back from the field. Need help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey there, Captain. How'd you like to stiff one of your own for a good cause?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Name's Aza. Or Private Gundo, if you prefer. On guard for House Organa with the rest of the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318043" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got word House Thul is smuggling in CryoBan weapons. Very illegal. Freeze you in three seconds flat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't count on House Thul for a fair fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Typical of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318045" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Organa could do with a little less fairness. But they want a clean battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318047" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope no one discovered this the hard way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318047" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds painful.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318048" id2="17" version="1065353216">First few died from shock. Rest are still waiting to get the feeling back in their toes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318050" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't seen this technology on the battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318050" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is news to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318051" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Thul victory's still not a sure thing. Probably saving it for the big offensive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sometimes fighting dirty's the only way to win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318053" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like their style.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318054" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not to House Organa. They want a clean, honest battlefield. Good luck with that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318056" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Got word&quot; from who?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318057" id2="17" version="1065353216">Used to run with a bad crowd. But I'm trying to go legit, with the Republic, you follow?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318059" id2="17" version="1065353216">So tell House Organa.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Little busy with the war and all. Few men the Republic can spare don't even get close.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318062" id2="17" version="1065353216">We squashed the smuggling ring a few days ago. But House Thul's got plenty of CryoBan weapons already.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318064" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't destroy what's left, they'll keep moving in on Organa territory, one frozen guard at a time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318065" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to help, if I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318066" id2="17" version="1065353216">These weapons could give House Organa the edge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318066" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why destroy them?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too unstable. Any shot could backfire, take out the whole squad. Thul will risk that. We won't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318069" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't want to be frozen.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318070" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sympathize, but if we don't handle this now, it's only going to get worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318072" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lot of the frozen come back from the Vinerium. Best lead we have on where to find the CryoBan weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318073" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Vinerium?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Royal farmland for the royal wine. Valuable. Good place to hide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318076" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're lucky I'm here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Long as you don't come back in a block of ice, I'll be impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318079" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bring me those CryoBan weapons quick. Thul doesn't need another edge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318081" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too busy. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine Republic you are. Makes a man wonder which side you're on.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="318084" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't talk to you now. I'm here on official Republic business.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
