<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>20</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/uprisings/terminal/veteran.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220466" id2="17" version="1065353216">A crisis has erupted on Tatooine. The notorious Dust Viper gang has stolen the security plans to the Alliance base on Odessen--and they're selling them to the highest bidder.

No one has ever survived a mission into Dust Viper territory, but we can't risk that data going public. Breach the Vipers' compound, neutralize their cutthroat leader, and secure the Alliance data before it's too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220470" id2="17" version="1065353216">A crisis has erupted on Tatooine. The notorious Dust Viper gang has stolen the security plans to the Alliance base on Odessen--and they're selling them to the highest bidder.

No one has ever survived a mission into Dust Viper territory, but we can't risk that data going public. Breach the Vipers' compound, neutralize their cutthroat leader, and secure the Alliance data before it's too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Working from a hidden space station lab, a rogue group of Republic scientists led by Doctor Alirra Semhess has developed an experimental adrenal. The adrenal, code named RS-33, radically augments a subject's strength and agility at the expense of mental faculties.

Left unchecked, Doctor Semhess and her colleagues could mass-produce RS-33 and create an army of unstoppable abominations to wreak havoc across the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Working from a hidden space station lab, a rogue group of Republic scientists led by Doctor Alirra Semhess has developed an experimental adrenal. The adrenal, code named RS-33, radically augments a subject's strength and agility at the expense of mental faculties.

Left unchecked, Doctor Semhess and her colleagues could mass-produce RS-33 and create an army of unstoppable abominations to wreak havoc across the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220480" id2="17" version="1065353216">A rogue faction of Sith Empire defectors is targeting--and destroying--the Alliance's most vulnerable outposts. If allowed to continue, these dissidents will shatter the very foundation of the Alliance.

They operate out of Vanguard Station, under the command of Sith Lord Anril and Major Korven--a former Cipher agent. Only an elite strike team can infiltrate the station. Gather your squad, and show our enemies that the Alliance stands by its own.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220487" id2="17" version="1065353216">A rogue faction of Sith Empire defectors is targeting--and destroying--the Alliance's most vulnerable outposts. If allowed to continue, these dissidents will shatter the very foundation of the Alliance.

They operate out of Vanguard Station, under the command of Sith Lord Anril and Major Korven--a former Cipher agent. Only an elite strike team can infiltrate the station. Gather your squad, and show our enemies that the Alliance stands by its own.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220489" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Crimson Fang, a previously unknown criminal organization, recently took Port Nowhere by force. They intend to use the moving space station as a base of operations for their illicit activities. 

Reports indicate the Crimson Fang have acquired a cache of powerful weapons that are being stored in Port Nowhere's cargo hold. Assemble a team and liberate Port Nowhere before the Crimson Fang unleash destruction upon the entire region.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220495" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Crimson Fang, a previously unknown criminal organization, recently took Port Nowhere by force. They intend to use the moving space station as a base of operations for their illicit activities. 

Reports indicate the Crimson Fang have acquired a cache of powerful weapons that are being stored in Port Nowhere's cargo hold. Assemble a team and liberate Port Nowhere before the Crimson Fang unleash destruction upon the entire region.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rogue Coruscant security agents are plotting a false flag terrorist operation. They intend to attack the Senate Tower and plant false evidence in the hopes of inciting the Republic to war against the Alliance.

Intel has traced the mastermind behind the plan--Commander Kallin, a former Republic veteran--to a hidden base inside The Works on Coruscant's lower level.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rogue Coruscant security agents are plotting a false flag terrorist operation. They intend to attack the Senate Tower and plant false evidence in the hopes of inciting the Republic to war against the Alliance.

Intel has traced the mastermind behind the plan--Commander Kallin, a former Republic veteran--to a hidden base inside The Works on Coruscant's lower level.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220517" id2="17" version="1065353216">The infamous White Maw pirates are repurposing Imperial and Republic artillery to raid Outer Rim territories. Under the leadership of a fearsome Houk name Droub, they have taken control of a lava works factory on Hoth to construct chilling war machines.

If left unchecked, this group will expand into Alliance territory. Secure the Outer Rim territories by rounding up a team and shutting down White Maw operations.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220524" id2="17" version="1065353216">The infamous White Maw pirates are repurposing Imperial and Republic artillery to raid Outer Rim territories. Under the leadership of a fearsome Houk name Droub, they have taken control of a lava works factory on Hoth to construct chilling war machines.

If left unchecked, this group will expand into Alliance territory. Secure the Outer Rim territories by rounding up a team and shutting down White Maw operations.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi Master Adelade is trying to awaken a dangerous abomination that has hibernated beneath the surface of Makeb for millennia. No records exist of this monstrosity, known only as Gethul. But if the creature awakes, it may be strong enough to destabilize Makeb's core and obliterate the planet.

Infiltrate the underground tunnel, secure explosives, and deliver the payload to Gethul's lair. Only then can you destroy the monstrosity--and save Makeb from Adelade's deranged plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi Master Adelade is trying to awaken a dangerous abomination that has hibernated beneath the surface of Makeb for millennia. No records exist of this monstrosity, known only as Gethul. But if the creature awakes, it may be strong enough to destabilize Makeb's core and obliterate the planet.

Infiltrate the underground tunnel, secure explosives, and deliver the payload to Gethul's lair. Only then can you destroy the monstrosity--and save Makeb from Adelade's deranged plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220533" id2="17" version="1065353216">A splinter group of ex-Imperials, led by Sith Lords Zanisk and Adacin, has taken over an old separatist base on Ord Mantell. The group has been launching attacks on nearby systems loyal to the Alliance, threatening the stability of the entire region.

Their base is heavily defended against a full-scale assault, but Alliance Intelligence suggests that a small, elite group may have better luck. Assemble your team and dismantle the uprising. Expect heavy resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220539" id2="17" version="1065353216">A splinter group of ex-Imperials, led by Sith Lords Zanisk and Adacin, has taken over an old separatist base on Ord Mantell. The group has been launching attacks on nearby systems loyal to the Alliance, threatening the stability of the entire region.

Their base is heavily defended against a full-scale assault, but Alliance Intelligence suggests that a small, elite group may have better luck. Assemble your team and dismantle the uprising. Expect heavy resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deserters from the Zakuulan military were tracked to Rakata Prime. Under the leadership of former Battalion Commander Tassar, they are building a new and improved Star Fortress.

Infiltrate their surface camp and eliminate Commander Tassar before her operations threaten galactic security.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deserters from the Zakuulan military were tracked to Rakata Prime. Under the leadership of former Battalion Commander Tassar, they are building a new and improved Star Fortress.

Infiltrate their surface camp and eliminate Commander Tassar before her operations threaten galactic security.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic loyalists under the command of General Amos Rike have displaced Alliance forces on Denova and seized control of the baradium mines. Efforts to reclaim the mines have been thwarted by Republic artillery bombarding the &quot;no man's land&quot; between the Alliance beachhead and the central processing facility. 

But where an army fails, a small team could succeed in navigating the battlefield trenches and taking out the Republic defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220555" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic loyalists under the command of General Amos Rike have displaced Alliance forces on Denova and seized control of the baradium mines. Efforts to reclaim the mines have been thwarted by Republic artillery bombarding the &quot;no man's land&quot; between the Alliance beachhead and the central processing facility. 

But where an army fails, a small team could succeed in navigating the battlefield trenches and taking out the Republic defenses.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
