<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>182</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x2/raid/explosive_conflict/empire/moff_altiss.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005588" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've reviewed the field reports. Kephess and his followers were a surprisingly formidable army. It took all of your combined resources to defeat them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005590" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've reviewed the field reports. Kephess was a surprisingly formidable enemy. Even you, with all your power, struggled to defeat him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005592" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it possible there was some truth to Colonel Grezor's ravings? Did you find any sign of the mysterious presence he spoke of on Denova?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kephess was not attuned to the Force, yet I sensed the dark side emanating from him. He was being driven by a sinister hand. Someone called &quot;the masters.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005593" id2="17" version="1065353216">I felt something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005594" id2="17" version="1065353216">You felt the presence of the dark side? Is it possible these &quot;masters&quot; are a group of rogue Sith?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005596" id2="17" version="1065353216">I kept hearing the troops talk about &quot;the masters.&quot; Not sure who they meant, but it was pretty clear the Trandoshan was just hired muscle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kephess wasn't in charge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005597" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Trandoshan didn't plan this. Somebody more subtle was calling the shots. The soldiers called them &quot;the masters.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kephess wasn't in charge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005598" id2="17" version="1065353216">If these &quot;masters&quot; were strong enough to manipulate Kephess, we need to find out who they are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before, you said Grezor's claims were just an excuse to cover up his incompetence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005600" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you hated Grezor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you blame me for not having faith in a Nautolan? I thought Kephess was nothing but an opportunistic mercenary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005603" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the Trandoshan was more dangerous than I imagined. Obviously there's more to this than meets the eye.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005605" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard mention of &quot;the masters&quot;; Kephess may have answered to them. But if they exist, they didn't reveal themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005605" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're jumping at shadows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not surprising, my lord. Who would dare to openly challenge the Emperor's Wrath?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kephess's soldiers spoke of &quot;the masters,&quot; but weak minds are easily manipulated. I found no evidence of their existence on Denova.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005608" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're jumping at shadows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005609" id2="17" version="1065353216">They may have fled when you arrived, my lord. They might prefer to strike from the shadows rather than reveal themselves to the Dark Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heard the troops talking about &quot;the masters,&quot; but I never saw them. As far as I'm concerned, Kephess was running the show.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005611" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're jumping at shadows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005612" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose that's possible. Could be these &quot;masters&quot; don't even exist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Misinformation and rumors are powerful weapons. The troops spoke of &quot;the masters,&quot; but I found no evidence of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005614" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're jumping at shadows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting theory. Kephess could have lured our troops over by inventing these mysterious &quot;masters.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insects interfere. They do not understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005621" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are the six. The Dread Masters. Heed our warning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005622" id2="17" version="1065353216">I helped you escape from the Republic prison on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005622" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remember you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imprisoned, our power faded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now we are free. Now we are strong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005627" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters? Am I supposed to know that name?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005628" id2="17" version="1065353216">In time, all will know our name. The galaxy will bow to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005630" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you threatening me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005630" id2="17" version="1065353216">What warning?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005631" id2="17" version="1065353216">The minds on Denova were weak. Easily manipulated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005633" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are more difficult to control. But no more difficult to destroy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you the reason our soldiers defected and Kephess betrayed the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005635" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were on Denova?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Denova was a test. Weak minds twisted and turned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005638" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard of you. The ancient Sith prophets. Masters of terror and fear. But you're on our side--we all serve the Emperor!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005640" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor was strong. He spoke to us. Guided us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now the Emperor is quiet. None who remain are worthy of our loyalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005643" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor has gone silent before. Yet he always comes back. Remember that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005643" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor will return.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005644" id2="17" version="1065353216">I serve on the Dark Council. Any allegiance you had to the Emperor you now owe to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005644" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should answer to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005645" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got a pretty high opinion of yourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005645" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a little arrogant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005646" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are the Dread Masters. You are nothing to us. We serve a higher purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005648" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you may be underestimating those of us who are still around. The Empire is still strong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005648" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's kind of insulting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005649" id2="17" version="1065353216">We care nothing for the Emperor or the Empire now. We serve a higher purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this some kind of power grab? With the Emperor gone, you think you can just seize his throne?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005651" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you're taking over?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005652" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor's throne means nothing to us. We are driven by a greater purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005654" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am the Emperor's Wrath. If you've turned against the Empire, then I will destroy you--just like I destroyed Kephess!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005654" id2="17" version="1065353216">You underestimate me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your threats would be more effective if you had the courage to deliver them face-to-face.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005655" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't scare me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005656" id2="17" version="1065353216">You might have been able to manipulate Kephess and his soldiers, but you didn't even have the guts to face me in person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005656" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't scare me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005657" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever you were trying on Denova failed. This... meeting... is a sign of desperation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005657" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bold talk. But it's only talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your victory here is insignificant. We are driven by a higher purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kephess was our tool. Our vessel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005662" id2="17" version="1065353216">The vessel is damaged. It can be repaired.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kephess is ours. Heed this warning. Do not interfere again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005668" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters have spoken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005672" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have any idea how I'm going to explain this in my report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without the Emperor to keep them in check, the Dread Masters have gone rogue. Easy enough to understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep it simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005674" id2="17" version="1065353216">But what does it mean? As far as I know, they have no followers, no army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005676" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters manipulated the minds of our soldiers on Denova and turned them against us. Making that public could cause a panic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't. Keep it quiet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good point. But I still don't understand why they did it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005679" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't even guess what they're up to. They obviously don't care about the galactic war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me everything you know about the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005681" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need more intel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005682" id2="17" version="1065353216">There isn't much. They're six ancient Sith Lords the Republic imprisoned on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005684" id2="17" version="1065353216">After we broke them loose, they just sort of disappeared. I can't even imagine what they're after.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wouldn't surprise me if they just disappeared again. Like nightmares when you wake up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005687" id2="17" version="1065353216">They might go into hiding for a while, but they're obviously planning something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005687" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eventually they'll be back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005688" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll send this up the chain of command, but unless the Dread Masters strike somewhere else, I doubt we'll find them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005690" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've already got our hands full with the Republic. We can't afford to fight a war with the Dread Masters right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005690" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hopefully, we won't have to. I'll send this up the chain of command, but I doubt anything's going to happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005693" id2="17" version="1065353216">We hit them pretty hard here on Denova. It may take them a long time to recover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005693" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think they're scared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005694" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're right. Because right now, we don't have any way to even track them down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005696" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Grand Moffs aren't going to spend resources on an enemy we can't see. Not with the Republic breathing down our necks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005698" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least we've got the advantage on Denova now, thanks to you. I'll be sure to mention that in my report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Moff Altiss at your service, my lord. I hope the Emperor's Wrath can guide us back to our former glory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005706" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord. I am Moff Altiss. Thank you for coming; perhaps a member of the Dark Council can restore us to our past glory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005708" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Moff Altiss. I know you have done much for the Empire, though it pains me to know we rely on mercenaries for help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005710" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Moff Altiss. Normally I despise clandestine operatives, but your service record is extraordinary. No doubt your classified missions are even more impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005712" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Moff Altiss. You have served the Empire well in the past; now I must ask for your aid again... though it pains me to do so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005714" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Moff Altiss. I never imagined my call for aid would attract such important and powerful people. Perhaps that speaks to what the Empire has become.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005716" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once, this operation would have been executed with precision. Our failure on Denova shows how far the Empire has fallen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005717" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful, Moff Altiss. Your words are close to treason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005717" id2="17" version="1065353216">You dare insult the Empire?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005718" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, I only desire to restore the Empire to its past glory. But we need Denova--the planet is rich with baradium, a valuable explosive ore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005720" id2="17" version="1065353216">The greatest threat to the Empire comes from within. We cannot allow ourselves to be fractured. As a Moff, you should understand this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005720" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must not say such things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005721" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trust the Dark Council will lead us to victory, my lord. But we need Denova--the planet is rich with baradium, a valuable explosive ore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005723" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't pay me if you're wiped out. If the Empire keeps losing to the Republic, I might have to switch sides.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005723" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree. You're slipping.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005724" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not if we can claim Denova. The planet is rich with baradium, a valuable explosive ore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005726" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should probably keep your doubts about the Empire to yourself. Unless you want to be arrested for treason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005726" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't say that out loud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. I'm speaking out of turn. Our focus must be on securing Denova. The planet is rich with baradium, a valuable explosive ore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Struggle does not show weakness. Only failure. And I will not allow the Empire to fail on Denova.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005729" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire is still strong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005730" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have faith you will bring us victory on Denova, my lord. The planet is rich with a valuable explosive ore called baradium.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005732" id2="17" version="1065353216">A handful of strategic retreats can be the prelude to a prolonged advance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005732" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do not see the whole plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005733" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, I did not mean to question the action of the Dark Council. But we need Denova--the planet is rich with baradium, a valuable explosive ore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005735" id2="17" version="1065353216">This war is taking a toll on both sides. We need to take advantage of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005735" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're holding our own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Taking Denova would be an excellent way to demoralize our enemy--the planet is rich in baradium, a valuable explosive ore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005738" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you ran into a bit of a roadblock. No big deal. That's why you call me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005738" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not that bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005739" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire is lucky to have such a powerful ally. We need Denova--the planet is rich with baradium, a valuable explosive ore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your droid wouldn't give me any details about this mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005741" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's happening on Denova?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just below the planet's surface are massive deposits of baradium, a powerful and versatile weapons-grade explosive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005744" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic hired Kephess, a legendary Trandoshan warlord, to secure the world. We sent in Colonel Grezor, a Nautolan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grezor is a product of the reformations enacted after Malgus's failed rebellion. He was rapidly promoted to see if lesser species can handle the rigors of command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like Colonel Grezor lacked both the experience and the skill for a mission like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005747" id2="17" version="1065353216">No wonder things went bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005748" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly! Before the reformations, he would never have been given this command. Now we must pay the price for his failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005750" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you're prejudiced against Grezor's kind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005750" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't like Nautolans?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005751" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Nautolans are a lesser species, unworthy of leading Imperial troops. Grezor's failure proves it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005753" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume the Trandoshan made short work of Colonel Grezor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005753" id2="17" version="1065353216">So Kephess killed him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005754" id2="17" version="1065353216">A simple defeat on the battlefield would have been easy enough to clean up. But Grezor's failure was far worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kephess betrayed the Republic and declared himself ruler of Denova. Our troops on the surface defected, and swore loyalty to the Trandoshan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005758" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's seized the baradium supplies, offering them for sale to the highest bidder. No word on Grezor's fate, but we suspect he--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Command, do you copy? This is Colonel Grezor. We're pinned down--we need reinforcements!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful. For all we know, Grezor is working for Kephess now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005761" id2="17" version="1065353216">This could be a trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005762" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree. He's either a traitor or completely incompetent. Hard to say which is worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005764" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grezor can give us an update on the situation on the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005764" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need a status report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005765" id2="17" version="1065353216">If a simple update isn't too much for him to handle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grezor's still alive. Maybe he's not as incompetent as you thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess you underestimated him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005768" id2="17" version="1065353216">His survival hardly makes the mission a success.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005770" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel Grezor, this is Moff Altiss. We need your field report before we decide on a course of action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005772" id2="17" version="1065353216">My field report? We're getting slaughtered! Me and a few loyal officers have been on the run ever since the troops defected. Get us out of here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005774" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you mad, Colonel? You're either a traitor or a failure. Either way, we should leave you here to rot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005776" id2="17" version="1065353216">It wasn't just Kephess and his war beasts, Moff Altiss. There's something else down here. A... a presence. That's what broke the morale of our troops!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005777" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't try to blame some mysterious presence for your failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005777" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're making excuses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Believe whatever you want, but something was making the soldiers nervous. They abandoned their posts, and Kephess broke our ranks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005780" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you talking about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005780" id2="17" version="1065353216">A presence?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005781" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't really explain it. But we all felt it. It made the soldiers nervous. They abandoned their posts, and Kephess broke our ranks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005783" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every second we spend discussing this gives Kephess more time to reinforce his position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005783" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're wasting time, Altiss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005784" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know how this sounds. But whatever you think of me, you have to get my officers out of here. We're running out of time!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005786" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've locked onto Colonel Grezor's position. I can clear out the area with an orbital bombardment to make a secure landing zone for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel Grezor is of no further use to us. Give the order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Begin the bombardment now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005788" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? No!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005790" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fleet commanders, this is Moff Altiss. Lock onto these surface coordinates and fire at will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005794" id2="17" version="1065353216">The orbital strike has secured the landing area perimeter. A shuttle will take you to the surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make sure the colonel gets out alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Evacuate Grezor first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005797" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you wish, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make sure the colonel gets out alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Evacuate Grezor first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005800" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose the Nautolan deserves a military hearing before we decide his fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005802" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel Grezor, prepare for evacuation. A shuttle is on its way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grezor and his men are safe. The landing area perimeter is secured. A shuttle will take you down to the surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find Kephess and destroy him. The Trandoshan's death will allow us to take control of Denova.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1032600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Evacuate Grezor first.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
