<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>30</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x2/raid/explosive_conflict/empire/n4_s4.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005810" id2="17" version="1065353216">It would be unwise to make the situation on Denova common knowledge. Moff Altiss appreciates your discretion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005814" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor's Wrath! Forgive my surprise, my lord, but your reputation precedes you. It is a stroke of great fortune for my master that you are here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, my lord. Please forgive a humble droid for approaching a member of the Dark Council, but my master is in great need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Data files confirm you are the Grand Champion of the Great Hunt. My master would be very interested to meet the galaxy's premier bounty hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005820" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are whispers that you were once a key operative with Imperial Intelligence. My master has urgent need of someone with your skills.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005822" id2="17" version="1065353216">I extend this offer to all of you, as my master may require the combined efforts of several talented individuals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive my impertinence, but my master is in urgent need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005826" id2="17" version="1065353216">I represent Moff Altiss. She has instructed me to seek out those capable of fixing a critical mission on Denova that has gone awry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Help her? Your master must face the consequences of her own weakness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Failure should be punished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005828" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am a member of the Dark Council; it is not my responsibility to clean up after some incompetent Moff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why should I fix her mistake?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Moff Altiss is not to blame for what transpired. She is merely attempting to salvage something from this disaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005831" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do you always wait until something goes wrong to bring me in? Probably cheaper just to hire me up front.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005831" id2="17" version="1065353216">You people need my help a lot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005832" id2="17" version="1065353216">It does seem inefficient. But Moff Altiss is not to blame for this disaster. She is only tasked with salvaging something from the situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005834" id2="17" version="1065353216">It wouldn't be the first time I cleaned up someone else's mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fixing mistakes is what I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005835" id2="17" version="1065353216">To be clear, Moff Altiss is not responsible for this disaster. She is merely trying to salvage something from the wreckage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Failure to do so would seriously weaken the Empire's position, leaving us vulnerable to our sworn enemies in the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that a Republic world, or one of ours?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005839" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not familiar with Denova.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that a Republic world, or one of yours?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Denova? Never heard of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005841" id2="17" version="1065353216">The world was only recently discovered. Military forces claimed it for the Empire. The Republic responded with an army of mercenaries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005843" id2="17" version="1065353216">The outcome of the battle will have far-reaching effects for both sides. We cannot afford to lose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005845" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me what I need to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005845" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005846" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am not authorized to discuss any of the details. I can only say that Moff Altiss is eager to meet with you face-to-face.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005848" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is a great honor for a lowly protocol droid to share the presence of such powerful and important individuals.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
