<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>16</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x2/raid/explosive_conflict/empire/transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let the walkers secure the beach. You push forward to engage Kephess and his troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025081" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Nerril checking in. Scouts spotted some drouks heading your way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025084" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're hitting Kephess hard on the main front. Maybe you can find an alternate route to his camp through the mines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025088" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those baradium deposits are highly unstable. One missed blaster bolt can blow you sky high!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025091" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Captain Nerril. Enemy reinforcements closing on your position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025099" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're closing in on the Imperial defector camp. Time to make those traitors pay!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like Kephess is transporting the baradium to his main camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025108" id2="17" version="1065353216">The defectors were equipped with heavy explosives. Probably planted land mines around the whole area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025110" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel Vorgath is leading the Imperial traitors. Don't let him escape!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025118" id2="17" version="1065353216">Primary units engaging Kephess on the main front. Try to find another way to his camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025120" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's too much interference. We're losing your signal. Prepare to drop out of radio contact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025129" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're picking up your signal again--and just in time. You need to flank Kephess at his camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025131" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take down their shield generator!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025133" id2="17" version="1065353216">Orbital bombardment commencing. Time to clear out!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Incoming artillery! We'll try and draw Kephess's fire away from your position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kephess is stepping up his baradium processing. Could be stocking up for a major galactic offensive.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
