<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>78</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/republic/starfighters_of_corellia/captain_bathens.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me, Master Jedi, but can you bonk this guy on the head? It's the only thing that might make him see reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477473" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's Major, right? I'm Shane. You need to talk some sense into your buddy here, or he's going to lose the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477474" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can always spot my own! Name's Trigo Shane, help a free trader out and convince this ground-pounder he's got the wrong idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, I've not seen you around before--name's Shane, Trigo Shane--but maybe you can help me for a second.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477479" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've turned me up a tidy profit, bucko, recovering those weapons. Nice to work with someone trustworthy for a change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477481" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was big risk grabbing those weapons--Old Bathens here'd never do it--but the payoff's been great!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your quick thinking has given us a real edge against Imperial assets. Grabbing those weapons was brilliant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those snub fighters won't give your men any more trouble, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Told you it'd work, Bathens! You owe me a hundred credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477488" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll admit, I didn't expect to see you again. I've never been so pleased to be wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477490" id2="17" version="1065353216">With those fighters out of the way, the Republic will have no problem establishing air superiority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477491" id2="17" version="1065353216">With air support, Republic troops should finally be able to put the Imps on the run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hopefully this turns the tide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed. You've done us a great service, and it's our turn to make sure your efforts aren't wasted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477494" id2="17" version="1065353216">It wasn't that big a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477495" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may think it's nothing, but you've certainly outdone yourself. Now it's up to us to turn the tide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477497" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should have attacked the fighters straight away, there's no telling how many lives might have been saved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your indecision is dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477498" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no way it would have worked without your help. I feel vindicated, regardless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477500" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for slipping some of those weapons back with you. Those babies will turn a pretty profit, and help shove the Imps out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477502" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's a little something for the extra effort, after all, part of the profit's yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477504" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's impressed, stick-in-the-mud Bathens just hates to admit a pirate like me was right. Wouldn't have worked without you, though. Thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477506" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got a bet with Bathens here that you'll pull this off, so hurry up 'cause I'm not interested in losing money.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477507" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many times must we go over this? Any benefits of attacking the spaceport aren't worth the cost in lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="477509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Open your eyes, Captain. It's the only way to keep the Imps from wiping you out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477511" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have to understand what's going on before I can help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477511" id2="17" version="1065353216">What seems to be the problem?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477512" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's nothing to concern you, really.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell the truth Bathens! Tell them you'd rather watch Imp starfighters shred your men than take a risk and attack their hangars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477516" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think we've been introduced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477516" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477517" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's all right, Master Shane is supposed to be here. He's providing a &quot;freelance&quot; perspective on fighting the Empire's troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477519" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm providing, but you're not listening! Every battle, Imperial starfighters mutilate his troops--I know where they're parked but he won't attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477521" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're talking about the best defended hangars on Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477523" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't talk to a ranking Republic officer like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show the captain some respect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477524" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's rank like a wet bantha. He's got a chance to save his men's lives but won't take it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477526" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's enough! I will put up with your harassment of me, mercenary, but do not drag other parties into it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen, every time he attacks, Imperial starfighters butcher his men. Taking out their starfighters would solve the problem, but he won't!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477530" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't even need a frontal assault; nasty enough team could slip into the starport and blow those ships under the Imps' noses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477531" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it. I can handle a starport assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where do I sign up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477532" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not under my command so I can't order you to stand down, but my opinion is clear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477534" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're committed to this folly, we do have demolitions charges. Placed correctly, they'll bring down the hangars onto the fighters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477536" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's all it takes, why hasn't anyone destroyed them before now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477536" id2="17" version="1065353216">You almost make it sound easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477537" id2="17" version="1065353216">The starport has elite troops and Sith guarding it; a squad might get inside but they'd be discovered in moments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477539" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you're both nuts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't walk away! You know what the Empire means to people like us; if we don't take a stand we're out of work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477542" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't make big speeches, that's for officers. We both know the score, are you helping us or yourself?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, I'm just a ship-captain, but even I see that Corellia's the key. If it falls, eventually, the galaxy goes too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477545" id2="17" version="1065353216">All my infiltration teams were wiped out weeks ago. I've got no one capable of doing the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Officially I'm an advisor, I can't ask you to do anything. But we both know if those starfighters are gone, the troops will have a fighting chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477548" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's my duty to help turn back the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477548" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm honored to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477549" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know about duty, for me it's just good business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cloaked in the Force, I will have no problem entering their spaceport.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477551" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be easy for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477552" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't follow that mystical mumbo-jumbo, but if it works for you then I say go for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477554" id2="17" version="1065353216">Infiltration and sabotage are my bread and butter, just watch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477554" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is what I do best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477555" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you're perfect for the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477557" id2="17" version="1065353216">From one trader to another, I'll handle this. But you owe me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477557" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it--we'll swap favors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477558" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got just the way to make it up to you--I've stripped my share of weapons in my day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477560" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use this gunripper and pull some of those Imperial weapons. They'll give the Republic an edge and we'll turn a tidy profit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477562" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you're done, or if it gets too hot, just set the charges and get out. No one'll be any wiser.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay already, I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use these demolitions charges on the structural supports; they'll collapse the hangers onto the fighters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477566" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, take this gunripper too. I used it to pry weapons off, ah, pirate ships we raided on the Rimma.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477568" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imps have some fancy toys on their fighters; if you can bring some back, we can put them to good use.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477570" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477571" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to see someone else has some appreciation for the proper way. Maybe now he'll stop hounding me about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477573" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm right, and you know it. You can't blame me wanting to win the war, instead of waiting to get shot to pieces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477575" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a cold eel, standing around while the Imps rip your men to shreds. Especially when you know I've got a solution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477577" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've already told you, your plan is out of the question. We simply don't have the resources.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477578" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll concede that the idea was sound. With the fighters out of the way, the Republic has less to fear on the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477580" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha! Admit I'm right you old warhorse, it's the least you can do after we saved your hide.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
