<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>92</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic military = suffered heavy casualties securing base</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Love what they've done with the place. You could almost forget this was a Colicoid nest.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would be better with Colicoids to hunt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297424" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfectly good lab being neglected. Where's the zazz? I should have Holiday redesign this whole space.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could the Republic have picked a creepier place to hang out? Keep expecting giant bugs to come out of the walls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297426" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's dark and dirty, but not the worst Republic base I've ever visited. Rodia still holds the title.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297427" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's incredible to consider how long the Balmorrans have been carrying on this fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soon, our allies will not cower in places like this. They will tread freely, with open sky above them and Imperial corpses below!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297431" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 sensors = detecting large Colicoid swarms nearby</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297432" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got a bad feeling about this area. An installation that big shouldn't look so deserted.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is Colicoid scent all over, Herald.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297434" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic really needs to take better care of its facilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297435" id2="17" version="1065353216">That control station looks important. Kind of surprised it's still intact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297436" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chatter on the comm frequencies says that tower got overrun by Colicoids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Satellite control towers. These will be a priority target for the Imps to be sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Satellite control towers. Standard configuration. I'm surprised they're still in one piece.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297441" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suspension bridges = destroyed by artillery // T7 + Jedi = within blast radius</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297442" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there any place on Balmorra that hasn't been blown to smithereens?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. What prey will Scorekeeper send?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would people voluntarily live on this world?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Broken bridges are bad luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297446" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like the Empire burned its bridges to keep us out. Not that it's doing any good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297447" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imps really hit this area hard. Must've been something important here--probably just dust, now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yet more destruction wrought by our Imperial foes. They stop at nothing!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sobrik = Imperial stronghold + highly dangerous</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sobrik. What it lacks in ambience, it makes up for in hospitality.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Empire even binds the sky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sobrik had a name for being quite the scenic spot once. Until the Empire made itself at home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297455" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sobrik isn't likely to appreciate us busting in, Captain. Then again, who is?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperials beware! Bowdaar comes for you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sobrik. The Empire will not give up this foothold on Balmorra easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297458" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sobrik. The very heart of the Empire's hold on this world lies before us!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297461" id2="17" version="1065353216">Troida Military Workshop = good place for droid parts?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297462" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place used to crank out top-of-the-line weapons before the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297463" id2="17" version="1065353216">Things are toys, for hunters without own skill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Amateurish equipment. Now if I'd been working here, the Empire would--never mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Troida Military Workshop, huh? Bet they've got some first-class blasters laying around....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297466" id2="17" version="1065353216">Boys and their toys... it's always the same--guns, gears and grit. Lucky for them, I like that sort of thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Advanced production facilities like this are a critical resource. Our forces need to take them and hold them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297468" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Republic liberates Balmorra, these fine machines will contribute to the cause of liberty!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dark spaces = favored by Imperials + insects</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's put the Empire out of the prison business on Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297473" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is place for caging. Where points are lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297474" id2="17" version="1065353216">My, the Empire has been busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297475" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never get tired of busting people loose from Imperial prisons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Building prisons must be the Empire's core competency. They seem to have one everywhere we go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297477" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we can free the prisoners here, the Balmorran resistance would be very grateful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Freeing the prisoners here is our patriotic duty! Let none who stand for liberty suffer in bondage!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297481" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial fortifications = deep + well-defended</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch your step--that's a long drop down. Balmorra's apparently never heard of railings.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Empire has hidden well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297484" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose if you have a crater, you may as well make good use of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297485" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place reminds Bowdaar of Kashyyyk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at this Imperial base. What's the word I'm thinking of... oh, right: &quot;deathtrap.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297487" id2="17" version="1065353216">It doesn't look like the Imps have been holding this ground for long. If we push hard, we could probably smash right through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rather hasty fortifications on the Imperials' part. Certainly not up to regulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Battle zone = highly hazardous // Jedi = tread carefully</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Know what Balmorra needs? More smoldering ruins. They don't have nearly enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is still echoes of battle here. No good deaths.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297494" id2="17" version="1065353216">I intercepted the odd Imperial broadcast, back on Nar Shaddaa. The Empire spun this carnage as a &quot;glorious victory.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297495" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of all the places we've been on Balmorra so far, this is the scariest. Wide open spaces are great places to get killed in a war zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297496" id2="17" version="1065353216">You always take me to the nicest places. The destroyed walkers, crashed ships, smoking craters... it's all so rustic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such devastation. I don't know if Balmorra will ever recover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297498" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is only a taste of what the Empire is capable of. They must be stopped!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial forward line = heavily fortified // Enemies = numerous</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297502" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire sure knows how to lay down a welcome mat. The turrets are a nice touch.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Balmorra will be scarred.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Crude and unnecessary--why use trenches when electrostatic strands work just as well?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297505" id2="17" version="1065353216">This could get hairy real quick. The Empire's forward lines are no walk in the park.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297506" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enemies are everywhere. Bowdaar will find them!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fighting through trenches like these is never easy. We'd better take it slow and watch our backs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Storm the trenches! Drive our enemies out like the vermin they are!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Balmorran Arms Factory = site of Republic defeat // Jedi + T7 = avenge the fallen!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297512" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I thought Balmorra was rough on the outside. We'll be lucky to get out of here alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph. Place is warren.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't look into that generator's light too long, Jedi. If these Balmorrans didn't build it with proper shields, say farewell to your retinas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297515" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire sure picked a nasty place to hole up in. On the other hand, there's bound to be sweet gear lying around....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297516" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a weapons factory, right? It occurs to me we might be slightly outgunned by the Empire....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial defenses will be heavier here than anywhere else on Balmorra. We should be cautious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our enemy's final stronghold! We must press on until none are left standing!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023143" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perplexity: This base appears to be repurposed from a Colicoid nest--or vice-versa.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rumination: It is highly unusual to see intact satellite control towers in a war zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revelation: That generator powers the entire droid factory. High-yield explosives would fix that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023152" id2="17" version="1065353216">Conclusion: Sobrik is home to many Imperial troublemakers, master. Let us delete them all!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023155" id2="17" version="1065353216">Appreciation: Oh, master--you bring me to the nicest places. I may find useful upgrades here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Criticism: I will never understand organics' compulsion to keep prisoners. Deletion is more efficient.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023161" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assertion: An impressive fortification. To conquer it, one must delve to the very bottom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Judgment: Most of the troublemakers here have already been deleted. How disappointing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023167" id2="17" version="1065353216">Query: I find trench warfare a refreshing change of pace, don't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023170" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prediction: We will encounter maximum resistance from Imperial troublemakers here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Approval: Some see a broken bridge, but I see a glorious deletion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Conjecture: The lack of allied activity suggests a target-rich environment ahead. This warms my circuits.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
