<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>11</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/the_streets_of_cademimu/shared/transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514362" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Ortol? Anyone? Whoever you are, listen--those missile batteries are all that's protecting Cademimu. You can't take control from me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514364" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Imperial fleet command. Planetary defenses are disengaging--and we've got the governor's shuttle on scanners. We'll take it from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514365" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Republic fleet command. Looks like the missile batteries are disengaged, and the governor's shuttle just became vulnerable. Leave the cleanup to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514366" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Ortol, report! What is the status of the intruders? Report!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514367" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is General Ortol to the intruders. The governor may be cowering in his bunker, but we will do our job. You won't get any further.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514368" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is General Ortol to all forces--the command center is under attack! Do not let the enemy take control of the missile batteries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514369" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people, do not listen to the lies on the HoloNet. There are no riots in the Mercantile District, and the missile batteries are perfectly safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514370" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fellow citizens. Some of you have questioned the makeup of the Cademiman Guard--you ask &quot;Why have we recruited offworlders?&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514372" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I say if a man like General Ortol wants to fight for our planet, it would be selfish to deny him that privilege.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514373" id2="17" version="1065353216">My fellow citizens. The coming days will be difficult--you will hear lies about civil unrest, about attacks on our soil.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514375" id2="17" version="1065353216">But our world is protected--not just by our arsenal, but the Cademiman Guard patrols the streets to keep you safe.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
