<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>34</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tatooine/bronze/republic/down_the_hole/ledo_melnic.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615882" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the only reason Anchorhead is still here. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="615884" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have to worry about the Mandalorians. They were no match for a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="615885" id2="17" version="1065353216">The outpost no longer has to fear the Mandalorians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="615886" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have to worry about the Mandalorians anymore. I took care of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="615887" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good news, Ledo. Yours truly just cleaned up that little Mando mess of yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615888" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you wouldn't let me down!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here. Take this. I know you didn't ask for a reward, but I feel like I should give you something.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's the reward I promised you. I took up a collection with all the local merchants. I think you'll be satisfied.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. All of Anchorhead is in your debt.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry. You need to stop the Mandalorians before they go to war against Anchorhead!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="615898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is everything okay? You look like something's bothering you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="615899" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sense you are troubled.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="615900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something wrong, pal? You're skittish as a Jawa.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615901" id2="17" version="1065353216">That obvious, huh? Ledo. Ledo Melnic. I'm a magistrate.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Supposed to keep things orderly here. But recently, I sort of... put most of Anchorhead in danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615905" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should have known better than to stand up to those Mandalorians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me take care of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615908" id2="17" version="1065353216">That rarely ends well.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615909" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just hope something can be done before it's too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615911" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few Mandalorians were shaking down merchants. I told security to run them off whenever they showed up.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now the Mandos have crippled three of my officers and started converting an old storage facility into a siege-proof bunker.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615915" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're about to go to war against security, the militia, anyone who won't give them the run of Anchorhead. Someone needs to clear them out, or we're done for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615916" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615917" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's how to stand up to a bully! My job would be so much easier with more people like you around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615919" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do I get out of this?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615920" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh. I didn't realize Jedi were so, ah, self-serving. But don't worry. I'll make sure you're well compensated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615922" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do I get out of this?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615923" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure I can find suitable compensation for you. I guess it's only fair.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get inside that bunker and take those Mandos down--don't know how many there are or what they've done to the place, but it won't be pretty.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615927" id2="17" version="1065353216">And watch out for their leader--he's got a reputation for hunting Trandoshans, rancors... not to mention Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615929" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't help. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh. That's not good. You were kind of my last hope. Come back if you change your mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615932" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm too busy to talk. Being magistrate is a full-time job, you know.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
