<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>49</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/ilum/world/republic/the_last_battle/crystal_ball/lord_loryat.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662099" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop! I yield! I yield!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662100" id2="17" version="1065353216">The base is secure. I need a squad to take Lord Loyat into custody.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662100" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arrest her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662101" id2="17" version="1065353216">But... Darth Arho always claimed the dark side was stronger than the light. He swore the Empire would always triumph over the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662103" id2="17" version="1065353216">He lied to me. He used me. And then he betrayed me. I'm nothing but a fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now you see the truth. You still have to pay for your crimes against the Republic, but it's not too late to choose a different path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662104" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can still change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662105" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have to pay for your crimes against the Republic. But if you cooperate, you'll be shown mercy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662105" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can still change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662106" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. Your words give me... comfort. Something I have not felt in a long, long time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662107" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're stupid enough to trust someone like Darth Arho, then you deserve whatever you get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662107" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll say.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662108" id2="17" version="1065353216">I deserve your scorn. But heed my words: When you encounter Darth Arho, do not be so merciful. Spare his life and he will make you regret it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662109" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not finished with your master. There will be a reckoning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662109" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, he'll pay, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662110" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're right. I want him to suffer for what he did to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662111" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take her into custody. I need to get back. Agent Bradber is waiting for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662114" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't let you live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too late. [Kill her]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662115" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then make it quick!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662120" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's over, Lord Loyat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662121" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know how you found me, Jedi, but coming here was a mistake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662123" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, the leader of the infamous Havoc Squad. Your reputation is well-earned, but coming here is suicide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662125" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, Rans has sent the great champion of the Jedi to challenge me? Your martial skills are legendary, but you will not succeed here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662127" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it isn't the Republic's dirty little secret--the one the army and the Jedi turn to when they fail. But this is one mission you should have refused!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662129" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least you were wise enough not to challenge me alone. Unfortunately, you and your companions will all suffer the same fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662131" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have no idea what torment you are about to suffer! I am Darth Arho's personal apprentice! Those who hear my master's name tremble in fear!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662132" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your master's not that special. The galaxy is full of brutal thugs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662132" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's nothing to be proud of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662133" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't see your master anywhere. It's just you and me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662133" id2="17" version="1065353216">But he's not here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662134" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, but it takes more than words to make me tremble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662134" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that supposed to scare me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662135" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know nothing of my Darth Arho. He embodies all the Dark Council represents. His wrath is legendary!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662137" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, hurry to my side! Together we will destroy these Republic fools!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Arho? Can you hear me? It is I, Lord Loyat...! Master? Are you there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662140" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just as disappointed he's not showing up as you are. Taking you both out in one battle would have made things so much simpler for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662140" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad. I'd like to meet him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662141" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really thought lover-boy was coming. Talk about a bad breakup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662141" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, that's gotta hurt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662142" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you really believe he'd risk himself to save you? For a Sith Lord, you still have a lot to learn about the dark side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662142" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith have no loyalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662143" id2="17" version="1065353216">He wouldn't abandon me. This... this must be a test. Yes. A test of my strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your master isn't coming. It's just you and me, and you can't win this battle. Drop your weapons and I promise you'll be treated fairly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surrender and you can live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arho may have abandoned me, but I still command the power of the dark side!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662147" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody's going to save you now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662147" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's do this. [Attack her]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662148" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will destroy you myself, and prove to my master I am worthy to serve him!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
