<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>6</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/weekly_heroic/mission_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1174104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Daskarta has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Frinn Mesa sector of Makeb. For additional details about the mission, Daskarta may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1174129" id2="17" version="1065353216">Archivist Varus has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Tarlam Settlements sector of Makeb. For additional details about the mission, Archivist Varus may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1174132" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

A particularly heinous band of former Regulators situated on the Fingers has been shooting down and looting civilian shuttles headed for a refugee camp.

Draw out these Regulators by fabricating and activating a shuttle distress beacon at one of the shuttle wreckage sites to keep them from doing harm to any more civilians.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1174133" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

Many of Makeb's citizens were unable to reach the Ark before its launch. Some couldn't make it because they were shot down by ex-Regulator forces on Telemur Mesa, who are keeping the civilians imprisoned.

Retrieve the shuttle manifests from the Regulators while doing what you can to limit these mercenaries' capabilities in the area.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1174134" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

A group of former Regulators on Makeb have called on various extraplanetary forces--Mandalorians, assassin droids and fallen Jedi, mostly--to help them take control of the planet. These forces are reaching the planet via a ground-to-atmosphere turbolift called a &quot;gravity hook.&quot;

Ambush the potential Regulator allies arriving at Gravity Hook Four before they can make their way off the mesa.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188837" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --

A large cache of Isotope-5 is being held by renegade mercenaries in the courtyard of Toborro the Hutt's palace. They've got a massive Isotope-5 droid posted on guard duty at all times--our forces haven't been able to put a dent in the thing. We need you to take that droid down.

-- END --

[Operation: Toborro's Courtyard]
Defeat Golden Fury (Any Difficulty Mode).

[Recommended Gear]
Story Mode: Item Rating 148
Hard Mode: Item Rating 168</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
