<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>6</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/weekly_heroic/mission_board_imperial.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188811" id2="17" version="1065353216">MISSION ASSISTANCE--BY ORDER OF IMPERIAL COMMAND--MESSAGE READS:

Renegade mercenaries have claimed a substantial Isotope-5 cache in the courtyard of Toborro's palace. Their primary defense is a massive droid powered by the substance; this particular model is substantially more dangerous than others our forces have encountered. 

We will have that cache. Destroy the droid and clear the way for our retrieval teams.

For the Empire.

END MESSAGE

[Operation: Toborro's Courtyard]
Defeat Golden Fury (Any Difficulty Mode).

[Recommended Gear]
Story Mode: Item Rating 148
Hard Mode: Item Rating 168</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188814" id2="17" version="1065353216">D3-X9 has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gravity Hook Four sector of Makeb. For additional details about the mission, D3-X9 may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188815" id2="17" version="1065353216">GR-18 has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gravity Hook Seven sector of Makeb. For additional details about the mission, GR-18 may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188819" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

Former Regulators have obtained a prototype isotope-5 rocket from the remnants of the Archon's weapons stockpiles. 

Steal the rocket from their long-range artillery depot located on the chain of bridged mesas known as &quot;the Fingers.&quot; Our science team will monitor the rocket as you launch it into a nearby mesa to assess its potential for Imperial use.

END MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188820" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

Refugees fleeing Pelratha Mesa, which collapsed due to the Empire's hastening of Makeb's destabilization, have crash-landed on Telemur Mesa. Their shuttle's flight recorder contains statistical data that could potentially expose our role here on the planet. 

Retrieve the flight recorder and use its data to pin Pelratha's collapse on the Regulators.

END MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188821" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

An Imperial misinformation architect has crafted the components of a potent lie: that the destruction of Makeb has been long foretold by the planet's own scientists; and that the powers that be on the planet knew about, ignored and covered up any such evidence. 

To sell this fiction, this data must be uploaded to the various computers within the planet's Cultural Archives in the Tarlam settlement.

END MESSAGE</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
