<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>29</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/imperial/hub_2/a_cure_for_armageddon/drill_site_computer_b.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010401" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have the second platform secured. Send in the engineers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010402" id2="17" version="1065353216">On their way.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1029399" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Nadrin. That groundquake is the result of the first team's drilling; expect the tremors to worsen as additional lasers come online.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1029400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are we actually approaching stabilization? Or are we breaking apart the core for nothing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1029400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is the plan working?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1029402" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take care of things here. Any information on the final target?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1029402" id2="17" version="1065353216">On my way to the next.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1029403" id2="17" version="1065353216">The groundquakes will not impede me. Continue drilling until the core is stabilized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1029403" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do your part; I'll survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1029404" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last drill platform is surrounded by heavy cannons and the Archon's personal guard: Whiphids and their hunting pets.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1029407" id2="17" version="1065353216">We cannot be certain until all three drills are online. But no warning signs yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1029410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander J'Ruush oversaw the gravity hook for the Archon. He was a Whiphid, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1029410" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fought a Whiphid before, no?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1029411" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many Cartel soldiers and mercenaries are on this planet? They must be thinned out by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1029411" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemies just keep coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1029412" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Archon likes them. They're strong, combative and smarter than they look.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1029413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imagine what they're saying about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1029415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please secure passage for our engineering team quickly. Now that drilling has begun, our window of opportunity is limited.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1038611" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Whiphids and their hounds can locate our people by scent, and even if our engineers get through, the cannons can obliterate the platform as a last resort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1038612" id2="17" version="1065353216">That army isn't meant to kill me. The Archon's trying to slaughter any of our people who get close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1038612" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no longer the main target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1038613" id2="17" version="1065353216">He knows he can't stop you, but he can still win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1038615" id2="17" version="1065353216">The wreckage of machines is piled behind me. Dead mercenaries are heaped in my path. The Archon's guard will fall, too. Onward to slaughter!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1038615" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll enjoy the killing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050133" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last drill platform is surrounded by heavy cannons and the Archon's personal guard: Nikto and their hunting pets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050135" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Nikto's hounds can locate our people by scent, and even if our engineers get through, the cannons can obliterate the platform as a last resort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050136" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said the Archon's people are mainly Nikto? What should I expect?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1050136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me of the Archon's guard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050137" id2="17" version="1065353216">Loyalty, dedication, self-sacrifice--traits the Hutts cultivate over generations, since they can't buy them.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
