<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>35</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_1/the_arc/foreman_tiero.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009306" id2="17" version="1065353216">My crew's hard at work. No one's stopping until the ark's complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009307" id2="17" version="1065353216">Veedrig and his little toady are close by. You can't miss them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009308" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic, huh? Don't know what you're doing on Makeb, but thanks. These Cartel idiots won't listen to reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009310" id2="17" version="1065353216">I try calling for help and get a blaster shoved in my face. The Hutts work us to death, treat us like slaves--no, like animals!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009311" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're here to commandeer the ark for the people of Makeb. Once it's secure, you and your men will be freed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009311" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll save you and the ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009312" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're working eighteen-hour days, no breaks, no visits home....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009314" id2="17" version="1065353216">You stood up to that Cartel thug pretty well. What's your name?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009314" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tiero. I'm foreman here, for what it's worth. You saw what happens when I try to do my blasted job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009317" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's all on Veedrig's orders. My men break their backs building his ark while he steals everything not bolted down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009319" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're here for the ark, not your laundry list of complaints.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop whining.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure. Why would anybody listen to the foreman?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to Veedrig, the ark's weeks behind schedule. My crew can't finish the ship while that slimy Devaronian's selling off its components.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009323" id2="17" version="1065353216">First the Hutt Cartel betrays Makeb, now their contractor betrays them. Their greed will ruin them both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009323" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts deserve his deceit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009324" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd love to see the Hutts catch Veedrig red-handed, but I'll settle for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Veedrig's locked himself in here for more than safety. He's covering up his deception so his Hutt employers don't find out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009326" id2="17" version="1065353216">That explains his secrecy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009327" id2="17" version="1065353216">He even bribed the guards. But you can expose him, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Veedrig's scam is about to end. When we neutralize him, be ready to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009329" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll put us back on schedule.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009330" id2="17" version="1065353216">You actually want the ark completed? I suppose we can do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Takes a steady hand to steal from the Hutts. Depending on his skill, Veedrig will either get himself killed or make a fortune.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009332" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a risky scam.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Snakes always manage to slither out of trouble. But you can stop this one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Veedrig. Fast talker, horns on his head, likes kissing up to Hutts?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009335" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know that name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, you know him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009338" id2="17" version="1065353216">That stupid Devaronian may have doomed the whole planet. I'll make sure he dies first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Veedrig will pay for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let him talk his way out of this. He's good at the chatter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009341" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll tell my crew to lay low. Put Veedrig in his place, and we'll help you out however we can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch out!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
