<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>25</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_1/the_arc/giants_spear_holoterminal.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009287" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ilosov--we're at the Giant's Spear. What have you got for us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009288" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ark construction site's behind a triple-plated durasteel blast door. Takes three separate keycards to open the thing. Only Cartel representatives carry them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heh, guess the Hutts only trust the Regulators up to a point. You need to find the Cartel's top lieutenants and get their keycards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009293" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for the intel and advice. We'll contact you again when we unlock that blast door.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009293" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get Cartel keycards--check.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009294" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep searching the files in case there's anything else. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009295" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there a faster way?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009297" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would it be possible to simply cut through the door with, say, a lightsaber?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009298" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would it be faster to blast the door down? If I don't have the firepower, I'm sure somebody here does.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009299" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd be at it for days. One thing Hutts know how to make is strong doors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009301" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hutt lackeys don't deserve to live--and I'm feeling especially vindictive today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009301" id2="17" version="1065353216">There won't be any survivors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contact me when you've unlocked the blast door. I'll let you know if we find anything else in these files. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049911" id2="17" version="1065353216">We sent probe droids to scan the zone ahead of you. Their readings... not good news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regulator fireteams are patrolling the site. Some of Vice Commandant Grevin's finest, backed by top lieutenants from the Hutt Cartel. Everyone's packing military hardware.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049914" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the expert on Regulator tactics. How do we get through your old friends?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1049914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get tactical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049915" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fireteams are spread out for patrol sweeps. Take those teams out fast enough, and you shouldn't have to worry about a coordinated defense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049917" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any chance Grevin is commanding these forces? It'd be nice to have another talk with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1049917" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is the Regulator leader here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049918" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't look like it. Too bad--that son of a Hutt deserves to fry with the rest of his two-faced traitors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049920" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let them pack all the hardware they want. Won't be the first army we've wiped out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1049920" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're ready for anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fair enough, but that's not all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Happy hunting.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
