<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>72</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_1/the_arc/veedrig.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never let it be said I'm not generous in defeat. You can have this incredible marvel of starship design at a twenty-percent discount.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thirty percent?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009166" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your composure is impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009168" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were obviously hired for your negotiating skills. It certainly wasn't for shipbuilding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009169" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a big-picture man. Details are for little people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009171" id2="17" version="1065353216">Project Failsafe is falling to pieces, and you're still negotiating? Some Jedi work their entire lives to achieve that level of calm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rule number one: Never sweat the small stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I should wait for something else to fall off. Get you down to half price.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009175" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, good--you're open to haggling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009177" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me get this straight: You're half dead and trying to sell me an unfinished starship? You must've taken the Hutts for a fortune.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fortune and a half--but who's counting?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009180" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think you understand the gravity of your situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009180" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bad play, Veedrig.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009181" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gravity, heh... good one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009183" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you prefer quick executions? I'm leaning toward &quot;slow and painful,&quot; myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009183" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me how you want to die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009184" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm hoping to bid you up. How about temporary crippling?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009186" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admit the ship needs a little work, but she's almost ready to fly. Besides, being incomplete means there's room to customize.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009188" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me live, and I'll have this baby ready to leave the atmosphere in no time. You won't find a better offer--trust me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009189" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't count on being trusted, but you can work for our people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009189" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009192" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, Veedrig. Time to earn your pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009194" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looking forward to it. Could you spare some kolto, first?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009196" id2="17" version="1065353216">No deal. [Kill him]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009198" id2="17" version="1065353216">That speech might've worked on a Hutt, but not me. Scum like you make me sick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009199" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm in no mood to negotiate with a greedy thug. You earned your fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009200" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been blasting criminal scum since I got here. I don't see any reason to stop.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009201" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must think I'm a complete idiot. Don't answer that. In fact, shut up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009204" id2="17" version="1065353216">This one's actually useful. We can put him to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009206" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything you want. I'll get my welding gloves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Haven't had contact with the outside in weeks.... This is Foreman Tiero and Republic forces calling from Giant's Spear. Does anyone read?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009212" id2="17" version="1065353216">Loud and clear, Tiero. We sent those Republic forces. What's the ark's status? Is it secure?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009213" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bad news, Ilosov. Veedrig was scamming the Hutts. The ark is nowhere near complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009213" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ark isn't finished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009214" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those idiot Hutts can't even save themselves right! Stand by....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009215" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go ahead. Give him the bad news about the ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009215" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell him, Tiero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009216" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's incomplete, but... Is the ark that important?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009217" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ark's only half-finished. There's no way we can evacuate the planet with this pile of junk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009217" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're all doomed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009218" id2="17" version="1065353216">Evacuate the planet? What are you talking about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009220" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't just give up. Stand by.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009222" id2="17" version="1065353216">Foreman, this is Shalim Avesta. Makeb's core is tearing apart, and we can't stop it. That ark is our people's only hope of escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009224" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I send you every able body I have and guarantee your safety, can you finish the ark in time to evacuate our world?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009226" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll blasted well try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009228" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts are surely organizing a counterattack. We're forming a battle plan to defeat it. We'll brief you back here--hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009229" id2="17" version="1065353216">We sealed the blast door to keep Hutt reinforcements out, but there's bound to be another way out of here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009229" id2="17" version="1065353216">On our way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009230" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Hutts are striking back, should we leave these workers and the ark unguarded?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009230" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will Tiero be safe alone?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009231" id2="17" version="1065353216">You locked the main blast door. We can hold out until reinforcements get here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009233" id2="17" version="1065353216">These workers might run the moment we leave. Someone should keep an eye on them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009233" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't trust these people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009234" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've all got families. You think we'd just leave them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009236" id2="17" version="1065353216">The foreman knows what's at stake if they don't finish the ark. We can trust him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Veedrig kept a private shuttle pad nearby. You can take his transport while we get to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009240" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're still talking? Seriously?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009243" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got the best Ugnaught engineer in four sectors on retainer. She's a genius with electro-plumbing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009245" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have the classiest refresher on Coruscant, boss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still can't decide what to put in the sonic shower. Felucian glimmer-stones look so elegant, but I love Rylothian onyx tile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009248" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must be Veedrig--and this is Project Failsafe. There's been a change of plan. You don't work for the Hutts anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surrender the ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009249" id2="17" version="1065353216">Feel free to go solve your interior-decorating problem. This entire facility is now Republic property.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009249" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah... decisions, decisions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009250" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why settle for just one? They're both excellent gravestones--and your days are numbered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009250" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can be buried under both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009253" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're those Republic people Toborro's screaming about on the holo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009255" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're that Republic hero Toborro's screaming about on the holo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009257" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Cartel's so worried, they're paying double to finish the ark ahead of schedule. That's on top of what they're offering to kill you....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1057887" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be so rich after this!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1057890" id2="17" version="1065353216">C'mon, you stupid droids!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1057893" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, fine--you win!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
