<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>77</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/korriban/world/the_hate_machine/ephran_zell.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657592" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah! My old friend. Do forgive me--I'm quite busy with my research right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657593" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made it! Did it work? Did the Red Engine produce an inscription?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657594" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fed it blood, and it gave me this tablet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657594" id2="17" version="1065353216">After the fight, yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. Can you translate the hieroglyphs on the stone?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take a look.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657596" id2="17" version="1065353216">The tablet of Tulak Hord? Inscribed in the language of the ancient Sith....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, yeah.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. Oh yes. These are Tulak Hord's teachings--the very methods he used to build the terrible machine below!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657601" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have dreamed of this tablet--dreamed of looking upon Tulak Hord's teachings and studying the arcane science of the dark side. I am honored you give me this opportunity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657604" id2="17" version="1065353216">May your madness bring you knowledge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Learn well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657605" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you say, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember that power comes from hate, not study.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Research isn't the Sith way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657608" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I do not seek power. I seek only to learn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take these--small relics I've unearthed that deserve to be used by a true Sith. Not a reward, but recognition of your strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, I must excuse myself, and my research must continue. It will be some time before the tablet gives up all its secrets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657613" id2="17" version="1065353216">How will you proceed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657614" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will complete my studies here. And when I am done... there will be other dead lords, other dreams, and perhaps other machines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't waste it, archaeologist. I expect your studies to bear fruit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657616" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you should be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. When my studies here are complete, I shall lay all I have learned at the steps of the Academy... before leaving for another tomb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657619" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must excuse myself. But take these--a few relics I've unearthed that deserve to be held by a true Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657621" id2="17" version="1065353216">I beg of you--find the machine, and fuel it with blood!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657628" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord! Allow me to approach. The wind outside has torn my ears to tatters, and my eyes grow strained and bloody in the dark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come closer, acolyte! The wind outside has torn my ears to tatters, and my eyes grow strained and bloody in the dark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657631" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've studied this tomb for years--slept on its stones and dreamed of its depths. Now, I need assistance to solve its final mystery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657632" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you have secrets to share, I would learn them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fascinating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then listen to me, and to my story. Listen close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657635" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't dig through dirt for scholars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657635" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not your laborer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you misunderstand the chance I am offering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657638" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you are?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657639" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Ephran Zell. For generations, my family has studied the tombs of Korriban, traveling from one to the next to learn the history of the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Really? So are you mad or just obsessed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Crazy man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why should my sanity matter to you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657644" id2="17" version="1065353216">This tomb is the final resting place of Tulak Hord. The tomb's maze was built to his precise specifications.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657646" id2="17" version="1065353216">But he built his maze to hold more than just his body. He built it to secure his greatest creation--his terrible machine. The Red Engine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep going. What &quot;Red Engine&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Machine?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657648" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where do I come in?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because I need you. The machine needs you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657651" id2="17" version="1065353216">I really don't share your fascination with history.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not interested.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657652" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tulak Hord had power and knowledge unknown in this age! Surely, that interests you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657654" id2="17" version="1065353216">The machine was his life's work--a perfect puzzle that hid all his secrets. It was a vault and a library all at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657656" id2="17" version="1065353216">The scholars in the Academy--they say the Red Engine was never completed. They say it never functioned. But I know how it works, and I know how to fuel it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657657" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean &quot;fuel it&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657657" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fuel?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then why not inform the scholars?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657658" id2="17" version="1065353216">So tell the Academy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657659" id2="17" version="1065353216">They think that I--not a Sith, nor an educated man--couldn't discover the truth. They ignore my findings and are blinded by arrogance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657661" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're talking about a machine that's been here for centuries. If it still worked, the Sith would know by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657661" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's probably broken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657662" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Sith's power comes from passion--not from decades of study and research. This is the only reason I've learned what they will not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657664" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen, now. Anyone can activate the Red Engine--but unless it receives its sacrifice, it will only sputter and die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657666" id2="17" version="1065353216">The machine needs blood and hatred to become fully operational. If a Sith could slay the tomb's beasts in its presence, their deaths would be its fuel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Broaden your mind! See what your fellows refuse to see. I promise you--it will be worth your while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657669" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. You are wise among the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657672" id2="17" version="1065353216">It may be worth an effort. You're certain this will work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657672" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll look into it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657673" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have spent too many years learning the ways of the tomb, dreamed too many dreams, to be mistaken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why not go yourself?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657676" id2="17" version="1065353216">My anger is not deep enough, nor my sword arm strong enough to satisfy the Red Engine's appetite. But you--you can do this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there compensation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657678" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've found many a lesser artifact in my time within the tombs. I can spare a few to compensate you for your time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657680" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find the machine within the tomb--work its mechanisms.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657682" id2="17" version="1065353216">And when at last it reveals Tulak Hord's secrets, I beg of you--bring me its scripture. Bring me the knowledge I have dreamed of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657684" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're done. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes--yes, of course. I will wait for another, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="657687" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seems unwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657688" id2="17" version="1065353216">With respect, I suggest you stay away from this tomb--you are not ready for the darkness within.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="657689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Move along. There's nothing you can do to help with my research.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
