<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>91</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x3/flashpoint/titans_of_industry/republic/adjudicator_refain_2.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006500" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work at CZ-198. Back to cataloging Czerka's attic space, I suppose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006503" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you made it out of CZ-198 in one piece. And with perfect timing. The Chancellor's signal just came through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006505" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi. Again, you prove yourself to be an indispensable defender of the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impeccable work, Major, though I've come to expect nothing less from Havoc Squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once again I ask for your services, Captain, and once again I have nothing but praise for the results.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006511" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thank you all for your service. The Republic needs its most dedicated, loyal citizens to defend it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006513" id2="17" version="1065353216">I already have a team preparing to sweep CZ-198 and secure the facility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka was doing more than research at CZ-198. It created an alien creature as its security system: the Vigilant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka made a monster there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006515" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is all the information recovered on the creature, Chancellor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006517" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is monstrous even for Czerka. And we've gone easy on them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell the team to be careful. Rasmus Blys didn't release his workforce during the lockdown, and there are still innocent people at CZ-198.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006519" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are workers inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006520" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's other reasons for the team to be careful, Chancellor: the Vigilant. Look at this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006522" id2="17" version="1065353216">CZ-198 has entire rooms of prototype technology and research data, just waiting for someone to claim them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006522" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a treasure trove.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006523" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sending a preliminary report and inventory now, Chancellor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006525" id2="17" version="1065353216">CZ-198 had... a living security system? Genetically engineered? We've been far, far too lenient on Czerka.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006527" id2="17" version="1065353216">I recommend we arrest Czerka's chief executives. We need to interrogate them regarding the Vigilant, and whatever else they're hiding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006529" id2="17" version="1065353216">You just assume every Czerka official is a criminal? This Vigilant creature was made at a closed facility. You can't blame us all for Rasmus Blys's mistakes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006530" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should be better than Czerka, Chancellor. If we want to learn about the Vigilant, we have full access to the labs at CZ-198.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006530" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree. No interrogations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well. But tell your colleagues, Executive Laphmer: If they have any confessions to make, now is the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006533" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll remind them, Supreme Chancellor, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006535" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Vigilant was only the latest horror that Czerka Corporation created. It's about time someone was punished for its crimes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone must answer for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006536" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't right! What happened to Republic justice?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006538" id2="17" version="1065353216">It protects those Republic citizens who obey the law, Executive Laphmer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006540" id2="17" version="1065353216">CZ-198 will be assessed, and its technology reclaimed. My thanks again. I suspect we'll soon be putting Czerka's technology to good use.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rasmus Blys, the Vigilant... what's going on at CZ-198?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reconsider, adjudicator. This information is worth at least one mansion on Alsakan! Adjudicator!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006549" id2="17" version="1065353216">My apology on Executive Laphmer's behalf, Master Jedi. I'm Adjudicator Refain; we're... renegotiating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse the noise, Major, Executive Laphmer has a number of... grievances. Adjudicator Refain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please excuse Executive Laphmer, Captain, he's rather upset. I'm Adjudicator Refain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006555" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have to excuse Executive Laphmer's manners, and... volume. I'm Adjudicator Refain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006557" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm handling the Republic takeover of Czerka Corporation, of which Master Laphmer is--was--a senior executive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka's collapsing under scandals, financial crises and lost factories. Fortunately, the Republic's been authorized to seize Czerka's assets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006560" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't been following the HoloNet news. What is Czerka Corporation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006560" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain Czerka to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006561" id2="17" version="1065353216">For centuries, we were an industry leader in droid and weapons manufacture. Now we're being picked clean.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka Corporation had a lot of wealth and power. What changed that the company collapsed so quickly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006563" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happened to Czerka?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Immoral idiots destroyed our Tatooine operations. Then we lost a fortune during the war, along with key executives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006566" id2="17" version="1065353216">Full access to Czerka Corporation's labs and vaults. You must have recovered quite the haul.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006566" id2="17" version="1065353216">What assets have you claimed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006567" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prototype hardware and rare bio materials--that's just the appetizer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka's cooperating with the seizure. But one of its facilities, CZ-198, rebelled and entered lockdown. No one in or out, no communications.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Executive Laphmer is offering information about CZ-198's security, but he's demanding a mansion and a lifetime salary in exchange.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006572" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about an apartment on Coruscant and a nice safe, bureaucratic job? It's more than most Republic citizens get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scale those demands down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006573" id2="17" version="1065353216">An apartment on Coruscant. This is what I've been reduced to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Adjudicator, you can't expect a Czerka executive to have realistic demands. We need that data on CZ-198 now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time's short. We agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006575" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, done. It's not like our negotiations have got anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006577" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will give that datapad to Adjudicator Refain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006577" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Force Persuade] Hand it over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006578" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll give the datapad to Adjudicator Refain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006580" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, I--thank you. Let's take a look.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trust me, Laphmer, there are worse things than losing your wealth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's my offer. [Punch him]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph. Such as?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting negotiating tactics you have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006586" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is... CZ-198 is a level ten research facility. All of Czerka's top secret data. Classified research projects, banned weaponry....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006588" id2="17" version="1065353216">And, of course it's all protected. By a prototype security system, called &quot;the Vigilant.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka can use any security system it likes, but whatever's hidden at CZ-198 will be brought to light.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka can't hide behind it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006590" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this &quot;Vigilant&quot; is protecting such a high-level facility, Czerka will have spared no expense perfecting it. We should be cautious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006590" id2="17" version="1065353216">That system will be trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006591" id2="17" version="1065353216">With that level of secrecy, I'm guessing CZ-198's bosses won't have let the workers slip through the lockdown.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006591" id2="17" version="1065353216">There'll be civilians inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006592" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course not, that's standard procedure for our--I mean, their, facilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006594" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can give it a fancy name, but every system's got a workaround somewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Security system? No worries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just what kind of security system is the Vigilant? That doesn't sound like a Czerka product.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006595" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is this Vigilant?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006596" id2="17" version="1065353216">The datapad only says that it's a last-ditch emergency measure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006598" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm willing to bet CZ-198 will have plenty of tricks up its sleeve, besides this &quot;Vigilant.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006598" id2="17" version="1065353216">And likely other defenses too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006599" id2="17" version="1065353216">CZ-198 has some of Czerka's oldest, darkest secrets. Forget asset seizure, CZ-198's a genuine threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006601" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need someone I can trust to breach CZ-198's defenses, seize whatever projects are there, and ensure the Vigilant stays offline. Can you do that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006602" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count on me. I'd like to see what Czerka Corporation considers &quot;top secret.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006602" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me where to find this facility and it'll be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where is CZ-198?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006604" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a private moon--off the charts, naturally, but this datapad has all the details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006606" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I go up against the Vigilant and whatever else Czerka's been hiding, I hope the Republic plans to share its windfall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006606" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the reward is right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006607" id2="17" version="1065353216">So long as CZ-198 is secured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006609" id2="17" version="1065353216">One last thing. The overseer at CZ-198 is Special Executive Rasmus Blys. This performance review calls him &quot;dynamic and energetic.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Translation from Czerka-speak: absolutely ruthless. The Vigilant may be the least of your concerns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006615" id2="17" version="1065353216">One minute, this Czerka executive's giving me a headache.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
