<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>6</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x3/flashpoint/titans_of_industry/republic/bounty_board_rep.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1113792" id2="17" version="1065353216">** CZ-198 SYSTEM SLICED -- ENCRYPTED MESSAGE FOLLOWS **

FROM: Capt. Lu Chagra, Rep. Military-Industrial Liaison

Resistance at the CZ-198 facility is worse than we thought, with entrenched Czerka enforcers making our research reclamation efforts extremely difficult. I would consider it a huge favor if you could lessen the enforcers' impact.

** END ENCRYPTED MESSAGE **</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1113793" id2="17" version="1065353216">** CZ-198 SYSTEM SLICED -- ENCRYPTED MESSAGE FOLLOWS **

FROM: Capt. Lu Chagra, Rep. Military-Industrial Liaison

The ZX-10 represents Czerka's most ambitious combat droid design to date, and CZ-198 has mass produced many millions of credits' worth of them. We would love to buy them from Czerka, but Rasmus Blys had the ZX-10 line fitted with a tamper-proof security system that turns any sliced models into the galaxy's most sophisticated statues.

Entering a particular sequence into the ZX-10 storage pods' keypads will destroy the droids within. Please use this code before Blys' enforcers get wise to the idea of powering up the droids for their own purposes. Be warned: you may have to confront the occasional droid that has severed its pod connection before your sabotage is complete.

** END ENCRYPTED MESSAGE **</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1113794" id2="17" version="1065353216">** CZ-198 SYSTEM SLICED -- ENCRYPTED MESSAGE FOLLOWS **

FROM: Capt. Lu Chagra, Rep. Military-Industrial Liaison

Here at CZ-198, Czerka has actually designed and mass-produced an artificial substitute for kolto. Think of the impact this could have on the war effort against the Empire! Snatch up as much as you can, would you?

Speaking of the Empire, we believe their forces on CZ-198 are planning to claim large quantities of a particularly nasty biotoxin for their ongoing chemical warfare program. Destroy any stores of the biotoxin you find before the Imps get their vile mitts on them.

Again: obtain the kolto and destroy the biotoxin. You have my thanks, as ever.

** END ENCRYPTED MESSAGE **</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1113795" id2="17" version="1065353216">** CZ-198 SYSTEM SLICED -- ENCRYPTED MESSAGE FOLLOWS **

FROM: Capt. Lu Chagra, Rep. Military-Industrial Liaison

It appears that Czerka has created an anti-toxin that can be taken before or after exposure to that nasty biotoxin they've manufactured. As our forces arrived here, Czerka employees attempted to flush the anti-toxin into the waste system, but we stopped the facility's trash compactor before it could crush the chemical's containment vessel.

Please retrieve the anti-toxin from the trash compactor so that we might protect our forces--and, indeed, the masses--from this terrible threat.

** END ENCRYPTED MESSAGE **</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1118392" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Republic by completing the following missions on CZ-198:

[DAILY] Workforce Reduction
[DAILY] Manual Shutdown
[DAILY] Give and Take
[DAILY] Anti-Toxin Recovery
Flashpoint: Czerka Corporate Labs
Flashpoint: Czerka Core Meltdown</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1157738" id2="17" version="1065353216">** CZ-198 SYSTEM SLICED -- ENCRYPTED MESSAGE FOLLOWS **

FROM: Capt. Lu Chagra, Rep. Military-Industrial Liaison

A group of panicked engineers have activated one of Czerka Corporation's top of the line military grade Eradicator Droids and deactivated it's target selection protocols.  Left unchecked, it will leave this facility damaged beyond repair.  

Eliminate it before it causes excessive collateral damage.

** END ENCRYPTED MESSAGE **</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
