<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>37</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x3/flashpoint/titans_of_industry/republic/rk_c3.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi! To speak with the defender of Coruscant and Corellia is quite, quite an honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good day, Master Jedi. How pleasant it is to address the protector of the Rift Alliance!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, Major, what an honor--to speak with one of the Republic's greatest defenders!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain! How marvelous to meet the hero of Corellia, the savior of the Republic's finest shipyards!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings! I hate to distract you from the station's glorious Republic architecture, but I'm afraid this is urgent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006637" id2="17" version="1065353216">The esteemed Supreme Chancellor Saresh has sent a message regarding my former masters, Czerka Corporation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006639" id2="17" version="1065353216">In recent years, Czerka has suffered many scandals and financial losses. The Republic has been authorized to begin seizing Czerka assets and property. I myself was a Czerka droid!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka Corporation had a lot of skeletons in its closet. Sooner or later, its past was going to catch up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka has a bad reputation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka Corporation is hundreds of years old; it has more wealth than some planets. I have trouble imagining it falling apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka can't be collapsing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Certain... events on Tatooine and Corellia have been very damaging, Master Jedi. For Czerka, it's this or bankruptcy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006644" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka did a lot of weapons research, right? Here's hoping some of that tech makes it to the front lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006644" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any military assets?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006645" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do hope so, Major. But there is one minor snag--no trouble for you, I'm sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems life off the corporate ladder is working out for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006647" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seem happy about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006648" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, indeed, Captain! But not everyone agrees.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006650" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I've heard of Czerka, but I can't quite place the name....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006650" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is Czerka Corporation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, Czerka Corporation is a pioneer in several fields: droid manufacture, weapons design, biological research and development. Or it was, before this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006653" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think the Republic can just swoop into a corporation's offices and take what it wants.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seizing assets isn't legal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006654" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, it's all been negotiated, partly as compensation for Czerka's, er, miscalculations on Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sadly, one Czerka facility has gone into lockdown, refusing to hand over its assets. It's a remote moon base, called CZ-198.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006658" id2="17" version="1065353216">CZ-198 is a vital facility. The honorable Chancellor Saresh is anxious to see it secured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006659" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we have any idea what Czerka was working on at CZ-198?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006659" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is the facility special?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, all records on CZ-198 were redacted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006662" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Czerka Corporation locked CZ-198 down, it probably has something to hide. I should look into it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006662" id2="17" version="1065353216">So am I.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our beloved Chancellor Saresh said you should speak with a man called Adjudicator Refain for any details. He's handling the Czerka takeover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006665" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here is Adjudicator Refain's contact information. Farewell, fellow Republic citizen!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006667" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have time to get involved in a Czerka-Republic squabble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006667" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't help. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006668" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's very disappointing. But, I'm sure you have your reasons. Farewell!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006672" id2="17" version="1065353216">With my reprogramming complete, I welcome the chance to serve the Republic!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
