<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>55</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris_imp/world/controlled_demolitions/maris_csayni.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, my lord. Maris Csayni, Imperial Intelligence. Your arrival is most fortuitous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, sir. Agent Csayni. Impeccable timing. Having a cipher in the field is more than I could have hoped for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543786" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trust you've found Taris as pleasant as any fetid, rakghoul-infested planet can be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Despite our best efforts, the Republic continues to expand their presence--infecting every corner of this disgusting planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543788" id2="17" version="1065353216">This planet's stubborn refusal to die would be admirable if it weren't so... inconvenient.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543789" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been monitoring the Republic's reconstruction efforts. Their most ambitious project is a joint effort with the Cathar--a massive Tarisian skyscraper.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543790" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;New Tarisian Dawn,&quot; they're calling it; maudlin, I know, but it's already inspired the Republic and Cathar to intensify their efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Morale is the key to winning Taris--or destroying it. The last thing we need is a symbol for would-be colonists to rally behind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543792" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our agents have identified several infrastructural weak points where explosive charges could help reduce that building to smoldering rubble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543793" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, the Republic and Cathar have been training an elite guard to oversee the building's coronation. A more... militant symbol of their alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543794" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need someone to break in and plant those charges. Can you handle this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573793" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps now the Republic sees the futility in trying to revive this planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573794" id2="17" version="1065353216">You return. Judging by those explosions, I'd say your mission was a success.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our recon droids obtained footage of a number of dead snipers. I look forward to studying the holovids later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573797" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can hardly wait to raze that blasted edifice to the ground. For the Empire, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573798" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did my part. If you want off this planet, make sure you do yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573798" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's in your hands now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573799" id2="17" version="1065353216">That building's days are numbered, I assure you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Happy to do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573802" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573803" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll let the Republic play with their pet project awhile longer. Let their spirits get even higher before we crush them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have fun out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, hunter. Maris Csayni, Imperial Intelligence. I'd like to employ your services.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome. Maris Csayni, Imperial Intelligence. Your arrival is well-timed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573815" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's nothing more than defiance for its own sake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573815" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's mere insolence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573816" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's absurd. Only the dead should live in a graveyard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573818" id2="17" version="1065353216">That won't do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573819" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed. The more they establish themselves here, the longer it will take to drive them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573821" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the feeling you don't like it here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not fond of Taris?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573825" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic has to latch onto whatever comfort it can find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573825" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're just desperate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too true. They cling to that tower like an infant clutching its blanket.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroy the building. Problem solved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blow it up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573829" id2="17" version="1065353216">My thoughts, exactly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573831" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your point?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573834" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will bury the Republic in their own ambition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gladly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573835" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's greatest triumph shall become their greatest failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573835" id2="17" version="1065353216">A fitting end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573836" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you'd appreciate the irony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573838" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm used to taking down people, not buildings, but I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573838" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Crush their forces and their spirits. Textbook sabotage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573839" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've done this before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573840" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I can leave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eager to get off this planet, too? I sympathize.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those charges alone won't level the structure, but they'll cripple it so we can easily demolish it when the time is right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573845" id2="17" version="1065353216">One last thing--a team of Republic snipers is camped out on the top floor of the skyscraper.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573847" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've been tracking our movements and directing their ground forces against us. If possible, I'd like to see these upstarts... disposed of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573850" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm busy. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573851" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm never going to get off this planet, am I?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573853" id2="17" version="1065353216">This dying world has limped on long enough.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
