<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>25</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/bronze/biohazard/captain_jaggard.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our bioweapon's safe, and the Republic's fuming--truly a wonderful day on Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720267" id2="17" version="1065353216">The spy was dead when I found him. He hid the bioweapon, but I dug it up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Poor Republic--all that trouble for nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720270" id2="17" version="1065353216">At any rate, congratulations. I'll include a full description of your heroics in my report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720272" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now if you'll excuse me--I must see to the bioweapon's safe transport off Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720274" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire invested years in this bioweapon. We can't lose it now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720277" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm honored, my lord--and grateful. We've suffered a security breach, and Sith help would be most welcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Jaggard, sir. Good to have you. We've suffered a security breach and could use your assistance with our cover-up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720281" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just the hunter I was hoping to see. I have a top secret contract that requires your talents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720283" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd prefer our security breach be known to as few as possible, but discretion's worth less than your combined talents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720285" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly fifty-two minutes ago, a Republic spy infiltrated an Imperial capital ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720287" id2="17" version="1065353216">The blast-happy scum killed sixteen loyal officers and made off with a sample of our most deadly bioweapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720289" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now this spy's on Balmorra, trying to hand the weapon off to the Republic. We must recover it first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720290" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's property will not fall into Republic hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720290" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll retrieve your bioweapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720291" id2="17" version="1065353216">When he shows his face, I'll blast it and grab your poison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720291" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get your bioweapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. This subterfuge must be punished--starting with the spy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720294" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will be too easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720295" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't underestimate this spy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720297" id2="17" version="1065353216">He crash-landed in the swamp. Republic search parties are moving in, but the real problem is the wildlife--Balmorra's nastiest man-eaters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Also... be careful with the bioweapon itself. The casing might be damaged, and I'd rather not have to explain a thousand unplanned casualties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720301" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720302" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see. Well, forget I even mentioned the bioweapon. It doesn't exist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720304" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry--my business is classified.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
