<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>69</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/world/imperial/kingmaker/lieutenant_muir.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Viktus awaits you at the Panteer hideaway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723802" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord? Lieutenant Muir. The matter is dealt with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723804" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. Yet more proof that the servants of the Empire are capable of any task. I'll see to it that you receive your due rewards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect. The Empire is fortunate to have such a capable servant. This accomplishment will be well rewarded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723807" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have served the Empire well, but there is more yet to be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723809" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's next?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I'm done here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723811" id2="17" version="1065353216">So long as enemies remain to be crushed, the Empire's work is never done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723813" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am currently engaged in negotiations with the Panteer survivors at their mountain hideaway. I will arrange for you to be allowed inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be sure to conduct yourself... cautiously. The Panteer hideaway is neutral soil. They won't tolerate uncalled-for aggression.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723817" id2="17" version="1065353216">One obstacle still stands before our plans for House Thul: Bouris Ulgo, the supposed &quot;king&quot; of Alderaan himself. We'll speak more when you arrive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723819" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723820" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell, agent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back. Probes have confirmed the full elimination of Ulgo's strike teams. I will contact Darth Viktus immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723825" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will contact Darth Viktus as soon as the mission is complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723828" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, please stand by a moment. I have urgent orders to put you into contact with my superior, Darth Viktus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah. So you've finally arrived. I've been told that you've accomplished much for the Empire during your service to Darth Baras.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah. You've arrived, finally. I'm told that you've served Darth Zash well in your time as her apprentice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723834" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Darth Viktus. Our Empire has need of you, Sith--here and now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723835" id2="17" version="1065353216">I live to serve, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723836" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would be pleased to do whatever you require, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gladly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent. I am ordered by my superior, Darth Viktus, to place you into direct contact with him at once. Please stand by.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, Cipher Nine. I've heard much about you. Your record of service to the Empire is most impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723841" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Darth Viktus. I am granting you the opportunity to serve your Empire even further--immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723842" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am always honored to serve the Empire, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold up, bounty hunter. I have orders from my superior, Darth Viktus, to place you into contact with him immediately. Don't go anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723845" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah. Lieutenant Muir finally caught up with you. I imagine it comes as no surprise that your... activities have not escaped the Empire's notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723847" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Darth Viktus. Today, you have the opportunity to perform a great service to the Empire. This service will reap plentiful rewards. Do you accept this opportunity?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Somebody's got to reap those plentiful rewards--might as well be me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count me in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold up, there. I am commanded by my superior, Darth Viktus, to inform him immediately upon your arrival. Please stand by.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723851" id2="17" version="1065353216">You. The Empire would like to offer you an opportunity to serve its interests on Alderaan. Immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surely I would be a preferable agent for this task, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave this to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Couldn't a fellow Sith deal with this, my lord?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will the Empire be compensating us for our time and expertise?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723854" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the pay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723855" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rewards for dutiful service are always generous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723857" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm an agent of Imperial Intelligence, my lord. I would be proud to be of assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723857" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could help in this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your participation would be most welcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723860" id2="17" version="1065353216">What exactly is needed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723861" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't help you right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723862" id2="17" version="1065353216">It would be... unwise to ignore the opportunity to serve the Empire's interests.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723864" id2="17" version="1065353216">The task at hand involves House Panteer--the weakened former rulers of Alderaan. Though most believe them wiped out, a few stragglers yet survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723866" id2="17" version="1065353216">These surviving Panteers are needed to legitimize House Thul's eventual rule. We are creating an understanding with them even now, but the forces of House Ulgo plan to interfere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723867" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can I serve the Empire in this matter, my lord?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are the Ulgos so concerned about House Thul?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723868" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is Ulgo's interest?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bouris Ulgo, House Ulgo's leader, was a Republic war criminal before he usurped Alderaan's throne. His hatred of the Empire is well known.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not exactly exciting stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your amusement is not my concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ulgo has strike teams massing thranta for transport. They intend to assault the Panteers' mountain hideaway and slaughter all surviving members of the house.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723876" id2="17" version="1065353216">The eradication of House Panteer would greatly impede our plans for House Thul's ascendance--it cannot be allowed. You will find the Ulgo strike teams and destroy them at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ulgo's men will be eradicated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723879" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would accept nothing less.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723881" id2="17" version="1065353216">When it is done, report back to Lieutenant Muir. We will continue our discussion then. Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="723883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I will, maybe I won't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723884" id2="17" version="1065353216">It would be best if you kept the interests of the Empire foremost in your priorities. Report back to Lieutenant Muir when you have done as you should.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="723888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please excuse me. I have Imperial business to attend to.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
