<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>47</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_01/scene_05_companions_marr.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156964" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're free and clear... but it's not looking good out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156965" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ship is free, all systems in the green. Not sure for how long, though... the situation is pretty grim out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156966" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're clear, but I'm seeing a lot of red dots on the sensor grid out here... what's the plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156967" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're all clear, Captain! More bad guys out here than I can count, though....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156968" id2="17" version="1065353216">That did it--we're free! But, uh... there's an awful lot of those guys out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah! We're loose! Just got to pick one of the million some-odd ships out here to shoot at first....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156970" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're clear to fly... but the odds are not looking good out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156971" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're loose--nice going. But I can't say things are better out here than they were in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1156972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make a break for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156974" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't just leave you behind!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156975" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have to. Please, Kira.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156978" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right... but you'd better be right behind us. May the Force be with you, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156982" id2="17" version="1065353216">And leave you behind? Not a chance!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156983" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is not an option, Major! We are not leaving you here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156984" id2="17" version="1065353216">And leave you in the middle of all this? Not a chance!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156985" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? And just leave you here, in the middle of all this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156986" id2="17" version="1065353216">And leave you here to rot? Are you kidding me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156987" id2="17" version="1065353216">No! We are not leaving you behind!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you joking? You want us to ditch you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do what you can to cover us from out there. We need all the help we can get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1156997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay and defend Marr's ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1156998" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right--we'll give it our best shot. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood. We'll fly a defensive pattern and try to draw some of the enemy fire. Stay safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Copy that--we'll show 'em what Havoc Squad's made of. Good luck, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157004" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can say that again. We'll give it everything we've got--stay alive in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fancy flying, coming right up! Just don't expect any miracles, okay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157006" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time for these slugs to learn who they're messing with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it done--just hang in there, boss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Two against... huh. The readout isn't set for numbers that high. Two against a lot--should be fun. See you on the other side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157009" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm giving you an order, Jorgan. Move it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood. We'll make sure reinforcements and medical crews are ready when you catch up--good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157011" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've gotten out of worse. I'll be right behind you--go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157012" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't be far behind--don't get any ideas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157013" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. I'm gonna hold you to that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157015" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so. We'll hold you a seat at the sabacc table--don't keep us waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157016" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm counting on you. Hurry, Felix.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast it... all right. Just don't be far behind us. We're counting on you, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. It is the only way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157019" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... if you say so. We'll bring whatever help we can find, just... don't die out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157020" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are. Get moving--fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157021" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blasted, stubborn... you'd better be right behind us. I mean it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157023" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you see an opening to escape, take it. Someone has to make it back to the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157024" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you see an opening to escape, take it. Someone has to make it back to civilization.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157025" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you see an opening to escape, take it. Someone has to make it back to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157026" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm commanding you. Hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157027" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. It's your call. Just... do us a favor and don't die out here, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1157031" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy has breached the engineering deck--they're after the primary generator. I'm on my way now--meet me there.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
