<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>97</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/rishi/class/knight/orgus_din.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136567" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell, Padawan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Orgus?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136570" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know, when I died--strange to say that--it wasn't my victories that gave me comfort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136572" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was all their faces--the people I'd helped. The people I'd served. Made the pain forgettable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suppose you last long enough to see the war end. How will you live? How will you find comfort, when your time finally comes?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136575" id2="17" version="1065353216">With or without the war, I'll serve the Order as long as I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136575" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be a Jedi until the end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136577" id2="17" version="1065353216">That means following the code and fighting if I have to. The Republic will always need Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good friend of mine always dreamed of dying in a shop hold-up on Coruscant. There's always something to fight for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136580" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the war ends, I hope to be rid of my lightsaber forever. I want a quiet life--maybe on a farm, or cooking street food on Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136580" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd like to retire someday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sometimes the Force leads us to simplicity. I hope you find what you want.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136583" id2="17" version="1065353216">You make it sound like the end of the Empire would put an end to conflict.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136583" id2="17" version="1065353216">War never ends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136585" id2="17" version="1065353216">There will always be pain, and there will always be struggle. I'll dance that dance forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where there's struggle, there's also hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136588" id2="17" version="1065353216">What we did today--I lied a bit. It wasn't just about helping Rishi or reminding you why you fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136590" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was about healing an old scar you've almost forgotten. One that still aches inside you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136591" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136592" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were under his control. His darkness soaked through to your spirit. When we freed you, you pushed the memories of his training down deep.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136594" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can bring those memories back. You're strong enough to handle them; let the light cure them and make you whole.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136595" id2="17" version="1065353216">I stood against the Emperor on Dromund Kaas. I don't fear him in my memories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. Let me be healed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nor should you. Fear only leads to hate. Today on Rishi, you felt love.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136599" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am whole.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136600" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not looking for healing. What happened... happened. I have to deal with it myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136600" id2="17" version="1065353216">My scars are part of me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then all I ask is that you remember Rishi, and the people you served here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136602" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll remember.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136603" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor immersed me in the dark side. Darth Revan was the only other Jedi to come back from that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136603" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want the darkness I forgot!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136605" id2="17" version="1065353216">My memories of that time are power. That power is my right and my weapon. I claim it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136606" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know I think you're mistaken. No point in another lecture.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136608" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll give you what you asked for and hope you remember the right lesson today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136611" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am whole.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then it's my time to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Master Orgus--for all you've done for me. May it bring you peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136613" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll always remember you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136614" id2="17" version="1065353216">It already has.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136616" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's still much I wish to understand--about the galaxy and the Jedi way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any last advice?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136617" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have all the answers; maybe that's for the best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136619" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were my Master, Orgus Din, but I found my teachers elsewhere. It's past time you rested.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our paths diverged long ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136622" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won't see me again, Padawan, but you won't have to. You won't be alone in the dark days to come.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136624" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force will be with you. Always.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go and do good, Padawan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136627" id2="17" version="1065353216">I grew up here, you know. And I mean here--this house, not just Rishi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, I was young when the Jedi found me. Don't remember much more than the walls, a blanket and a few friendly faces....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136630" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Orgus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136631" id2="17" version="1065353216">...but it seemed as good a place as any to visit one last time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, Padawan. Got time for a final lesson from an old friend?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136634" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to see you, Master. Any lesson you have to share, you know I'll listen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always, Master Orgus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whether you'll act on it is something else, hm? It's good to see you, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136637" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must know that there's great danger on Rishi. Can you guide me against the Order of Revan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this about the Revanites?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136638" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I? Maybe, but it's not really my place--besides, you outgrew me as a planner ages ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then tell me why you're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136640" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may have instructed me on Tython and saved me from the Emperor, but I don't remember us as friends. Does death make you nostalgic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136640" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hoped I was done with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136641" id2="17" version="1065353216">More than you'd think, and we've never been as different as you liked to believe. Don't make me haunt you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are you here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136643" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since you set out to defeat the Emperor, you've been fighting almost nonstop. You've been waist-deep in dirt and fear and blood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since the Emperor's fall, the war's only gotten uglier, and there are dark times coming--for the galaxy and for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136646" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've sensed what's to come?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just a little, and I'm worried you'll forget why you're fighting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Defending the Republic, vanquishing the Sith... those are tools a Jedi uses in the service of life, of people. Not ends unto themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every day, I face pain. I inflict suffering--out of necessity, on those we call &quot;the enemy&quot;... it eats at you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136650" id2="17" version="1065353216">It can be hard sometimes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136651" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the nature of war. I went through it, too. I want to help you reconnect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136653" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I fight, I'm fighting to preserve life, not destroy it. I serve the Force, and the Force is peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136653" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't forgotten, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136654" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't doubt you. But when's the last time you felt connected to that peace?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136656" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think I kill out of passion, out of hunger. You think I've embraced the dark side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136656" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think I've fallen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136657" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not here to scold or tell you how to fight. I'm here to help you reconnect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136659" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're going to take a little time, help the people of Rishi. Folks eking out a living, good and bad, living in fear of guns and pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136661" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're going to make their lives better, as only you can. You're going to feel why you're a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136662" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can think of no better way to spend my time here. Where do we begin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136662" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Orgus, I have an urgent mission. I know what you're saying, but this isn't the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136663" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have time for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136664" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then when is? You can't go on like this, and I promise--we won't let the galaxy die because you were feeding a child.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136665" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've surpassed you, Master Orgus, and I've surpassed the need for this kind of lesson.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136665" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't know what I am now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe so. Then humor me, and I'll make you a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever it is you're seeking to achieve, whatever you want to become--I'll help you when you're done here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136669" id2="17" version="1065353216">How?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136670" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've still got some tricks you haven't seen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136671" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well. Where do we begin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136672" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are a lot of people without homes on Rishi. Those people are catching Tanamen Fever; on Corellia, they'd cure it for free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here, no one much cares. No one but you--your Doc can treat a person in minutes, you've got a ship packed with food and medicine....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136675" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, you do. No Sith Lords, no ancient evils this time. Just doing a bit of good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136678" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's all right. Don't be afraid.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
