<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>24</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/rishi/class/knight/transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136689" id2="17" version="1065353216">How far will the good you've done go? You've changed a lot of lives here and there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those lives will affect others. Ripples can become a tsunami.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136693" id2="17" version="1065353216">Next year will be better. But in ten years, these people will send the pirates packing--those who don't settle down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136695" id2="17" version="1065353216">In a century, Rishi will thrive. The locals will live in harmony with life and nature.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136697" id2="17" version="1065353216">It started today, with you. They won't remember. But be proud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't look like much, does it? But I asked you to do this for a reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better town, cleaner town, gives people pride. Gives a sense of control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136704" id2="17" version="1065353216">But it's also practical. Neighborhoods grow like gardens. They need space, they need to intertwine. You're pulling weeds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wet season's going to be better next year. Folks will work better, eat better. They'll have time to sit and talk and dream of a better future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136709" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can do that when you're not scrambling to survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136711" id2="17" version="1065353216">One more job for you, give you a little exercise. Gang war years back left a lot of buildings in ruin. All that rubble's still there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scrap hauler droids could do the job in hours, but scrap haulers are a luxury for these people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136715" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi with a lightsaber and the Force, though? You could clean it up easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136718" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've changed a lot of lives, but we're not done yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136720" id2="17" version="1065353216">The monsoon baffles protect the spaceport during the wet season--or they're supposed to when they're not broke.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pirates just take shelter, but everyone else spends months wading through water, miserable and struggling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136724" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you suppose they'd use those months for if they weren't hurting?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136726" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got technical training and one of the best astromechs in the galaxy. See what you can do about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136729" id2="17" version="1065353216">This one won't remember you. Don't take it personal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136731" id2="17" version="1065353216">But he will bring joy back into his wife's life. She'll be stronger for it, and she'll build a stronger community.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136734" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too weak to talk, but he'll remember this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not only that, in a few months, he'll be back on his feet. He's a gambler, a con man--but he'll do what it takes to stop the fever on Rishi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136739" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you? Why are you helping us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a lot of trust for strangers on Rishi. Can you blame them?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
