<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>15</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/tython_and_korriban/imperial/lana_transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127878" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're in, but we're not there yet. The Jedi Temple Library is heavily secured. You'll have to find a way to breach the entrance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127879" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't make it to the temple until you do away with the shielding that's keeping our forces confined to the area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko here. As expected, the Republic isn't making our advance to the Jedi Temple easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127884" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Lana Beniko. Not the greatest position, I know, but the Lower Wilds is as close to the Sith Academy as our team could manage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127885" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've received word from Sergeant Tarsten on the ground. It appears your arrival hasn't gone unnoticed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127886" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't envy you right now. I don't know what I'd do if I saw the academy in the enemy's hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our initial strike team had hoped to secure the landing area by now, but enemy reinforcements have been hammering us with heavy artillery fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127890" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's an array of sensors out there guiding the attacks. Destroy them and we'll finally start to make some headway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look for the Republic command platform. That's where you'll find the shield controls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127896" id2="17" version="1065353216">A word of warning: Jedi do adore their libraries. I wouldn't expect to find the room unoccupied, were I you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Encrypted transmissions have been traced back to the Dark Council Chambers. That must be where Republic command is operating from.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127916" id2="17" version="1065353216">We hope you don't find any Dark Council members up there. Captured or dead: either would constitute a gross humiliation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127919" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's pulled out all the stops with this invasion, but we fully expect your retaliation to surpass their efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fight your way up to the Valley of the Dark Lords and reclaim the Sith Academy. Spare no one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127924" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Republic barricade has just been fashioned to bar your progress. While hastily constructed, it is formidable--but we have every faith in you.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
