<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>80</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/tython_and_korriban/imperial/lana_beniko.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1114412" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force ever serve you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1114425" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's Darth Arkous you ought to be addressing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Truth is, I have great deal to say. Now that we're alone, we can have a real dialogue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116613" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Lana Beniko. I need you to meet with me--somewhere private. You may be the Empire's only hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why don't you start by telling me a little bit more about yourself?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's talk about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then start talking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get right to the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116941" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Arkous wouldn't appreciate you going behind his back like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116941" id2="17" version="1065353216">You distrust Arkous?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh. What is it you want to know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116943" id2="17" version="1065353216">What wouldn't I want to know? You fascinate me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116943" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116944" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're unusual for a Sith. You don't even have a title.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116944" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why not &quot;Lord Beniko&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116945" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you end up as advisor to Darth Arkous?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about you and Arkous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116947" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, I don't imagine he would--especially considering what I have to say...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Arkous wasn't entirely forthcoming about his reasons for invading the Jedi Temple--not even with me. He was after a very specific item. An artifact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knowledge, answers, truth, the Force: these are the things I hold dear. Titles don't interest me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116951" id2="17" version="1065353216">Considering the places you've gone, all you must have seen, I'm flattered that you would feel that way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116954" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wanted to better understand war, so I asked to be posted with him. Over time, he came to trust my opinion, so here I am.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we...? Sorry, I don't mean to appear antisocial, but I do have pressing concerns....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116957" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sort of artifact? A holocron, a device, some ancient weapon? The less I'm in the dark, the better I can understand Arkous' motivations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116958" id2="17" version="1065353216">I overheard Arkous talking to Goh. It did seem like they had some ulterior motive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116958" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew something was off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116959" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were successful on Tython. The Republic was humiliated. The rest is irrelevant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116959" id2="17" version="1065353216">So?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116961" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish I could say. Whatever it is, Darth Arkous was in a rage with Lord Goh until he found it. And there's more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116963" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the full scope of the issue ended with Tython, that might be true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116964" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I knew more, I could determine what that motive is. There's very good reason to be concerned about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116965" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meaning?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116966" id2="17" version="1065353216">I now believe that the Republic's attack on Korriban wasn't a retaliation for Tython. It was intended to coincide with our own attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major offensives coordinated across two warring militaries? I'm not saying it's impossible, but it's close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Highly unlikely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116968" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attacking Korriban while the Empire still held the Jedi Temple didn't make much sense to me at the time. It still doesn't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116968" id2="17" version="1065353216">It did seem odd....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116969" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you think that has something to do with what Darth Arkous is up to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you accusing Arkous?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117035" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is a stretch, but these attacks occurred nearly on top of one another, and that cannot be a coincidence. It's all making sense now....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117037" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm his advisor; he's meant to confide in me. He used to, but not anymore. I fear I may now begin to understand why....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117040" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're of great importance to the Empire, yet you exist outside of it. Hunter... I can't think of anyone better suited to be on my side right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117045" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's something in the Force that I've never felt before. It exists nowhere and everywhere at once. Writhing, growing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117046" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should sense that as well. Are you sure?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone like you, Commander--most would never trust you. But you're practically the only one I trust right now. Help me unravel this mystery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117048" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I sense this &quot;growth&quot; because I'm tied to it somehow, maybe by association to Darth Arkous. I think.... I think the Empire's in terrible danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117049" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds ominous....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117051" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm far from weak, but I'm only one Sith. Whatever's coming, I can't stop it alone, Wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117052" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm used to offering my counsel to others... now I turn to you for yours, Dark Lord. Will you help me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nor should it--not from our current vantage point. But a wider context may exist that could explain recent events....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117056" id2="17" version="1065353216">You say you &quot;sense something&quot; and all but accuse Darth Arkous of plotting against the Empire, and I'm supposed to just believe you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1117056" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't trust you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117058" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew I could count on you. I felt it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117061" id2="17" version="1065353216">If my word isn't enough, I suppose I'll have to prove it to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Potential rogue operatives. Galactic repercussions. You've got yourself an ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1117063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intriguing. I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you've got a heap of trouble in your future. Turns out I happen to like trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1117064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could be dangerous. I'm in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117065" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did not join the Dark Council to stand idly by while the Empire crumbles around me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1117065" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will. The Empire won't fall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117066" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone conspiring against the Empire will answer to me and suffer for their foolishness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1117066" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will stop it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117073" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won't have to; you have me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1117073" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] I'll stand with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever you require, you only need but ask, and I will make it so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1117074" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Anything for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117075" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't think of anyone better 'cause there isn't. But you already know that, don't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1117075" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Got that right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't think of anyone else I'd rather do some unraveling with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1117076" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] We'll make a good team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117079" id2="17" version="1065353216">You came. Good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117081" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm aware I've been somewhat quiet following your success on Tython. Don't mistake my reticence for apathy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117085" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose I do....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117088" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see if I can't make sense of what happened on Tython and Korriban and what all of this means.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117090" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever I find, I'll let you know as soon as I can. Stay vigilant, and may the Force ever serve you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117092" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that right...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117094" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well. I'm afraid there's nothing for us to act on just yet. I'll keep my eyes and ears open; you do the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1117096" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have to be at Arkous' side now, but I'll remain in touch. I promise.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
