<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>61</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/imperial/coronet_arms_massacre/lord_malichose.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473084" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen to it that word of your deeds is spreading. Soon every planet will learn the price of defiance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473085" id2="17" version="1065353216">My scouts have reported that you have exceeded even my own high expectations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473087" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will make certain that word of this slaughter is spread throughout the galaxy. Soon none will dare oppose us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473088" id2="17" version="1065353216">This massacre only whetted my appetite for more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473088" id2="17" version="1065353216">How else may I serve you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473089" id2="17" version="1065353216">While I would not deny your zeal, I will be busy spreading word of your victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473091" id2="17" version="1065353216">That wasn't warfare, it was butchery. I should never have agreed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473091" id2="17" version="1065353216">I regret helping you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473092" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your squeamishness is a surprising but natural response. Once you see how you have helped us, you will recover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473094" id2="17" version="1065353216">You cut the very heart out of the resistance. It is the only possible outcome for those who dare oppose the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473095" id2="17" version="1065353216">My skills were wasted on this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473096" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your inability to see the impact of your actions does not concern me. It is not the tool's job to understand the mind of the craftsman.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473098" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your enthusiasm for attacking the Republic's troops is laudable, but the artillery must also be destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473099" id2="17" version="1065353216">The artillery is of important strategic value--but everyone in the hotel must die. The galaxy must learn the price of defiance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473100" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have scouts to give me status reports. Contact me when you are finished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473103" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Lord Malichose. We met on Alderaan once. Your...innovative work fomenting strife there has become standard practice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473105" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your talents at influencing a population might be similarly useful here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473107" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Lord Malichose. I have heard of your strength in the Force. Your skills could serve the Empire perfectly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473109" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Lord Malichose. My sources have told me much about your capabilities, and the Empire has need of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473111" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Lord Malichose. Your service to the Empire has been admirable--but we require more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473113" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Decimus summoned me because he is concerned about the progress of this occupation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473115" id2="17" version="1065353216">The resistance has continued too long. If Corellia is not brought to heel quickly, other planets may follow her example.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only force will crush these insurgents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473116" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been too soft on them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed. The problem arises in their perceptions--they view not surrendering as equal to winning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473119" id2="17" version="1065353216">This resistance must learn that the will of the Empire is absolute.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473119" id2="17" version="1065353216">They cling to hope like fools.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473120" id2="17" version="1065353216">They fight a different war. They believe that not surrendering is winning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473122" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say the word, I am yours to command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473122" id2="17" version="1065353216">How may I serve you, my lord?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473123" id2="17" version="1065353216">Name the target, I'll take care of it. For the proper payment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473123" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me what you want done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473124" id2="17" version="1065353216">Follow my orders, and your name will be on the lips of millions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473126" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's tough to dislodge an enemy when he's got nowhere left to run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473126" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're defending their homes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473127" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sort of sympathetic thinking is responsible for this situation in the first place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473129" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia's not my problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473130" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will not allow your apathy to undermine the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473132" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is not enough to defeat the resistance in battle. We must snuff out their last flicker of hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473134" id2="17" version="1065353216">The encampment in the Coronet Arms Hotel has become a symbol of the uprising. Losing the hotel would gut this pathetic rebellion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473135" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would have expected a target with more strategic value</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473135" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why attack a hotel?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473136" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic has placed artillery within and refuses to abandon it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473138" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we aren't careful, it could make the resistance more determined than before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Symbols are difficult to break.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473139" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is why we must break them utterly and without remorse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473141" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there a way to break them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473142" id2="17" version="1065353216">The soldiers held the hotel through multiple bombardments and repelled two charges. They are now celebrated as heroes across the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473144" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kill them all. Let the resistance see the true price of defying the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473145" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it serves the goals of the Empire, I can do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473145" id2="17" version="1065353216">I consider it my duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your loyalty is unquestioned. While you are within the hotel, the Empire needs one additional service from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473148" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will break their pathetic resistance, without mercy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473148" id2="17" version="1065353216">There will be no survivors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your zeal for bloodshed is admirable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473151" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must disable the Republic artillery as well. We cannot risk them returning to the hotel and using it again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473153" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave none alive, be as...creative as you like. The word will spread quickly and Corellia will weep.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473155" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a difference between military action and committing war crimes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473155" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473161" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only to those who foolishly maintain that war can be civil. No matter, I will find someone more dedicated to our cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473163" id2="17" version="1065353216">This occupation has been handled too softly. A population does not respect what they do not also fear.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
