<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>58</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/world/planetary_checkup/fez_burba.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our business is concluded--but I'm sure you will hear my name again in the context of some brilliant finding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682904" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back, my illustrious colleague. Tell me you've taken the seismic readings?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="682905" id2="17" version="1065353216">I managed the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="682906" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't break a sweat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fantastic. I tell you, we are going to make history together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="682908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't know why I bothered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682909" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can you say that? We're going to make history with these results!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quickly. Please, let me examine the Burba Seismic Activity Reader....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Incredible. My genius is truly incredible. My theory is accurate. The planet is in danger! This reading proves it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682914" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were right. I suppose you'll be getting your grant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="682914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. Yes, I suppose I will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682917" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think we should evacuate the planet just yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="682917" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's not be hasty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682918" id2="17" version="1065353216">Far more research will have to be done to convince the Senate, but this will get the ball rolling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682920" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure you should be so pleased.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="682920" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a callous attitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scientific discovery is always thrilling, my friend. I assure you, I am not celebrating the implications of this finding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Worry not. You have done a great deed today. Take your reward and celebrate!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682924" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? It can't be. This indicates there is no unusual seismic activity at all!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682925" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seems your theory proved to be incorrect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="682925" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, but it's true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682926" id2="17" version="1065353216">This means the planet won't be destroyed, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="682926" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's good news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes... I mean, of course. I'm just surprised. It's atypical for one of my theories to be wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682928" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing wrong with the reading I took.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="682928" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't mess up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682929" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just can't believe it. I haven't been wrong in so long....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682931" id2="17" version="1065353216">This could reflect very poorly on my reputation. I suggest you take your compensation and keep quiet--I believe the reward is generous, given the outcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682933" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, if you'll excuse me, I have much to consider. Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682935" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you waiting for? I need the seismic readings as soon as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682938" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi! Thank you for coming over. I am Fez Burba, scientist-notary of the Republic and planetary consult to the Galactic Senate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally, military assistance! I am Fez Burba, scientist-notary of the Republic and planetary consult to the Galactic Senate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, humble citizen. I am Fez Burba, scientist-notary of the Republic and planetary consult to the Galactic Senate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682952" id2="17" version="1065353216">My current project could alter history. If my theory proves correct, I will be the most famous scientist who ever lived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682954" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider this--we all know the Imperial bombardment of Coruscant wreaked havoc on the infrastructure. But what if it also damaged the planet's very core?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would there be a way to repair the damage?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="682955" id2="17" version="1065353216">What could be done?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps, depending on the extent of it... but most likely, the planet would have to be evacuated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="682957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Damage to the core could cause geothermal instability, plate fragmentation--in short, level the whole city.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682959" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the stupidest thing I've ever heard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="682959" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're crazy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682960" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assure you, it's not impossible. The bombardment of Lexus Nine created a rift beneath the surface that caused unprecedented cataclysms. Everyone died.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682962" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is crucial that I get seismic readings from the lower levels. Specifically, from the Works sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682972" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the spirit of scientific inquiry and on behalf of the safety of the Republic, I need you to perform this critical mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prove my theory correct, and the Senate will grant me a substantial endowment for further research. I will give you a generous reward as compensation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682975" id2="17" version="1065353216">If your theory's incorrect--what happens then?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="682975" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if you're wrong?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682976" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will still pay, of course, but your compensation will be significantly less.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682978" id2="17" version="1065353216">All that's required is that you take the Burba Seismic Activity Reader--my invention, of course--and use it in the Works.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682980" id2="17" version="1065353216">The reader is both accurate and user-friendly. The challenge will be in the journey, not in the science.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="682982" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682983" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should warn you--in the unlikely case that my theory is wrong, I'll have to pay significantly less. Budgetary constraints, you know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682985" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get lost, you pompous freak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="682985" id2="17" version="1065353216">No way. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well. You certainly don't have to be rude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="682988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, not right now! I'm working.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
