<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>138</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/macrobinoculars/roth/imperial/evie_bo.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103802" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah. Our hero returns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103804" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our heroes return. Very good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Had you merely stopped the Shroud's craven attack, I would have been content. But to strike a name from my most-wanted list.... All the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't believe I followed that maniac. Thanks to you, I don't gotta worry about him ever again. The Shroud can't touch me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deposit the credits to my account, Mortis. I'm out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103809" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we're done here...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103810" id2="17" version="1065353216">The survival of the Empire is all that mattered here, as I would imagine Darth Mortis has already made clear to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103810" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't kill him for you, Bo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103811" id2="17" version="1065353216">What will you do now that you're no longer employed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103811" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's next for you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Working for a spy, one thing you can't do is see your family. So maybe that--if Darth Mortis says I'm free to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103814" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shroud wasn't quite as formidable as I was led to believe. I'm surprised you never caught him, Mortis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103814" id2="17" version="1065353216">He wasn't so tough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103815" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid Darth Mortis cannot hear you. I control the holo now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103817" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did so enjoy your fevered battle against my double. He did have the look down, but sadly lacked my fighting prowess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103819" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll--I'll help them find you, Shroud. Help them find you and kill you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Evie. Oh, Evie. It saddens me to do this, but you've left me no choice. With but a word, I bid you farewell....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103823" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Asunder.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agh! No...! No!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103827" id2="17" version="1065353216">A neural scrambler, activated upon my utterance of the trigger word. She's gone now, our Evie. Well--her memories, at any rate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103828" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say any word you like, Shroud. You're an insignificant coward for not facing me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103831" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not as though I wouldn't enjoy that, Wrath. It's merely inconvenient for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103833" id2="17" version="1065353216">It would seem you aren't a master strategist after all; rather a master of theatrics. Pathetic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103834" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do try, but we can't all put on airs from the storied halls of the Dark Council, can we?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cheap tricks and doubles? Nothing I haven't seen before, Shroud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103837" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would expect such confidence from a veteran of the Blacklist--but believe me, hunter, you've seen so very little.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103839" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you were truly a master spy, you wouldn't have tipped your hand so soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless I was so sure of my state of security that I had nothing to fear from anyone--including you, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103842" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have to remember that one for the next time I'm betrayed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103843" id2="17" version="1065353216">You would have to duplicate my original design first. I don't see it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103845" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll run out of doubles eventually, Shroud, and when that day comes....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103845" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll kill you, Shroud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well. This has been a truly fascinating effort. I may not have succeeded in my goal, but if not for my failure, we would never have met.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103848" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do look forward to sparring again--so to speak. I'll see you around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103850" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shroud? Alive? And what's wrong with her?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103852" id2="17" version="1065353216">What am I doing here? Who are you? And... and who....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who am I?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103855" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a veteran mercenary who will use those skills to serve the Empire for the remainder of her life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103855" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the Empire's property.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103856" id2="17" version="1065353216">I--I am? If you say I am, then... okay. I must be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103858" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm satisfied with that arrangement--so long as her talents have remained intact, of course. She's worthless to us otherwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103860" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm needed elsewhere. Good work saving Kaas City from that madman. You may keep the macrobinoculars. Consider them a bonus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your intervention was instrumental in ending the Shroud's plot. The least the Empire can do in return is help you recover your mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103863" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire will help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103864" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103866" id2="17" version="1065353216">A fair enough plan. After all, the information lost in her head is surely of value to us, considering the Shroud is still at large.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103868" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire is safe for now. You've done well. You may keep the macrobinoculars--with my compliments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103873" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's it. You did it. Kaas City's safe. Mortis says he wants to debrief you, so guess you better come on back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103875" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't believe it. You killed the Shroud!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now quick--shut down the works before that ship comes crashing into Kaas City! Hurry!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay--structural weaknesses, a dreadnaught, a ship remote and... schematics for a hyperspace beacon? And.... No. Aw, no.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103882" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shroud's planted a hyperspace beacon in Kaas City! Now he can pull the dreadnaught out of hyperspace within the planet's atmosphere! He'll crash it into the city!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103884" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll tell Mortis we gotta hunt for this beacon on Kaas, but it could be anywhere! Only way to shut all this down is to find the Shroud!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Luckily, his ego gave him no choice but to keep taunting you. I used those calls to triangulate his location. Go. Go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103889" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Mortis ain't gonna sound any alarms on Kaas, you know. No preemptive evacuations--except for himself, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got your new coordinates. You know the drill--smash, bash and grab.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow. Any regrets I might've had about abandoning the Shroud are gone. Wouldn't wanna be in your way....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Huh. Operating instructions for a ship remote. Must be for that dreadnaught. Can't remote pilot that thing into Kaas without planetary defenses kicking in, so....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, I'm stumped. But here--got a treasure trove of relay data we can use. We're close. I'm feeling it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103901" id2="17" version="1065353216">There we go. Pinged another lieutenant. Can't make sense of the Shroud's plan of attack yet--let's keep plowing on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heh. Nice. Never saw eye to eye with that one, anyway. Okay, got your data packet... Invoices, more invoices....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103905" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shroud recently bought himself... a dreadnaught? Right, like he's got a crew to man a ship that big.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Datastamp confirms it's connected to the report on Kaas, though. Also gives us some more of the network to play with. New coordinates for you. We're getting there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103910" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know, this is actually kinda fun. I could get used to tearing down the Shroud's network....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, got enough here to put you into the next lieutenant's neighborhood, but you still gotta triangulate the doorstep yourself. Coordinates updated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103922" id2="17" version="1065353216">There. We got enough to pin down the lieutenant's location. Now go do your worst.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey--that's one of the Shroud's spy droids. Won't help us triangulate anything, but keep an eye out for more of them suckers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103926" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yep, that's it--that's exactly what you're looking for. Keep at it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, I just thought of something we might wanna look into. Coordinates plugged in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103929" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shroud's out there. Go get him!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103932" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see you've finally arrived. Let me introduce you: this is Evie Bo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103934" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can speak for myself, okay? I'm top lieutenant to the galaxy's most brilliant freelance superspy, the Shroud. I mean, I was.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103935" id2="17" version="1065353216">The who?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103937" id2="17" version="1065353216">No mere spy can stand against the unchecked power of the Force--certainly not some supposed legend I've never heard of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103938" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt this &quot;brilliant&quot; character is a match for me; I'd have heard of him otherwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103939" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so, my lord. But there's a reason you haven't heard of him before now: he's that good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103941" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this guy's wanted so badly, how come I've never heard of him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103942" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're saying there's a prominent spy that I haven't heard of? Am I hearing you correctly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103943" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shroud's taken to laying so low he's just about been forgotten. Won't be true much longer, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103945" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you don't work for him anymore? What happened?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103945" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Was?&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103946" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happened is the whole reason I'm here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103948" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mind your manners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103950" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't go around spouting off at Darths. Me, I can get away with it--but you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103951" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch how you address your betters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103952" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let her speak as she will. I find her base gruffness... quaint.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103954" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shroud's been semi-retired a while, but he got fidgety. Took a gig from the Hutt Cartel to spy on you guys. Republic, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems in all his spying, the Shroud's found something. A challenge. He's planning some kinda rogue attack--on Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me everything you know about this attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103957" id2="17" version="1065353216">He has to be stopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103958" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the problem. I tried to uncover what I could...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this a political statement? Some sort of revenge?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would he attack?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Morality, petty emotional stuff--that don't enter into it. Can he do it and can he get away with it? That's what matters to him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103963" id2="17" version="1065353216">You say the Hutt Cartel's been spying. What are they after?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103963" id2="17" version="1065353216">What were the Hutts up to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some business on Makeb? The Hutts wanted to make sure they had all their angles covered first. Didn't care, didn't ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Repeat what you told me, Bo. Explain why you've turned traitor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103968" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shroud, he always consults with me. This time, though--nothing. So I pried. Learned about Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103970" id2="17" version="1065353216">An attack on the Empire? That's suicide. Told him as much. As thanks for speaking my mind, he tried to have me killed, so here I am.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103971" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were right to come here. Your boss has signed his own death sentence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103971" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is indeed suicide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. That's what I needed to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your employer clearly doesn't know what an asset he has.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103974" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] He's a fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pouring it on a little thick, pal. Let's stick to the impending doom on the Empire's capital world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lady, I'm flattered, but it ain't me you should be thinking about right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, please--let us continue with the matter at hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103981" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we know you aren't just some disgruntled employee making things up? Or a double agent?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103981" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't buy it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103982" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're smart to be on your guard. I would be, too--but I ain't lying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103984" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can assure you our interrogators have thoroughly &quot;vetted&quot; our informant. She's being quite truthful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like I said, he told me nothing--but I got a line on where another lieutenant's holed up. And I got special macrobinoculars to help you find him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103988" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're the Shroud's design--beyond top of the line. Contracted the parts from all over, assembled them himself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103990" id2="17" version="1065353216">These macrobinoculars are no mere magnifiers; they're fitted with a wide range of analytical and communications applications, even a Miraluka interface. They will be utterly indispensable in your search.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103991" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would prefer to find this &quot;Shroud&quot; and choke the details out of him, but I suppose this method will have to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103991" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be your... investigator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103992" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find plenty resistance, if that's your thing. Might even face the Shroud himself, and he's no pushover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103994" id2="17" version="1065353216">No doubt this &quot;Shroud&quot; has already set his plans in motion. I suggest we employ haste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time is short. Let us begin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103995" id2="17" version="1065353216">The meter's on and the chrono's ticking. Tell me where I'm headed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103996" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm all for saving the Empire from harm, but I'll be disappointed if I don't meet this so-called &quot;superspy.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope I can meet this &quot;Shroud.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103997" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this goes as expected, he'll wanna meet you, too. But I wouldn't wish that meeting on anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bo, you said I'm looking for a lieutenant.... What information will he have?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103999" id2="17" version="1065353216">What will I find?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104000" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shroud keeps his data fragmented across his entire surveillance network. That lieutenant will have a piece of the Shroud's plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104002" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know.... This all sounds like paranoid nonsense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104002" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remain unconvinced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104003" id2="17" version="1065353216">An attack on Dromund Kaas could easily be catastrophic for us. We have no choice but to be ever vigilant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104005" id2="17" version="1065353216">The lieutenant's basic coordinates are already plugged into the binocs. You'll use them to find key relay points that will help us triangulate an exact position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104007" id2="17" version="1065353216">While you're out there, I'll be scrounging together more intel. I'll keep up on your progress through the binocs and keep you informed of whatever I find, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104009" id2="17" version="1065353216">May your actions be swift and your results beyond reproach; the fate of the Empire requires it. Mortis out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah? What're you looking at?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess I owe you my thanks? Can't remember why, though....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
