<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>42</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/class/trooper/general_garza.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come in, Captain. This is General Garza. I understand you've just docked over Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hoth is locked in a three-way resource battle between the Republic, the Sith Empire and a powerful alliance of pirate warlords. It's pure chaos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670916" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be sure to stay on my toes, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670916" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670917" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's so valuable on an ice world?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670917" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why fight over Hoth?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670918" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hoth was the site of a major fleet battle during the first war. Many advanced warships, both Republic and Imperial, crashed on its surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670920" id2="17" version="1065353216">Both sides need the material from those ships, and both sides want to learn the secrets of the other. The pirates, of course, see opportunity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670921" id2="17" version="1065353216">If our people need help, they can count on Havoc Squad's support.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670921" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do what I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670922" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure any assistance would be deeply appreciated, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670924" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have to keep my eyes open for any ship-mounted weaponry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670925" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure your new recruit can help you in that regard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670927" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm here to recruit a new member for Havoc Squad, not to fight over scraps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not my problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670928" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are pieces of highly valuable technology--something your new recruit understands quite well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670930" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Hoth were a nice place, I wouldn't be here, would I?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670930" id2="17" version="1065353216">No surprise there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take it as a good sign--your new recruit can clearly take care of himself if he can survive a tour on Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670933" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're recruiting a technical specialist named Sergeant Yuun. Judging by his service record, he's the finest technician in the entire Republic military.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun is a Gand, an uncommon species in the Republic, and he follows an indigenous shamanistic training. No one understands it, but his results are unmatched.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670936" id2="17" version="1065353216">If he can get the job done, then I'll be glad to have him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Results are what counts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whether through mystical powers or luck, Yuun's gained a reputation from his squad-mates for doing the impossible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670939" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's a Gand?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gand?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gands are insectoid bipeds, native to a planet of the same name. They rarely leave their homeworld, making Yuun doubly exceptional.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad isn't the place for some nutjob shaman.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a freak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670943" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad is the place for the best, Captain, and Yuun more than qualifies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Currently, he's scavenging crashed Imperial warships to piece together a functional Umbra encrypter--the machine responsible for the Empire's most secure military codes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670947" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's critical that Yuun completes the Umbra encrypter--we've never come close to breaking the code, and the amount of intelligence we could gain is immense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670948" id2="17" version="1065353216">With Havoc's help, the job will be done in no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670948" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make it happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670949" id2="17" version="1065353216">As long as I see some action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670950" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have to contend with both pirates and Imperial troops in order to locate the Umbra components Yuun needs. Combat is a certainty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670952" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you forgotten the massive superweapon we need to destroy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670952" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have more important goals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670953" id2="17" version="1065353216">This could give us information to help bring it down--or uncover the next major Imperial threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun has already been informed of his transfer into Havoc Squad. I'm told he's excited to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contact me again when the mission is concluded and Yuun has completed the Umbra encrypter. Garza out.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
