<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>269</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/class/trooper/yuun.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun will meet you aboard your ship presently, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant, our mission is complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain! Truly, your journey has been one of unrivaled heroism and accomplishment. Yuun stands in awe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498469" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would never have pulled it off without you and your squad, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498469" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had plenty of help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad could never have done this without you and your team, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498470" id2="17" version="1065353216">We had plenty of help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun is honored simply to have had a part in these occurrences, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just another amazing success.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your expertise is certainly without equal, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we go now?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498477" id2="17" version="1065353216">This journey is very nearly complete, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun must now guide this final piece into its place, thereby completing the whole. A moment, please.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498481" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is done. The Umbra encrypter, returned to functionality. Vast knowledge of our enemies can now be uncovered with ease.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498482" id2="17" version="1065353216">This could change the entire face of the war, Sergeant. You should be proud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498483" id2="17" version="1065353216">This journey was merely part of Yuun's duty to the Republic, nothing more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any Imperial transmissions we can test it on?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's try it out!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun apologizes, but only this test phrase regarding grain allocations was available. All other transmissions are highly classified.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498488" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't exactly exciting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun assures you, sir, many of our comrades will be ecstatic to begin testing this work.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun would ask a small favor of you now. Many preparations must be made before Yuun embarks on Havoc Squad's path.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could you do Yuun the honor of formally delivering the Umbra encrypter to Colonel Fierros, Yuun's former superior?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498494" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would be honored, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498495" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is Yuun who is honored by your indulgence, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498497" id2="17" version="1065353216">I only helped, Sergeant. You should be the one to turn this in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498497" id2="17" version="1065353216">This should be your honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun's deeds are done, and many already know of them. Other tasks must take precedence now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498500" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll run your errand for you if it gets us out of here faster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498500" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is ridiculous.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun appreciates your assistance in this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once all preparations have been made, Yuun will meet with you aboard your ship, sir. Thus, will our new journey begin.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun will meet you at Aurek Base upon the hunt's completion. Journey well.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498508" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pirates' stronghold is in the Star of Coruscant, a crashed Republic superdreadnaught. Legions of cutthroats guard its approach.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498510" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last Umbra component is there. Please, Captain--will you brave the guns of our enemies and finish this hunt at last?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498511" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get the last component, no matter what the opposition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Affirmative.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498512" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your bravery is truly unsurpassed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498514" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's one more daring and impossible assault?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498514" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've made it this far.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun cannot express how much Yuun appreciates the many dangers you have faced in the walking of this path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aren't you going to help me out on this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498517" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not coming, too?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun regrets that Yuun cannot join in this last journey. Yuun's squad is shattered and must return to base.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498520" id2="17" version="1065353216">While you acquire the last piece, Yuun will assemble the rest. Please meet with Yuun at Aurek Base when your hunt is complete. Journey safely, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain! Thank you, your arrival is very fortuitous. These pirates seemed to come from nowhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498526" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I see Corporal Sajin is not with you. What has happened, Captain?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498527" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pirates hit Sajin's team before I arrived. There were no survivors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sajin's team was KIA.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sajin's team was wiped out before I could get there. My condolences.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498528" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, but he's dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun appreciates your kindness, sir. Their sacrifice will not be forgotten.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498531" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pirates wiped the floor with Sajin and the others. No one survived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498531" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were slaughtered.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun... sees.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, you knew pirates were attacking, and you didn't call to warn us?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Silence, Private. The captain would surely have called if it had been the right action to take. Is that not so, Captain?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498537" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did what was necessary to accomplish our objectives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498537" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun does not follow your meaning, but this can be discussed later. Other concerns stand before us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498540" id2="17" version="1065353216">I tried to call, but it was no good, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498540" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] Uh, my holo didn't work.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun understands. Signal transmission has been a great problem for Republic forces on Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498543" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pirates couldn't know we were on to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498543" id2="17" version="1065353216">I needed you to be the bait.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain... this is most disturbing. Yuun hopes you will not use Yuun in this manner in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain. Thank you for your timely warning. Yuun fears to imagine what might have happened without your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498547" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're soldiers; we look out for each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498547" id2="17" version="1065353216">No problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun is honored to share brotherhood with one like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498550" id2="17" version="1065353216">It must be tough, losing Sajin and the others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry about your losses.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. But death is merely the final path of all beings. Dwelling on it only wastes thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498553" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you could predict the future, Yuun. You shouldn't have needed my warning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't see this one coming?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498554" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is true. Yuun has had little time to meditate on the signs recently. This has cost us most dearly.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498556" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pirates' interest in the Umbra encrypter is troubling. Yuun had thought only the Republic would seek this knowledge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498558" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found something, sir--it's a recording one of the pirates was carrying. Let's see here--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498560" id2="17" version="1065353216">--got a chance at serious credits on this one. If you fail me in this, I'll hang your hides on my walls!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave no witnesses. Grab the Umbra parts at these coordinates, and don't come back to the Star of Coruscant without them--got it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498565" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did pirates learn about the Umbra?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498566" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is a perplexing mystery, but we have no time to meditate on its meaning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498570" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the Star of Coruscant?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498571" id2="17" version="1065353216">An old Republic superdreadnaught, lying broken upon Hoth's surface. It is the pirates' stronghold, guarded by an army of murderers and thieves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498575" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hunt this scum down and take her out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498576" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last Umbra component is surely in her possession. The only path is confrontation.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only two more Umbra components are needed to complete the reconstruction. Signs lead to two caves within this region.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498580" id2="17" version="1065353216">To speed our hunt's conclusion, Corporal Sajin has led part of Yuun's team to search the first of these caves, near your current position. Could you assist him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498581" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll meet up with Corporal Sajin right away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Affirmative.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you very much, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure, Yuun. I'll keep your kids out of trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Babysitting, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun has no offspring. Yuun's concern is for Corporal Sajin and his team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surely Corporal Sajin can handle a simple search op.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't he take care of himself?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun does not doubt Sajin's ability to find the Umbra component. Yuun is concerned for Sajin's safety.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Premonitions of danger lurk in Yuun's mind. Perhaps our enemies closing in... please be cautious, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498591" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep my eyes open, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Copy that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498592" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no doubt in Yuun's mind that Havoc Squad can conquer any approaching threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun will proceed to the second cave while you meet Sajin at the first. Please come and meet with Yuun once Sajin's work is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498596" id2="17" version="1065353216">What have the signs shown you, Yuun?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me what you've seen.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. Bloodthirst. Fury. Desperate desire for the Umbra components but limited understanding of the machine's purpose. And above all, fear of failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course you sense danger--we're in a war zone!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498599" id2="17" version="1065353216">More useless mysticism.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498600" id2="17" version="1065353216">This threat is more specific--something harries our path, seeking the same ends with a different purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498602" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun will meditate more on this while searching the second cave. Please meet Yuun there when Sajin's search is complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Journey well, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain--Yuun congratulates you on your success against our enemies. No Imperial troops have interrupted the team.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain--the diversion has succeeded. Yuun's team has discovered much promising salvage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take your time, Sergeant, I'm keeping the Imps busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498609" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll hold here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun appreciates your noble risks on behalf of our hunt for knowledge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498612" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the best time I've had in a while!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498612" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're missing some fun!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun is encouraged by your positivity.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please contact Yuun from Senth Outpost nearby when your battle is complete. Holo signals transmit poorly in this area, and the transmitter there is much stronger. Yuun out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498617" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm collapsing the cave and making my way out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to go. [Detonate charges]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun is pleased that the detonators are of assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please contact Yuun from Senth Outpost nearby once you've escaped--signals are poor here, and the holotransmitter there is much stronger. Yuun out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Journey safely, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun has meditated on the recovered data and determined the wrecks likely to bear Umbra encrypter parts. But Yuun also discovered this:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Outpost Four-two-seven, this is Major Artano, information control specialist for General Rakton's command group.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic personnel are searching Imperial shipwrecks on Hoth. This cannot continue. Full security details will be posted at all crash sites immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498629" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am en route to Hoth now. Any questions about General Rakton's orders may be addressed to me upon arrival. Glory to the Empire!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498630" id2="17" version="1065353216">Might be harder to get those Umbra pieces, now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498630" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who's this General Rakton?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498631" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Rakton?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498632" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Rakton. Commander of forward assault operations, Imperial military forces. Believed responsible for all major campaigns in Republic space.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakton? He's Republic enemy number one--the man who plans and leads all of the Empire's major campaigns against us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498636" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Rakton is the Empire's top field commander and campaign planner. Supposedly, he's never been beaten.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498638" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakton? He's that big-time Imp general, right? The one they claim never lost so much as a school brawl?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun knows only rumors. Rakton is said to be the Empire's marshal, guiding their soldiers' many belligerent works against the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498642" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do we do now, sir? The Empire knows we're coming!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498643" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Empire puts up guards, then we fight through them, soldier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498643" id2="17" version="1065353216">We deal with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498644" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, sir, Captain, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498646" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pull yourself together!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apologies, sir. It won't happen again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Care to divine a magical solution for us, Sergeant?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your problem, Yuun--fix it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498650" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've drawn the Empire's full attention now. Great work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498650" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is your fault, Yuun.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun believes we can turn this situation to our advantage. Many sites to be guarded have no Umbra components at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498653" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Havoc Squad attacks one of these useless sites, guards would be drawn away from the others, allowing Yuun's squad to acquire Umbra components elsewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498654" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just pick a crash site and we'll move out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498654" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice thinking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess there's no other choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498656" id2="17" version="1065353216">This path may be difficult, but Yuun is certain that the final result will be worthwhile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Getting shot at to cover your moves isn't my idea of a good time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498658" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like playing decoy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498661" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best plan we're going to get, sir. And Havoc can take the heat.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498664" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun regrets this, but Havoc Squad can face the danger far better than Yuun's team.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498666" id2="17" version="1065353216">A nearby cave is guarded by the Empire. Assaulting it should draw much attention from our enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here, Captain--please take these detonators. If the Imperial reinforcements become too much, you can collapse the cave and escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's make it happen, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498670" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498671" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun is confident that Havoc Squad can surpass any enemy or barrier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498673" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never back down from a fight, Yuun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498673" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not a coward.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun would never doubt the courage of Havoc Squad's famed leader.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun's team will finish reloading and depart immediately. Journey safely, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498678" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was incredible. I can't believe we pulled it off!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498680" id2="17" version="1065353216">All ends can be reached if the proper path is followed, Sajin. One need only be wise and shrewd enough to see it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498681" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and your team should be very proud of your performance, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work, everyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498682" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun is honored by your praise, Captain. With Havoc Squad's help, we have walked a path that we never could have walked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498684" id2="17" version="1065353216">What were you able to learn from the database, Sergeant?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's save the chat for later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498685" id2="17" version="1065353216">My team did all of the hard work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgetting Havoc Squad's help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498686" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did all of the hard work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgetting my help already?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498687" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun's team was fortunate to have your assistance, Captain. Your help opened a path that would not otherwise have been available.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain. Yuun wishes to thank you for protecting the lives of Yuun's team, but also to warn you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turrets defend the halls you approach. A powerful force field lies beyond them, impassable and impenetrable to weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498693" id2="17" version="1065353216">The force field cannot be disabled remotely, but its structure is familiar to Yuun. Nearby control panels may be accessed and connections severed to allow passage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Flank and sabotage the turrets ahead--sounds like a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Copy that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498695" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun only wishes that more could be done to clear your path to the knowledge we seek.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498697" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure how to disable a turret that way, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498697" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not very technical.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your concern is understood. Yuun will endeavor to provide assistance when called for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498700" id2="17" version="1065353216">First I have to bail you out, now you can't even disable turrets!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you any use at all?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498701" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun apologizes for informing you of unpleasant truths.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Journey carefully, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, please stand by. Yuun will remove the security door from your path momentarily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498708" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll hold this position until you get the door open.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498708" id2="17" version="1065353216">Copy that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498709" id2="17" version="1065353216">No obstacle stands long in the path of knowledge, Yuun assures you. The way will be open shortly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Much obliged.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498711" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun is pleased merely to apply skill in service of our greater cause. The way will be clear presently.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498712" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun apologizes. The way will be clear as soon as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498715" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, Yuun has discovered that an alarm has been raised, and troops are being summoned to the location of Yuun's team.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498717" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials' numbers are too great. Yuun's team will surely be slain unless Havoc Squad intercepts these enemies in their barracks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498718" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll hit the barracks and stop the Imps immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498718" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun humbly thanks you for your help. Harmonious actions usher victory and truth ever closer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498721" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you soldiers or not?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun is shamed that this situation has occurred. Please accept Yuun's humblest apologies and thanks for your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498724" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun's team requires some preparation. We will begin our infiltration presently.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498725" id2="17" version="1065353216">The signs guide Yuun to the Crescent Canyon Facility nearby. It was built by Ortolan colonists but is now conquered by Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial computers in the facility will contain locations of Imperial shipwrecks. Imperial shipwrecks will contain the Umbra components we seek. Do you follow?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Having the Imperials' own records should speed up our search.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Affirmative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Searching the Imperials' computers can't hurt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498729" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess so.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498730" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun senses your hesitation. Experience no negativity--our search will assuredly yield great knowledge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498732" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we know the Imps' computers actually have the info we need?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498732" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you basing this on?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498733" id2="17" version="1065353216">The signs are many. As Yuun explained to Sajin, the smoke damage on the last component we discovered reveals the terrain we must tread.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498735" id2="17" version="1065353216">The crescent pockmark indicates the Crescent Canyon Facility and the faded coolant halo symbolizes the knowledge to be gained there. Do you follow?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's assume you're right; what's your plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498736" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498737" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, burn marks on a piece of metal are your clues?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498737" id2="17" version="1065353216">Huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498738" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is right! You understand very quickly. Yuun is a Findsman and follows these signs to quarry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498740" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to base a military operation on this nonsense?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498740" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're full of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun is a Findsman. On Gand, Findsmen follow signs like these to locate their quarry, as Yuun does here. The quarry is never lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial security in the Crescent Canyon Facility is very strong. There are many dangers and sealed doors within that must be bypassed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun's team will disable the security measures from the wings while Havoc Squad activates the Imperial database. Is this agreeable?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc is used to going in first. Just point us in the right direction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Affirmative, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see where this crazy ride goes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure, why not?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498748" id2="17" version="1065353216">I decide who goes where, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498748" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make the decisions here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, disabling security will require Yuun's technical skills. If this is not done, the database cannot be reached.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before infiltration begins, Yuun asks that Havoc Squad disable motion sensors which would alert the Imperials to our intentions. They are spread across the facility's perimeter.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun will contact you when infiltration has begun. Please journey carefully, newfound friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498757" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you see here? Tracing the lines of the smoke damage, we see our path through the snows. Each piece shows signs leading us to the next.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498759" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's amazing. I never would've imagined--officer on deck!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain! Yuun is pleased to make your honorable acquaintance, and to share this hunt for knowledge with one so renowned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why don't you give me the details of your operation, Sergeant?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498762" id2="17" version="1065353216">At ease, everyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498763" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're going to be part of my team soon, Sergeant. What do you think about that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ready to join Havoc?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498764" id2="17" version="1065353216">This appointment gives such honor. Yuun can only hope to prove valuable during our search for the Umbra encrypter components.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498766" id2="17" version="1065353216">The faster we get your work here done, the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's not waste time chatting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. Speed is the essence of the hunt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498769" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold up--am I really the only one who doesn't understand what freak-face here is saying?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498771" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your sounds are difficult to reproduce without vocal chords. Is Gand no longer part of Special Forces language training?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Specialist Vik is new to SpecForce. He hasn't completed standard training yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498772" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, it still is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. Sorry I said anything--let's just get on with this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="498775" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you wish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498777" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vik's a clever guy; he'll get the hang of it. Right, Vik?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498777" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure he'll pick it up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vik is here to blow stuff up, not to talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="498778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ignore him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="498779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, this is going to be fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="760442" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is strange.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="760444" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star of Coruscant?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="760446" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now we know the enemy's face.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="760448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Copy that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="760449" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not very technical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="760450" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like what I'm hearing.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
