<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>80</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/dromund_kaas/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211244" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a city girl, but there's something about this place that rubs me wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211245" id2="17" version="1065353216">So much has changed since I was last on this world. This bastion of the Sith is glorious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211246" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kaas City, all shiny and new. Makes you want to burn the whole thing down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow, that must be the Citadel! That's the center of the universe as far as the Empire's concerned... how big do you think those flags are?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211250" id2="17" version="1065353216">This road is rough in the dark. I keep stumbling.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211251" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do the Sith bury their dead, if only to dig them back up again?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211252" id2="17" version="1065353216">They dug up something down here. I don't get it, though--you bury history for a reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211253" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nar Shaddaa was nothing like this, there's nothing to be sentimental about there. If something's old and unused, it gets knocked down and built over, usually with a casino.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211256" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just when you thought there weren't enough big statues on this planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211257" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Sith who cannot finish a statue does not deserve a statue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211258" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's, what, a couple thousand slaves here? If they had any brass, they wouldn't have waited 'til the statue was half-built to start shooting. They deserve what they get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211259" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would you look at the size of that statue... there must have been an army of slaves building it. No wonder the Imperials haven't stamped out the rebellion yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thing I'm not afraid of heights. Or invading a hostile Sith compound, for that matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hiding behind walls. Cowardly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every time we get near a checkpoint, I expect someone to start shooting. Planetary security... just try to frisk me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grathan's estate should be just over this bridge. We don't want to get trapped there. Everything I've dug up about Grathan is seriously disturbing, even for a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith sure do love their monuments. If they're trying to impart a sense of doom, you can tell them... uh... mission accomplished.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211269" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dark energies here. A good place for a feast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211270" id2="17" version="1065353216">People have nightmares about this sort of stuff, and you make a whole planet out of it. How can you live here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, uh, I know I might be a little late mentioning this, but I'm getting some seriously creepy signals out here. I really don't think we should go in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Dromund Kaas, where freedom goes to die, and legends are forced on the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dromund Kaas, land of glorious shadow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211276" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice jungle. You people've got a freaky world; they ready for us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211277" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sheesh, it's so dark. Let's see what time it is here...? Oh, apparently it's always this gloomy. Lovely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211280" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow, nice lights--walk in here, you get an instant headache.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211281" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will be ruin some day, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211282" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're scared of you here, aren't they? You come, you go... you're the freaking secret police.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211283" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's very... patriotic. Do you get the feeling that we're really out of place here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211286" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I ever mention I have a fear of being crushed by falling rock?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211287" id2="17" version="1065353216">None of these pathetic Sith compare to Tulak Hord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211288" id2="17" version="1065353216">On Rattatak, place like this could be ten years old. Big stuff doesn't last long on Rattatak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211289" id2="17" version="1065353216">These monoliths have seen better days. I wonder what it used to be. Then again, I probably don't want to know the answer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211292" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a pretty big wall--must really want to keep out the riffraff.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211293" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do the Sith fear that they build so many walls? They should be out conquering, not hiding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211294" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at this. No one's ever come close to your planet, but you look like you're about to fight a war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211295" id2="17" version="1065353216">Considering that the Empire rules every corner of this planet, and the amount of nasty wildlife I've seen so far, I'm not sure I want to know what a wall that size is keeping out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211298" id2="17" version="1065353216">Somebody misplace some giant slabs of rock?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Old glories. Forgotten Sith. Leave them be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211300" id2="17" version="1065353216">We loot a place like this, sell the antiques on the black market... who'd have to know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211301" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you noticed all these carvings? Who'd have thought the Sith were so big on statues?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Man, I could make a fortune in here. You think maybe I can just take a little... no? Okay, okay.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211305" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place reeks of death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you say something? Swear there's someone talking to me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211307" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can still hear them talking... I cut off my holoreceiver, but I can still hear them. If I lose it, please don't leave me down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kaas City makes me feel tiny. I don't suppose you share in that sentiment.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211311" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Sith build and build when they should be conquering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211312" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like the city isn't big enough. This some Sith project, or you just need space for a few million slaves?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211313" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's kind of funny, seeing so much of the new Kaas City growing up around the old Sith architecture. It's like stepping through time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Towers ought to be towering. I approve.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211317" id2="17" version="1065353216">These towers do not compare to the monuments of old.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211318" id2="17" version="1065353216">Slow down. We can spread out, have a picnic, watch the lightning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hate to be the maintenance guy for that. Can you imagine having to trudge out here every time a vine cat climbs the signal tower?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211322" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know what you're thinking--nice place for a slaughter, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211323" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith do battle over this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211324" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope you don't mind taking down your own people. If you do, I can handle it myself....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211325" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know, this place might have been pretty once. I wonder what it was like before the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211328" id2="17" version="1065353216">One day, I want a statue erected of me. Don't even pretend I'm alone on that one.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211329" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is the point of such monuments?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211330" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, all those people--you know they're crazy, right? Trust me, I've seen enough cults in my day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that supposed to be the Emperor? He looks kind of cozy, but why build a monument all the way out here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that Revan? Impressive secret shrine thingy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211335" id2="17" version="1065353216">A forgotten Sith Lord with a collection of devout followers. Still, who even remembers the deeds of Tulak Hord?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211336" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like this place, I don't like being here. Do what you have to with the statue and let's get out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211337" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's Revan... I heard he took that mask from a Mandalorian before he started his crusade to drive them out of the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, I had a room like this growing up back home. No big deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211341" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place makes me uncomfortable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211342" id2="17" version="1065353216">More machines, more droids. Didn't know Sith were such tech freaks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211343" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, I bet there are a lot of dirty secrets kept here. No telling how long it'd take to try and slice these systems, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Market value of this place must be sky-high. Makes my brain hurt trying to figure.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211347" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've not seen such a collection since Tulak Hord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Old pirate story about a guy who steals a Sith relic. Skin turns black, disease eats him up--but if you want to grab what's in here, I'm up for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211349" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't touch anything if I were you; there's no telling what security Grathan has on this stuff... or how dangerous they are without them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211352" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wouldn't mind a little refreshment. You know, if we're going to be here a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211353" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do we waste our time in this place?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knew a guy who went to a Sith party, once. He was the &quot;entertainment,&quot; came back... wrong. Had to put him down; this place is messed up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211355" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, this place looks lively. I guess the Imperials have something that passes for fun after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211358" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm hearing ominous theme music in my head. Kinda catchy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="211359" id2="17" version="1065353216">The guts of the great city.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211360" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one sleeping on the streets, no dark alleys where the rich folk get scared... this isn't a city. It's a prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="211361" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you think this place is big, you should see Nar Shaddaa. Buildings as far as the eye can see, and alleys you can get lost in forever.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
