<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>19</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/02/ep_00_hk_bonus/holojournals_shroud.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200256" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud war journal, entry 5963. Investigation of the attacks on Republic and Imperial settlements has led to Wild Space.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200338" id2="17" version="1065353216">New players have entered the game. That won't do. I will find these interlopers and sweep them from my board.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud war journal, entry 6812. Manipulating Darth Marr and my old enemy to find Zakuul succeeded beyond all calculations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200341" id2="17" version="1065353216">They and that so-called &quot;Eternal Emperor&quot; are dead. But removing the son and daughter may be more challenging.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud war journal, entry 7944. Acina declared herself Empress of the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200344" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hardly surprising given the power vacuum, but I'm shocked by the sheer volume of popular support for that oily dianoga.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200346" id2="17" version="1065353216">People seem to genuinely like her. What's this galaxy coming to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud war journal, entry 9233. Days like this remind me why I enjoy the great game.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200349" id2="17" version="1065353216">My extortion campaign against Republic senators blocked Chancellor Saresh's effort to extend her term indefinitely. Once again, democracy prevails.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200350" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud war journal, entry 9889. After five years of meticulous planning, &quot;Operation Stranglehold&quot; can finally begin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200352" id2="17" version="1065353216">At last, the galaxy will be under my total control. Listen to me--I'm positively giddy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200353" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud personal log, entry 80764. Five years, for nothing! How could that menace come back from the dead at the precise moment it would ruin my plans?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200355" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate, hate, hate that &quot;Outlander&quot;! Going to bed early.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud war journal, entry 0001A. Starting a new diary and a clean slate for &quot;Operation Kill the Outlander.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200358" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enemy intel is scarce for now, but I'll soon fix that. There are plenty of Alliance droids wandering about, after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud war journal, entry 4281. I captured an SIS agent on Coruscant. A friend of Theron Shan and a minion of Saresh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200608" id2="17" version="1065353216">He revealed so much valuable information, but I'll never get his smell out of the interrogation room. I'll build a new one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud personal log, entry 54171. I caught the cleaner staring at my terminal for more than three seconds. He claimed it was an accident.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1200616" id2="17" version="1065353216">I removed his eyes, tongue, and fingers to safeguard my secrets. He reacted... poorly. I'll have to replace him--and revise my employment contract.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
