<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>67</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/republic/morale_boost/lieutenant_rufar.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473744" id2="17" version="1065353216">The men all talk about how good it is to see those statues beaming down at us. I can't thank you enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473745" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've shown the men that those Mandos can be beaten--I can't thank you enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Mandalorians won't be troubling you anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473748" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard the cheers when the first statue came back. Figured you must have succeeded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473750" id2="17" version="1065353216">I saw a Comm report just before you arrived--our troops are pushing back hard, and really taking the fight to the Mandos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473752" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're already deeper than we've ever made it before. The Mandalorians are finally on the defensive, thanks to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473753" id2="17" version="1065353216">All your men needed was some relief; glad I could do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473753" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm pleased to have helped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473754" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've given us all something to hope for--a Corellia that's free of the Empire's goons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473756" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did what I could.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473757" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've lit a fire in their hearts--it's turned the battle around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. If I can't be there with my squad, it's good to know they've got a chance</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your soldiers have it easy now that I took out the rocket troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473760" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did the hard work for you</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, because Mandalorian troops are so easy to push back. Thanks for the help, but we'll take it from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473763" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you're working hard out there, but another group of rocketeers attacked Squad Epsilon. We can't let any of them get away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473766" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't tell you what it means to see you here, Major. You SpecForce guys are an inspiration to the rest of us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473768" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just wish I could help my squad--these Mandalorian rocket troops that the Empire brought in are tearing them apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473769" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're hurt, Lieutenant, but I might be able to do something for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473769" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I help them, soldier?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473770" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm honored, sir. It's those rocket troops--my squad can't handle elites like them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473772" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wasn't expecting visitors. I'd get up, but the med-droids just yell at me if I try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473774" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess I'm better off than Hawkins, but that's not saying much--the Empire's new Mandalorian rocket troops are tearing my squad apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't move. Just tell me how you ended up here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473775" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's your story, soldier?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir. We were supposed to take back the park when we ran into the Mandalorians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473778" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Mandalorians haven't used those before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rocket troops? That's new.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473779" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're some kind of elite squad, they've got jump packs and rapid fire blasters that punch through armor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473781" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wouldn't have this problem if you grunts learned to get out of the line of fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473781" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you should duck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473782" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's tougher than it sounds when you're facing Mandalorian elites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those jump packs let them go anywhere they want, and they pick us off like womp rats on a junk heap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now I'm stuck in here, my men don't have support--don't suppose a Jedi could back them up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473787" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're regular soldiers, Major, but you--everyone says Mandos aren't a problem for Havoc Squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473788" id2="17" version="1065353216">Us grunts have to stick together, Lieutenant. I'll get rid of those Mandos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473788" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything for a fellow soldier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473789" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd feel a lot better about being stuck here if I knew somebody took out those rocket troops--then my squad might have a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473790" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't refuse a wounded man; I'll take care of your Mandalorians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473790" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'd be an honor to help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473791" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't thank you enough for this. The Mandos set up their camps along the Cross of Glory Walk. A slap in the face.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473793" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take care of your Mandalorian problem. Where should I look?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473793" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me where the enemy is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473794" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've got camps all along the Cross of Glory Walk, but they can attack anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473796" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's something else--the Mandos turned off the holo-statues along the Walk when they put up artillery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Taking out the Mandos saves lives, but Master Jedi--getting those statues back would restore our heroes. Send a message to the whole city.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those statues show our heroes, Major. I told my boys, I'll tell you... restoring them would put the city's morale back on track.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those statues show our most valiant heroes. You can imagine what seeing them restored would do for the city's morale.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473801" id2="17" version="1065353216">People deserve their heroes. I'll see to the statues and the Mandalorians, rest assured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473801" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can restore the statues, too</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473802" id2="17" version="1065353216">Healing the people's morale is as important as removing the threat to their lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473802" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can restore the statues, too</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say no more. I'll get rid of the Mandalorians and reactivate those statues.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473803" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can restore the statues, too</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473804" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. Sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473806" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was pretty dull around here--restoring some statues and fighting a few Mandalorians should be fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473806" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can restore the statues, too</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you --there's not enough folks like you in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473809" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll fix the statues if I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473810" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the best I can hope for, I guess--at least the rocket troops will be taken care of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473812" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take care of the Mandalorians, but I make no guarantee on the statues.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473812" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can only get the Mandos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473813" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rocket troops are more important anyway. Once they're out of the way we should be able to do the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473815" id2="17" version="1065353216">According to the medics, I'll be waiting right here. If you have time to visit again... tell me how it goes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="473817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks, but no. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473818" id2="17" version="1065353216">That makes sense, right? Leave us grunts to die while you get the fame? Thanks for nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="473820" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not fair--I should be out there leading my men, not stuck in an outpost playing spectator.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
