<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>51</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/raid/shared/hutt_hospitality/yd_33.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984868" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Diplomatic Service offers its most gracious thanks for your assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984871" id2="17" version="1065353216">My registry indicates you are the Emperor's Wrath. It pains me that my inferior design prevents me from prostrating myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984873" id2="17" version="1065353216">My humble programming cannot calculate the sum pleasure of serving a lord of the Dark Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984875" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must apologize that my lexical archives lack an honorific sufficient for a bounty hunter of your credentials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive my familiarity, but my restraining bolt cannot contain my eagerness to address the Empire's superlative intelligence agent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984879" id2="17" version="1065353216">In fact, my circuits are overwhelmed to be in the presence of such august figures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pardon me, organic superior, I must trouble you for a moment of your time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984883" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am in the employ of the Imperial Diplomatic Service. My masters have urgent need of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984884" id2="17" version="1065353216">Diplomacy is for the weak. I speak, others obey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="984884" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not big on negotiation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984885" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is exactly why the ambassador needs you, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984887" id2="17" version="1065353216">My concerns span the Empire. Petty bureaucracies are beneath me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="984887" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your masters are nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984888" id2="17" version="1065353216">This matter concerns our Empire's most important ally, my lord, which is why the ambassador seeks your intervention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your masters are not one of my preferred employers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="984890" id2="17" version="1065353216">You people are too touchy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984891" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ambassador promises more flexibility than you had on Voss. This should be a situation you're quite familiar with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your masters have something they need handled discreetly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="984893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fill me in, and I'll consider.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely, sir. The ambassador said no one in the Empire has more experience influencing Hutt politics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984896" id2="17" version="1065353216">How may I assist the Diplomatic Service?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="984896" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready to serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984897" id2="17" version="1065353216">My masters have a bit of a crisis on their hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984899" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're waging war in over a hundred systems. The time for negotiating has long passed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="984899" id2="17" version="1065353216">Diplomacy seems pointless now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984900" id2="17" version="1065353216">When it comes to the Empire these days, I don't see a lot of talking going on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="984900" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can't be busy right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984901" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the burden of maintaining the Treaty of Coruscant alleviated, we're able to focus on more rewarding endeavors. Alliances, first and foremost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our relations with the Hutt Cartel have taken a sudden turn for the worse, and Ambassador Rove believes it'll take more than talk to salvage the situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984905" id2="17" version="1065353216">Each of you has had extensive dealings with the Hutt Cartel; your combined expertise will certainly turn things around!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984906" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll put an end to this petty squabble, one way or another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="984906" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll get a resolution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="984907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bring us up to speed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984909" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've had extensive dealings with the Hutt Cartel, and your presence will show how serious we are about settling this dispute!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984910" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts often forget that wealth is not the same as power. I will remind them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="984910" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't trifle with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well. I'll represent the Dark Council in this matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="984911" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have influence in excess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984912" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can always make time to put the Hutts in their place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="984912" id2="17" version="1065353216">This should be entertaining.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984913" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have the Hutts eating out of my hand--or choking on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="984913" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I do best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ambassador Rove will be thrilled to hear your enthusiasm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984916" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said this was urgent. When do I meet Rove?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="984916" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll talk to the ambassador.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984917" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did the Empire get into this position and what does the ambassador plan to do about it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="984917" id2="17" version="1065353216">What dispute, exactly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984918" id2="17" version="1065353216">For security reasons, those details were not transferred to my memory core. Ambassador Rove will be able to tell you more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984920" id2="17" version="1065353216">He awaits you on his diplomatic vessel. Please see him at your nearest convenience.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984922" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do hope my technicians overlook this momentous occasion during my next memory wipe!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="984924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always a pleasure to be in such notable company.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
