<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>200</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/ord_mantell/class/trooper/commander_tavus.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629207" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant, I thought my orders were very clear. You aren't supposed to be here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Tavus? What are you doing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629210" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's going on here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629211" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd better tell me what this is about, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629211" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want an explanation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629212" id2="17" version="1065353216">This entire mission was a lie! You've betrayed us--betrayed the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629212" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're traitors!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629213" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will take her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629215" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will take him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629217" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, Wraith. The sergeant deserves to know the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629219" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had hoped it wouldn't come to this. I harbor no ill will toward you. You're everything a warrior should be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629221" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I'm afraid the Republic no longer values her warriors--even the very best among them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629222" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've fought the Empire for years--do you really think things are better over there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629222" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can you believe that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629223" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire respects warriors, Sergeant. The Republic's top officials, on the other hand, have decided to cast us aside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629225" id2="17" version="1065353216">All of you swore to protect the Republic from its enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629225" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's no excuse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629226" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those oaths were sworn to a Republic that doesn't exist anymore, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629228" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're afraid you can't cut it anymore, so you're changing sides.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629228" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only cowards defect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629229" id2="17" version="1065353216">You couldn't be further from the truth, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629231" id2="17" version="1065353216">The truth is that no matter what they may say, the Republic Senate doesn't actually believe it can win another war against the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629233" id2="17" version="1065353216">That makes you and I a threat. Every Havoc Squad victory fires up people's imaginations, fills them with pride--which means the bureaucrats can't afford to let us keep succeeding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629234" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can win, Tavus. We have to win. The Imperials must be defeated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629234" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we can beat the Empire!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629235" id2="17" version="1065353216">How is the outright tyranny of the Empire any better?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629235" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bureaucrats? Are you serious?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629236" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've really lost it. What you're saying--it's absurd.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629236" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's just paranoid nonsense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629237" id2="17" version="1065353216">If only you'd been with us longer, Sergeant, you would understand. You might've even come with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629239" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic abandoned us. During a mission on Ando Prime, they simply left us to die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629241" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I won't try to persuade you. Honestly, I hope you die with your ideals intact. The rest of us will never have that luxury.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629242" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not too late, Tavus. You can still turn back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629242" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have to do this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629243" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turn back to what? The Republic that wants me dead and gone? No, Sergeant, I think not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629245" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would never become a traitor like you, Tavus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629245" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd never betray the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629246" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I suspected as much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surrender right now, or I'll have no option but to take you all down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629248" id2="17" version="1065353216">You leave me no choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629249" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, Sergeant, but you'll be the only member of Havoc Squad to die today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629251" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, uh, by the way, good work finding the ZR-57 for us. We were starting to worry that the separatists might, you know, waste our big present for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629253" id2="17" version="1065353216">But thanks to you, we can now present the Empire with this magnificent tool of destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629254" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials won't be very impressed once they realize the bomb is neutralized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629254" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad I deactivated it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629255" id2="17" version="1065353216">A clever bluff, Sergeant, but it won't help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629257" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad I could contribute to your treason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629257" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very funny.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assuming you leave here alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629259" id2="17" version="1065353216">You never lacked courage, but I'm afraid that courage will not help you now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629261" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd better get a move on, boss. If we don't break atmo in the next few minutes, every gun in the sky will have a clear shot on us.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="629263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time we were off. Colonel Vorr? Please give the sergeant the warrior's death she deserves.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="629264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time we were off. Colonel Vorr? Please give the sergeant the warrior's death he deserves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see what you've got!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bring it on!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go ahead and run. Someone's gonna catch you eventually.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629266" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're all cowards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629267" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll regret this, Tavus. I won't rest until I've taken you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629267" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't over.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="629268" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been an honor serving with you, Sergeant. Goodbye.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629271" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have the coordinates for the supply outpost on Mannett Point, Sergeant. Wraith is going to rendezvous with you inside, so move out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629272" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bellis discovered that the separatists have the ZR-57 securely inside their supply outpost on Mannett Point, a small island just off the coast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629274" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sent Wraith ahead to reconnoiter the outpost, and she successfully located a secure area where we believe the bomb is stored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629276" id2="17" version="1065353216">Judging by the dramatic increase in the number of guards and the complex security systems installed, we're certain the bomb is there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Honestly, with security like this, Mannett Point looks more like an Imperial military base than a separatist hideout to me. I think the seps are getting a helping hand, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629280" id2="17" version="1065353216">From the Imperials? That seems unlikely, Lieutenant. Surely our spies would have discovered any Imperial involvement on Ord Mantell long before now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629281" id2="17" version="1065353216">The seps do seem to be unusually well equipped, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629281" id2="17" version="1065353216">The lieutenant has a point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629282" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fighting Imperials is what I signed up for. I say bring 'em on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629282" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd love to find Imps here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629283" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said it, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629285" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would the Imps care what happens on Ord Mantell?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629285" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jorgan is just paranoid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629286" id2="17" version="1065353216">The whole reason the separatists are trying to leave the Republic is so they can join the Empire, Sergeant. It's obvious the Imperials would want to get involved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629288" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can discuss the possibility of any Imperial connections later. Let's focus on the mission at hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wraith can't breach the secured area of the Mannett Point outpost alone, so I'm sending you in immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629293" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629293" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready for duty, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629294" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds exciting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629295" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to know I'm your second choice for these kinds of ops, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629295" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should have been sent first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629296" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't a popularity contest, Sergeant. You each have your own specialties. And right now, I need your specialties inside that outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629298" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Mannett Point bridge is out of commission, so you'll have to make an amphibious approach to that island.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629300" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you arrive, effect entry into the supply outpost and rendezvous with Wraith inside. She'll give you further instructions at that time. Understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629301" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629302" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before I go, sir, there's a lieutenant named Virk running a bribery scheme with the men under his command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629302" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to report corruption.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Virk? I know the guy. He's a pretty pathetic officer, but nobody's ever made any official complaints--none that I heard about, anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629305" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Jorgan and I will see to this. You should get moving to Mannett Point, so that you can rendezvous with Wraith inside the separatist outpost. Dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bust in, find the green lady and do what she tells me to--got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629307" id2="17" version="1065353216">This mission is gravely important, Sergeant. Many lives depend on your success. Dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629309" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, welcome back, Sergeant. Good work dealing with that ambush--I'm sure the troopers from Forty-fifth Infantry will be singing your praises for some time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629311" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only because they don't know how reluctant the sergeant was to help them. You would have let your fellow soldiers die!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629312" id2="17" version="1065353216">It won't happen again, Lieutenant. You have my word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629312" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm very sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's move on, people. We have an important new mission to discuss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stopping random ambushes isn't my assignment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629315" id2="17" version="1065353216">My objective is the ZR-57.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629316" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a war, Lieutenant--and sometimes, people die in wars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Casualties are inevitable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough! We have an important new mission. There's no time for this pointless bickering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, Sergeant--good to see you again. Superb work on that ambush situation--adaptability like that is what Havoc Squad is all about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629320" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're too kind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629321" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have other good news as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629323" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're no closer to finding the bomb than we were before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still no ZR-57, unfortunately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629324" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not for long--I have good news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629326" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know how many more false leads I can take.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629326" id2="17" version="1065353216">The whole op was a waste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629327" id2="17" version="1065353216">It isn't a false lead if it saves lives. But you should be happy to hear this next piece of news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Jorgan has finished reviewing the intel from Bellis's field box. It's given us a real breakthrough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did Bellis manage to uncover the ZR-57's hiding place?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629332" id2="17" version="1065353216">What have we learned?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629333" id2="17" version="1065353216">He did, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to know the guy managed to do something besides get shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629335" id2="17" version="1065353216">So Bellis wasn't useless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turns out Bellis was actually pretty good at his job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't keep me in suspense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629339" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should hurry to Talloran and rendezvous with Bellis, Sergeant. Time is a luxury we cannot afford.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, the reason we're all here: A Republic transport, carrying among its cargo a ZR-57 orbital strike bomb, crashed in northern Avilatan six days ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recovery unit sent a team, but they were too late. Separatist forces had already stolen the transport's cargo, including the ZR-57, and fled.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629343" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone on our side must have tipped the seps off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629343" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like we have a leak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629344" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, we've considered that possibility--but we don't have time for a mole hunt. Recovering that bomb is priority one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629346" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are the ZR-57's capabilities, sir?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629346" id2="17" version="1065353216">How dangerous is this bomb?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing like risking your life cleaning up somebody else's mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629347" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate cleanup ops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629348" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a mess--there's no doubt about that. But Havoc Squad wasn't formed to do the easy jobs. We will retrieve this bomb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629350" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ZR-57 is--well, it's serious hardware, you know? I mean, it can pretty much vaporize this whole island. So, we'd better get it back or, well, boom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629352" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're investigating several leads to the bomb's location, but the one I'd like you to look into, Sergeant, comes from a Republic spy named Bellis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bellis reported making an important discovery, but he's in too deep to exfiltrate for a full report. Instead, you'll rendezvous with Bellis in a nearby village called Talloran.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629357" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629358" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should warn you, Sergeant: Talloran is separatist-controlled territory. Expect armed resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629360" id2="17" version="1065353216">Has there been a comm malfunction? Or are all of this guy's meets face-to-face?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629360" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why can't Bellis call it in?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Comms are risky here. The separatists have signal tappers everywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629363" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any grunt could do this op, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629363" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a waste of my skills.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Getting in and out of Talloran is more difficult than you might imagine. The separatist armed guards are everywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629366" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bellis will meet you in a small alley in Talloran. Find out what he's discovered, then return to the base immediately. Understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629368" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if Bellis's information doesn't lead us to the bomb, sir?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629368" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if the intel isn't useful?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629369" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we will have one less lead requiring our attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629371" id2="17" version="1065353216">This won't be challenging.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629372" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you may find the operation more taxing than you expect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629374" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have one last introduction to make: This is Lieutenant Aric Jorgan, an operations officer from the Republic's Ord Mantell Infantry Command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629376" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since we're on individual missions to search for this bomb, Lieutenant Jorgan is coordinating our efforts from here within the mission room.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629378" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, Sergeant, I'll be overseeing your op through the camera mounted on your armor, so I see what you see. It's activated when you leave the fort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629380" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make this completely clear, rookie--when you're in the field, what I say goes. Period.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629381" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629382" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can handle myself, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629382" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no rookie.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629383" id2="17" version="1065353216">Other members of Havoc have proven themselves on dozens of ops, Sergeant. You haven't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629385" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Tavus is my CO, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629385" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't take orders from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629386" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Jorgan is a superior officer. I expect you to show him the same respect you would show me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629388" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just make your way to Talloran, meet with Bellis, and find out what he knows without screwing anything up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629390" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make me proud. Show these separatists what Havoc is made of!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629391" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get that intel for us, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629391" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on me, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629392" id2="17" version="1065353216">There isn't a doubt in my mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629394" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to get back in the fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck in Talloran, Sergeant. Dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time for the real soldiers to go to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enjoy the show, Jorgan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629397" id2="17" version="1065353216">That will do, Sergeant. Dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, so if we focus our efforts on M-sector, I'm certain that--Sergeant! Welcome, welcome!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629401" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to have you here. I'm Commander Harron Tavus, Havoc Squad's commanding officer. We're all excited to have some new blood in the unit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629404" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm honored to be joining the very best unit in the Republic, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629404" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a pleasure, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629405" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to hear it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629407" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will you be giving me my assignments from now on, sir?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629407" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you my commanding officer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629408" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's correct, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's let the enemy do the bleeding, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629410" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep my blood to myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629411" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah! I like her already.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah! I like him already.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me introduce you to the other members of Havoc Squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629417" id2="17" version="1065353216">My second-in-command, Captain Zora, is the squad's infiltration and assassination specialist. We call her Wraith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629421" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Fuse--Lieutenant Vanto Bazren. He's an expert with every type of explosive in the known galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, uh, yes, hello, Sergeant, hello. Good to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629425" id2="17" version="1065353216">And this is Needles, Lieutenant Ryler Dorant. Needles is a medical genius--he's particularly adept at synthesizing powerful new combat stimulants and adrenals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629427" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfection is my art, Sergeant. It will be my honor to help you perform at your very best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629429" id2="17" version="1065353216">And of course, you met Gearbox on your way here, so that's everyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629431" id2="17" version="1065353216">People, this is the new sergeant I mentioned--ranked first in the Academy in Forward Assault, Search and Destroy, and Advance Recon. It's good to have you, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629432" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a real pleasure to meet all of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629432" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629433" id2="17" version="1065353216">I look forward to showing you what I can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait until you see me work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629434" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're all looking forward to seeing you in action, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629436" id2="17" version="1065353216">When do we start busting heads, Commander? I'm ready for some action!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629436" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get started!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soon enough, trooper, soon enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629440" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good day.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
