<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>86</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/ord_mantell/class/trooper/gearbox.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Approaching Drelliad village, sir. Scopes show small-arms fire and enemy movements in all quarters. Separatists are definitely moving on the objective.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Code red! Code red! We've been hit by an AP missile! A shoulder-launcher from somewhere in the village! Everyone hold on--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546857" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not supposed to be here, kid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546858" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's work to be done, kid. Time for talk later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546859" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd better get up to Fort Garnik, kid. Be careful out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice work, kid! You've got a talent--there's no denying that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546862" id2="17" version="1065353216">I, however, didn't have much success. This walker isn't gonna be moving anytime soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't beat yourself up. If it was possible, you'd have fixed it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546863" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you did your best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks, kid. Shame about the driver, though. Poor guy never had a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546866" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a waste of time. Just requisition a new one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who cares?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you kidding? With our budget, we'll be lucky if Command even sends us a dewback to replace the thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546869" id2="17" version="1065353216">What now, sir?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546870" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm gonna stay here and salvage all the goodies off this wreck before someone else does. You better head for Fort Garnik.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be sure to keep a lookout for seps on your way to the fort--they can come at you out of nowhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546873" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep my eyes open.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546873" id2="17" version="1065353216">I noticed that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure you don't want me to stick around and cover you while you work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will you be okay on your own?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546875" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, no, I'll--I'll be fine. Hey, I'm not exactly new to this, kid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without anyone else to slow me down, I'll be fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546877" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can handle myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546878" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know, you'd probably move even faster if you dropped some of that attitude, kid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay sharp out there. I'll see you later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546882" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do my best with this walker, kid, but you need to disable those missile launchers in the village before they take anyone else out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, there's not a feeling in this galaxy like riding a hundred-tonne walker right through the middle of a combat zone, huh, kid?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another beautiful day on Ord Mantell! You excited, kid? Nervous? You know, you're the first new entry to Havoc Squad in some time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546889" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll fight the enemies of the Republic with everything I've got, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546889" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready to do my part.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546890" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to call me &quot;sir.&quot; We're in the field--you can lose the formality.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546892" id2="17" version="1065353216">What made Havoc choose to bring me in?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why recruit a new member?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546893" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's just too much happening on Ord Mantell. Guys in charge decided we need an extra pair of hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546895" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got nothing to be nervous about--fighting is my life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546895" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was born for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confidence! I like it! Getting tapped for Havoc Squad at your age is nothing to sneeze at.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546898" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Lieutenant Bex Kolos, but everyone in Havoc calls me Gearbox. We're a tight unit--you'll like it with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546901" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm looking forward to serving with the best soldiers in the Republic, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546901" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's an honor to join you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546902" id2="17" version="1065353216">And we're glad to have you, kid. Believe me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546904" id2="17" version="1065353216">As long as all of you can keep up with me, we should be fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546904" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546905" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah! That won't be a problem, kid. Don't worry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me tell you why we're here: The separatists have nabbed a Republic bomb off of a downed transport--a serious bomb, one of those orbital strike numbers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are we on Ord Mantell?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc's here to find a stolen Republic bomb, one of those nasty orbital strike numbers. Apparently, a transport crashed with the bomb onboard, and the separatists got there first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546912" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no telling where these grimy bushwhackers have hidden the thing. They have popular support and hideouts everywhere. Finding this bomb won't be easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546913" id2="17" version="1065353216">No mission is too tough for Havoc Squad!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546913" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can handle this!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope you're right, kid. That bomb goes off and the whole island's one big crater.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546916" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't sound hard to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546917" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take it from me, kid: On an op like this, you don't sleep much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546919" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are the weapon specs?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546919" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the bomb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546920" id2="17" version="1065353216">The bomb is designed to slag a huge city, so it could wipe this little island right off the map.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="546922" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll get a full op brief once we reach Fort Garnik. For now, just sit back and--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Driver! Driver? Blast it, he's down. Backwater separatists aren't supposed to have armor-piercing missiles! They'll tear up every convoy that passes through here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546928" id2="17" version="1065353216">How should we proceed, sir?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546928" id2="17" version="1065353216">What should we do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major hardware in enemy hands--seems like the kind of thing we should've been warned about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546929" id2="17" version="1065353216">How could intel miss this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get out of this alive and worry about filing complaints later, all right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546932" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the separatists want trouble, let's give them some.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546932" id2="17" version="1065353216">So let's take these seps out!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546933" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds good to me, kid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546935" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got to get this walker moving again, and we've got to disable the seps' AP missiles--and we need them both done yesterday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fixing things is my specialty, kid--I'm nowhere near the fighter you are. I'll stay and get this walker moving again. You'll disable the separatists' missile launchers. Understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546938" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546939" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were hit pretty hard. What are the odds of getting this thing moving again?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you really fix the damage?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure, honestly. But it takes months to requisition a new one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could I ask why I'm doing all the fighting in this plan, sir?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546942" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got to be joking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546943" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've already paid my dues, kid. Now, there's missile launchers in that village to deactivate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546945" id2="17" version="1065353216">The separatists will probably have their missile launchers piled together in a cache somewhere in the village--and you can bet that cache will be heavily guarded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546947" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find the cache, disable the missile launchers, and then double-time it back here. Got it, Sergeant?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546948" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546949" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope the seps brought plenty of body bags--they're gonna need them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to rack up some kills.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck out there, kid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546951" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not the one you should worry about, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546951" id2="17" version="1065353216">Worry about yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546952" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever you say, kid. Now get out there!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546954" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't got time to talk, kid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't bother me.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
