<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>55</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/ord_mantell/class/trooper/needles.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629966" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a pity you couldn't follow simple orders, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Proceed to Zak's home and find out what he knows immediately, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629968" id2="17" version="1065353216">Earlier today, a man named Zak came to the fort from Oradam village seeking medical attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629970" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zak was suffering from acute radiation poisoning, causing catastrophic organ failures. His body was practically tearing itself apart from within--quite magnificent to observe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629971" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it normal for villagers to get radiation poisoning, sir?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629971" id2="17" version="1065353216">That seems strange.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629974" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can spare me the medical details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629974" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the picture.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629975" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you wish, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is this Zak guy so important, Needles?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does this matter?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629978" id2="17" version="1065353216">As a day laborer, Zak performs pointless, menial tasks that would never involve any kind of radiation exposure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629980" id2="17" version="1065353216">On the other hand, Fuse told us that the ZR-57 can leak significant amounts of radiation if handled improperly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zak must have been near the ZR-57, knowingly or otherwise. I want the details, even if you must pry them from his dying husk of a mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629984" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are we really going to be so ruthless, sir?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629984" id2="17" version="1065353216">That seems pretty harsh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629985" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a desperate situation, Sergeant. We need that intel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629987" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have everything Zak knows, sir. Believe me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629987" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do whatever it takes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629988" id2="17" version="1065353216">The medics who treated Zak weren't equipped to cure his condition--most of their supplies have been stolen by scavengers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629990" id2="17" version="1065353216">However, if you were to retrieve the necessary ingredients to treat Zak's affliction... I think you would find the offer of a cure very useful in gaining his cooperation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given that Zak's current medications can promise only a lifetime of excruciating pain, the potential for a full recovery should be an excellent motivator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Command knows exactly where the scavengers are--we just haven't had the resources to deal with them. Here are the coordinates and a list of ingredients to retrieve. Any questions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hit the scavenger camp, retrieve the ingredients to cure Zak's radiation poisoning. Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Negative--everything's clear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once I have the ingredients, where do I take them? What is Zak's location?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where's Zak?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Couldn't someone else handle this op? It doesn't sound all that hard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="629997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah--why me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="629998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps so, perhaps not. But it doesn't matter. I want the operation completed with absolute perfection, which means sending you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you've got the cure collected, you'll confront Zak at his home in Oradam village and question him about the ZR-57.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get this one done on the double, Sergeant. We've got the seps on the run, and I want to keep it that way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630006" id2="17" version="1065353216">After Mannett Point, an op like this will be nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630006" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will be a breeze.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best stay alert regardless, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630009" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Zak doesn't lead us in the right direction, we're in trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope this isn't a waste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630010" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm confident that Zak will be quite useful, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing fancy on this one, Sergeant. Just get the ingredients, get the intel from Zak, and then get back. Dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant, you've returned. Masterful work, eliminating the separatist officers. The beast has been beheaded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630016" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get the officers' data out to the rest of Havoc right away. As for you, Lieutenant Dorant here has a special op already planned out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630019" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready for duty. Just tell me what needs to be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630019" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you wish, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some leave wouldn't be bad right about now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630020" id2="17" version="1065353216">What, no time off?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630021" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no time for rest now, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630023" id2="17" version="1065353216">All due respect, sir, but we ought to be tracking down the ZR-57 right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630023" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should be out searching.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630024" id2="17" version="1065353216">If my mission for you goes as I believe it will, the search for the ZR-57 will be narrowed significantly. Let me explain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck on your mission, Sergeant. I'm sure you'll find that this task offers little challenge to someone of such extensive capabilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630028" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and I have nothing to discuss. Move along.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
