<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>232</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/imperial/hub_2/multi/kiar_onila.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055056" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ground to support team. I found our missing people; checking for survivors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055059" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord. I'm so sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander. I'm sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir. I'm sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055065" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Archon... he had machines... he put a tube in my head....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055067" id2="17" version="1065353216">He knows we saved the planet. Son of a sow's going to tell the Hutts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where did he go? We need to stop the Archon from getting a message offworld.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055068" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to find the Archon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055069" id2="17" version="1065353216">I failed, but I'm not stupid. This way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold still. It's not your fault; no one can stand up under that kind of interrogation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055070" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did the best you could.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055071" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut up and follow me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055072" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should have stuck with labeling packages at the Ministry of Logistics. You have no place under my command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055072" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you truly are a failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I never did. But I watched the Archon very carefully.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055075" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have three hundred men waiting for shuttles. You promised time to evacuate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055077" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have been paid. That alone should still your simian tongue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055079" id2="17" version="1065353216">Besides, Makeb is not exploding, and I now have proof. Prepare to attack all Imperial positions; once the atmospheric interference clears, I will alert the fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055080" id2="17" version="1065353216">Szajin, Archon of the Hutt Cartel. You have escaped my grasp for too long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055080" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have you now, Hutt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055081" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, the Wrath of the Emperor's rotting corpse. You made a valiant effort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055083" id2="17" version="1065353216">You stand in the presence of a lord of the Dark Council. Perhaps you should show your respect?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055083" id2="17" version="1065353216">We meet at last, Hutt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055084" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dark Council member for a day, and lord of a dying civilization. I show you more than you deserve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Szajin the Archon. Spymaster of the Hutt Cartel. It's a pleasure to finally meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Face-to-face at last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055087" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you. How I wish I could peel your mind; you do your kind proud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055089" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not bad. Tasteful, as Hutt palaces go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055089" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice place you've got here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055090" id2="17" version="1065353216">My interests are more... ethereal than Karagga's.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055092" id2="17" version="1065353216">My interests are more... ethereal than Nem'ro's.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055094" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your dedication to your employer is admirable. Saving a planet when you were hired... what, as a thief?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055096" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations, Archon. Now you know--the Empire did what the Hutt Cartel couldn't, and Makeb is safe from disaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055096" id2="17" version="1065353216">You figured out the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055097" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd suspected, but the last pieces locked into place when your servants lay on my operating tables.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055099" id2="17" version="1065353216">Archon! You attacked my people. You tortured them. Did you think I wouldn't find you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055099" id2="17" version="1065353216">You hurt my team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055100" id2="17" version="1065353216">By no means. Invading Stronghold One, seizing the laser drills to save Makeb... from the start, you have impressed me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alas, it is the Hutt Empire that will receive Makeb's bounty. My people will no longer be mocked as we are envied. We will not be criminals... but kings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055103" id2="17" version="1065353216">A galaxy run by Hutts... you really think that could happen?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055103" id2="17" version="1065353216">You believe Hutts can rule?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Millennia ago, we were idolized by the younger species. We brought a golden age to a million worlds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055106" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some of us treasure the memories of that time. I will make them memories no longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055107" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire has worked with the Hutt Cartel before. Why not work together again?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055107" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can still negotiate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055108" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because the destiny of Hutts is not to trade and scheme. It never was, no matter how far we fell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055110" id2="17" version="1065353216">In ages past, the Hutt Archons were warriors and judges, exemplars of my people's strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055112" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observe, all of you. You will see a Hutt battle as few have for ten thousand years!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055113" id2="17" version="1065353216">You feel those tremors? If you believe Makeb is safe from disaster, you must be mad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055113" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deluded fool. Makeb is doomed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Archon?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055115" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps we can negotiate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055116" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I were mad, you wouldn't be so desperately trying to stop me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your people are worms. They always will be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not interested. [Attack]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055120" id2="17" version="1065353216">You call yourselves men of war? Observe, and see what an Archon of the old Hutt Empire can do!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055126" id2="17" version="1065353216">The droids are pulling back. Secure the platform, and we'll send in the engineers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055129" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not enough skyfighters left to be a problem. Platform's all yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055132" id2="17" version="1065353216">That should do it. Clear us a path to the platform, and I'll send out the last crew.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055135" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are we all here? With your permission, my lord, we'll start the briefing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are we all here? Sir, we'll start the briefing at your command.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055138" id2="17" version="1065353216">After vigorous discussion, the Science Bureau has reached consensus on a plan to preserve Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055140" id2="17" version="1065353216">The isotope-5 deposits in Makeb's core generate powerful gravitational and electromagnetic fields. Until recently, those fields maintained the core's equilibrium.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055142" id2="17" version="1065353216">The, ah, rapid removal of isotope-5 caused the fields to fluctuate and destabilized the core. Now Makeb is tearing itself apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055144" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is now too late to reverse the destabilization process. Our only option is to accelerate it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055145" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have my attention, Nadrin. Why do we want to accelerate the planet's destruction?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055145" id2="17" version="1065353216">How will that help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055146" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're proposing to destroy the planet, not save it. Are you admitting failure?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055146" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not what I asked for.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055147" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not precisely, no. Please consider?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055149" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Remain silent]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055150" id2="17" version="1065353216">By forcing Makeb through the end stages of destabilization in a compressed time frame, the damage will be contained.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055152" id2="17" version="1065353216">There won't be time for the mantle to fully crack before the core settles into a new state of equilibrium.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055154" id2="17" version="1065353216">The acceleration won't be easy on the planet. The groundquakes will be worse than ever, and the aftershocks will continue for months.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055156" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mesas will disintegrate, the cities will burn, and the gasses released will likely poison the atmosphere. But it's that or total annihilation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055158" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll see a new Makeb, and when it's over, the isotope-5 will be intact and ready for harvest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055159" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a dangerous plan, but it's all we have. Let's proceed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055159" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well. I approve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055160" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're condemning this world's people. They may evacuate in time, but they'll never be able to return.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055160" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about Makeb's citizens?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055161" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll have a memorial, which is more than the Hutts offered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055163" id2="17" version="1065353216">If all this works and we don't die horribly... if we still can't mine the isotope, then it was all for nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be sure about this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055164" id2="17" version="1065353216">My team is working on guidelines for future mining operations. We'll need to be careful, but the task is manageable.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055166" id2="17" version="1065353216">May I? As we discussed earlier, the mining lasers are the key to manipulating the core. Our new engineers will operate the platforms.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055168" id2="17" version="1065353216">The timing's perfect. The whole population is fleeing the planet, so that'll get rid of the Hutts while we work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055170" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the Archon still thinks we're trying to mine the isotope. He's sent his forces to blockade the laser drill platforms. All his forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055171" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy is making a stand. What sort of opposition am I facing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055171" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me your analysis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055172" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Archon and his people wouldn't go down with the planet. Why are they still here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why isn't he evacuating?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055173" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't speak for the Archon, but he's offered his men a bonus and promised to keep shuttles waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055175" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't the first time he's interfered. What if he knows we're trying to save the planet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055175" id2="17" version="1065353216">He may suspect the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055176" id2="17" version="1065353216">In that case, he'll convince the other Hutts to halt the evacuation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055178" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll keep an ear out on the Hutts' communications--should tell us something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055180" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll want to scatter the Archon's armies around three drill sites so our engineering teams can move in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055182" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've spotted isotope-5 droids advancing on the nearest platform--programmed to target you personally, according to intercepts. I'd take it as a compliment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055183" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Archon has declared war. I am an army, and I will triumph.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055183" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will march to battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Targeting a Dark Council member is a declaration of war. Not that it will save the Archon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bold, but futile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055187" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever the Archon may think, he has no idea what I'm capable of. I'll take care of the droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055187" id2="17" version="1065353216">They aren't prepared for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055189" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been hunted by Jedi, Sith and everything in between. A Hutt and his droids are chump change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055189" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been targeted by worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055191" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said the droids are at the first platform. Not the others?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055191" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the other drills?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055192" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are massive life readings around the second and third, but no hard data. I'll update you when I know more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055193" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave the isotope-5 droids to me. But there is no margin for error--ensure that everything goes according to plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055193" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make sure you don't mess up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055194" id2="17" version="1065353216">I pledged my life to you before. I'd do it again in a heartbeat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055195" id2="17" version="1065353216">Engineering teams, prepare to move out!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055196" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the Empire!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055198" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Cytharat would've had tactical advice, but all I can say is, kill the rotters.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055206" id2="17" version="1065353216">Special Energy Project Center? You have input?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055208" id2="17" version="1065353216">We finished the software for the laser drills. It should mean greater precision, but we've never worked with Makeb hardware, so....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention, everyone! Briefing begins now!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055212" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mighty and fearsome lord. I am pleased to state that your experiment proved fruitful.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055214" id2="17" version="1065353216">Esteemed commander. I am pleased to state that your experiment proved fruitful.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055216" id2="17" version="1065353216">Research continues, but we believe we can stabilize Makeb's core by using the planet's mining lasers to reshape the isotope-5 deposits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055217" id2="17" version="1065353216">How much more research before you're sure? And what do you need from me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055217" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's our next step, then?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055218" id2="17" version="1065353216">We continue to finalize details. However, we will require a crew capable of controlling multiple mining platforms.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055220" id2="17" version="1065353216">These mining lasers--we're standing on one now, correct? They create the drill shafts?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the lasers.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055221" id2="17" version="1065353216">Correct. The lasers drill down, and gravity funnels draw minerals up. Makeb's standard protocol.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055223" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is for burying me. [Hurt him]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055225" id2="17" version="1065353216">That experiment almost trapped me underground. Don't force me to replace you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055226" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... will endeavor to prove my worth, limited though it may be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055228" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're still figuring out the details, but it looks like we'll need to fully crew a couple of mining platforms.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055230" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is an accurate assessment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Problem is, our team can barely operate these wretched things. We need experts--engineers and supervisors who can run the mining lasers under our command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055233" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people of Makeb know this machinery better than anyone. Where do we find workers?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055233" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll need to recruit locals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055234" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the trouble. Watch:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055236" id2="17" version="1065353216">How difficult would it be to get a ship of Imperial engineers to Makeb?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055236" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we land more people?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055237" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not practical in the time we have. Local workers are possible, but it gets tricky:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055239" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're telling me that with all the Empire's knowledge at our disposal, we can't work a few pieces of machinery?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055239" id2="17" version="1065353216">It can't be that hard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055240" id2="17" version="1065353216">Work it, yes. But we don't have the manpower or the experience to be delicate, and according to Nadrin....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055242" id2="17" version="1065353216">Improper application of the lasers runs a high risk of destroying Makeb immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055244" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best option is to recruit the best and brightest of the locals, but that's going to get tricky. Watch:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055246" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the Archon to Phobium Squad Command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055248" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperial forces are desperate, and I believe they intend to mine what isotope-5 they can before the core erupts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055250" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the Imperials will need assistance. Have your men place all engineers of level seven and above under protective custody.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055252" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's wrong about our goal, but it doesn't matter. The Archon's got black-ops mercs kidnapping the people we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055253" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they're still alive, they can still be made ours. Give me everything you know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055253" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll kidnap them back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055254" id2="17" version="1065353216">It saves us the trouble of finding those workers ourselves. Now we just need to follow the mercenaries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055254" id2="17" version="1065353216">That could be convenient.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055255" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Hutt isn't going to leave us alone. We need to deal with him, and soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055255" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Archon is a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055256" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see what more I can dig up on him. Meanwhile, we know where the workers are being held.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Phobium Squad is an off-the-books team of Regulator mercenaries: assassins the Hutts bought out with cybernetics. They're holding the workers in groundquake shelters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055260" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few engineering chiefs who escaped joined a Republic refugee caravan. Won't be long before Phobium Squad catches them, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055261" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see to the caravan and the groundquake shelters. Anything else?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055261" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get to it, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055262" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said Phobium Squad was paid off in cybernetics?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me more about the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cybernetics, stims, all the latest from Nar Shaddaa. They could buy slave colonies on their salaries, but this is tech not on the market.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055265" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't often get to save civilians from their oppressors. This should be interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rescuing people... how novel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055266" id2="17" version="1065353216">One more thing: We're still decrypting the order, but it looks like the Archon sent an isotope-5 droid to help secure the caravan. Just to make things difficult.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055268" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll stay in touch from here. Anything you need, let us know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is the inductor fully charged?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055272" id2="17" version="1065353216">One hundred percent and holding. Ready when you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055274" id2="17" version="1065353216">The radiation pulse from Makeb's core should be harmless; however, you may wish to shield your eyes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055276" id2="17" version="1065353216">Receiving data. Mapping locations of isotope-5 deposits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nadrin? What is that?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055280" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unexpected. The pulse has caused a minute shift in isotope-5 energy levels; a minor groundquake is imminent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055281" id2="17" version="1065353216">Minor or not, I'm kilometers below the surface. Any tremor could bury me alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055281" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place could collapse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055282" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did I know this operation couldn't run smoothly? Suggestions, anyone?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055282" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish I could be surprised.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055283" id2="17" version="1065353216">You assured me there was no danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055283" id2="17" version="1065353216">You stupid creature. [Choke him]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055284" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgiveness, please....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055286" id2="17" version="1065353216">Under my command, failure and treason are one and the same. I will remember this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055286" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055287" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no room for error in your calculations, Nadrin. And I don't have room for fools on my team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055287" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've failed me badly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055288" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I weren't down here about to be buried, I'd shoot you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055288" id2="17" version="1065353216">You stupid creature.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055289" id2="17" version="1065353216">We humbly beg forgiveness and acknowledge our many flaws!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055291" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need as much distance as possible. There's an emergency shelter near the cavern entrance--go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055294" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ground team to support. We're in position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055295" id2="17" version="1065353216">Acknowledged. Signal when you've unloaded the equipment.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055297" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Nadrin. All systems functioning within acceptable parameters.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please be advised that the primary inductor array will take several minutes to fully charge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055300" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep checking its status. I'll buy us whatever time we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055300" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055301" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will await your command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055302" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those creatures seem to be attracted to the equipment. It could be a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055302" id2="17" version="1065353216">We may not have that long.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apologies. That is... unexpected. We will await your next command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take your time. Something just came up to keep me... entertained.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time for fun. [Disconnect]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well? Come and take me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ground to support team. There's something blocking my way--the mine shaft is capped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055311" id2="17" version="1065353216">Checking the blueprints. Capping is standard practice when a site is shut down.... There should be another route.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055313" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. Sending details. Head on in and get ready to run the experiment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Support team, do you read? I've arrived at the drill shaft.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Position confirmed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055319" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have, perhaps, reached a maintenance station? The accompanying mine shaft should lead nearly to the planet's core.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055321" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you are deep enough, you might induce the core's isotope-5 deposits to release a radiation burst. That would allow us to determine the core's status.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055322" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was there for the briefing. I'll begin descent shortly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055322" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you making progress? Are we on track to stabilize Makeb before it explodes?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055323" id2="17" version="1065353216">How's your research coming?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055324" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Science Bureau is pursuing three lines of inquiry. I am coordinating, and I am hopeful that at least one stabilization technique will prove sound.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, without a test planet, final results are unpredictable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055328" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really believe that unleashing Makeb's energy will prove harmless?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055328" id2="17" version="1065353216">That still seems dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1055329" id2="17" version="1065353216">The theory seems sound. I may be mistaken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055331" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been going through the mine site blueprints--I'll copy you on the data--and it looks like the machinery is offline.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055333" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll want to flip the backup generators, get power to the turbolifts and locks. But there are... life-forms down there. Big ones.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055334" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have the means to defend myself. We'll speak when I reach the bottom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055334" id2="17" version="1065353216">I plan to stay alert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Acknowledged. Support team out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are we talking about wildlife? Something native to Makeb?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055336" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sort of life-forms?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reports say the deep drilling caused an... infestation of some kind. Why the rig was abandoned, I think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could be relatives of those creatures in the caves around Stronghold One. Be on the lookout, anyway. Support team out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055340" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the caves around Stronghold One, there were creatures that sought me out. They died.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1055340" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've fought the fauna before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055341" id2="17" version="1065353216">Might be the same thing here, but on a larger scale. Reports say the deep drilling caused an... infestation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1055343" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be on the lookout, anyway. Support team out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1056188" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're doing everything we can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1056193" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got an army to fight. Let's save the world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1056196" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should hurry. If the mercenaries start executing engineers, we're out of luck.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
