<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>37</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/korriban/world/allegiance/inquisitor_arzanon.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658747" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did well executing the traitors. Your loyalty to our Emperor is without question.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658748" id2="17" version="1065353216">I watched you deal with those traitors. Well done. That was an impressive display of loyalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658750" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take this reward as a token of the Emperor's favor... and wear this badge. It marks you as a defender of our Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658752" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay vigilant. Our enemies lurk where you least expect them....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prove your loyalty to the Emperor. Execute the traitors in the valley. I'll be watching.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658757" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wear the robes of a Sith, but you are not one of us, alien.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658759" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've completed your trials, apprentice, but that is not what makes a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stand and account for yourself, acolyte. Let's see what you're made of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658763" id2="17" version="1065353216">I look at you, and I wonder... are you among the truly loyal, or do you hide treason in your heart?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658764" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am heir to a great Sith bloodline. How dare you even ask such a question of me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="658764" id2="17" version="1065353216">You insult my lineage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658765" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do what the Emperor commands me to. Your special heritage does not place you above suspicion--nor should it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you always make a habit of accusing strangers of treachery and sedition?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="658767" id2="17" version="1065353216">What an insulting question.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658768" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are no stranger to me. I know everyone in this Academy--even its former slaves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="658770" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't answer to strangers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658771" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Inquisitor Arzanon, head of Academy security... and do not think you can so easily deflect my question.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="658773" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a stupid question.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658774" id2="17" version="1065353216">Defiance of authority is a hallmark of the immature... and the subversive. I recommend you reconsider your attitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658776" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is one threat our Empire must remain forever vigilant against: those within our own ranks who undermine and weaken us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intelligence reports indicate this valley shelters traitors--acolytes who seek to destroy our Emperor's carefully built order and replace it with their own weak-minded heresies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658780" id2="17" version="1065353216">They hide among the faithful and obedient, but make no mistake--they will destroy us all, given the chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658782" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've watched as the traitors scuttle about this valley and plot against us. We know their faces and their names.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658784" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is the Emperor's will that the sands of Korriban be slaked with the blood of these traitors. Prove your allegiance by executing them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658785" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be a great honor to serve you, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="658785" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do as you command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658786" id2="17" version="1065353216">And in serving me, you serve the Emperor. Remember that as you exterminate those vermin in the valley.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658788" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure we shouldn't just arrest them? They could be shown the error of their ways.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="658788" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do they have to die?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Treason is a crime with only one punishment: death. If you lack the resolve to uphold the law, that will say much about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658791" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll give you the means to identify the traitors. Eliminate enough of them to prove your loyalty, then return to Inquisitor Arzanon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658793" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will be watching your progress with great interest. Go now. See that the Emperor's will be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="658795" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658796" id2="17" version="1065353216">You would place your own will above the Emperor's? Heresy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658798" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will be watching you very closely from now on. If you side with the traitors, you will share their fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658802" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have much yet to learn, acolyte. I will be watching your progress with great interest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="658803" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are not Sith. Do not inconvenience me with your questions.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
