<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>50</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_09/scene_08_senya_valkorion.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168875" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's impressive, you know. People from all over the galaxy want to stand behind you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168876" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll need every last one of them and more to make this work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1168876" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168877" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is how it was always going to be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1168877" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's my destiny.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168878" id2="17" version="1065353216">That can't be what you were out here contemplating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1168878" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's really on your mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168879" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is, in a way. I was thinking how so many Scions followed Heskal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168881" id2="17" version="1065353216">He would have them die as he did because their deaths were foreseen. Their visions provide great insight, but they're not infallible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168884" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reminds me of the Heralds of Zildrog.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168885" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's another leader who paid for his certainty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168887" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say what you will about Valkorion, but he at least considered the viewpoints of others. He listened to me. Most of the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168889" id2="17" version="1065353216">He didn't--he would never have done what--what Arcann....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168890" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arcann had a twin. Thexan. They were inseparable until his death. Vaylin told me, during our fight... Arcann murdered Thexan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168893" id2="17" version="1065353216">His own brother. Maybe if I had raised him....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your fight with Vaylin--what happened?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168897" id2="17" version="1065353216">What she had to say, it struck me down to my core. Paralyzed me. She slipped away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168899" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now more than ever, I realize my children must be stopped and that I have to make peace with the choices I've made.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever you've done to get here, I hope you can do the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168903" id2="17" version="1065353216">She raises a good question: How do you look back on your path to this moment?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168904" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mean that whirlwind of insanity?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1168904" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a blur.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168905" id2="17" version="1065353216">I made the decisions I felt were right. That's about all any of us can ever do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1168905" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no regrets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168906" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're in my head. Why don't you take a look for yourself?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1168906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not going to read my thoughts?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168907" id2="17" version="1065353216">And what good would that do our alliance?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168909" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may not see an alliance, but our destinies are now intertwined. Take advantage of that fact and there is much you will be capable of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168911" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see you defeating Arcann, even if there are those on this world who disagree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168912" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does that mean? Who disagrees?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168913" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will learn soon enough....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168917" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's out there somewhere. Our own father, plotting against us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168919" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's not the only one. After I told Mother that you killed Thexan, she probably wants your head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168921" id2="17" version="1065353216">But it's not a problem. You have the throne, the fleet, this whole empire.... You're as safe from her as can be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168923" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish Thexan could be here now. He'd see I was right to challenge Father.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imagine it: the three of us ruling this empire as it was meant to be ruled.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168927" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd like it if Thexan were here, too. But that's no longer possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168929" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you really want us to feel more like a family again, we can make that happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thexen wasn't our only sibling....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1169228" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. That's what Heskal believed, too. Look at how the Scions followed him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1169229" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was worried Heskal had blinded you with his certainty like he did with the Scions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1169324" id2="17" version="1065353216">A life without regret is a life well-lived... though I suppose it remains to be seen whether you will ultimately succeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1169326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Personally, I see you defeating Arcann. Others on this world disagree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1169327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make light of it if you wish, but you've accomplished much and come far since your reawakening.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1169330" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are of one purpose, but your mind is your own. Use it well and you will succeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't matter. Father has a new favorite. He wants the Outlander to take all of this from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183486" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll die before I let that happen to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184154" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course you will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184157" id2="17" version="1065353216">I told you before that Arcann had a brother. Thexan. They were inseparable until his death. Vaylin told me, during our fight... Arcann murdered Thexan.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
