<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>43</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/voss/bronze/republic/baiting_the_trap/scientist.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85355" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to go back to my lab on Coruscant. At least there I won't get anyone killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85357" id2="17" version="1065353216">I owe it to my assistants to continue my work here on Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you find out anything about my assistants?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85362" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss transmissions you picked up were sent by Imperials. When your assistants went to investigate, the Imperials killed them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85362" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were lured into a trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85363" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry. They're gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85364" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're... dead? This is my fault. I should never have sent them out there alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85365" id2="17" version="1065353216">You didn't kill your assistants; the Imperials did. They wanted to disrupt your work. Don't let them succeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85365" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy's to blame. Not you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85366" id2="17" version="1065353216">You came here to learn about Voss. So did your assistants. They knew the risks, but they also knew how important your mission was.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85366" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't give up on your work.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85367" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right. If I abandon my research, then my assistants gave their lives in vain. I can't let that happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85369" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will be more careful in the future, but my work here will continue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85371" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were so desperate to uncover the secrets of Voss that you sent your assistants into an obvious trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85371" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were selfish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Voss transmissions were fake. You sent your assistants into an Imperial ambush, and it cost them their lives!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85372" id2="17" version="1065353216">You got them killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85373" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right. This is my fault. My desire to uncover the secrets of this world blinded me to the danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85375" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing I can do for my assistants now, but I won't let anyone else die. My work here is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85377" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for looking into this. I'll inform the next of kin.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85381" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me know as soon as you find out anything about my assistants.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85385" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi? Thank goodness. You're just what I need.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85387" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me. I don't mean to trouble you, but... you're a soldier, aren't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85389" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're one of those freelancers, aren't you? I... I need some help. And I'm willing to pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85391" id2="17" version="1065353216">My name is Doctor Forrod. I'm an archaeologist. I came here with my team to study the Voss and their culture.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, my assistants have gone missing. I'm afraid something terrible has happened to them. Could you look into this for me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85394" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the feeling there's something you're not telling me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85394" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there more to this?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85395" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ashamed to admit it, but I may have let my hunger for knowledge override my responsibility for their personal safety.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85397" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll help, for a price.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85398" id2="17" version="1065353216">My project is well funded. I'll see you're properly paid for your efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85401" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your zeal is encouraging. I only hope it's not too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85403" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few days ago, we picked up some unusual transmissions. They seemed to be in an ancient Voss dialect.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85405" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were able to locate the origin of the transmissions. I sent my assistants to investigate. I haven't heard from them since.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was there some type of warning or message?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85406" id2="17" version="1065353216">What did the transmission say?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85407" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dialect was too archaic for us to translate it. That's one of the reasons I was so interested in learning more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave it to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please hurry. My assistants have been gone three days now. I fear the worst.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85412" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm busy. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Easy for you to say. Go on your way, then. Leave me alone if you're not going to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss is a remarkable world. The people here are fascinating.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
