<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>22</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/event/rakghoul/republic/planetside_intro.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118803" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, I don't know if or when it will all be over! Now go back to your home, stay inside and stop bothering me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you all right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118806" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's just so frustrating! I want to get out there and help but instead I'm the quarantine zone's glorified babysitter--and not all that glorified.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118807" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think you want to be stuck in rakghoul country. You don't look equipped for it, for one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118807" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's safer for you here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118808" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you're a THORN volunteer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Funny, you don't seem to be tied to a stake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118809" id2="17" version="1065353216">So go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, obviously, I'd go grab all my blasters first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118811" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tralie Masoon. Signed up to make a difference. Whee.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha ha. Ever heard of a thing called work ethic? I'm not gonna just quit on THORN.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118814" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, look, you're clearly some kind of big deal. You need to go out there and take those rakghouls down for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118816" id2="17" version="1065353216">A little tip: there are tunnels out there just crawling with rakghouls. Like, I wouldn't even go. It's their point of origin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where do I find that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope I run into you at a cantina when all this is over. I wanna hear every last amazing, gruesome detail!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118831" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess I missed all the fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118832" id2="17" version="1065353216">They said you made it underground. Didn't think I'd see you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like I keep telling everyone, I am not an information kiosk. Try checking the news once in a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118835" id2="17" version="1065353216">How am I supposed to live vicariously through you if you're hanging out with me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124148" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look for THORN's massive drill thing. They call it The Spike. Can't miss it. It'll take you underground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124184" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey. Hi. Uh, not that I'm following your every move or anything, but heard you're near The Spike. You're really going down there. Cool.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
