<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>25</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/event/rakghoul/republic/republic_announcer.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123974" id2="17" version="1065353216">The leading cause of the spread of rakghoul infection is apathy. Be informed, look for telltale signs of infection, and stay alert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be advised: anyone exhibiting signs of genetic mutation from rakghoul-plague exposure should be seen as an imminent threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123976" id2="17" version="1065353216">To prevent further spread of the rakghoul plague, the use of lethal force on mutated individuals is strongly advised.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123977" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no cure for the rakghoul plague. It is important to stress that sufferers of rakghoul mutation cannot be saved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123978" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Supreme Chancellor strongly urges extreme caution during the present rakghoul threat. Please heed all THORN safety precaution guidelines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warning: the Interstellar Travel Council has issued a Level One Emergency Alert on Tatooine due to an outbreak of the rakghoul plague.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not attempt to evacuate loved ones from Tatooine. Full rakghoul quarantine protocols are presently in effect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123983" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hyland Organization for Rakghoul Neutralization seeks qualified aid volunteers on Tatooine. Locate a THORN representative onworld for details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123984" id2="17" version="1065353216">In uncertain times, safety remains the Republic's top priority. Therefore, solutions of all severities remain subject to consideration in ending the rakghoul problem on Tatooine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shipments originating from Anchorhead and other spaceports of Tatooine will be turned away while the rakghoul alert remains in effect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warning: the Interstellar Travel Council has issued a Level One Emergency Alert on Alderaan due to an outbreak of the rakghoul plague.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not attempt to evacuate loved ones from Alderaan. Full rakghoul quarantine protocols are presently in effect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123991" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hyland Organization for Rakghoul Neutralization seeks qualified aid volunteers on Alderaan. Locate a THORN representative onworld for details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123992" id2="17" version="1065353216">In uncertain times, safety remains the Republic's top priority. Therefore, solutions of all severities remain subject to consideration in ending the rakghoul problem on Alderaan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Visiting dignitaries from House Organa: please see your Republic attache for extended accommodations while the rakghoul alert remains in effect on Alderaan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warning: the Interstellar Travel Council has issued a Level One Emergency Alert on Quesh due to an outbreak of the rakghoul plague.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not attempt to evacuate loved ones from Quesh. Full rakghoul quarantine protocols are presently in effect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123999" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hyland Organization for Rakghoul Neutralization seeks qualified aid volunteers on Quesh. Locate a THORN representative onworld for details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124000" id2="17" version="1065353216">In uncertain times, safety remains the Republic's top priority. Therefore, solutions of all severities remain subject to consideration in ending the rakghoul problem on Quesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Though chemical-mine operations continue on Quesh, the planet remains in quarantine due to the rakghoul outbreak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warning: the Interstellar Travel Council has issued a Level One Emergency Alert on Corellia due to an outbreak of the rakghoul plague.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not attempt to evacuate loved ones from Corellia. Full rakghoul quarantine protocols are presently in effect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124007" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hyland Organization for Rakghoul Neutralization seeks qualified aid volunteers on Corellia. Locate a THORN representative onworld for details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124008" id2="17" version="1065353216">In uncertain times, safety remains the Republic's top priority. Therefore, solutions of all severities remain subject to consideration in ending the rakghoul problem on Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reports indicate that the rakghoul outbreak has not lessened Imperial presence on Corellia.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
