<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>21</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/event/rakghoul/republic/underground_intro.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118836" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm officially impressed. If only I could ensure you'd be around for every crisis....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your being here, it's given me hope. Let's stop this plague.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me. My full attention's required for outbreak crisis protocol seven.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Status update?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118847" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've exhausted outbreak crisis protocols one through fifteen. No effect. Rest assured, Mister Hyland, that I have many more scenarios yet to attempt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118849" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure we'll prevail, sir. One thing: I have lost some workers to the plague. Perhaps you could spare more personnel?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't know how much difference one fresh body will make, but it looks like you've got a pretty sturdy one with you there now. Hyland out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118852" id2="17" version="1065353216">In need of fresh bodies? Looks like you've got volunteers close enough to breathe on you there. Hyland out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, thank the heavens that's over! Do you know how hard it is to essentially lie to that man? That's Addalar Hyland! He makes weapons!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. Your confidence and calm seem to be a rarity down there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118863" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm told the rakghoul population is at its worst down here. Rest assured, that won't be the case for long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Relax. I'm here to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118864" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can hardly believe someone so frantic's in charge of an emergency situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some crisis specialist....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hyland has the right to hear the truth, don't you think?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why lie?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118866" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you are a volunteer? First good news I've had since I was assigned down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118867" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have every one of your top aid workers turn into bloodthirsty monsters and see what it does to your composure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118869" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's bad down here--about as bad as it can get. This is the epicenter of the plague--has to be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118872" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can thin out the rakghoul population, we just might have a shot at averting a galactic pandemic. Best of luck to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118874" id2="17" version="1065353216">I only really lied about my state of mind--but now that you're here, I feel better about our chances. I should warn you, though....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
