<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>56</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/world/the_neutralizer/major_garik.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492414" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just heard that Captain Dealk led his men against the survivors of your attack. He and his men were victorious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492417" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did it--you destroyed the Neutralizer! We've already tested our weapons. Everything's back to normal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now I can get my men back into battle. It's payback time, and the Empire isn't going to like our currency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492420" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't lie. It was tough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wish I could join you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. I'm sure you must have much more important things to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492424" id2="17" version="1065353216">My power is unmatched.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just knowing that we've got someone like you on our side gives the men a boost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492427" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really did save the Republic's hide on this one. The shipment of new weapons was delayed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492429" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you hadn't destroyed that machine, the planet would belong to the Empire. Good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492431" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you dealt with the Neutralizer yet? You should hurry--before they ship it out to the front lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492432" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were sitting ducks out there! A quarter of my men were killed and all because of defective weapons!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492434" id2="17" version="1065353216">It wasn't defective weapons. It was an attack by the Empire. Command is sending new equipment to take care of the problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492436" id2="17" version="1065353216">By the time new weapons get here, the Empire will own this planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe it won't come to that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492440" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi--we have an emergency. Without the order's help, we may lose Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492441" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on me to assist the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492441" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can I assist, Major?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492442" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force has brought us together. How can I assist you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492442" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me how I can help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain. We've got a real situation here. If we don't get SpecForce on the job, Balmorra will belong to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always ready to assist, sir. How can I help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad at your service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Freelancer. How would you feel about saving Balmorra and earning a few credits at the same time?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492446" id2="17" version="1065353216">How would I feel? Like a kid in a candy store. What can I do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492446" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're speaking my language.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492447" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're just in time. I hope what they say about you is true, because I need your help to save Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492448" id2="17" version="1065353216">What can I do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492448" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I can help, I will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492449" id2="17" version="1065353216">What exactly do you need?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. Although our intel is still a bit sketchy at this point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clean up your own mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492453" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think I'm exaggerating? The lives of thousands of innocent civilians are at stake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492455" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire has a prototype weapon called the Neutralizer which puts out an energy field that disables all standard-issue Republic weaponry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492457" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Disables&quot;?  Half of our guns exploded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492459" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know that, Captain. I'm hoping you can sneak behind enemy lines and destroy the Neutralizer's generators--I don't have anyone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492460" id2="17" version="1065353216">It doesn't sound like we have much time. I'll do whatever I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492461" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire knows the value of that thing, so you'll be up against automated defenses, Imperial troops and assault droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492463" id2="17" version="1065353216">But on the plus side, your lightsabers won't be affected. Neither will your... other advantages.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492465" id2="17" version="1065353216">But on the plus side, your weaponry is far too advanced to be affected by the Neutralizer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't this Neutralizer disable my equipment as well?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will my weapons work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Notice I said &quot;standard issue&quot; equipment. Your luck is our luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure you don't want me to take down the whole Empire while I'm at it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a suicide run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492471" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll be tough, I won' t deny it. You'll be up against Imperial troops, automated defenses and assault droids. But you're our only hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492473" id2="17" version="1065353216">So--will you do it? The fate of the Republic war effort lies in your hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, yes. I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. With your advanced weaponry unaffected, you'll retain the element of surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="492478" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you manage to pull this off, leave the cleanup to me. My men are hungry for revenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry. I draw the line at taking on an entire Imperial army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492481" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then when Balmorra falls, I hope you'll take on your share of the blame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Dealk. I'm looking into it. And I'd appreciate it if you didn't take that tone with a superior officer.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
