<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>47</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/class/smuggler/darmas_pollaran.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710638" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain! Who'd have thought, when we met on Coruscant, that I'd be calling you today with a formal Republic briefing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Personally, I'd prefer there to be nothing &quot;brief&quot; in our encounters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does that mean you're coming to Balmorra in person?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="710641" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] I miss you too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sadly, I have a deadly allergy to high-energy blaster bolts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710644" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not what I remember....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="710644" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, no?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooh, ouch. You'll have to give me a chance to refresh your memory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me what I'm doing here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="710647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's stick to the mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710648" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a key Republic target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senator Dodonna is eager to see how you handle your first mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710652" id2="17" version="1065353216">Balmorra was once the Republic's main supplier of everything military. Until the Empire moved in and the Senate voted to turn tail and run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710654" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which left the Empire holding everything the Republic had commissioned for &quot;Project Nebula.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710655" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's Project Nebula?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="710655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, I'll bite.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710656" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was supposed to be the Republic's answer to Imperial aggression.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Top-of-the-line prototype capital ships, ion cannons, cluster missiles and a few experimental goodies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="710660" id2="17" version="1065353216">So we have to...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710661" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire is sending the complete Project Nebula munitions shipment to their front lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710663" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are prototypes of top-of-the-line capital ships, ion cannons, cluster missiles... the Republic doesn't stand a chance against them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710665" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless you can get in somehow and divert the Nebula shipment to Palliser Station, a Republic base off Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710666" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senate didn't think that one through?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="710666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dumb move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710667" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voidwolf came in too fast and too hard. The Republic forces fled without much more than their bedclothes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710669" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic spent billions on Project Nebula's weapons, then the Imperials nabbed them before they fired a shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710671" id2="17" version="1065353216">And now the Empire is sending the complete Nebula munitions shipment to their front lines. The Republic's got no chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710672" id2="17" version="1065353216">You stopped talking. So, here's where you expect me to jump in and do something?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="710672" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh-uh. Stop looking like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710673" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think the munitions will pick themselves up and migrate back to the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="710673" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want me to get them back?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="710674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why come to me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because sneaking into protected facilities and boosting their cargo isn't part of Republic trooper training.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senator Dodonna wants you to work with the Balmorran resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710679" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can help you track down the Nebula shipment, then find a way to divert it to Palliser Station, a Republic base near Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710680" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's not going to leave their best munitions just lying around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="710680" id2="17" version="1065353216">How am I supposed to do that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710681" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senator's letting you figure out the &quot;how.&quot; Which gives you an interesting opportunity....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="710683" id2="17" version="1065353216">No problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then let me add a little spice. Once you've got the Nebula shipment, can the Republic really make you hand it over?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710686" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, dangerous mission behind enemy lines, key importance... how many zeros are we talking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="710686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's talk price.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710687" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic wants to get the munitions away from the Empire--however, not enough to pay market value.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710689" id2="17" version="1065353216">A smart operator might sell the prototypes back to them piece-by-piece... not that I'm the one who told you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, your contact on the ground is one of the rebels, Numen Brock. Check in with him when you land in Bugtown.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710693" id2="17" version="1065353216">And pick me up a gift, all right, sweetheart? Maybe a Mark-5 assault droid?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="710694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hats off if you can do this thing, Captain.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
