<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>84</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/open_worlds/class/sith_warrior/end_times/nataya_gannek.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1085609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me, Master!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088676" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hand is secure, apprentice. Join me aboard my ship at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just a few more minutes, Master. The information locked within these halls dates back millennia. It's incredible!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088680" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor's Wrath--we meet at last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your campaign to destroy the Emperor ends now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088681" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's over, Gnost-Dural.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088682" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know so little of my intentions, Wrath. But I know everything about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Return the captive servants.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surrender the Hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088685" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you would come for the Emperor's pawns, Wrath. I know everything about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088687" id2="17" version="1065353216">Face me, and your dying screams will wake the Emperor from his slumber.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088687" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will destroy you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088688" id2="17" version="1065353216">I anticipated your hatred, Wrath. After all, I know everything about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088690" id2="17" version="1065353216">Broonmark, you fled Republic service to ravage the enemies of the Wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1088692" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic clan strangles us, but the Sith clan feeds our hunger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088694" id2="17" version="1065353216">A chained beast, unleashed only to kill. You and Broonmark share this common purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jaesa, are you aware the Wrath murdered your parents while hunting you down?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course I knew. And if I could do it all over again, I'd deliver the killing blow myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088702" id2="17" version="1065353216">They perished so I could achieve glory as a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088704" id2="17" version="1065353216">My master did what was necessary to free me from the Jedi Order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jaesa, your former master Nomen Karr was a good friend. If he ever saw how many Jedi you've slain by the Wrath's side....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088708" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Wrath taught me to embrace my emotions. Nomen Karr couldn't even confront his own anger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jaesa burns with passion for you, Wrath. But it is not too late to save her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088712" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're waiting for me to weep in shame, don't hold your breath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088714" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a new master now--one who shares none of Nomen Karr's hypocrisy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088716" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are truly an expert of corruption, Wrath. But the Emperor's insidious powers eclipse even your own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088718" id2="17" version="1065353216">I learned how Darth Baras sent you to die, how you struck him down and how Captain Quinn turned against you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088720" id2="17" version="1065353216">My crime still haunts me, Jedi. I would rather die than disappoint my master again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quinn has feelings for you, Wrath. How interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088724" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll answer for that mistake for the rest of my life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given time, broken bones mend to become stronger than ever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Pierce, your master has spilled almost as much Imperial blood as Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088730" id2="17" version="1065353216">All for the good of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088732" id2="17" version="1065353216">You inspire great loyalty, Wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vette, the Wrath claimed you as a slave on Korriban--yet you still wear your cursed shock collar?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every moment is living agony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088740" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sore subject, Jedi. Push it, and I'll take my frustration out on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Torment poisons you, Vette. Be comforted by the knowledge that your master wears similar shackles.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vette, you've been chained to the Wrath since your master graduated from Korriban. But slavery is no excuse for the crimes you've committed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088746" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's complicated, Jedi. You'll never understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088748" id2="17" version="1065353216">She has feelings for you, Wrath. I underestimated your magnetism.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088750" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to judge me? Come back here, and say that to my face!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088752" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember, Vette--even a life without chains does not equal true freedom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Overseer Tremel, Darth Baras, Darth Vowrawn. The blood of your mentors stains your armor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vanquisher of Darth Baras, subduer of Darth Vowrawn, tenuous ally of the Dark Council. While you represent the Emperor, none will truly trust you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088758" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been observing you for months, peeling back the layers, searching for the answer to that elusive question: Who is the Emperor's Wrath?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088759" id2="17" version="1065353216">History will remember me as the Sith Lord who crushed Gnost-Dural.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088759" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am your executioner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Continue on this path, and you'll only be remembered as the last champion of a tyrannical despot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enlighten me, Gnost-Dural. Who am I?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088762" id2="17" version="1065353216">What did you surmise?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088765" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and your apprentice champion the light in an Empire corrupted by darkness. A noble but doomed cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088767" id2="17" version="1065353216">You rebel against the darkness that tears the Empire apart, but you can't reverse the damage alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088769" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are the purest of Sith, dedicated to the dark side and corrupting all in your wake. But power alone will not save you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088771" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are a Sith with ever changing priorities. But the time has come for you to choose a side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Silence your Jedi tricks and show yourself, Gnost-Dural!</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088773" id2="17" version="1065353216">No more mind games.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088774" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen to me, Wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088776" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Emperor awakens, he will annihilate the balance between light and dark, tearing the galaxy asunder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088778" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi Council has tasked Master Gnost-Dural with preventing his return.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088780" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you can aid us. Submit to my study, and join the Hand in captivity at my enclave. Your sacrifice will help cleanse the galaxy of the Emperor's corruption.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088781" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Emperor ascends to power, I will stand by his side and force you to bow before him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088781" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor gives me strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088782" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you would say that, but I had to ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088784" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no love for the Emperor, but I will not enter Jedi captivity to destroy him. There must be some other way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I help another way?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088785" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the only solution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you enter stasis, I will probe your consciousness for insight into the Emperor's weakness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088789" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Emperor's barbs have pierced your psyche, removing them may prove... catastrophic. But I will do everything in my power to free you from the Emperor's chains unscathed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088790" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you know me so well, you know I'd never accept.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088790" id2="17" version="1065353216">No deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088791" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suspected as much, but I had to offer you a chance at redemption.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088793" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep the Emperor's servants as collateral if you must, but I will not suffer imprisonment. We must work as equals if we're to stand any chance against our foe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088793" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a counteroffer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088794" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, but I cannot risk the galaxy to spare your pride.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nataya, subdue the Emperor's Wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088798" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've studied your every tactic, victory and defeat. May the Force guide my blade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Witness my answer, Gnost-Dural!</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088799" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no fool. [Attack Nataya]</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here is my answer, Jedi!</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1088800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never. [Attack Nataya]</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave, Master! I will stop the Wrath!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1089776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your apprentice plays the part of a Sith, while you nurture the light inside her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1089778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your apprentice hides behind the mask of a Sith, but her true hopes still burn within.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
