<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>26</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_07/ambients.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165915" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one seems to be discussing why anyone would sabotage the power grid in the first place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165918" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one seems to be discussing why anyone would attack the Spire and kill all those people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165920" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because who wants to acknowledge the truth?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165922" id2="17" version="1065353216">What truth is that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some folks live for destruction. They delight in causing others to suffer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165926" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's awful!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165928" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165932" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wonder how things'd be different if Arcann's twin took the throne.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165934" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thexan? Haven't thought of him in a long time, may he stay at rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Saw him at a ceremony once, in my life before. Stood calm and unwavering. Strong. Wouldn't have put the Heralds in charge of the Old World.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165938" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like having lunatics watch over a madhouse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165948" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't get why the Heralds want to see everything come to an end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165950" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't think folks should do things just because the &quot;dark serpent Zildrog, the destroyer&quot; says so? You ain't exactly alone in that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165952" id2="17" version="1065353216">See, that's it, though. I was taught Zildrog was a teacher. He offered tests and guidance to make people stronger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165954" id2="17" version="1065353216">Truth is, Zildrog lives out in the Endless Swamp. It's a monster that rises up and eats whoever's around!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Really?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nah, it's all nonsense. All of it. Going to buy a hat or not?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165960" id2="17" version="1065353216">You saw the Lady of Sorrows. Yeah, 'course you did. What did she look like?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165962" id2="17" version="1065353216">She had a crown, like. And--and a suit of armor. And she was fast and strong! She could punch and kick and--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165964" id2="17" version="1065353216">You watch too many holovids. You ever do see the Lady, my advice? Forget you ever did--and run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me, acolyte: What does the return of our great Zildrog mean to you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165968" id2="17" version="1065353216">It means death to disbelievers. It means the end of our corrupt society. It means great happiness for all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165970" id2="17" version="1065353216">You understand much. But do you know what will become of you? Your family?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165972" id2="17" version="1065353216">We give ourselves to Zildrog's glory so that the wicked may be punished. We die so that Zakuul may live on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. You are on your way. In Zildrog's name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165976" id2="17" version="1065353216">In Zildrog's name.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
