<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>41</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/republic/reclamation/officer_silas_console.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690414" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's about time you picked up. Davit's near-death, Hanley and Crissom aren't much better!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690416" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imps have us locked down tight and--and you're not with CorSec, so I'm going to guess that Checkpoint Lambda's been overrun too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690418" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're feeling generous, because our whole mission is in jeopardy unless someone out there can help us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690419" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have the Imps off of you as soon as I can get there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me how to find you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690420" id2="17" version="1065353216">No! There's something more important.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690422" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I knew more about your mission, I might be able to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690422" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sort of mission is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690423" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Empire occupied Corellia, they took control of a powerful tool to fight the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690425" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm listening, but talk fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690426" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's got us trapped, but while they're busy you could complete our objective.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690428" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a network of surveillance cameras, SurvNet, that covers the city and feeds back into monitoring stations here at CorSec Academy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690430" id2="17" version="1065353216">My squad was supposed to infiltrate the academy and disable those stations; right now, the Republic can't blink without the Imps seeing it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690431" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can see why those stations need to go. What about you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690431" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take care of the stations</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690432" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't forget about us, just make sure those stations get disabled first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690434" id2="17" version="1065353216">My squad and I are in the main building--we took out the monitors here before the Imps found us, but there are more nearby.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690436" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay sharp, and hurry. We'll see you when you get here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your lives are more important than the monitoring stations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690437" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't just leave you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690438" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can probably hold, as long as you're fast--we disabled the doors so the Imps have to cut their way in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690440" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not interested.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690441" id2="17" version="1065353216">You interested in visiting the families of my dead officers? Because they are buying time with their blood in here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690443" id2="17" version="1065353216">We locked down the monitoring stations in the academy's main building, but there are still plenty of them in the outlying structures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi, we've got the Imps focused on us--with your skills, you might be able to disable the remaining stations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690446" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a soldier--while we've got the Imps distracted, can you take out the remaining stations?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right now, the Imps don't know you're here. That means you can take out the rest of the monitoring stations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, Officer. As soon as the stations are disabled, I'll come help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690448" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle them, and save you</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690449" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do as you ask, but I won't forget about your team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690449" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stations first, then you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your head down, Officer. I'll be there as soon as the stations are out of commission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690450" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take care of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690451" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want me to blow stuff up? I'm happy to oblige.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure, I can do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690452" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't wait to thank you in person. Find us in the main building after the job's done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have it your way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690454" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate it. We'll hole up in the main building and wait for you to come find us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690456" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll send help as soon as I find someone who cares.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690456" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't help. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690457" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't just leave! What kind of--</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
