<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>61</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/world/imperial/shattering_the_peace/captain_westro.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649697" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll make the Republic sorry they ever survived the Sacking of Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Westro, Forty-second Imperial Infantry. A pleasure to have you for this mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649702" id2="17" version="1065353216">I followed Sith into battle during the Sacking of Coruscant. It's an honor to serve you, my lord. Let this fight be equally victorious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now begins the final eradication of the Galactic Republic. Once we cripple its people here, we will hunt them to extinction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649703" id2="17" version="1065353216">This day will be remembered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649704" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've suffered those vermin long enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649706" id2="17" version="1065353216">I witnessed the Sith's power firsthand during the Sacking of Coruscant. I'm privileged to serve you, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just so long as we're both aware how lucky you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649708" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've served with distinction for twenty years. You may rely on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649710" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still remember the vital role Imperial Intelligence played in the Sacking of Coruscant. You brought glory to us and terror to our enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649711" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're the first ones into battle and the last ones out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649711" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's what we do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649712" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm honored to serve alongside you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649714" id2="17" version="1065353216">I served alongside mercenaries like you at the Sacking of Coruscant. With your added strength, we'll return soon to finish the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649715" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the right price, I'll follow you into battle anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649715" id2="17" version="1065353216">As long as I get paid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649716" id2="17" version="1065353216">Plenty of spoils on Coruscant. I left there with a full cargo crate. Been itching to get back ever since.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649718" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll win the war together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649719" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be an honor to see all of you in action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649721" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we'd had people like you in our forces during the Sacking of Coruscant, we would've held that planet. Maybe we'll get that chance someday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649722" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope we do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649723" id2="17" version="1065353216">The larger the Empire grows, the closer we come to overpowering our enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649725" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire is stronger than ever, its people ready to crush the Republic. My ally here is no exception.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649725" id2="17" version="1065353216">Together, we'll seize victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649726" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do my best to honor you all, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, isn't that sweet. You've picked up a not-so-secret admirer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone has a fan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649729" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am honored to serve you as well, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649731" id2="17" version="1065353216">My job is easier when I'm unnoticed. My ally ensures I remain an unknown variable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649731" id2="17" version="1065353216">We do make an excellent team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649732" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd never overlook a member of Imperial Intelligence. Glad to have you for this op, agent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649734" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sometimes I feel left out of this whole Imp party. Then I remember the credits. There are credits?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649734" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some of us came for the money.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649735" id2="17" version="1065353216">This attack is too important to fail. You'll be well paid for its success.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649737" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't every old veteran say they sacked the Republic homeworld?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649737" id2="17" version="1065353216">You fought on Coruscant?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649738" id2="17" version="1065353216">I earned my scars at the Jedi Temple with Darth Malgus. Shot a Jedi in the back. Proudest moment of my life, until today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649740" id2="17" version="1065353216">Save the flattery. What's the mission?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649740" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's enough sucking up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our strike team has infiltrated the Republic's research complex and identified critical objectives. The enemy's forces are strong there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your mission is to coordinate with our people, secure the strike team's goals and destroy every Republic combatant in your path. Any questions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649744" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll show those Republic fools they have no business on Nar Shaddaa.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649744" id2="17" version="1065353216">None.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does your strike team know what forces the Republic has in place?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649745" id2="17" version="1065353216">What will we be fighting?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recon teams report heavy resistance. Elite soldiers, mercenary forces, even Jedi. They'll attack you on sight. Be ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649748" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have pressing business elsewhere. How much time will all this Republic bashing take?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649748" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many goals are there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649749" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy's made several major advances. We must neutralize them all, whatever the cost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649751" id2="17" version="1065353216">One last detail... the Hutts sent one of their droids to monitor Republic activity in the area. When you're done assisting our people, find the droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649752" id2="17" version="1065353216">Locate our contacts, wipe out the Republic and find the Hutt droid--got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649752" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649753" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's so special about this droid?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649754" id2="17" version="1065353216">This droid is tapped into Nar Shaddaa's entire security grid. No telling what details it'll pick up during the battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649756" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, scrap the droid with everything else?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something else to destroy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649757" id2="17" version="1065353216">Negative. The droid's an important contact. It's gathering useful intel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our people await you in the research complex. You have their coordinates. Glory to the Empire!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me. I'm awaiting orders from my superior.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
