<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>50</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/world/imperial/shattering_the_peace/dx_ax.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649973" id2="17" version="1065353216">The DX annihilator network continues monitoring the Republic retreat. Hold all queries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Facial recognition scanning complete. Matching records from &quot;Ukabi incident&quot; datafile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Facial recognition scanning complete. Matching records of Imperial operative profiles.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649980" id2="17" version="1065353216">DX annihilator network online. Interface activated. Opening holochannel....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations are in order. Republic forces have fled the research complex, broken and demoralized. Even better, the few survivors don't know it was us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their unlucky friends know all too well. I was the last thing they saw.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649983" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dead ones do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649984" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can never tell if you enjoy your work. Always so grim.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649986" id2="17" version="1065353216">I enjoy few things more than breaking and demoralizing. One could say it's my life's work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649986" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was a pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649987" id2="17" version="1065353216">May you have a long and happy career.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not many can inflict the kind of damage we did. The Republic's smart. They'll piece it together quick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649989" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll figure it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knowing and having proof are two different things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649992" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy's advanced research is now ours. Imperial Intelligence will put that technology to better use.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649992" id2="17" version="1065353216">We gained valuable data, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649993" id2="17" version="1065353216">The data is already on its way to Dromund Kaas. The Republic's loss is our gain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649995" id2="17" version="1065353216">It only takes one witness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649995" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can you be sure?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649996" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're monitoring Republic comm frequencies--even the coded ones. They send emergency alerts in the event of an Imperial attack. They haven't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649998" id2="17" version="1065353216">This operation was a masterpiece. It's a shame we can't sign it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anonymity is such a waste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cheer up. When the last Republic world falls, everyone will know we are responsible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial celebrations are premature. The DX annihilator network has exposed secret Republic allies and backup operations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calculations indicate a complete enemy recovery within one standard month. The Empire must invade the Network Access annex and eliminate all threats.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650004" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've come too far to give the enemy a second chance. Let's finish this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our mission isn't over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650005" id2="17" version="1065353216">After all the damage we inflicted, how could they compensate so quickly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could they recover that fast?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650006" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't want to find out. The Dark Council won't tolerate failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650008" id2="17" version="1065353216">When was the last time you had a memory wipe?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your circuits are faulty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't blame the droid. Clearly, the Republic is more entrenched on Nar Shaddaa than we realized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell us everything about the enemy's hidden position--starting with how we get there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650013" id2="17" version="1065353216">A secure turbolift on this level will transport directly to the objective. Shadow Syndicate and Imperial Intelligence personnel are converging to assist you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we really need help from a criminal organization that tried to betray us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650014" id2="17" version="1065353216">That syndicate is dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650015" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic must not be allowed to regain its strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never heard of the Shadow Syndicate. What is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650017" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Shadow Syndicate&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650018" id2="17" version="1065353216">A coalition of the most powerful organizations on Nar Shaddaa. Allies to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650020" id2="17" version="1065353216">The DX annihilator network's assistance won't be forgotten.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650020" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been useful, droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650021" id2="17" version="1065353216">Record of this coalition will persist in our memory banks as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650023" id2="17" version="1065353216">The plan is to kill everyone. We don't need extra targets in the cross fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650023" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll just be in the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650024" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have no idea what's awaiting us. Knowledge is power--acquire some before you attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coordinate with our allies and rout the enemy--but be mindful we maintain discretion. Zavrasha out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Transmitting secure turbolift coordinates and Shadow Syndicate contact profile. DX annihilator network continues monitoring the Republic retreat. Will advise if new data becomes available.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650032" id2="17" version="1065353216">The DX annihilator network is collating data. Hold all queries.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
