<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>89</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/world/imperial/shattering_the_peace/narvusin.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650036" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Lords of Chance clearly favor the Empire. I'll have to start practicing the Imperial salute....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650038" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's done. The Republic won't be recovering from the damage we've inflicted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Truly, the Lords of Chance love a winner. Your path must be paved in solid aurodium.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650041" id2="17" version="1065353216">My employer wishes to congratulate you personally--and offer a gift. I present Godoba the Hutt of the Shadow Syndicate....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="650043" id2="17" version="1065353216">How pleasing to see you again. I'm glad we had this opportunity to work together and smooth over past differences.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't think anyone's forgotten what a fickle worm you are, Godoba.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650044" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not forgiven.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="650045" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, let us move beyond this. Can't you see that I wish to be your friend?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="650047" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is always a pleasure to greet powerful allies. I have long admired the Empire's taste in heroes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Words are the least sincere form of appreciation. What else have you got?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Flattery is cheap.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="650049" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are shrewd. I admire that--and will reward it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650051" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been a long battle. My patience has worn thin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650051" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get to the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650052" id2="17" version="1065353216">We couldn't have beaten the Republic without your help, Godoba.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650052" id2="17" version="1065353216">We appreciate your assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="650053" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am glad you acknowledge this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="650055" id2="17" version="1065353216">A great opportunity has revealed itself to strengthen the bonds of our grand alliance. My servant will explain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650057" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is evacuating the wretched little families of its diplomats and researchers. We'll destroy their transport on your order. But we must be quick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killing the enemy's resolve is the fastest way to win a war. Take away their reason to fight, and they'll collapse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650058" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy will be demoralized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650059" id2="17" version="1065353216">You understand the strategy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650061" id2="17" version="1065353216">You people are utterly immoral. I like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650061" id2="17" version="1065353216">I enjoy committing atrocities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650062" id2="17" version="1065353216">We thought you'd appreciate the gesture.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650064" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I hear &quot;gift,&quot; I expect something I can spend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650064" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not my idea of a gift.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650065" id2="17" version="1065353216">Notoriety is a currency you can spend to generate new opportunities. Just think how you'll impress the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is the Shadow Syndicate willing to do this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650067" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's quite an offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperials are our best customers. We just want you to be happy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650070" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're under strict orders to keep this conflict quiet. Killing a ship full of civilians would attract attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zavrasha wouldn't approve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650071" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's more important, pleasing some petty bureaucrat or stabbing your foe in the heart?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why isn't there time to think this through--or consult my superiors?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650073" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the rush?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650074" id2="17" version="1065353216">The transport is about to depart. If it jumps to hyperspace, we'll lose our chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="650076" id2="17" version="1065353216">If their families pay the price of failure, the Republic will think twice before sending more people to Nar Shaddaa.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650078" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the perfect opportunity to bury your enemy's ambitions forever. Say the word, and we'll ensure that transport never reaches its destination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650079" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make their deaths painful--and memorable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650079" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, kill them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="650080" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for accepting my gift. You won't be disappointed!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Receiving a transmission... our unmarked warship just intercepted the Republic transport. I'm sorry you can't see the fireball. It's spectacular.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just knowing the Republic's loved ones are dead is enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650084" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your unmarked warship had better remain a mystery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650084" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep the Empire's name clean.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650085" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic won't be able to prove a thing. We'll tell them it was Sisar pirates. They'll get the message.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650087" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure your warship's holo-imagers saved a detailed record.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make me a recording.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650088" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent idea. I'll see what we can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650090" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shadow Syndicate will need to find a more appropriate gift for the Empire than committing war crimes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650090" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, we don't kill civilians.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="650091" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are so difficult to please! But I will keep trying. Enjoy your victory over the Republic. Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650093" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel Harok is waiting for you at the spaceport. It's been a pleasure. May the Lords of Chance always smile on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650097" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your contacts are waiting. May the Lords of Chance smile upon you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650100" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, my new Imperial friends! The Lords of Chance are sorting the quick from the dead in here. Which will you be?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650101" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, friend! The Lords of Chance are busy sorting the quick from the dead. I hope you fall into the former category.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speed is not a factor in my survival--only the power of the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650102" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dark side conquers all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650103" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Lords of Chance are known to respect brute strength, from time to time. I'm sure you'll abide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650105" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm quick as lightning. Is that good enough?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650105" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm faster than anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650106" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would think so. Remind me never to race you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650108" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know who these &quot;Lords of Chance&quot; think they are, but deciding who lives and dies is my business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650108" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do the sorting around here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650109" id2="17" version="1065353216">And from the look of you, business must be good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650111" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's easy to dodge trouble when you see it coming. My vision has always been excellent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650111" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm fast when it matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650112" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eyes in the back of your head, eh? I'd expect nothing less from an Imperial spy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650114" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you belonged to the Shadow Syndicate. Are these &quot;Lords of Chance&quot; friends of yours?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650114" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Lords of Chance&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650115" id2="17" version="1065353216">Friends, indeed. They've kept me healthy and wealthy for years. They watch over gamblers. Protect and profit the risk-takers. But enough about them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just when I thought I'd met all the crazy people on Nar Shaddaa.... Tell me why we're talking--and make it quick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650117" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sort of lunatic are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650118" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to be so gruff. I'm here to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650120" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shadow Syndicate is at your command. Along with Imperial Intelligence, we're here to support your campaign against the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650122" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire has many enemies. We'll ensure they fail. Speak to the contacts on the list I'm transmitting you. They'll have details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650123" id2="17" version="1065353216">Things are about to get violent. If you value your life, find a place to hide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650123" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay out of the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650124" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Lords of Chance always protect the clever beings who take cover. But thank you for the warning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650126" id2="17" version="1065353216">What level of threat response should we expect?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650126" id2="17" version="1065353216">How much opposition is there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650127" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are the mission objectives, besides killing Republic forces?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="650127" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me the plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650128" id2="17" version="1065353216">The goal is to sabotage the enemy's efforts by whatever means necessary. Your contacts know more than me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650130" id2="17" version="1065353216">This area is deadly, but take heart--your odds of surviving are nearly even.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650132" id2="17" version="1065353216">Return to me when you've crushed your enemies. We'll have business to discuss. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="650136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apologies. I am awaiting people of great importance. I regret you do not qualify.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
