<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>139</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/world/imperial/esh_kha_containment/colonel_grang.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shame the Esh-kha can't fight for us. Still, you made the right call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707988" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made the right call. When we're ready, the Esh-kha will serve us well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707990" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Esh-kha's prison break is over. Here's their key.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Incredible. We must report this at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Calum. The situation's under control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for the update, Colonel. I will call off the bombardment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707999" id2="17" version="1065353216">First Ellis Ruger, then the rioting aliens, now the Esh-kha.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708001" id2="17" version="1065353216">First you free the Dread Masters, now you halt the Esh-kha's escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708003" id2="17" version="1065353216">First you storm the Esh-kha's vault, then you actually stop their escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such feats require more than strength and skill with a lightsaber. The Emperor is most impressed, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708006" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor and I understand each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708006" id2="17" version="1065353216">He told you that, did he?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708007" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708009" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dark side alone cannot accomplish such feats. The Emperor recognizes your power, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intelligence has many operatives embedded on Belsavis. You outperformed them all. The Emperor is most appreciative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Few mercenaries would accept such contracts, much less complete them. The Emperor thanks you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our mission on Belsavis succeeds because of your talents. You have earned the Emperor's gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708014" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't dispense empty accolades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who pays me? You? The Emperor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. Anything for a loyal servant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708019" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather have his money.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. I will arrange a transfer through the usual channels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me, Commander. There's still the matter of the surviving Esh-kha. Thousands remain caged on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything else?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708025" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's still the surviving Esh-kha to deal with. Thousands remain caged here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your recommendation, Colonel?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708029" id2="17" version="1065353216">The key's ours. Why not keep the Esh-kha riled up? Then some day, we unleash them on our enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708031" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate their potential, but your inability to control them makes your opinion worthless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708033" id2="17" version="1065353216">You, on the other hand, have triumphed over these aliens. Are they too dangerous to control? Or does their brutal efficiency outweigh the risks?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shy away from the Esh-kha, and you turn your back on the perfect weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use them as weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well. Deliver the key to me, Colonel. In time, we may unleash these creatures on the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Free those monsters and you'll unleash a terror on the galaxy--something you'll never control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708037" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Esh-kha are too dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel, deliver the key to me for incineration. Then catalog the remaining Esh-kha vaults. Containment is our top priority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708040" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you wish, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708042" id2="17" version="1065353216">As for you, the Emperor still requires your services. The Dread Masters must be freed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708044" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic has moved the Sith Lords. They're in Belsavis's deepest depths--with the prison's most twisted monstrosities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our operations groups pursued, then fell silent. Seek them out, contact me and together we will coordinate the Dread Masters' escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you again for your services. The Emperor will watch your progress closely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708056" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me. Colonel Grang's saying some words for the fallen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Herral was a good soldier. He fought like a true Imperial, and he died a hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give the kid a medal. Tell his Senator father he died quick. Not a word about Belsavis or these creatures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, sir. We have company.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pardon the mess, my lord. Lost most of my unit to a bunch of crazed aliens. You're looking at all that's left of Operations Group Three.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708065" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, agent. Afraid I can't offer hospitality since those crazed aliens attacked. You're looking at all that's left of Operations Group Three.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708066" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is an Imperial operation, merc. But, as you can see, I have some vacancies to fill. Interested in hunting some rampaging aliens?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708067" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't kill a single alien unless credits are on the table.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Depends on the pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708068" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least you're honest. Assist, and I'll pad your account.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not really. Should I be?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708071" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe credits will buy your interest in the Empire's cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse the mess. Lost most of my unit to an army of crazed aliens. We're all that's left of Operations Group Three.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Calum sent me. Concerning the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708074" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm here on official business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708075" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters aren't here. But if we don't exterminate these aliens soon, we'll never free them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your men have failed you, Colonel. My lightsaber will serve you better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps I can help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708078" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate the offer, my lord. Blasters didn't work against those aliens, but maybe your lightsaber will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708080" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis devours the frail, Colonel. You should've brought stronger men.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708080" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your unit must have been weak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708081" id2="17" version="1065353216">My men weren't the problem. It's those aliens... I've never seen anything like them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis is harsh. But victory demands sacrifice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chin up, Colonel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708084" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're on the same page. We can't afford a loss here--freakish aliens or not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708086" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can fill the boots of twenty men, but I'll cost you just as much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708086" id2="17" version="1065353216">You Imps need to hire help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708087" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm willing to pay. Anything to get back at those aliens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708089" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're being vague, Colonel. What species are we talking about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708089" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of aliens?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708090" id2="17" version="1065353216">No idea. Looks like we stumbled on some uncharted freaks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708092" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soldiers die. Deal with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708093" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not their death that gets me. It's those things that tore 'em apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708095" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were deployed to free prisoners--old friends of the Empire incarcerated by the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708097" id2="17" version="1065353216">My team broke open vaults. Then we unleashed these vicious aliens--Esh-kha, they're called. I hear you've met them before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708098" id2="17" version="1065353216">I met the Esh-kha in battle. I was the only survivor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708098" id2="17" version="1065353216">Correct.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708099" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've toasted my share of Esh-kha during my stay on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708099" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, we've met.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708100" id2="17" version="1065353216">There was a disagreement. The Esh-kha lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708100" id2="17" version="1065353216">We exchanged a few words.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708101" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some Esh-kha got in my way. They're dead now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708101" id2="17" version="1065353216">Met 'em and blasted 'em.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708102" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suspected as much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708104" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's classified.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708105" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard the rumors anyway. About you saving the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708107" id2="17" version="1065353216">At any rate, we're still recovering intel on the brutes. Take their prison records for instance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708109" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you freed the Esh-kha?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708110" id2="17" version="1065353216">I apologize, my lord. I've since dedicated myself to ending their rampage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708112" id2="17" version="1065353216">My unit acted of their own accord, but I don't want to malign the dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708114" id2="17" version="1065353216">I reported the incident to Commander Calum immediately. We also collected prison records describing the aliens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Found files calling the Esh-kha an ancient conqueror species, imprisoned thousands of years. Still working out the details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708118" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our mission was to clear the path for the Dread Masters' rescue. That meant springing prisoners to keep the Republic busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708120" id2="17" version="1065353216">My team broke vaults open. We unleashed something awful. Vicious aliens, armed and out for blood. There's no record of their existence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turn these creatures against the Republic, and our problems are solved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such aliens could be useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708122" id2="17" version="1065353216">We tried herding them, but they're too smart. Broke loose and went berserk. That's when we discovered their prison records.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708124" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me you set up a perimeter and contained the outbreak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708124" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trust you followed protocol.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708125" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. But the aliens broke through. That's when we started digging through the prison's records.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708127" id2="17" version="1065353216">New species fetch high prices. I can't wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708127" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like worthy prey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708128" id2="17" version="1065353216">Collecting trophies won't be easy. Not if the prison records are any indication.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708130" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just broke up an entire wing of rioting aliens. I can handle a few more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708130" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aliens don't scare me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708131" id2="17" version="1065353216">These brutes are off the charts, not your typical back world freaks. Luckily we discovered their prison records.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708133" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not afraid of aliens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708134" id2="17" version="1065353216">That may be, but these brutes are smart and armed. And prison records aren't exactly encouraging.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708136" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should've checked those vaults before opening them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bad move, Colonel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708137" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic didn't have any records. It wasn't until after they were out that we discovered old prison data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Found references to &quot;Esh-kha,&quot; an ancient conqueror species locked up for thousands of years. Details are still unclear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708141" id2="17" version="1065353216">This alien scum's out of the military's league, my lord. I'd be grateful if you could wipe them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708142" id2="17" version="1065353216">Containing these freaks will take an expert, both in combat and black ops. You up for the mission?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708144" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hear that, hunter? Thousands of years. How'd you like first shot at a freshly thawed species?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708150" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're dealing with some mean scum. And if we don't wipe them out fast, we may never rescue the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708153" id2="17" version="1065353216">These aliens are vile bullies. If we don't exterminate them soon, they could wipe out our entire operation on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708154" id2="17" version="1065353216">Years of imprisonment have made them hungry. I'll break their resolve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708154" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave the Esh-kha to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708155" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Esh-kha never should have strayed from their cells. Now they'll taste my power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708155" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well. I'll handle them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, my lord. Those brutes don't know what they're in for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708158" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make sure the Esh-kha are forgotten for another thousand years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708159" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. It's time those brutes see some Imperial justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708161" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expect payment for each fallen Esh-kha. And I'm keeping count.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708161" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll help, but I have demands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708162" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fulfill the contract and we'll take care of everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708164" id2="17" version="1065353216">I might help. Perhaps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708165" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's good enough for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708167" id2="17" version="1065353216">What bounty am I looking at?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most of my unit's dead. You can have their fee, plus more if you're thorough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708170" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find the Esh-kha in their prison vault. Search the place. We can't risk missing any.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708172" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can do it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708173" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Esh-kha are everywhere. Soon there'll be no escaping them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708175" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm conducting official Imperial business. Move along.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make the Esh-kha pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="755773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could be fun.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
