<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>95</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/world/republic/special_delivery/master_sergeant_volere.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720884" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck. Without you, this could have been a strategic failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hear the whole situation. And don't soften any bad news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where? And how many?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720904" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just assumed we were all coming from the same place. If House Organa falls, it's the end of the Republic on Alderaan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720912" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you have a strategy, don't keep it just for yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720912" id2="17" version="1065353216">So how do we stop them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720916" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're going to give them a special delivery. It will be neither kind nor pretty. Ordnance jobs never are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thul serves the Empire. I'll stop every one individually if I have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720935" id2="17" version="1065353216">I consider it my duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720936" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can be distracting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720936" id2="17" version="1065353216">I might be able to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720938" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a little presumptuous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720939" id2="17" version="1065353216">My apologies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720941" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apologies, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720943" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm truly sorry, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720945" id2="17" version="1065353216">No offense meant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720947" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are still Thuls down there if you want to mop up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720948" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Thuls cannot be allowed to get past us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoa, listen to that comm chatter. Guess the Thuls picked up a little profanity while they were in exile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720950" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need someone with the flash and power to distract the Thuls and cover our men as they work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720951" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Kashim says you've got flash and power. We need someone like you to distract the Thuls while we plant the charges.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720952" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've no doubt you can get the Thuls' attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720954" id2="17" version="1065353216">The main priority is that he stays alive and gets those charges laid. Kill the Thuls, distract them, I don't care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720956" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Master Sergeant Volere, and I will skip the pleasantries. Thul special operations soldiers are deploying as we speak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me brief you. The Thul spec ops teams are coming from troop transports offshore. If they deploy everyone, we're in it deep.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hammering individual soldiers won't work--we have to take the offense against those ships now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720960" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can take on a ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720961" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to engage them directly. Each of my men here are carrying about twenty kilograms of high explosives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720963" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fight a whole troop transport?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hear me out. These men are all the explosives experts we could scramble on such short notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720965" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a nice fantasy, but counter to our objective.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720967" id2="17" version="1065353216">The plan is to rig the Thuls' scout crafts and let them return to their command ship. Then we perform the detonation remotely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720968" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their landing craft riddle the beaches, and High Command expects us to repel them. Are you ready to go in?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720969" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will help, but the Jedi Code frowns on such cold-blooded slaughter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720969" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's the only way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720970" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a dirty trick, sure, but one that will keep us from waking up with the enemy in our homes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Low risk. High yield. I approve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720972" id2="17" version="1065353216">A solid plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720973" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank your generals when you get back home. Our officers get Republic training.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720975" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're sure to notice the tampering on the crafts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't work. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then go down alone and try to clear that beach. See how far you get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720978" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be moving on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720979" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll stay here until we can get reinforcements and take out the ones on the coast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720981" id2="17" version="1065353216">And Command is planning to set up a base here to repel future attacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720983" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seemed underhanded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720983" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was unpleasant work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720984" id2="17" version="1065353216">Born of desperation. If we lost this beach, the Organa estate would soon follow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every Thul on that ship was sworn to kill anyone loyal to the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember that if you feel a speck of shame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720989" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about their invasion? Did we succeed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Job well done?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720990" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're calling it off! Retreating back to their medical ships behind Thul lines!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720994" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've got special ops teams on the beach, and it gets worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720996" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Thul spec ops teams come from troop transports just offshore. The transports are getting intel from the beachhead for an invasion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720998" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll split into teams. My explosives specialist here will go with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="721000" id2="17" version="1065353216">When he's done, get out. We wouldn't mind a few survivors to take our surprise back to the transport.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="721001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Escort my man to the boats. Keep the Thuls away--drive them off, kill them, whatever. Laying the charges is the priority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="721003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good timing. Two of the landing craft just returned to the troop transports.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="721005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you ready? Like the famous last words say, &quot;let's see what this button does.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="721007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't pay attention to me! Cover your man!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="755942" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are still a few Ulgos out there, if you're looking for some exercise.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen to that comm chatter. I didn't know nobles could use language like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764762" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the intel erased and their scanners destroyed, the Ulgos won't be sending anything but distress calls.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764764" id2="17" version="1065353216">You came through just when we needed you. I'll make sure the rest of Alderaan hears about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hit those Ulgos hard. Then our men will show them some real fireworks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764767" id2="17" version="1065353216">None of my men are up to this. We're going to need some real firepower here, someone tough....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764769" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or a bunch of someones. Squad like you could take on the entire Ulgo army.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764771" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi. I'm sure your mission here is important, but we need help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad! I don't mean to interrupt, but House Organa could use your assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold there! You're that merc, aren't you? The one command's been talking about. You're hired.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764777" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Obatt. And this is Master Sergeant Volere. I'll skip the pleasantries. Ulgo special ops soldiers are deploying as we speak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764778" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should evacuate!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764779" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic didn't come to Alderaan for a rescue mission. We mean to help Organa win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764781" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're soldiers too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764782" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're soldiers too.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764783" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ulgo's not here to attack-- not yet. From what we can tell, they're mostly gathering intel, preparing for a full-scale invasion later.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764785" id2="17" version="1065353216">The long-range scanners they've set up can detect every move we make. We can't let that intel get back to Ulgo command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just give me your orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. We're counting on your assistance to make this plan work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't bring me into this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764790" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll get hazard pay for your trouble, if that's what you want. Just hear us out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764792" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our operatives will erase the data from the long-range scanners, then down the towers with explosives so Ulgo can never use them again.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764794" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Kashim says you've got flash and power. We need you to distract the Ulgos while our man plants the charges.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764795" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need someone with flash and power to distract the Ulgos and cover our men as they work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764796" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would be honored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764797" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm all about flash.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764798" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've no doubt you can get the Ulgos' attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764800" id2="17" version="1065353216">The coordinates to the Ulgo recon camp. Once you've reached the area, signal our explosives man and his escort.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764802" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll only get one shot at this. Hold out as long as you can until those charges are set.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too busy, sorry. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764804" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. Just don't be surprised when House Ulgo has us surrounded.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, can't spare the time. The Ulgos have gotten too close for comfort.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain! Sir, I don't mean to interrupt, but House Organa could use your assistance.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
