<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>52</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/world/the_thrill_of_discovery/tarkos_sund.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621598" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did good work. I appreciate it. Sund Tech appreciates it. The Republic appreciates it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621599" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are two things that would really make my day right about now--an Alderaanian brandy, or news that you found the accelerator and cleared the track.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621601" id2="17" version="1065353216">One or the other. I'm not picky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621602" id2="17" version="1065353216">The track's clear, and I found the accelerator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621602" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did as asked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alderaanian brandy would be good right now, but it's the latter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm... Alderaanian brandy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621604" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can salvage to your heart's content--just give me my fee.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Credits. Now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621605" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here you go. Don't spend it all in one place--I hear there's a superfast speeder hitting the market in ten to twelve months.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621607" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need that accelerator found and that track cleared--and the Republic needs it, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen here, all you blaster-wielding frontier fighters! Sund Technologies is the best provider of wartime technology the Republic has.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, I'll tell ya, there are some very violent creatures out there--rakghouls, nexu--I have the injuries to prove it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621612" id2="17" version="1065353216">But when there's work to be done and credits to be made, Sund Tech doesn't rest, and neither should you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621614" id2="17" version="1065353216">What I am offering is a high-paying technological recovery operation that will revolutionize the Republic's work here on Taris.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621615" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of technology are you researching here on Taris?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Technology?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, the usual--the kind that makes me filthy and disgustingly rich. No, no, I'm kidding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trust me--you'll be lucky if you dig up a rusty can opener in this dump.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621618" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won't find anything here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rusty can opener? That's a good one. I'll have to remember that one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Taris was destroyed hundreds of years ago--how could there be anything useful here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621621" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt you'll find anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621622" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to be dedicated to your work, but this seems like a strange place to look.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621622" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt you'll find anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621623" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is no place for civilians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621623" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not safe here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621624" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no ordinary civilian. I'm a businessman, a man of the galaxy. And, if I may say so, a brilliant--and handsome--inventor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621626" id2="17" version="1065353216">In other words, you're a profiteer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621626" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you're in it for the money.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like that's a bad thing? People expect companies to be profitable, but a person who profits is called a profiteer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621629" id2="17" version="1065353216">I happen to know that three hundred years ago some enterprising swoop racers got their hands on a revolutionary engine accelerator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621631" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I thought, here's the Republic struggling to reclaim Taris because of bad conditions and poor transportation--and the solution's right here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621633" id2="17" version="1065353216">All they need is someone to transform that accelerator into the kind of innovative high-efficiency transportation Sund Technologies is known for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you had any luck recovering it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you find it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, there has been a little bit of a--minor--setback.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was it the usefulness or the credits that occurred to you first?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621637" id2="17" version="1065353216">You hardly seem patriotic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621638" id2="17" version="1065353216">Money, pah. It's the thrill--can you imagine how fast a speeder would be with that accelerator attached?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621640" id2="17" version="1065353216">It certainly sounds like a good idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621640" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like your thinking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you imagine the speed those things will have? Pure adrenaline.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621643" id2="17" version="1065353216">Problem is the old swoop tracks are crawling with beasts--beasts that nearly chewed my leg off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621645" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not going to say I've overreached myself here, but I'm not really the fighting kind. I could use some help finding the accelerator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621646" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will you pay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621648" id2="17" version="1065353216">One up-front finder's fee. No royalties. A man's got to turn a profit somewhere. I'll throw in some genuine Sund tech if you like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, come on! I'm still alive, aren't I?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just head out to the old tracks and scan the old bikes. If you can clear out the beasts so we can salvage the accelerator when you're done, even better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sund Technologies is here for the Republic--I promise you that!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
