<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>168</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/voss/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86318" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shrine of Healing, huh? Pretty impressive for a medcenter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86319" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shrine of Healing seems to be one of the primary Voss religious structures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86320" id2="17" version="1065353216">These people are very grounded, confident. I sense unfettered self-assurance from the Shrine of Healing. It calms me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86321" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shrine of Healing. Sounds therapeutic, serene. Idiots don't understand they're at war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Weirdest medcenter I've ever seen. If I go down in battle, just let me die--do not bring me to these crazies.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Healing is for the weak.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86324" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is much power in this place. Much feasting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86325" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is supposed to be the site of some kind of pilgrimage, right? So what do we do? Bow our heads and fold our hands?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86326" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shrine of Healing is a sacred place for the Voss. Try to be respectful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Normally I don't have much interest in living cultures, but this &quot;Shrine of Healing&quot; is fascinating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see what those creeps keep in here, huh? &quot;Shrine of Healing&quot; my foot....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86329" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should be honored to see the shrine. Few in this galaxy ever will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86330" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unusual architecture, but nothing technologically unique. Typical for their culture.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86331" id2="17" version="1065353216">We toured the Sith ruins on Dromund Kaas when I was a child, but I've never seen an alien shrine. I'm quite excited.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Multiple life-forms detected inside. We may proceed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it me or is this place actually kind of creepy for a Shrine of Healing? Maybe it's part of the whole &quot;trials&quot; mystique?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not the most welcoming shrine I've ever seen. Then again, it sounds like they take a lot of pains to keep just anybody from wandering in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got a bad feeling. Something not quite natural. Don't think these trials are all talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86336" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place where boss going to take test?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't see the big fuss about these little Voss runts, ain't got better things to do than sit around and scratch this junk on walls. Good for nothin'.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Put on your shiny shoes and get ready to play diplomat. I bet that's where the Voss bigwigs are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86341" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Tower of Prophecy, my lord, where the most powerful Mystics receive their visions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86342" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a beautiful planet. I'll take it over the vaunted snowy mountains of Alderaan any day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86343" id2="17" version="1065353216">These people are too self-important. I hope the Empire appropriates and enslaves them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86344" id2="17" version="1065353216">Locked and loaded here. Say the word and that tower comes down.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86345" id2="17" version="1065353216">More Voss in there. We don't like how they speak.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pointless ornamentation. What a waste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86347" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Tower of Prophecy, huh. The Voss don't say much, but they sure build nice stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86348" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Tower of Prophecy. The center of Voss culture. Where the Mystics present their visions and the interpreters study. It's beautiful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86349" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unbelievable. That's--that's the Tower of Prophecy. Where the Voss interpret their visions! I wonder if they'll let me take samples from the walls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86350" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's the capitol. Different species, same show of power... Voss just think they're better than the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86351" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many Diplomatic Service members have been to Voss. Few have been inside the capitol.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86352" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's something charmingly naive about building a capitol without orbital shields. At least we have options.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86353" id2="17" version="1065353216">That must be the capitol. A quick peek couldn't hurt relations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86354" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have completed my analysis of Voss vulnerabilities and pain thresholds. I would like to choose a pair of the creatures for dissection.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86355" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think that's the Tower of Prophecy over there. Imperial net says that's where most of the Voss Mystics spend their whole lives. Sounds more like a prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice view, maybe I'll retire up here. Build a little mansion on the edge, add a nice deck and sit sipping Corellian wine. What do you think?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86357" id2="17" version="1065353216">City's been expanded on recently. Notice all the Imperial and Republic construction? Bribes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86358" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss place make Blizz nose itch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice place. All clean and peaceful. When we gonna trash it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, that is one big gun. I guess if size matters, the Gormak win, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86363" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak clearly have technical skill and sophisticated arms. They may not be the simple savages the Voss make them out to be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such a wanton culture. The Gormak are ready for war, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86365" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I like the Gormak. Any culture that flexes its muscles like this is okay by me. The hatred for Force users is unfortunate but still, good people on the whole.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86366" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pretty sweet cannon they got there. Wouldn't mind seeing its blast effect. Through macrobinoculars, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Big guns are no match for our claws!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86368" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Gormak creatures carry the faint scent of the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86369" id2="17" version="1065353216">These guys mean business, huh. Haven't seen a cannon like that since a buddy of mine stole an experimental dematerializer off the black market. That thing looks like it'd take a good chunk out of Voss-Ka if they had a mind to fire it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86370" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope the Gormak don't decide to fire that thing. It's pointed right at Voss-Ka, and it looks like it could do real damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86371" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is a very large gun. I hope we're not on Voss-Ka when they decide to fire it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice gun. Nasty recoil. Think I can handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86373" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak don't seem to think small. We know they're contained, but... in a thousand years, what will they do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86374" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gormak technology really is fascinating. What I wouldn't give for a long talk with their engineers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86375" id2="17" version="1065353216">That thing's large enough to bring down starships. The Gormak are more dangerous than we thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86376" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak are socially primitive, but their technology is worthy of study and integration. I will begin to upgrade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86377" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh my--look at that thing! The Gormak could probably blow Voss-Ka right off the mountain with that!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86378" id2="17" version="1065353216">How'd you like that mounted on the ship, eh? A little flashy for that junker of yours, but style isn't one of your strong points anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86379" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some artillery. Any idea what tech that's using? Not a blaster cannon, that's for sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86380" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh! Oh! Boss! Boss take Blizz to see big tech thing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86381" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh yeah, can't wait to get my hands on that. I say we blast that little city right off the mountain and get off this borin' rock.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86384" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I ever tell you I have a fear of dying at the hands of a dark alien presence?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86385" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like this, my lord. A tactical assessment of what we're up against in here is impossible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86386" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unrestrained and sinister darkness resides here. My blood goes cold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86387" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such darkness here. I've never felt such pure concentrated hatred. It's awe-inspiring.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86388" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad I restocked and juiced up--have a feeling I'm gonna need a full load for this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86389" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no light here--darkness reigns! We feel at home!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86390" id2="17" version="1065353216">The throbbing heart of impenetrable darkness. Glorious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86391" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not saying I'm scared or nothing, but this &quot;Dark Heart&quot; isn't the kind of place I want to stick around. Anything that scares both the Voss and the Gormak is bad news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86392" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is an evil place, full of dark side energy. You are powerful, my lord, but I'm not sure even you are strong enough for this place. No wonder the Voss and the Gormak fear it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86393" id2="17" version="1065353216">This must be what the Voss call the &quot;Dark Heart.&quot; Such fascinating ruins. And to think, I never would have seen them if it weren't for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86394" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's something really messed up about this place. Like the Dark Temple all over again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86395" id2="17" version="1065353216">We see things in the shadows, agent. We hear something like a scream....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86396" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place is old, Cipher. Much older than it should be, given what we've seen of the Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, something feels... off here. I can't explain it, I just--I think we should go back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86398" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your life readings are fluctuating. The Nightmare Lands phenomenon is worth further examination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeugh... something just ran up my spine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86400" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't see what all the fuss is about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86401" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reminds me of Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86402" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ick, dusty!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86403" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just got that warm fuzzy feelin', like bathin' in blood.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86408" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shrine of Healing = Voss sacred site // T7 = promises not to touch anything</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86409" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place makes the hairs on my neck stand up--and not in a good way. Don't know about you, but the Voss give me the shivers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86410" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't go in for this Voss Mystic healing business, but I do admire the architecture here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86411" id2="17" version="1065353216">I held a single-entrance fortress similar to this on Amador. Enemy bodies were stacked twenty-high around the outside when that battle was over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86412" id2="17" version="1065353216">The shrine radiates power. The Force is strong here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is power here, but not of blood and hunt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86414" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll say this for the Voss: That spiritual nonsense of theirs translates to beautiful architecture.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86415" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't belong here. This is a Voss place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86416" id2="17" version="1065353216">I almost feel like I should leave my weapons behind. This is no place for soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86417" id2="17" version="1065353216">This looks... old. Much older than anything in Voss-Ka. Do you think it was always a shrine?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86418" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Shrine of Healing is really something. Must have taken forever to build.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trees on Voss are tiny. Bowdaar misses Kashyyyk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wonder what sort of treasures the Voss are sitting on in there. Not that I advocate stealing....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86421" id2="17" version="1065353216">A foolish location for a place of healing. One could die just getting here. Perhaps that's the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86422" id2="17" version="1065353216">My Force powers go all tingly here. That's never happened before!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Must be the Shrine of Healing. Pretty impressive--I can see why the Voss are so proud of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86424" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shrine of Healing. A very important landmark according to our data on the Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86425" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss Shrine of Healing. It is highly valued by the local citizenry, so it must be highly valued by us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86426" id2="17" version="1065353216">So that's the Shrine of Healing, huh? Not bad, not bad at all. These Voss can really build 'em.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86427" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shrine of Healing. Yuun wonders at the mysteries of this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss-Ka = neutral territory // Conflict between Republic + Empire = discouraged by Voss</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86431" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss is a lot prettier than I expected. Sure beats the last few places we've been.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86432" id2="17" version="1065353216">You finally brought me someplace nice. Look--shops and restaurants. Things worth fighting over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86433" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Republic-friendly territory, sir. The Imperials have their own zone nearby. I recommend we keep our distance from it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your Republic begs favors from the Voss here. A pointless pursuit. These people are aggressively self-interested.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss are... strange. Not hunters, not prey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86436" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss-Ka really is quite lovely. A little quiet for my tastes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss invited the Empire in. Deserve all they get when it goes bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best smiles on for the Voss, everybody....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86439" id2="17" version="1065353216">The trees, the people... Voss-Ka's so much like home. How long can we stay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86440" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear the Voss locals are a strange bunch. Probably best to leave them alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86441" id2="17" version="1065353216">The air on Voss is clean. Bowdaar approves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86442" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard the Voss don't enforce Republic laws. People are free to do what they want, as long as they leave the Voss alone. My kind of place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86443" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss say they have great warriors. I look forward to testing that claim.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86444" id2="17" version="1065353216">An associate of mine says Voss is a place where almost anything goes. The natives haven't even outlawed spice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86445" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is Voss? Beautiful place. I'd heard stories, but I never thought I'd actually come here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86446" id2="17" version="1065353216">This world is quite striking. I've read that the Voss have very impressive medical techniques--I'll have to look into it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86447" id2="17" version="1065353216">A beautiful world! We must do all that we can to defend it against Imperial degradation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice place, even if I've never heard of it. I can get why people might want a piece of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86449" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun sees many signs, many paths. This world has seen much, and will see more.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cannon = advanced technology // Gormak = built it themselves?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice gun. You could put a city out with that thing. Wish it wasn't aimed at Voss-Ka.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently, the Gormak spent everything they had building the nicest, biggest gun on Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86455" id2="17" version="1065353216">Advanced artillery like that shouldn't belong to savages. If we can't take that position, our only recourse is to destroy it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86456" id2="17" version="1065353216">A giant gun. How crude. These Gormak have little imagination in their choice of weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cowardly to fight from afar. Not even smell enemy's blood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86458" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak truly are ingenious. Homicidal, but ingenious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gormak weaponry. That's got to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sheesh. Look at the bore on that monster. It could blow a building clean in half.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86461" id2="17" version="1065353216">All those resources, all that time and skill, and they make a weapon. What a waste!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at the size of that cannon the Gormak built. I gotta get me one of those.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86463" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bowdaar does not fear that weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86464" id2="17" version="1065353216">This cannon explains everything. The Gormak have an inferiority complex--and they're prepared to blow up Voss-Ka to improve their self-esteem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your starship would benefit from having such a weapon mounted to the hull. It would discourage pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86466" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is one big cannon. Makes me nervous just being near it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoa. That's some serious artillery. Let's hope we don't have to find out if it works.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at the size of that cannon... the Gormak are clearly more advanced than our intelligence indicates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86469" id2="17" version="1065353216">An impressively constructed artillery piece, to be sure. My sensors detect several inefficiencies, however.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that's a cannon! Can we take it with us? The Voss won't mind, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such impressive ingenuity, turned to such negative purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86474" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = analyzing remains // Bones = large beasts + Voss + Gormak + &quot;other&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most people would just put up a &quot;do not disturb&quot; sign. Whatever awful thing lives here doesn't do things halfway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you get past the giant piles of bones, this place isn't that bad. Oh, who am I kidding?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86477" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice of the enemy to advertise its location. Let's take care of business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86478" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sense a familiar presence. If I did not know better, I'd think the Emperor had been here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cave calls challenge to us, Herald.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi, something tells me that cave is not to be trifled with. Let's just keep going.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86481" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't like turning my back on that cave. Something's in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86482" id2="17" version="1065353216">My old sergeant used to say, some places watch you. And that cave? That's watching us right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Back home, we call caves like that &quot;mouths of the hidden.&quot; In the old stories, they speak with the voices of the dead. In... stories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at all those bones, Captain. Whatever lives down here must have a blasted huge appetite.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86485" id2="17" version="1065353216">A great predator nests here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's not get ourselves added to those piles of bones. Keep your eyes open down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bones of the dead. Someone here enjoys displaying trophies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86488" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's an awful lot of bones. Say, I just remembered an important appointment back on the ship....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like a lot of stuff ends up dying around this cave, sir. Let's make sure we're not next.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever is in that cave, the remains scattered about are too numerous to count. We should be cautious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Biological remains detected in all directions. The cave seems to be the source--let's investigate!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86492" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know about this place, boss. Something in that cave has been doing a lot of killing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="86493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Signs of danger and darkness surround us in this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023293" id2="17" version="1065353216">Complaint: The Shrine of Healing... so this is where the Voss undo all my hard work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023296" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis: The Tower of Prophecy, indeed. I predict I will soon be annoyed by a Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insight: Whatever their faults, at least the Gormak are honest about their intentions. Witness Exhibit A.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023302" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revelation: My scanners indicate all manner of undesirables in various states of emotional distress. It's like coming home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hypothesis: Would it be unethical to delete Imperial troublemakers while under Voss care?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Judgment: Voss has primitive architecture and miniscule resources. Why do we seek their favor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Truism: Size matters. The Gormak clearly understand this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observation: Several mass deletions occurred here, master. We always visit the most exciting places.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
