<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>68</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/imperial/jaggalors_on_the_loose/lieutenant_boonan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448804" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord--don't mind my saying so, but you picked the right time to show up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great work with the jaggalors. We'll move advance units out within the hour.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448807" id2="17" version="1065353216">The jaggalors are dead. You've got nothing to worry about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448807" id2="17" version="1065353216">I took care of the jaggalors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, well. Looks like our advance is back on track.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448810" id2="17" version="1065353216">And one of the rarest species of Corellian wildlife is dead. Excuse me if I don't celebrate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448814" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't mind him. He's just a sore loser. As far as I'm concerned, you've done a great thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448816" id2="17" version="1065353216">A little respect might lengthen that life of yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch your mouth, zookeeper.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, of course. My deepest apologies. I was only upset... Please, forgive me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Civilians--don't know when to shut up. Anyway, thanks for your help. I'll get the advance moving again within the hour.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448823" id2="17" version="1065353216">I used the compound on the jaggalors. They're the Republic's problem now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448824" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still think killing 'em would've been easier. But it'll be nice to see those Republic boys on the menu for a change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for not harming them. When this planet finds peace again, those creatures will be the pride of Corellia once more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Press on with your advance, Lieutenant. Victory awaits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to do my part.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely. We'll be sending out lead units within the hour.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448831" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expect to get the credit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely. We couldn't have done it without you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448835" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you've finished celebrating, why don't you get back to killing Republic soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough back-slapping.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. I'll deploy advance units right away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448840" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't advance our position till those jaggalors are taken care of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448841" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a good little collaborator, so I heard you out. But you tell me how to do my job again, I'll bleed you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please--I'm sorry. I'm only asking you not to hunt and kill these creatures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunter, you're just the kind of professional I need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir. Finally, someone who can get this done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448857" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well... Just the kind of professionals I need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448861" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's turned loose a bunch of jaggalors from the Coronet zoo. We're getting torn to shreds trying to advance through the area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448863" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire halts for no man or creature. An Imperial lieutenant should know this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448863" id2="17" version="1065353216">We do not bow to animals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, my lord. Which is why I'm looking for help with these jaggalors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448868" id2="17" version="1065353216">How clever of them. Fortunately, clever plans can be undone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448868" id2="17" version="1065353216">A shrewd strategy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448870" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's where I'm hoping you can help, my lord. These jaggalors....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunting's what I get paid for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like open season.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pay's no problem, long as you take care of this jaggalor predicament.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448880" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire can't afford delays. What's your plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448880" id2="17" version="1065353216">The advance has to continue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448882" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think it's one you'll appreciate, agent. These jaggalors....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like there's some disagreement on how to handle things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why the bickering?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ignore him. He doesn't have a battalion of men getting torn apart. These jaggalors....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448892" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm trying to remember the last time I heard an excuse this pitiful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zoo animals? Pathetic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, if I'd never seen a jaggalor I'd say the same thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448897" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're Corellian predators. Powerful, extremely aggressive. Last squad they attacked, we found pieces spread over two klicks. I need them put down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448901" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are rare and graceful predators. The kings of Corellian wildlife. Yes, the Empire's advance must continue, but please--don't exterminate the jaggalors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448903" id2="17" version="1065353216">We haven't been introduced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who exactly are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448905" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's a zoo administrator. He's been working with the occupation so I said I'd hear him out. Doesn't know when to shut up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448909" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a lot of flattery for creatures doing so much damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448909" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're defending these things?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448911" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm only saying they're animals acting on instinct. They don't mean harm to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448915" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not serious...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448917" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope I haven't offended. I'm just suggesting there's a way to free up your advance without hurting them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please--the zoo has a pheromone compound for managing jaggalor aggression. You can redirect their hostility at their Republic handlers. Same result, no killing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448925" id2="17" version="1065353216">You kill 'em, you know they're neutralized. No surprises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448928" id2="17" version="1065353216">The way to deal with an unruly animal is to put it down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448928" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll kill the jaggalors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448929" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I'm going to be sick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448933" id2="17" version="1065353216">Simple solutions are good solutions. Good hunting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448937" id2="17" version="1065353216">No sense killing them if we can turn them against the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448937" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll use the compound.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448939" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won't regret this. Here's the compound. Treat the jaggalors with it, and I'll treat the lieutenant's men.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448943" id2="17" version="1065353216">To the jaggalors, we'll smell like pack-mates, and the Republic handlers will smell threatening.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448947" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't mean to be rude, but I've got a lot on my plate right now. Excuse me.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
