<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>76</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/camp/heroic_weekly/mission_board_imp.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193284" id2="17" version="1065353216">B-6NX has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gorinth Canyon sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, B-6NX may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193285" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Larbec has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gorinth Canyon sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Lieutenant Larbec may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193286" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Neddis has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gorinth Canyon sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Captain Neddis may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193287" id2="17" version="1065353216">By order of Lysennius Melchiro, Imperial Governor of Balmorra. Offworld sympathizers from crack Republic commando groups have illegally joined the Balmorran resistance in opposition of Imperial domination. 

Rodian, Chagrian and Kel Dor mercenary forces, decorated Republic war heroes, all are well coordinated and have taken up a position near the AA guns outside of the Balmorran Arms Factory. Their snipers have been responsible for 304 Imperial casualties and the destruction of over fifty Imperial aircraft to date. 

Reward offered for anyone who will crush the alien rebels and liberate the AA guns.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Revis has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Farnel Research Facility sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Doctor Revis may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193289" id2="17" version="1065353216">By order of Darth Lachris, revered governor of Imperial Balmorra, champion of the siege of Coruscant. In spite of the Empire's glorious victory at Balmorran Arms, the battle has not been won.

The Republic's top tactician, field commander and gunner have regrouped the scattered resistance forces and are preparing a fresh assault on Imperial Balmorra!

The Jedi Noth Armin, Sergeant Tove Weylan and the mercenary Korin Norrus have been coordinating strikes against Imperial ships and have so far brought down three Imperial squadrons.

Eliminate them and show the resistance the futility of their cause. The wealth and gratitude of your Empire will be at your disposal.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193290" id2="17" version="1065353216">By order of Darth Lachris, revered governor of Imperial Balmorra, champion of the siege of Coruscant. Due to the previous governor's incompetence, the resistance has managed to establish a factory for the production of chemical weapons near the toxic waste pools.

They are using the toxic waste to produce bombs to poison Imperial forces. The bombs are guarded by the resistance's top marksmen. Previous attempts to take back the factory and dismantle the bombs resulted in the annihilation of two crack commando teams.

Dismantle the bombs. Eliminate the resistance. The wealth and gratitude of your Empire will be at your disposal.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193291" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Piloc has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Farnel Research Facility sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Lieutenant may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193752" id2="17" version="1065353216">Duke Keldas Thul has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Kaamos Territory sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Duke Keldas Thul may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Malichose has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Elysium above the Glarus Valley sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Lord Malichose may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corporal Lanoyo has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Kaamos Territory sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Corporal Lanoyo may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193755" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rehmar Thul has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Kaamos Territory sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Rehmar Thul may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fannatex has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Kaamos Territory sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Fannatex may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193757" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gevin Thul has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Kaamos Territory sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Gevin Thul may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corporal Haddon has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the High Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Corporal Haddon may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193760" id2="17" version="1065353216">TA-350 has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the The Tomb sector of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, TA-350 may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Ferrid has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Minimum Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Lord Ferrid may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Shaar has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the High Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Lord Shaar may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Arten has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Tomb sector of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Lord Arten may be contacted via a Monitoring Station Console. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193764" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ava Seldin has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the High Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Ava Seldin may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Junia Tavrak has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Incorporation Islands sector of Corellia. For additional details about the mission, Junia Tavrak may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Raddus Venn has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Incorporation Islands sector of Corellia. For additional details about the mission, Raddus Venn may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Helricks has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Labor Valley sector of Corellia. For additional details about the mission, Captain Helricks may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Moff Tarandon has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Government District sector of Corellia. For additional details about the mission, Moff Tarandon may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193769" id2="17" version="1065353216">By order of the Dark Council, the legendary Mandalorian bounty hunter Valen Korik is wanted for betraying the Imperial-Mandalorian alliance and murdering two Sith Lords in Kaas City in open combat. He is considered extremely dangerous and is believed to have fled into the Dark Temple. 

Only persons authorized to enter the Dark Temple should give pursuit. Korik is believed to be heavily armed, and the situation in the Dark Temple remains unpredictable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193770" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major Shellaster has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Dark Temple Approach sector of Dromund Kaas. For additional details about the mission, Major Shellaster may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193771" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vort Norman has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jungle Valley sector of Dromund Kaas. For additional details about the mission, Vort Norman may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vol Kolla has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Nalis Quarry sector of Dromund Kaas. For additional details about the mission, Vol Kolla may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193777" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Sunder has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Malignant Bog sector of Dromund Kaas. For additional details about the mission, Lord Sunder may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corporal Xeleste has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Highmount Ridge sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Corporal Xeleste may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Doresh has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Icefall Plains sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Lieutenant Doresh may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193780" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Vujaar has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Starship Graveyard sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Captain Vujaar may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193781" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Kavsun has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Glacial Fissure sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Sergeant Kavsun may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Switts has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Captain Switts may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193783" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Zeleron has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Lieutenant Zeleron may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Viatar has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Captain Viatar may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Varos has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Lord Varos may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Jerrod has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Captain Jerrod may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gedron Hix has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the River Lands sector of Hutta. For additional details about the mission, Gedron Hix may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193788" id2="17" version="1065353216">Foreman Rhamm has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Old Muckworks sector of Hutta. For additional details about the mission, Foreman Rhamm may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Foreman Rhamm has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Old Muckworks sector of Hutta. For additional details about the mission, Foreman Rhamm may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193790" id2="17" version="1065353216">Geric has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Old Muckworks sector of Hutta. For additional details about the mission, Geric may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193791" id2="17" version="1065353216">G-4T has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Eastern Ice Shelf sector of Ilum. For additional details about the mission, G-4T may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193792" id2="17" version="1065353216">A powerful and dangerous Sith named Lord Sundar has gone mad and now roams the tomb of Tulak Hord. If you can eliminate him, you have been promised a great reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193793" id2="17" version="1065353216">A researcher named Ephran Zell located an ancient Sith device known as &quot;The Red Engine,&quot; which is said to contain Tulak Hord's greatest secrets. Ephran Zell wants you to brave the tomb, activate the Red Engine and then kill creatures in its presence to fuel the device.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193794" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Heedley has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Corellian Sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Captain Heedley may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193795" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL TERMINATION INCENTIVE
BOUNTY LISTING #X489J2

Several Jedi combatants have invaded this sector. They are secretly lending support to the rebel alien refugees opposing Imperial interests. Loyal servants of the Emperor are encouraged to confront these Republic meddlers and eliminate them with extreme prejudice.

Reward will be delivered upon verification that the Jedi at key coordinates have all been neutralized.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Skav Mora has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Industrial Sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Skav Mora may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193797" id2="17" version="1065353216">HUTT CARTEL EMERGENCY BOUNTY POSTING

The Cartel seeks combat-worthy individuals who value Hutt generosity! A large pack of savage vrblthers has infested Network Access. These deadly predators are wreaking havoc at the power station. Trillions of important data files are at risk. The entire HoloNet itself may cease functioning!

The Cartel will lavishly reward any who eradicate the vrblthers and repair the damage before it is too late. Please be advised, several security teams have indicated the presence of unusually large vrblther pack elders. Additional information is unavailable, as the security teams have since disappeared.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Sharoleigh has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Industrial Sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Lord Sharoleigh may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gorn Sweevas has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Industrial Sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Gorn Sweevas may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent Ryleah has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Network Access sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Agent Ryleah may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glort has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Network Access sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Glort may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193802" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lya Charrel has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Brell Sediment sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Lya Charrel may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intelligence Report No: 97-213. Clearance Level: 4.

The old Tarisian government lives. Approximately three centuries ago, the leaders froze themselves in carbonite within Transport Station 5.

Intercepted transmissions confirm the Republic's elite Ember Squad was dispatched to recover the frozen leaders. If revived, their knowledge will accelerate Taris's reconstruction by three thousand percent.

Darth Gravus orders immediate action. Stop Ember Squad's thawing mission and eliminate the frozen Tarisian leaders. Hazard fee payable on completion.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193804" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Bourom has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Sinking City sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, General Bourom may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Komo has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Republic Resettlement Zone sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Lord Komo may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Praetor Nollus has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Tularan Marsh sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Praetor Nollus may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193807" id2="17" version="1065353216">From the desk of Darth Gravus: 

The Republic rats have fled underground. An entire battalion rallies in Gadon's Superhighway, a massive swoop track beneath your very feet.

The scum unite under Taren Vor, a Jedi commander descended from old Taris. He aims to build a subterranean supply network. If successful, the Republic will infest the planet for decades.

Stop this mockery of Taris's ruin, and your valor will be repaid. Crush the Republic's highway, bury their army and annihilate the Jedi leader.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Officer Vengo has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Infinite Dessication sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Officer Vengo may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Reskin has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jundland sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Captain Reskin may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Cibinel has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jundland sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Captain Cibinel may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193811" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana Corrs has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Mos Ila sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Lana Corrs may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gezda has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jundland sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Gezda may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vuk Dimitrius has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jundland sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Vuk Dimitrius may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193814" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Marcus has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jundland sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Commander Marcus may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Outsiders and potential allies: The Voss seek knowledge of the past. Scholars opened a tomb, ancient and untouched. None survived.

Monsters and machines, horrors beyond memory, awaited them. Voss warriors were sent to fight. Now they are lost, also. Outsider help is required.

Enter the tomb under the Old Paths. Destroy its guardians. The Voss will have knowledge. Outsiders will have their reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Outsiders and potential allies: Voss commandos defied the law and entered the Nightmare Lands. Unthinking bravery. Corruption has overtaken them.

It has destroyed their minds, but enhanced their bodies. They wield strange powers and command wild beasts. Darkness seeps beyond the Nightmare Lands' borders.

Bring the warriors a merciful death. End their suffering. The Voss will be grateful. Material reward offered.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention outsiders and potential allies: The Gormak have led the Rock-eater into the tombs near the Shrine of Healing.

An escort of Gormak guides and controls the powerful cyber-beast, seeking a passage into the Shrine of Healing itself.

Entire Voss commando units sent to stop the beast have been devoured.

Defeat the Gormak guardians and destroy the Rock-eater, and material rewards will be granted.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention outsiders and potential allies: A challenge.

The Trial of the First Commando opens below the shrine. Only the greatest Voss commandos participate. They duel and grow strong.

First Commando Nakar-Sel hears of your Empire's strength. He speaks: Prove it against him, and the commandos who make Gormak weep.

The healers watch. There will be injury, but none shall die. If you do not fear pain, win pride.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1194905" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

Former Regulators have obtained a prototype isotope-5 rocket from the remnants of the Archon's weapons stockpiles. 

Steal the rocket from their long-range artillery depot located on the chain of bridged mesas known as &quot;the Fingers.&quot; Our science team will monitor the rocket as you launch it into a nearby mesa to assess its potential for Imperial use.

END MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1194906" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

Refugees fleeing Pelratha Mesa, which collapsed due to the Empire's hastening of Makeb's destabilization, have crash-landed on Telemur Mesa. Their shuttle's flight recorder contains statistical data that could potentially expose our role here on the planet. 

Retrieve the flight recorder and use its data to pin Pelratha's collapse on the Regulators.

END MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1194907" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL MILITARY DISPATCH--AUTH: UNDER-MOFF BENSEN--MESSAGE READS:

An Imperial misinformation architect has crafted the components of a potent lie: that the destruction of Makeb has been long foretold by the planet's own scientists; and that the powers that be on the planet knew about, ignored and covered up any such evidence. 

To sell this fiction, this data must be uploaded to the various computers within the planet's Cultural Archives in the Tarlam settlement.

END MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1194908" id2="17" version="1065353216">D3-X9 has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gravity Hook Four sector of Makeb. For additional details about the mission, D3-X9 may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1194909" id2="17" version="1065353216">GR-18 has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gravity Hook Seven sector of Makeb. For additional details about the mission, GR-18 may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1197904" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss could use assistance with a number of dangerous, high-priority missions. Completing these missions will increase your reputation among the Voss.

Complete [HEROIC] Ancient Guardians
Complete [HEROIC] Cleanse the Corrupted
Complete [HEROIC] Rock Eaters
Complete [HEROIC] The First Commando's Call</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
