<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>72</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/camp/heroic_weekly/mission_board_rep.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193159" id2="17" version="1065353216">Urgent! House Organa seeks aid! Despite our diplomatic efforts, House Thul has brought chaos and bloodshed to Alderaan. We have received reports of Imperial probe droids in the area, further evidence that House Thul has allied themselves with the Empire.

If these reports are true, the Empire's intel must not be allowed to reach House Thul. Organa forces brought down a probe droid in the area, but were overwhelmed by Thul forces during recovery. Hazard pay is offered to any volunteers able to overcome these invaders and reach the wreckage. Proceed with caution: Thul forces appear to have advanced reconnaissance and combat training.

If successful, deliver any intel recovered to Rickard Organa. For House Organa!

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193161" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent Essor has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the King's Pass sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Agent Essor may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193162" id2="17" version="1065353216">Elz Organa has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the King's Pass sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Elz Organa may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dolin Organa has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the King's Pass sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Dolin Organa may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Obatt has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Apalis sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Lieutenant Obatt may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Feero has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Camp Traken-4 sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Feero may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent Protarius has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Sobrik sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Agent Protarius may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193170" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alay Selray has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gorinth Canyon sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Alay Selray may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193171" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Nic'ala has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Sundari Flatlands sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Captain Nic'ala may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Larindaz has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Sundari Flatlands sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Larindaz may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chedd has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gorinth Canyon sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Chedd may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Galway Bourke has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gorinth Canyon sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Galway Bourke may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193175" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Tenn has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Sundari Flatlands sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Sergeant Tenn may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Pol Tamso has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Sundari Flatlands sector of Balmorra. The mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193210" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Skylast has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in The Tomb sector of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, General Skylast may be contacted via his Tech Station. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193211" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major Valyn has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Maximum Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Major Valyn may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193212" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Shohn-Lowt has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the The Tomb sector of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Master Shohn-Lowt may be contacted via a Monitoring Station Console. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193213" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent Hextal has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the High Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Agent Hextal may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193214" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent Firehawk has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Minimum Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Agent Firehawk may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193217" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Everis has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the High Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Doctor Everis may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193218" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Herron has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Blastfield Shipyards sector of Corellia. For additional details about the mission, Sergeant Herron may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193219" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Kirin has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Labor Valley sector of Corellia. For additional details about the mission, Doctor Kirin may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel Tott has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Axial Park sector of Corellia. For additional details about the mission, Colonel Tott may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193221" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Bathens has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Government District sector of Corellia. For additional details about the mission, Captain Bathens may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193226" id2="17" version="1065353216">CORUSCANT SECURITY ALERT 

Criminal gang &quot;The Fondor Five&quot; confirmed active in Old Galactic Market sector. Last seen entering Fartrader Lounge. All five gang members carry death sentences and substantial bounties from numerous violent felony convictions. 

Bounty payment to be rendered contingent upon substantive proof of gang members' final status. 

CITIZENS STRONGLY DISCOURAGED FROM PURSUING BOUNTY - SUSPECTS CONSIDERED ARMED AND EXTREMELY DANGEROUS!

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193229" id2="17" version="1065353216">Security Officer Stansum has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Black Sun Territory sector of Coruscant. For additional details about the mission, Security Officer Stansum may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193230" id2="17" version="1065353216">Luran Gonthor has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Justicar Territory sector on Coruscant. For additional details about the mission, Luran Gonthor may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193231" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ensign Belkan has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jedi Temple sector of Coruscant. For additional details about the mission, Ensign Belkan may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leebo Nobim has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Highmount Ridge sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Leebo Nobim may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193233" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Grollix has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Starship Graveyard sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Captain Grollix may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193234" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Keloh has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Whiterock Wastes sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Sergeant Keloh may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193235" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Calia has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Glacial Fissure sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Lieutenant Calia may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193236" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kerkarr has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Kerkarr may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193237" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corporal Fabel has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Corporal Fabel may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Neelo Droobas has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Neelo Droobas may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193239" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jaro Dev has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Jaro Dev may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193240" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maya Drin has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Maya Drin may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193255" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Moran has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Eastern Ice Shelf sector of Ilum. For additional details about the mission, Master Moran may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193256" id2="17" version="1065353216">SIS Agent Jatta Kuum has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Nikto Sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, SIS Agent Jatta Kuum may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193257" id2="17" version="1065353216">REPUBLIC EMBASSY SECURITY SERVICE
CITIZEN TRAVEL ADVISORY

To all Republic citizens in the Red Light Sector: Be advised the Gauntlet criminal gang has set up a death duel tournament in the back alleys. Poor refugees are running the gang's ordeal for credit rewards. The Gauntlet is broadcasting holos of these fights. No refugee has survived to collect a prize.

The Hutt Cartel refuses to intervene in this despicable &quot;entertainment.&quot; All tourists should avoid the area, but trained Republic agents are encouraged to end the Gauntlet's activities by destroying its holorecording equipment and driving off the gangsters.


This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clan Sharratt issues a challenge to the Republic's so-called champions. If you're warrior enough to face the greatest Mandalorian clan on Nar Shaddaa, come to our coordinates. We promise a warm welcome, but only if you come quickly.

We have just sipped upon the finest combat stims on Nar Shaddaa, and we're feeling especially good right now. We want a worthy challenge. If you won't come to us, we'll just have to start torching Republic buildings until we find something better to amuse us.

-- Kassor Quade, Clan Sharratt Chieftain

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193259" id2="17" version="1065353216">TERMINAL ACCESS DETECTED...
CLEARANCE APPROVED

The Strategic Information Service has an ultraviolet-level mission requiring immediate action. The Empire's chief engineers have arrived to upgrade Shadow Town's cranial explosives technology. This is a rare opportunity to exploit the enemy's vulnerability.

If Republic scientists can examine the cranial device's technical schematics, they could learn how to safely deactivate the explosives detonator. This would allow SIS agents to extract prisoners from Shadow Town. Proceed to the Shadow Town prison control center, neutralize resistance and recover the schematics.

END TRANSMISSION

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193260" id2="17" version="1065353216">Harum  has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Industrial Sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Harum may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193261" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greggo Brudd has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Industrial Sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Greggo Brudd may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tythan Phomm has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Network Access sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Tythan Phomm may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jax Dumont has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Network Access sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Jax Dumont may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Posted By Ord Mantell Central Authority: 
A tribe of Mantellian savrips have been attacking patrols from the island near Oradam Village. Negotiations with the bestial creatures are not possible.

Ord Mantell Central Authority is offering a bounty on the leaders of savrip tribes. Thank you for your assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gizmel Gam has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Savrip Island sector of Ord Mantell. For additional details about the mission, Gizmel Gam may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Travi Pott has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Savrip Island sector of Ord Mantell. For additional details about the mission, Sergeant Travi Pott may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193267" id2="17" version="1065353216">Amille Razna has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Republic Resettlement Zone sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Amille Razna's message may be played from her droid G-5KN. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Volunteer Operation 78775-R

Objective: Warhead Retrieval
Contact: Major Teranos
Brief: One of our transports came under fire from Mandalorian raiders just after she broke Taris atmo. Cargo was class seven anti-ship warheads--all ejected safely. Can't say the same for the crew.

The Mandos are already headed for the warheads' landing site--need volunteers to intercept them and signal for pickup when the warheads are secure.

Anyone that gets it done gets double hazard pay. We ID'd the Mando commander as Duran Gorr--the guy takes down Jedi for his day job, so expect major opposition.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193269" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Reldar Kandik has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Brell Sediment sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Captain Reldar Kandik may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Private Selro has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Tularan Marsh sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Private Selro may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kord Murdok has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Tularan Marsh sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Kord Murdok may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193272" id2="17" version="1065353216">Larris Cozekk has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Tularan Marsh sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Larris Cozekk may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193273" id2="17" version="1065353216">[You log in to the Citizen's Militia network and find an urgent message:]

Alerting all responsible citizens. Posted: Sorin Schaff, the citizens' militia's chief backer, is being held captive in his own home by Twin Suns pirates.

The pirates' leader, Braigin Helk, has proved too much for militia forces. We request the help of any and all combat-trained professionals to defeat Helk and liberate the homestead.

Coordinates provided. The Citizens' Militia thanks you for your support.

&quot;Vigilance, community, defense.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193274" id2="17" version="1065353216">[You log in to the Citizens' Militia network and find an urgent message:]

By order of Mayor Airen and the Citizens' Militia--Geonosian attacks on Tatooine farmers and settlements have grown bold.

The Geonosians are highly coordinated, and multiple swarms are often involved in the raids. We have heard their coded signals in the night, but we are unable to interpret them.

The signals originate at their main camp. Find their signal devices, obtain the code, and bring it to Captain Sabha of the militia.

&quot;Vigilance, community, defense.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ledo Melnic has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Anchorhead sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Ledo Melnic may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193276" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jundo Martik has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jundland sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Jundo Martik may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193277" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lapad Dula has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Dune Sea sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Lapad Dula may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bleb Blek has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jundland sector of Tatooine. For additional details about the mission, Bleb Blek may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do Zonn has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Ruins of Kaleth. For additional details about the mission, Do Zonn may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193280" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention outsiders and potential allies: Dangerous mercenaries have allied with the Gormak. 

They trade combat training for Gormak weapons and cybernetic upgrades.

The mercenaries slaughtered several Voss commando units sent to break the alliance.

Eliminate the cyber-mercenaries and material rewards will be granted.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193281" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention outsiders and potential allies: The Gormak madness grows. 

The Thalak tribe camps in the boneyards. These Gormak walk the Nightmare Lands without fear. They return changed. 

Now the Thalak tribesmen build new machines. Each one has the strength of ten. Voss commandos fight them by dozens, and die.

Outsiders who destroy the Thalak tribe will be rewarded. Speed is necessary. Voss-Ka trembles.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193282" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention outsiders and potential allies:

Material reward is authorized for the defeat of the Gormak &quot;Savage Slayers.&quot;

These new beastmasters use corrupt Gormak devices to draw strength from their cyber-abominations.

They are stronger than any Gormak and cannot be defeated while their beasts live.

Defeat the beasts, defeat the slayers.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193283" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention outsiders and potential allies: You are privileged.

The Trial of the First Commando begins. Voss commandos gather below the shrine to train in battle. Fearless outsiders may participate.

First Commando Nakar-Sel and fellows wait to defeat challengers. Nakar-Sel drives back Gormak armies. He will not spare you.

The healers speak: None shall die. All pain will be real. Victory will be true.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1194911" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

A particularly heinous band of former Regulators situated on the Fingers has been shooting down and looting civilian shuttles headed for a refugee camp.

Draw out these Regulators by fabricating and activating a shuttle distress beacon at one of the shuttle wreckage sites to keep them from doing harm to any more civilians.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1194912" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

Many of Makeb's citizens were unable to reach the Ark before its launch. Some couldn't make it because they were shot down by ex-Regulator forces on Telemur Mesa, who are keeping the civilians imprisoned.

Retrieve the shuttle manifests from the Regulators while doing what you can to limit these mercenaries' capabilities in the area.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1194913" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

A group of former Regulators on Makeb have called on various extraplanetary forces--Mandalorians, assassin droids and fallen Jedi, mostly--to help them take control of the planet. These forces are reaching the planet via a ground-to-atmosphere turbolift called a &quot;gravity hook.&quot;

Ambush the potential Regulator allies arriving at Gravity Hook Four before they can make their way off the mesa.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1194914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Archivist Varus has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Tarlam Settlements sector of Makeb. For additional details about the mission, Archivist Varus may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1194915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Daskarta has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Frinn Mesa sector of Makeb. For additional details about the mission, Daskarta may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1197902" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss could use assistance with a number of dangerous, high-priority missions. Completing these missions will increase your reputation among the Voss.

Complete [HEROIC] Cyber Mercenaries
Complete [HEROIC] Not Afraid Enough
Complete [HEROIC] Savage Connections
Complete [HEROIC] Trial of the First</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
