<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>45</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/bronze/imperial/droid_malfunction/sd_9.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mission to retrieve memory cores complete. Repairs for this unit progressing normally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290141" id2="17" version="1065353216">Droid. I have your Rakata memory cores.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290142" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analyzing... scan complete. Data is intact. Rakata schematics, work orders and material lists are present.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290144" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prison may be duplicated. Forwarding to Imperial Intelligence for review. Your assistance is appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290146" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Rakata memory cores must be retrieved. This unit does not understand the delay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Halt. This is a restricted area. Imperial sentients only. Scanning for potential threats.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290151" id2="17" version="1065353216">Squad cannot be classified. Sentients do not appear hostile. Begin report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290153" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord. Welcome to Maintenance Bay 772. This unit will report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290155" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sentient has received credits from Imperial accounts. Classification: mercenary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290157" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial officer, rank unknown. All units must report to superior officer present.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290159" id2="17" version="1065353216">Designation: SD-9. Mission to retrieve Rakata memory cores failed. Design of Belsavis prison cannot be duplicated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290160" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't accept failure, even from a droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290160" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm disappointed in you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290161" id2="17" version="1065353216">This unit regrets the flaws in its design. This unit believes its mission could still be completed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290163" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Rakata built more than cell blocks here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290163" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is no ordinary prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Error: Data is outside mission parameters. This unit is only concerned with Belsavis prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290166" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone's escaping this place. I'd call that a failed design.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290166" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to copy this failure?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290167" id2="17" version="1065353216">Security has failed due to warfare and severe decay. The Empire would improve the design.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who authorized this? Where would this prison go?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain your mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290170" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mission was originally authorized by: classified. Duplicate prison would be built at: classified.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Duplicated?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis prison is the most secure detention center in the galaxy. Its success can be duplicated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290175" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't ask for a report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Error: This unit has been heavily damaged. This unit must report before related data is lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290178" id2="17" version="1065353216">This unit was sent to obtain memory cores from Rakata units long deactivated. These units were used to construct this prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290180" id2="17" version="1065353216">Information in said memory cores can be used to construct a duplicate prison, in the event the Empire cannot conquer Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290181" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why couldn't you get the memory cores?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290181" id2="17" version="1065353216">But your mission failed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290182" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire? Lose?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290183" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire? Lose?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290184" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire is prepared to deal with all contingencies, no matter how unlikely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290186" id2="17" version="1065353216">So go try again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290187" id2="17" version="1065353216">This unit has been severely damaged. Other units would be equally vulnerable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290189" id2="17" version="1065353216">Several class-A battle droids accompanied this unit in the search. Said droids were destroyed by rioting Esh-kha prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290191" id2="17" version="1065353216">Esh-kha continue to occupy suspected location of Rakata memory cores. Memory cores must be successfully retrieved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290192" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me the location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290193" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll waste some time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290194" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Esh-kha are strong, but disorganized. This unit is certain you will succeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290196" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coordinates are provided. Return the memory cores to this unit's position for proper analysis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290198" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not my problem. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290199" id2="17" version="1065353216">Error: The memory cores must be retrieved. This unit must report its failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290201" id2="17" version="1065353216">Self-diagnostic in progress. Self-diagnostic complete. This unit is in need of maintenance.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
