<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>83</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/crimson_vengeance/republic/master_satele_shan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="513947" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513949" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Carrick Station. We're back, Master Satele.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chandrila is safe, Darth Ikoral is defeated and Republic teams have secured his warship. Our victory is complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513952" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've also received an interesting communique. Stand by....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513954" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith Empire extends its congratulations for your victory over Darth Ikoral. Know that his actions were not sanctioned by the Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Also know that we've learned the identities of your strike team members. Should they invade Imperial territory again, there will be consequences.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Malgus is looking for any excuse to declare war on the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513957" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's taunting us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513958" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe it may be the opposite. You've destroyed another powerful Sith Lord and shown that the dark side can be defeated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless Malgus had spies aboard that ship--or this station--there's no way he could know about us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513960" id2="17" version="1065353216">He shouldn't know us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our security is always at risk. But if he's bluffing, it implies a certain desperation, don't you agree?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513963" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only consequence will be when Havoc Squad tears down Dromund Kaas brick by stinking brick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513963" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blasted right, there will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513964" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are many more battles to fight before that moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513966" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a Sith for you. Subtle as a thermal detonator, and twice as ugly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513966" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a repulsive blowhard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513967" id2="17" version="1065353216">He did not choose his face. It chose him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bring it on, Malgus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513970" id2="17" version="1065353216">It isn't like a Sith to issue threats. I believe he's... worried.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513972" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was barely worth my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513973" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the first time I've ever sensed uncertainty in that man, and you inspired it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513975" id2="17" version="1065353216">A confrontation with Malgus appears inevitable, but not today. For now, our focus should be to honor those we lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your service has been exemplary, as always. Stay safe--and may the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="513979" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513981" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Carrick Station, responding to emergency command protocol &quot;corestar.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. Listen carefully. Nineteen hours ago, we lost contact with the Jedi enclave on Rhinnal. The Republic patrol frigate &quot;Toron Voq&quot; went to investigate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513984" id2="17" version="1065353216">The vessel's crew reported the enclave had been slaughtered. No survivors. As we were speaking, the Toron Voq came under heavy fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Its captain only had enough time to transmit images of a Sith warship before he and his vessel were destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513987" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy must have been hiding. They destroyed the enclave and waited for us to send a ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513987" id2="17" version="1065353216">We fell into a trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Later reconnaissance has revealed that the Sith took their time butchering our people. They were just leaving when the Toron Voq arrived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513990" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we got a unique signature reading on that Sith attacker, we can hunt it down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did we ID the enemy ship?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our one consolation is that the enemy vessel is unique. It's a ship design that hasn't been seen in decades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513993" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's it--we're at war!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513994" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was not an attack by the Empire--at least, not the Empire we've been facing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three hours ago, we intercepted a coded transmission from Darth Malgus to the Sith Dark Council. Stand by....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513998" id2="17" version="1065353216">The destruction of Lord Senu's fortress was but a prelude. Our enemy intends to purge the Empire of any Sith who lacks pure blood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Ikoral will continue to attack both our positions and the Republic until he is stopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is this Sith attacking his own people?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514001" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have a common enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Ikoral believes only pure-blooded Sith like him are worthy of survival. All others should be exterminated to maintain Sith purity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514004" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do we know about this renegade Sith?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Ikoral?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514005" id2="17" version="1065353216">He was a famous leader who left the Empire seeking remnants of pure-blooded Sith over seventy years ago. It seems he found them</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514007" id2="17" version="1065353216">It sounds like our favorite Sith Lord plans to do our job for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let Malgus handle him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514008" id2="17" version="1065353216">We cannot wait for the Empire to clean up this mess. Darth Ikoral's warship was just detected near Chandrila, a major agricultural world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514010" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that insane Sith destroys our food production centers, billions will starve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514011" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was too late to save Uphrades from Darth Angral. I won't fail a second time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not on my watch. Never again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514012" id2="17" version="1065353216">The failure at Uphrades was not yours--but you understand what's at stake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514014" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm determined to preserve the Republic's security--and feed our allies. What's the plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514014" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't permit that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514015" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must intercept our enemy before he reaches his target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514017" id2="17" version="1065353216">That Sith is about to find out he picked the wrong fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough is enough. Let's fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let us hope the enemy is unprepared for your tactics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514020" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that happened, I could earn a fortune hauling grain around the galaxy--but I won't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514020" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't have that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514021" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad that your first instincts were humanitarian.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514023" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we prevent that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514024" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we know Malgus and Ikoral aren't working together to draw us out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are we walking into a trap?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514025" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our scouts have verified that two enemy fortresses commanded by alien Sith were destroyed. This is no bluff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514027" id2="17" version="1065353216">The datalogs on Darth Ikoral's warship contain decades of valuable strategic data we desperately need--and you've proven capable of capturing any vessel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our fleet is on its way to Chandrila. Rendezvous in the attack shuttle I've commissioned at Carrick Station. Defeat Darth Ikoral. Take his ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514030" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure facing that Sith head-on is the best plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514030" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're asking a lot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514031" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't about him. The astrogation routes and galaxy map on his vessel will help us topple the Sith Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514033" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can sense the strain you're under, Master. Were you close to someone at the Jedi enclave that was destroyed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you alright?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514034" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sensed the deaths of many Jedi, all at once. The last time I felt that was when the temple on Coruscant was destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you're taking this personally. I thought Jedi weren't supposed to do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you alright?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514037" id2="17" version="1065353216">I simply want justice. You can provide that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514039" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith are as good as dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not misunderstand me. I'm not sending you to assassinate--only to ensure our people did not die for nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry to your shuttle. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514043" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start Veteran Mode]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="514044" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1170842" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start Master Mode]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
