<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>52</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/bronze/republic/one_fell_swoop/yedduu.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169627" id2="17" version="1065353216">The residents of this sector will have a better future because of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169629" id2="17" version="1065353216">That swoop gang won't be causing any more trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169630" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard what happened--news travels quickly in this sector. They attacked you, but you fought them off!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169632" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have avenged my brother and freed us from the tyranny of the swoop gangs!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169634" id2="17" version="1065353216">By avenging my brother and freeing us from the tyranny of the swoop gangs, you have earned your reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169636" id2="17" version="1065353216">On behalf of all the citizens of this sector, thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169638" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use the EMP immobilizer to disable the swoop bikes. I'll be here when you're finished.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169641" id2="17" version="1065353216">This sector used to be a good place to live. Quiet. Clean. Safe. Then the swoop gangs took over.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169643" id2="17" version="1065353216">They terrorize the shopkeepers. Attack innocent civilians on the streets. Destroy our homes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169645" id2="17" version="1065353216">And they slaughter anyone brave enough to stand up to them, leaving him bleeding in the gutter while they roar off on their swoop bikes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169646" id2="17" version="1065353216">They killed someone you cared about, didn't they?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169646" id2="17" version="1065353216">This sounds personal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169647" id2="17" version="1065353216">My brother. We ran a little shop together. The swoop gangs demanded we give them protection money.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169649" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you hate it here so much, just move somewhere else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why don't you move?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169650" id2="17" version="1065353216">No! My family has lived here for too many generations to let the swoop gangs push us out!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169652" id2="17" version="1065353216">My brother refused to pay the swoop gangs off. He said, &quot;Yeddu, we must take a stand!&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169654" id2="17" version="1065353216">These swoop gangs need to be taught a lesson.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169654" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone should stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169655" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sound like my brother. He refused to pay the swoop gangs off. He said, &quot;Yeddu, we must take a stand!&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169657" id2="17" version="1065353216">They killed him for his defiance. I swore I would avenge him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169658" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not thinking clearly. You seek closure in your brother's death, but throwing your life away is not the answer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hate leads to the dark side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169659" id2="17" version="1065353216">So... one angry Nikto against an entire swoop gang. How do you think that ends up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169659" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a bad move to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169660" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have to worry. I have a plan, but I'm too much of a coward to act on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169662" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll say this much for you: You've got guts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169662" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seem pretty determined.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169663" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to see you're not going to back down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your brother would be proud.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169664" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't understand. I made a promise to my brother, but I'm nothing but a coward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169666" id2="17" version="1065353216">How?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169667" id2="17" version="1065353216">I bought some EMP immobilizers from the black market. The blast will fry the circuits of any swoop bike caught in the explosion.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169669" id2="17" version="1065353216">The swoops are parked in the streets near the gang's base. But I'm too afraid to go there and plant the immobilizers. What if they see me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169670" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not afraid of this gang. Give the immobilizers to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169670" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169671" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the right price, I'll plant the immobilizers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169671" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could hire me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169672" id2="17" version="1065353216">This really isn't my problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169672" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going now. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave this to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169674" id2="17" version="1065353216">You would consider helping me with this? A stranger? I... I don't know what to say. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take these EMP immobilizers. Place them near the gang's swoop bikes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169678" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you set them off, the blast will fry all the circuits. We'll see how tough those gangs are when they can't just fly away on their precious swoops!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169679" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169680" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll help... for a price.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169681" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have much, but whatever I have is yours if you take out those swoop bikes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169683" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful. With or without the immobilizers, the gang will not be happy to see you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169685" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll wait here. Come back and see me when you're done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169687" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. I understand. Why should you risk yourself to help me?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169690" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have time to talk with strangers.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
