<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/jedi_consular/chapter_3/shattering/cc_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is no good, Herald. We disable explosives, word comes in of dozen more.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time is too close. We pull back now or fall to Imperial trap. Ship is dying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi, we've done our utmost, but we just found another stockpile of those bombs, and the timer's counting down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500040" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's simply too many. Either we pull back now, or we don't get out at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500042" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry. I think the Javelin is lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Herald, have seen explosives droid spoke of. Voss commandos disable now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is dozens, all over starship systems. Have said to hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500050" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi, we reached the starboard cooling tanks. That droid wasn't lying--they're plastered with bombs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500052" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've told the others how to disable them safely, but it's a fiddly process. This will be a close-run thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500056" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have silenced this Empire's whispering. The void is blank to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500058" id2="17" version="1065353216">We wait for you, Sky Hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500059" id2="17" version="1065353216">We wait for you, Silent Teeth.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500060" id2="17" version="1065353216">We wait for you, Ember Fist.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our vessels are leaves on the wind, this Empire snatches in vain.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our vessels court this Empire's lightning, as you ordered. Some are struck, but we trace the enemy's steps and grow wise.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500065" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yet now they flee, Sky Hunter. Does this Empire have a newborn's heart?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500066" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yet now they flee, Ember Fist. Does this Empire have a newborn's heart?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yet now they flee, Silent Teeth. Does this Empire have a newborn's heart?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500071" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss and I taking weapons control and armory.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soft things here fled before us. Is strangeness they did not fight. May you find better prey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Armory's secure, but they locked the door to weapons control. We're cutting through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not to jinx it, but I expected stronger resistance than this. Might be a harder fight up ahead. Iresso out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500080" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold on, Jedi. Security system's being stubborn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Done. I'll watch for any more. Zenith out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500084" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oops. Let me get that force field for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500086" id2="17" version="1065353216">All done! Tharan and I will keep an eye on the network room.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500088" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commandos say force fields have dropped. Am destroying their generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500090" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is done. Should be no more barriers for you, Herald.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500092" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stand by. A crewman slipped past us and triggered a bunch of force fields.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500094" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lousy Imperial fail-safes... there, you should be good to go. Iresso out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500096" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hang on, Jedi! Looks like they blocked your route, we're working on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500098" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, there it goes. Take care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me and the commandos are at the network room. We'll see what we can do without Tharan and Holiday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I'll hit security. Double-team them. Zenith out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500105" id2="17" version="1065353216">We spotted a security system, too. We'll go back for it later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500106" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're in the network room! Breaking Imperial coding... makes me all tingly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500108" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zenith sneaked off to security. I imagine he knows what to do with an Imperial security system. Ta-ta for now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500109" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll have a crack at security too, if we get the chance. Ta-ta for now.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
