<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>50</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/jedi_consular/chapter_3/shattering/li_45.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings again, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478875" id2="17" version="1065353216">I imagine the blast will be quite impressive from here, for an instant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah. Greetings, Master Jedi. All parameters are met, my work can finally be demonstrated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is your commanding officer hiding somewhere?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where's the captain?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Following standard procedure, all personnel above the rank of lieutenant have been evacuated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478880" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sense trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain yourself, droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Obeying my standing orders, I have seeded this vessel with detonite charges.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478884" id2="17" version="1065353216">These charges are sufficient to destroy the Javelin, its occupants and nearby vessels. I apologize for any inconvenience caused.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478885" id2="17" version="1065353216">These reinforcements were bait; the Empire wanted our alliance dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478885" id2="17" version="1065353216">We walked into a trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Allow me to outline the genius of my work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478888" id2="17" version="1065353216">That explosion could wipe out all our ships, and the Esh-kha.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our fleet will be lost!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478889" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, don't worry, Master Jedi. You'll be dead before then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Disable those charges or I'll break you down to your components.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Disarm the bombs, immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478892" id2="17" version="1065353216">All interfering remote &quot;safeties&quot; have been removed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478894" id2="17" version="1065353216">I placed multiple detonite charges in mathematically precise positions. There was no response when I warned other Imperial vessels, I assume they know of the countdown.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478900" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have placed multiple detonite charges in mathematically precise positions. All Imperial vessels have been signaled to withdraw, as the countdown has begun.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="478904" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is snare Empire laid for us. Is bad death, to fall because of trick!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then the entire purpose of sending this dreadnaught was to set a trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478908" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's willing to sacrifice a whole dreadnaught, just to trap us? I should feel flattered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Empire's so sharp it cuts itself. And we fell for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478912" id2="17" version="1065353216">So we walked right into a trap?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478915" id2="17" version="1065353216">By my calculations, even if dozens of the charges are disarmed, it is now impossible to prevent the Javelin's destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478916" id2="17" version="1065353216">But if we disable as many as we can, there won't be enough of a blast to destroy our ships.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478916" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can still save our fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478917" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may attempt it, but my placement of the charges is flawless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478919" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't you care that the explosion will annihilate you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478919" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you'll be destroyed too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478920" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can still take satisfaction in a job well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478922" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to enjoy proving you wrong. Now tell me where to find those charges.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478922" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't count on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478923" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are charges on all main coolant regulation systems, to ensure complete destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="478927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will send warning to all on board.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Holiday, tell the others about those bombs before our friend here gets another bright idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478929" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll alert the others. We'll need everybody to get those bombs disarmed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478930" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll pass on the good news to everyone. And the bomb positions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478931" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll send the bomb locations out to everybody!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478932" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and I can take care of the charges nearby, and trust the others to reach the rest in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478932" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll get the closest bombs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478933" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do it. If we work together, we can handle the charges nearby and then run for the ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478933" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no time to waste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478934" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can reach the closest charges in time, but if the entire Javelin is rigged, we may not be able to save it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478934" id2="17" version="1065353216">This ship may be lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me the location of the closest bombs, and tell my friends where to find the rest. That's an order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478937" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this is how you wish to spend your final minutes, Master Jedi, I have no direct orders prohibiting it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478939" id2="17" version="1065353216">A shame my accomplishment will soon be superheated vapor, but such is the nature of demolition work. Good day.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
