<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>41</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/mtx/chronicles/shroud_mtx.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111733" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud Intelligence File 2M1: I've always said it will take more than credits to pull me out of retirement. I require inspiration. A challenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111735" id2="17" version="1065353216">A request from the Hutt Cartel to spy on the Galactic Republic and the Sith Empire for them? That certainly qualifies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111737" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's no secret that the Hutt Cartel only pretends at legitimate business concerns; in truth, they are the galaxy's largest criminal syndicate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111739" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mere act of contracting my services would suggest that the status quo is not good enough anymore. They have become proactive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111741" id2="17" version="1065353216">But what is this new ambition of the Hutt Cartel? Why now? And what fate would they have the Empire and Republic suffer as a result?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111743" id2="17" version="1065353216">My questions will have answers. I'm the Shroud; no secret can elude me for long....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud Intelligence File 2M2: The Hutt Cartel has been especially loose with their credits of late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111749" id2="17" version="1065353216">To give their dirty credits the air of legitimate business dealings, the Cartel maintains a seemingly impossible network of complex transactions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, I recognized the patterns some time ago. In monitoring their expenses, I noticed they've diverted an extravagant sum to the InterStellar Regulators, a freelance security force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111753" id2="17" version="1065353216">At present, the Regulators have only one contract: the planet Makeb. No great strategic value, no discernible resources--yet somehow it's tied to the Cartel's aggressive plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111755" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've dealt with the Regulators' high command before. Vice Commandant Grevin does love a payday. Perhaps he'll be open to an offer for more information....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud Intelligence File 2M3: You'd think a major crime syndicate like the Hutt Cartel would impress upon its members the importance of discretion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111761" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've intercepted transmissions of note--quite easily--from a former lieutenant of Nem'ro regarding another Hutt by the name of Toborro.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111763" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seems Toborro has been staffing up, paying triple the standard rate for quality mercenaries to come to Makeb. Unusually generous for a Hutt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111765" id2="17" version="1065353216">From his databanks, it's all too clear. Toborro wants the Cartel to be forever unchecked by Imperial and Republic encumbrances.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111767" id2="17" version="1065353216">This ambitious plot of the Cartel's--it must have originated from Toborro. Perhaps I'll have one of my operatives accept his offer of employment....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111771" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud Intelligence File 2M4: I've just learned that the Hutt Cartel has its very own Archon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111773" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Archons date back to when the Hutt Empire was at its height, millennia ago. They were dedicated to the preservation of their empire at all costs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111775" id2="17" version="1065353216">This particular Archon, Szajin, is the Cartel's preeminent strategist and intelligence minister. Every file I've decrypted had to go through him first. How did I not see it before now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111777" id2="17" version="1065353216">It must be Szajin who had the Cartel hire me in the first place. He has to know I'd learn about him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps this constitutes an invitation to match wits. If so, I accept. I could use a worthy opponent....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111783" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud Intelligence File 2M5: The trouble with having operatives virtually everywhere is the &quot;virtually&quot; part.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111785" id2="17" version="1065353216">What I wouldn't give to have access to the Arcanum. The Sith Empire's most valued relics, gravest dangers and darkest secrets--all of it locked within one impenetrable stronghold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111787" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seems a fanatical group devoted to the Dread Masters have been looking to breach the Arcanum's walls as well. I'd like to think they could be of some use.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111789" id2="17" version="1065353216">But infiltrating this so-called &quot;Dread Guard&quot; is no easy task. Members won't be swayed by credits or coercion. Any moles could easily be indoctrinated to their cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111791" id2="17" version="1065353216">In any case, the Dread Masters appear to be taking advantage of every resource at their disposal. I must track their dark maneuvers very closely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud Intelligence File 2M6: Label yourself a spy and others will come to expect certain things from you, such as spying. But that's no longer enough to hold my interest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111797" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have severed ties with the Hutt Cartel, as it would seem they do not appreciate the extent of my ambitions. Funny, that--considering their own newfound aspiration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111799" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galaxy is in a state of unrelenting, explosive change. Every day brings new threats, new alliances, new fronts in this blossoming war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111801" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the environment in which I thrive. Where I can commit the grandest, most brazen acts of destruction and upheaval--and remain at large, untouched.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111803" id2="17" version="1065353216">As the pieces fall into their proper place, a strategy emerges. My new challenge. I can hardly wait to get started--so I won't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud Intelligence File 2M7: The Empire thought they could sneak through Makeb with no one the wiser. Apparently, they've forgotten about me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such a desperate state they're in. Lurking around in secret like frightened children. Imperial Intelligence decimated. And then there's the matter of recruitment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111811" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of my operatives has made note of an Imperial Captain who was unmistakably Cathar. Aliens. Not merely as rank and file, but as officers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Marr is loosening restrictions in the Emperor's absence. But is it solely out of desperation? Or is this a glimpse of Marr's vision for an Empire yet to come?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever the answer, it would seem that now is a time of great change. Change breeds chaos. And chaos, opportunity--for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111819" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shroud Intelligence File 2M8: No matter how much you pay your staff, Supreme Chancellor, there will always be someone willing to pay them more. Someone like me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leontyne Saresh: former Imperial slave, career politician, Twi'lek leader of the Galactic Republic--and would-be eradicator of the Sith Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Her communications are quite telling. In my view, this new, aggressive Republic is a mere prelude to what Saresh truly has planned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111825" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the problem with such an impassioned pursuit of the goal ahead is that you lose sight of your periphery. You leave yourself vulnerable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Threats can come from anywhere. Like, say, from a freelance spy roused from his retirement. A legend long forgotten--for the moment.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
