<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>75</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/bringing_down_the_hammer/republic/master_satele_shan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="513535" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hammer Station is destroyed, Master Satele.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513538" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people of Saleucami and the other conquered worlds send their gratitude. The enemy has retreated to their home system.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those conquered worlds will need help rebuilding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Start the relief efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Relief ships are already en route with food and medicine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should we pursue the Advozse Hegemony's forces, or focus on shoring up the planets they conquered?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513542" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's our next move?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513543" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hegemony is no longer a threat. This is a time to heal our losses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513545" id2="17" version="1065353216">We shouldn't give the Advozse Hegemony a chance to regroup. Let's send the fleet to wipe them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's finish them off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513546" id2="17" version="1065353216">There has been enough killing. The Advozsec learned a painful lesson today--one they won't forget.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to you, we know how Hammer Station survived destruction. Years ago, its autopilot was set to fly the station into a nearby star.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513550" id2="17" version="1065353216">According to the data you recovered, a mechanical failure cut the station's engines just short of its final destination. Advozsec salvagers discovered it several months ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513551" id2="17" version="1065353216">The salvagers towed Hammer Station back to Hegemony space and gave its government the weapon they'd always wanted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513551" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can fill in the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513552" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the end, the responsibility lies with the Republic. We should never have built such a terrible weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513554" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't anyone from the Republic bother to make sure that the station was destroyed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513554" id2="17" version="1065353216">This shouldn't have happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513555" id2="17" version="1065353216">The failure occurred beyond our sensor readings. It took years for Hammer Station to drift where the Advozsec salvagers could detect it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513557" id2="17" version="1065353216">If word gets out this was our fault, it will cause unrest in the Outer Rim systems. Planets might secede from the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513557" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to keep this a secret.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513558" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senate Security Committee will decide what to do about this incident--but in my experience, truth is always best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513560" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regardless, your valiant efforts will be remembered. Take care--and may the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="513562" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513565" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Republic Emergency Response Corps secure holofrequency &quot;polaris.&quot; A crisis on the Outer Rim requires immediate intervention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513567" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Advozse Hegemony have obtained a Republic battle station and are using it for acts of aggressive expansion, conquering entire star systems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513568" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never heard of this group. What are they after?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are these people?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513569" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're a xenophobic political faction seeking to expand. Until now, they've been a containable threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513571" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did Advozsec &quot;obtain&quot; our battle station? Did someone leave it unlocked with the keys inside?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Battle station?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does this emergency take precedence over my main assignment, Master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513572" id2="17" version="1065353216">I already have a mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513573" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hegemony must be stopped immediately. Millions of innocent lives are at stake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513575" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't even know who you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513576" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Satele Shan, Grand Master of the Jedi Council. I coordinate with the Republic Emergency Response Corps during military crises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513578" id2="17" version="1065353216">No offense, but this sounds like Jedi work to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513578" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a job for your people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513579" id2="17" version="1065353216">Defending the helpless from tyranny is the work of all Republic citizens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513581" id2="17" version="1065353216">During the last war, Republic scientists developed a mobile battle station code-named &quot;Hammer.&quot; It bombarded planetary surfaces using asteroids as weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hammer Station was indiscriminately destructive. The project was canceled and its prototype ordered destroyed. We don't know how the Advosze Hegemony now possess it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513584" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll solve that mystery later. The point is, that station could level whole cities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513584" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's irrelevant right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513585" id2="17" version="1065353216">The planet Skine resisted the Hegemony's demands to surrender. Hammer Station reduced its capital city to ashes two hours ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe our friends figured out how to construct their own Hammer Station?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could they have built one?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513588" id2="17" version="1065353216">They lack the resources to build anything of that magnitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do I get the feeling we're about to add &quot;battle station demolitionist&quot; to our resumes?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513590" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want us to destroy it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513591" id2="17" version="1065353216">A direct fleet assault would be suicide. Shields are useless against asteroid strikes. The station can target and destroy large vessels easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513593" id2="17" version="1065353216">But an assault shuttle could evade the asteroids and deliver a commando team to destroy Hammer Station from the inside. We just need volunteers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513594" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is what I trained for. I'll bring down that station, whatever it takes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful. The Jedi Order cannot afford to lose you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Violence is not my way, Master, but destroying that station appears to be our best hope for peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513597" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I must.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513598" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force is strong in you. Let it guide you to victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513600" id2="17" version="1065353216">You came to the right soldier. I specialize in storming enemy fortresses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513600" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on Havoc Squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513601" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I ask is that you come back in one piece.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513603" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it on one condition: If I die, you build a statue in my honor. Something really impressive--and expensive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513603" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll need to meet my terms.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed--but I hope we never have need to fulfill that bargain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513606" id2="17" version="1065353216">And what happens to that commando team when the station blows up--posthumous medals?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a one-way trip.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Overloading Hammer Station's primary weapon will take time. The boarding party can flee before its detonation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513609" id2="17" version="1065353216">A weapon like that could defeat the Empire once and for all. We're better off keeping it intact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513609" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should capture the station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some weapons should never be used.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroying the station is your main objective, but we need to know how the Hegemony obtained it. Any data you recover could prove useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hammer Station has just entered orbit above Saleucami and demanded its surrender. Your assault shuttle is standing by. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="513615" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start Veteran Mode]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="513616" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1111979" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start Master Mode]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
