<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>105</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/world/imperial/breaking_the_maw/fixer_308.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670728" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll have that droid brain reproduced in no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670729" id2="17" version="1065353216">The admiral's ships are pummeling the pirates. There can't be many survivors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670731" id2="17" version="1065353216">I went to the pirates' hideout. I found this neural chipset for a battle droid. I think Loramarr designed it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670732" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, the stamp seems consistent with his work... wait. It's brilliant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670734" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's solved the traditional limitations of a chipset brain. Hold on a moment, I need to make a call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admiral? We've recovered a battle droid neural chipset from the White Maw. It's the advancement we've been waiting for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670738" id2="17" version="1065353216">From the White Maw? What are they doing with tech like that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670739" id2="17" version="1065353216">They had it hidden in the last known location of the inventor Loramarr.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670739" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hoarding it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670740" id2="17" version="1065353216">Loramarr. That would make sense, his robotics always were top-notch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670742" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a quad-photonic neural chipset, Admiral. If you put this in a battle droid, it'll think on its feet better than most humans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why didn't you say something about this earlier?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670744" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could have briefed me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Frankly, I wasn't sure the engineering was possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670747" id2="17" version="1065353216">We didn't even know it was more than theory. An innovation like this... its value is a different magnitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670749" id2="17" version="1065353216">And a reproducible brain like this, far beyond war droids... producing it would be its own industry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670750" id2="17" version="1065353216">What you're telling me is I just handed you a small fortune.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670750" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's my cut?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670751" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will make certain you are amply rewarded. Fixer--get that chipset off-planet at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670753" id2="17" version="1065353216">I live to serve. The Emperor. My people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670753" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670754" id2="17" version="1065353216">It sounds like I did the right thing coming to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I do well?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670755" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's an understatement. If Loramarr invented a reproducible quad-photonic brain, our battle droids could be much smarter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670757" id2="17" version="1065353216">It could change the course of the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670758" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let me stall you. Get that chipset to the technicians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670758" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then get on it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670759" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be done immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670761" id2="17" version="1065353216">For someone who dropped off the map, Loramarr's work still seems cutting-edge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not bad for a recluse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Completely. We'll get this to the space station at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670764" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll alert the Reclamation Service to the Loramarr area. There's no telling what else might be there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670766" id2="17" version="1065353216">As for you... I'd take a well-earned vacation. Somewhere warm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670767" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's all yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanking you for something on this scale seems trite. But thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670770" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get this to the space station at once and then alert the Reclamation Service to the area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670772" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no telling what else they might find in there. And you've delivered it to us on a plate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670774" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll let you know if the admiral's dragnet catches anything interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670775" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this works, we will write the final chapter on the White Maw.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670776" id2="17" version="1065353216">In conclusion, Admiral, this seems like the most opportune window we'll get. All I need is the go-ahead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670778" id2="17" version="1065353216">It meets with my approval, Fixer. You may brief the volunteers and commence with the mission. Over and out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670780" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, the operatives. I'm Fixer 308. We've been tracking you since we heard about your success with the Talz.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670781" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, just who I was expecting. I'm Fixer 308. We've been tracking you since we heard about your success with the Talz.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, there you are. I'm Fixer 308. We've been planning for your arrival ever since we heard about your success with the Talz.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670783" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, the operatives. I'm Fixer 308. We've been tracking you ever since you rid that power station of the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670784" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, welcome. I'm Fixer 308. We've tracked your success since your victory at the power station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, you've arrived. I'm Fixer 308. We've been planning for your arrival ever since you rid the power station of the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670786" id2="17" version="1065353216">The operatives. Good to finally meet you. I'm Fixer 308. I've been tracking your activities since your defeat of the Hailstorm Brotherhood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670787" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, we meet at last. I'm Fixer 308. I've been tracking your activities since your defeat of the Hailstorm Brotherhood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670788" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome. I'm Fixer 308. I've been tracking your success since that business with the Hailstorm Brotherhood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670789" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was no trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670790" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, the operatives we were expecting. Good. I'm Fixer 308. We've been tracking you since you came to the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670791" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, just who I was expecting. I'm Fixer 308. We've been tracking you since you came to the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670792" id2="17" version="1065353216">There you are. I'm Fixer 308. We've been tracking you since you came to the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670793" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you have for me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670793" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me your intentions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670794" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been hitting the White Maw hard lately, enough so that they've called a meeting of their gangs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why don't I find that comforting?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670796" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's disturbing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670797" id2="17" version="1065353216">We want you to handle something for us. The White Maw has been damaged enough to call a meeting of their gangs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Had I known that was my audition, I'd have put in more effort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670799" id2="17" version="1065353216">I feel used.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670800" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have more to worry about. Current intel indicates that the pirates have suffered enough damage to call a meeting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670802" id2="17" version="1065353216">The loss of a power station was a bigger blow than we thought. Every one of their gangs will be represented.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670804" id2="17" version="1065353216">At this meet will be the leaders of the Bala D'ur, the Hailstorm Brotherhood, the Scourge and all the other gangs in the White Maw.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670806" id2="17" version="1065353216">We intend to get you into that meeting and have you capture or kill everyone present. The hard part is getting there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me guess. They're going to be surrounded by guards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds risky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Private armies, practically. And the meeting location is secret, so you'll have to take drastic measures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guards and walls have never kept me out before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave that to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670811" id2="17" version="1065353216">That part of the plan I trust to you. But there's more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670813" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we do that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670814" id2="17" version="1065353216">The shuttles of the leaders' trusted captains will have the meeting's coordinates programmed into their navicomputers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670816" id2="17" version="1065353216">What you'll need to do is find a lieutenant with a shuttle, kill him and get his access card to steal his ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you get access to the shuttle, fly it to their hideout, track down the gang leaders and take them out. Can you do that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670819" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like the place will be swarming with White Maw... at least until I get there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670819" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like a challenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670820" id2="17" version="1065353216">All things are possible through the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670820" id2="17" version="1065353216">My limits are few.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Considering these pirates will all be in the same room, I'll charge my group rate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670821" id2="17" version="1065353216">No problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. Here's a dossier on the leaders you'll be terminating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shall I do this with or without a blindfold?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clear and easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670825" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's a dossier on the leaders to terminate, so you'll be able to identify them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our psych profiles indicate that, given the opportunity, some of them may surrender. It's up to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lastly, if you find an opportunity to search their files, take it. There's no telling what secrets these malcontents have hidden away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670832" id2="17" version="1065353216">That seems like a long string of chances, ones I will not be taking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you crazy? [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670833" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see. Then we'll assign one of our squads before this opportunity disappears. I'll break the news to them shortly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not now, the admiral's on the comm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670837" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you will appreciate the effort I put in to keep this quiet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670837" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the credit, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670838" id2="17" version="1065353216">There was no reason to cut me out. I would have supported you had you mentioned it to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough. What matters is that if this is indeed what Fixer says, our battle droids could be a generation smarter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670843" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may have taken all the credit from this, but there's no telling what else they may find in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670845" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found this in one of the pirates' hideouts. It's a chipset for a battle droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting... it does seem very advanced... wait. This looks like Loramarr's work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670848" id2="17" version="1065353216">What have you been... scratch that, I don't want to know. I have to make a call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670850" id2="17" version="1065353216">I went to Loramarr. There was little there of interest besides amazingly hostile droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I'll get Dorn Base to acquire a strike team for us before notifying the Reclamation Service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670853" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will scout the area personally to verify your report. And you should probably go offworld before any contradictions arise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670855" id2="17" version="1065353216">There may not be any, but if I were you, I wouldn't stay on this ice ball any longer than I had to.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
