<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>39</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/world/imperial/breaking_the_maw/fixer_308_holo.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188455" id2="17" version="1065353216">So the White Maw finally falls. I wonder, was this the nerve center of their operation? Or are there valuables hidden elsewhere?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188456" id2="17" version="1065353216">I searched their files and found nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="188456" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] No hoard that I know of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Strange. I guess we overestimated them. Still, once the admiral's forces secure the area, we'll find out for certain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188459" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're finally coming apart. It's taken two years of building up intel, unable to focus our full efforts on the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188461" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found a place called Loramarr in their databanks. It's likely their stash is there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="188461" id2="17" version="1065353216">I may know about their loot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Loramarr. I wonder if that has to do with the inventor Loramarr. He was quite a droid maker before he vanished a decade or so back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188464" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should probably send a salvage team to investigate, but seeing as you trusted me with this information....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188466" id2="17" version="1065353216">...I think I'll mark the area as &quot;unsecured&quot; until you're finished with it. That way, the Reclamation Service doesn't get first crack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188467" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's kind of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="188467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't mention it. Especially not where internal security might be listening.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188471" id2="17" version="1065353216">My interest is in aiding the Empire, not lining my pockets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="188471" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, I wouldn't suggest that, of course. My concern is wholly for the Reclamation Service's safety.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do as you see fit. I'll go monitor the admiral's fleet as it descends on the pirates. That should prove entertaining.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. I doubt I could have trusted someone else to bring this operation to a close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admiral, we have received no word since the shuttle departed. We fear the worst.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Satellites recorded heavy blaster fire in that area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188482" id2="17" version="1065353216">It does seem unlikely that they've survived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188483" id2="17" version="1065353216">It does seem unlikely that she survived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188484" id2="17" version="1065353216">It does seem unlikely that he survived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188485" id2="17" version="1065353216">The White Maw leaders are dead. I am not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="188485" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's over. We won.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188486" id2="17" version="1065353216">The White Maw's leaders are terminated. Those who aren't, seek amnesty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="188486" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's over. We won.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188487" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm in remarkable shape for a dead person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="188487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't bury me yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this how you talk about me behind my back?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="188488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such little faith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, praise the Emperor. We were about to send a rescue party.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188491" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was dreading being the intel officer famous for getting all of you killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188493" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't have wanted to see what they'd do to me once I contacted Korriban and told them I got a Sith Lord killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188495" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was dreading telling Aristocra Hadro that I'd gotten his prize problem solver killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188497" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was dreading telling the rest of Intelligence that I'd gotten you killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188499" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll send bombers and fighters down to pacify the pirates. We'll need to intercept any White Maw starships fleeing the system.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="188501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent, Admiral. Over and out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670862" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds good.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
