<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>150</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/world/republic/project_noble_focus/colonel_hauer.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once Project Noble Focus starts producing results, you'll see why it was necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706486" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic needed this project more than it needs a few deadbeat convicts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706488" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's done. Sulkhaz fell in battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706489" id2="17" version="1065353216">There, you see, Graal? Problem solved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706491" id2="17" version="1065353216">You created that murdering slime, Senator. Far as I'm concerned, you're the problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706493" id2="17" version="1065353216">You remember the warden. Afraid he doesn't much care for our little project.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706495" id2="17" version="1065353216">You haven't met the deputy warden, have you? Good man; doesn't approve of our little project, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your &quot;little project&quot; jeopardized the entire prison and violated countless ethics laws. You should be put away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Torturing prisoners may fly with the Sith, but the Republic is above that sort of thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706498" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706499" id2="17" version="1065353216">The senator has much to answer for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706499" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706500" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't mind tossing him in the stockade myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706500" id2="17" version="1065353216">That makes two of us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706501" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think you're annoyed? I'm the one who had to clean up this mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706501" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706502" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry you got dragged into this. Never should have escalated this far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706504" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought the project was classified. How'd you find out about it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, you know everything?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706505" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Weequay found his way here, told us the whole story. Said you helped him. Poor sap looked like he needed it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706507" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few prisoners escaped and found their way here. Were scared half to death, rambling on about secret experiments and war games.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706509" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's just a few convicts. Nobody will miss them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody cares, Graal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't care. What the Senator did was unconscionable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706512" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spare me the show. The Republic has poured countless resources into containing these degenerates. It's high time we got something in return.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706514" id2="17" version="1065353216">And we have. Project Noble Focus has given us a world of insight into the different species' strengths and limitations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just think, entire campaigns planned with each species' capabilities in mind. Our wartime efficiency will skyrocket.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706517" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't give you the right to experiment on prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706517" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's still wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706518" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's right and what's necessary are rarely one and the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your project drove the Rattataki to murder. That should tell you something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706520" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the repercussions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah--that the Rattataki are some tough customers. Lesson learned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706523" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's true....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever your feelings, this project--and our involvement in it--needs to remain classified.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think of the backlash if this gets out. Every planet in the Republic will be up in arms.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Entire systems could secede over this. Surely a few dead convicts aren't worth all that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't use the Republic to cover up your part in this. You broke the law.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706529" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're going to jail for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706530" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right. It might get ugly, but the Republic needs to hear about this. I expect to see you back here real soon, Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph. We'll see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706534" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's right. Preserving the Republic's stability is more important than punishing these two.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. We'll keep it a secret.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get off my planet then, Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Happy to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706539" id2="17" version="1065353216">With Sulkhaz dead and the experiments terminated, things should start to normalize there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706541" id2="17" version="1065353216">As soon as I have some guards to spare, I'll send them down there to clean up. Thanks for your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706545" id2="17" version="1065353216">That settles that. Now to bigger concerns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706547" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got trouble in the maximum security wing. General Skylast says some unidentified species is tearing through his men.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706549" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Deep Prison is where the true horrors of Belsavis lie. If Skylast can't stop them, all this will have been for nothing. Help him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706562" id2="17" version="1065353216">This may be our only shot at Sulkhaz. Make it count.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our satellites have picked up a large number of Rattataki in the Neimoidian compound. Up to their usual antics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706565" id2="17" version="1065353216">And here I was hoping it was just a social call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706567" id2="17" version="1065353216">The satellite images we've seen are pretty grisly. Far as we can tell, they're butchering the Neimoidians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706568" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got to get down there and put a stop to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706568" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should help them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706569" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not so concerned about saving Neimoidians as I am putting down the Rattataki.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't the Rattataki ever sleep?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706571" id2="17" version="1065353216">These guys are relentless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently not. It's been a steady stream of mayhem since they escaped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706574" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sticking my neck out just to save a few convicts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706575" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could care less about the Neimoidians. We've got bigger fish to fry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706577" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've confirmed that Sulkhaz, the Blood of Talath's ringleader, is personally overseeing this latest massacre.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706579" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's everything you could want in a fanatical leader: loud, ruthless and utterly demented.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eliminating Sulkhaz will take the fight out of the Rattataki, show them who's in charge. You've got to get down there and stop him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever it takes to end this madness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706582" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706583" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are times when violence is a necessary step toward peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706583" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will do what I must.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706584" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Sulkhaz is about to find out how we do things in Havoc Squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gladly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706585" id2="17" version="1065353216">One ex-nutcase, coming up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706585" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd be happy to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706586" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I get back, we're going to have a little chat about this project of yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706586" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. But then we talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, fine. Just get it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Expect a bloody fight. Sulkhaz rarely does anything without someone dying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make sure it's not you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count me out. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706594" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't afford to let this opportunity slip by!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senator Tudos told me you diffused the bomb. Not a moment too soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706598" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I see you brought back the stolen power cores. I'll have our engineers start modifying the warden droids immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706600" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Rattataki still have the run of the wing, but at least we've contained them... for now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706601" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to talk about Project Noble Focus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706601" id2="17" version="1065353216">About these experiments....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706602" id2="17" version="1065353216">There'll be time enough for that once the Rattataki have been dealt with. Focus on the crisis at hand for now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706604" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's one crisis averted. What's our next move?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706604" id2="17" version="1065353216">What now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706605" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now's the time to wipe them out and be done with this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706605" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's finish them off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706606" id2="17" version="1065353216">You just might get your shot at that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706608" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got to disarm that bomb before the Rattataki set it off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel Hauer? Warden Graal told me you could use a hand here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706613" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right. Heard you put down a riot in his neck of the woods. Heck of a feat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Certainly piqued my interest. Senator Tudos, chairman of the Penal Oversight Committee. Delighted to finally meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Been a while since we saw any new friendlies out here. Good to have you here. I'm Colonel Hauer. A word, if I may.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, do come in. Senator Tudos, chairman of the Penal Oversight Committee. A pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706623" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know, I'm about to propose some new legislation to the Senate--bold stuff, very controversial. A Jedi's endorsement would go a long way....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706625" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know, I applied for military service myself when I was your age. Didn't pan out, but I do love a good war story....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe later we can talk about shifting some, ahem, sensitive cargo to my estates on Coruscant....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surviving a planet-wide riot is no easy thing. No doubt you trekked through fire and blood to get here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senator. Focus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right. Things have spiraled out of control here--thousands of prisoners on the loose, segregation thrown out the door. A veritable frenzy of interspecies violence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I'd hop on the first ship out of here. This is no place for a Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706634" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not safe here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tempting, but the Republic has invested no small sum into this facility. I need to make sure certain... interests are being protected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706637" id2="17" version="1065353216">You kept the prisoners segregated? What for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Segregation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706638" id2="17" version="1065353216">These criminal types are notoriously intolerant of other species. The genocide we've seen here only proves it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let them go at each other's throats. Makes our job easier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine by me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706641" id2="17" version="1065353216">It crossed my mind. But as their duly appointed representative, I owe it to them to stamp out this anarchy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706643" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our biggest concern is a tribe of Rattataki called the Blood of Talath. Bunch of raving fanatics bent on slaughtering every other species.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706645" id2="17" version="1065353216">They are ambitious, crafty. Recently took to ambushing warden droids and stripping away their power cores.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intel suggests they're compiling the stolen power cores into one massive bomb. Probably mean to blast their way out of here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706648" id2="17" version="1065353216">Throw everything you've got at them. Contain them while you still can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706648" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Out of the question. I have my hands full just keeping this station secure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706651" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're as likely to hurt themselves as anyone else. Perhaps they can be reasoned with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you talk sense into them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706652" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Reason&quot; is not a virtue I'd attribute to these guys. Have yet to see them communicate without killing someone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706654" id2="17" version="1065353216">The infrastructure here looks pretty solid. You don't think it'll hold?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706654" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will that work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706655" id2="17" version="1065353216">The walls are reinforced with duracrete, but even they won't withstand a few dozen power core explosions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706657" id2="17" version="1065353216">With any luck, those loonies will cross a wire and blow themselves up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706657" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe they'll screw it up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unlikely. They're crazy, not stupid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pretty resourceful for a bunch of murderous lunatics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706661" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're organized, I'll give them that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then they'll be somebody else's problem. Good riddance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706663" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least they'll be gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706664" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not that simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706666" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Rattataki break free, they'll kill anyone they find--guards, prisoners....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not to mention Senators. You've got to disable that bomb and contain this madness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Rattataki aren't going anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave it to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Splendid! I knew we could count on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706672" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't the colonel do it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ensuring the Senator's immediate safety is my top priority right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706675" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'd probably be best to keep the Rattataki from acquiring any more power cores.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706677" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can retrieve some of the power cores they stole, we should be able to modify the warden droids to prevent future tampering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706679" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dismantling that bomb comes first, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706681" id2="17" version="1065353216">There should be a security terminal somewhere in the area. Report in when you've diffused the bomb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706683" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not my duty. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706684" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see. Far be it from me to force you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706686" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the safest place in the entire wing.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="770626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess I have to go long.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="770629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Barely worth my time.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
