<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>27</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/bronze/chasing_history/hacken_berge.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626975" id2="17" version="1065353216">The history of the Promised Ones is a sad history indeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626976" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would expect any surviving records to be carefully hidden and protected from the elements. Bring your findings to my assistant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would you like a chance to be part of one of the great mysteries of the Republic's past?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626979" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have irrefutable proof that Revan once sheltered here, soon after returning to the Republic from the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626981" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are many tales of how Revan rescued Bastila Shan and changed galactic history, but there were smaller lives touched as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626982" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're talking like these are people I should know about....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="626982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who's Revan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan? The great Jedi general of the Mandalorian Wars? Who turned to the dark side but was brought back to the light by Master Bastila Shan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626985" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shameful! This is why the galaxy needs research like mine, to bring history to life for its people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="626987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you want something?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626988" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Hacken Berge, historian from the Galactic Library on Coruscant. I am undertaking one of the most important historical research projects of our lifetime.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626990" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have time for stories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="626990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Out of my way!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, but surely you have time to take part in one of the great projects of our lifetime.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three hundred years ago, the outcasts of Taris lived deep below the city, where the rakghoul plague originated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan's journals record bringing them a cure for the plague and leading them to a secure colony called &quot;the Promised Land.&quot; Yet we don't know if they survived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you asking me to look for a lost colony from three hundred years ago?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="626996" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want me to find them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or any sign of what became of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="626999" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place is a toxic wasteland. There's no way anyone survived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="626999" id2="17" version="1065353216">They must be dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="627000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then what killed them? And what might that teach us about Taris? If you are braving the wilderness anyway, keep your eyes open.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="627002" id2="17" version="1065353216">My assistant is coordinating excavations. Anything you find, bring to him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="627004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps these Promised Ones left some record--something to talk to us across the ages.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="627006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who cares? [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="627007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those who do not understand history cannot learn from its disasters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="627009" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are so many mysteries to uncover....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
