<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>39</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/bronze/republic/strengthening_the_chain/major_harris.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288721" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our forces in the maximum-security block are finally getting their supplies. We'll lock down this prison in no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288724" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll bet your group struck some fear into those prisoners. Good--they'll be easier to contain.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288726" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt the prisoners were expecting a Jedi's personal attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288728" id2="17" version="1065353216">The prisoners got a taste of their own medicine, courtesy of the Republic's finest.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288730" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there's any justice, those prisoners are soiling themselves and cowering in the jungle.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288732" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll send a fresh resupply team to our forces in the field. We'll have it easier locking things down, thanks to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288734" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once we secure the area, we'll round up that scum and put everyone away for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288738" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only way to reopen our supply lines is by scattering those Rattataki mercenaries and eliminating their leaders. Hurry!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally--reinforcements! Blasted good ones, from the look of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288743" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi--perfect! You're the solution I've been looking for.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major, am I glad to see you! Got a situation right up your alley.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288747" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not Imperial or a prisoner, and you're still alive. Good enough for me! I need your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288749" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're officially outside prison grounds--this part of the jungle was designated for future construction, but it's just outposts and old vaults for now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Problem is, the lack of security means escapees are pouring in from the main wing. They ambush and slaughter my reinforcements, then vanish like ghosts into the vegetation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="288752" id2="17" version="1065353216">These aren't common criminals. Who are they? How do they attack your people and get away so easily?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288752" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288753" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's more Rattataki, but these aren't Blood of Talath. This is a group of mercenary commandos who butchered whole settlements on Obroa-skai.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288755" id2="17" version="1065353216">We captured them alive, dumped them here and threw away the key. Unfortunately, the Empire set them loose.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288757" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Rattataki have survival training and no love for the Republic. Even worse, they looted our supplies. They could hold out indefinitely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288758" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="288759" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we can recover the equipment they stole, it might force them to surrender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288759" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if we take the supplies?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288760" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's too late for that. The prisoners are spread out. They don't have a main camp for us to raid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288762" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have nothing but bad news.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288763" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is one shred of good news in all this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a job for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recruit better soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288767" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are no ordinary prisoners. It's the Rattataki again--this bunch murdered entire settlements on Obroa-skai before we captured them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288769" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intelligence reports indicate the prisoners are led by a few experienced men. Eliminate those leaders, and the others won't have tactical guidance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288771" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can provide the prisoners' last known location. I need you to go in, disperse them and remove their leaders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288773" id2="17" version="1065353216">With your help, we'll lock down Belsavis twice as hard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you prepared to pay me?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't believe you, of all people, would demand payment... I'll think of something--just stop the attacks on my men.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288778" id2="17" version="1065353216">I lead the Ninety-fourth Supply Division. If I don't have what you want, I'll get it. Just deal with that scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288780" id2="17" version="1065353216">The prisoners are hiding in the jungle at these coordinates. They'll have the advantage of terrain and surprise. Be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, I can't. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288783" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast it... at least spread the word we need help here. Maybe someone else can lend a hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, no time. Keeping the supply lines open takes everything I've got.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
