<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>45</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_1/trouble_in_paradise/navigator_uptin.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009407" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything we built, just... crumbling away. And for what, credits?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009408" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show those Hutts who's boss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009414" id2="17" version="1065353216">It takes courage to fly through danger. Trust your instincts, and we'll be fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009414" id2="17" version="1065353216">I commend your bravery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never had a Jedi on my ship before. Wish I'd spruced up the inside a bit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't Makeb's first colonists run into this problem? The interference destroyed their communication equipment, they had to build the colony in isolation....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009417" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know of this interference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009418" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right. Took decades to build a world worth having. Now the Hutts have stole it away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ion shielding, huh? Wouldn't mind some of that. Lots of hot landing zones around the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your shields sound handy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get rid of those Hutts, Major, and our Business Council will buy you a ship ten times nicer than mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Electromagnetic interference... that lightning will shake us like a rattle. You'd better know how to fly this thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009423" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't want to explode.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009424" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've flown five hundred clean insertions, Captain, but you know what they say: There's always a last time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009426" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did the Cartel conquer your planet if most ships can't even get through the atmosphere?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009426" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the Hutts landed an army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009427" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our politicians figured why draft an army when you can hire mercenaries? We bought the best--bunch of hard cases called the InterStellar Regulators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009429" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the Hutts didn't bother fighting them. They bought off the Regulators with a bigger bid. Ask Shalim Avesta, he'll tell you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009431" id2="17" version="1065353216">My shuttle's prepped. Hop aboard, and we'll be on our way. Might want to take your anti-nausea stims, too....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't show off your piloting skills. Just get us down there alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009434" id2="17" version="1065353216">No fancy maneuvers, got it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009439" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm doing cross-checks. Give me a few minutes, all right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047053" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the Republic heroes who've come to free my homeworld? You're all so... wow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047055" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're one of the Republic heroes come to free my homeworld? You're just... wow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047057" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish we'd joined the Republic ages ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047058" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you stand with the Republic, it stands with you. We'll protect you from the Hutts, the Empire and anyone who threatens your freedom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1047058" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's going to be alright.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047059" id2="17" version="1065353216">That means a lot. The past two weeks have been a nightmare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your people could've joined us when the Sith Empire returned to the galaxy. What stopped you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1047061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why did you stay neutral?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047062" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was before my time, but we've always minded our own business and not gotten involved in other peoples' fights. Stupid, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047064" id2="17" version="1065353216">You pledged yourselves to the Republic--but we have our own war to win after this. Makeb will do its part, and then some.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1047064" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll owe us a lot for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047065" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got minerals, riches, hyperspace routes--whatever the Republic needs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047067" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was here when the Hutts blocked all of Makeb's comm channels. Haven't been able to get a signal from my family since. No idea what's happened down there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047068" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts haven't been in control of your world for long. Most likely, your relatives are safe in their homes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1047068" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure your family is safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047069" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I keep telling myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047071" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's only one way to find out--fire up that shuttle's engines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1047071" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll know soon enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047072" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts don't treat conquered people well. If you're lucky, your family members are just slaves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1047072" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prepare for the worst.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'd better get going.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047075" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't know if they told you, but Makeb's atmosphere is a real mess. Most ships get torn to bits by electrical storms on entry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047077" id2="17" version="1065353216">My baby's got special ion shields to absorb the electromagnetic interference, but we're still in for a rough ride. Hopefully we won't land in little pieces.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
