<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>24</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/bronze/republic/back_alley/security_chief.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="938637" id2="17" version="1065353216">A word please? Only take a minute.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="938639" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi, huh? Interesting. Won't ask what you're doing here, but I'm required to give you a warning: Don't leave the tourist area. It's too dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="938641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic military, yeah? Your credits are always welcome, but I'm required to give you a warning: Don't leave the tourist area. It's too dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="938642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your look says you're no stranger to dangerous neighborhoods, but I'm required to give you a warning: Don't leave the tourist area. It's too dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="938643" id2="17" version="1065353216">Traveling in a group is a good idea, but I'm still required to give you a warning: Don't leave the tourist area. It's too dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="938648" id2="17" version="1065353216">Problems in the district?</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="938650" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="938708" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't bother me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="938710" id2="17" version="1065353216">My superior says I have to warn everyone. So I'm warning you. Gang war is heating up: Officially everything past the security droids is off limits.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="938712" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's the Bleeders again. Used to just drag tourists off and harvest a body part or two. Now they're rich, armed and getting ambitious.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="938714" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bleeders have declared war on all the red light gangs and any outsiders. Cartel's official stance is &quot;just let them fight it out.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="939137" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll only get worse that way.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="939138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Works for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="939139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Worst security in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="939140" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you're already smarter than anyone in my chain of command.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="939141" id2="17" version="1065353216">You see what I have to deal with, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="939142" id2="17" version="1065353216">Except that the gangs won't stay contained. If the Bleeders win, they'll want more and more.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="939144" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't want to just stand here and watch my district burn, no matter what the cartel says.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="939148" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got a pile of credits and equipment donated from the local merchants for anyone who wades in there and teaches those Bleeders a lesson in humility. Just saying....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="939153" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have a good time but be safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="939156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bleeders have already contacted the cartel. They want me to negotiate a peace with the other gangs.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="939158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently the Bleeders are under the impression one of the other gangs brought in offworlders who can take down a dozen men at will.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="939160" id2="17" version="1065353216">On an unrelated note, I have a token of affection here from the local merchants' association....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="940892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bleeders are still plenty dangerous. Watch yourself.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
