<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>60</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/voss/world/republic/stolen_treasure/doctor_chull.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71713" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got the research station set up, and thanks to you, we should have those power cores installed soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71715" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've recovered all the power cores. Here you go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71716" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can use these to help the Voss set up a geothermal monitoring station that will last for years. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71718" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mark my words: The Republic will gain more inroads with the Voss through technology than ideology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71719" id2="17" version="1065353216">They could be dangerous if used for other purposes than research.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use the power cores wisely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rest assured, my colleagues and I are more interested in holding the planet together than splitting it apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71722" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was nothing, really.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your humility wouldn't serve you well in science--you should claim your achievements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71725" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because of you, we'll have a research station that brings people together, instead of driving them apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your power cell technology could protect the Voss, if you used it to improve their weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Armaments would be better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71727" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad that not everyone thinks as you do. The beauty of science is that it can create as well as destroy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because of your efforts, we'll have the chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71731" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll be ready for those power cores soon, assuming you recover them before the Gormak wipe us out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71734" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, Master Jedi, welcome. We're still cleaning up after the latest raid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71736" id2="17" version="1065353216">And here comes the military, after everything of value has already been destroyed or stolen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to what's left of our research station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71740" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could try and find you a chair, but I suspect the Gormak will be back sooner rather than later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not that I blame them--Gormak are like any other military culture, abusing science to make better bombs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71743" id2="17" version="1065353216">What would the Gormak want with your station?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would they attack here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71744" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does any military want? They want our advancements to make more powerful weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I can help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71747" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could use a hand; the Gormak smashed anything they didn't want to carry, and left plenty of casualties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Technology keeps our enemies at bay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better bombs ensure peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71750" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd expect that response from a soldier, not that technology's done any good in keeping the Gormak away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71752" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's certainly cowed the Gormak into submission--wait, no it hasn't. It's done rather the opposite.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71754" id2="17" version="1065353216">We brought in some experimental power cores--part of an effort to promote the Voss's science studies--but the Gormak stole them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now instead of being used for geothermal research, they'll be fueling some Gormak war machine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71757" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let the Gormak use them to threaten the Republic or Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71757" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get your cores back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71758" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll want to hurry then--if they install those cores in a new warship, nothing will be able to protect Voss-Ka.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can the cores be used as a weapon?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me more about the cores.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not on their own, no, but they can last for years, which makes them ideal for the Gormak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their war machine isn't a danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71763" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak aren't a threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71764" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a fool to underestimate them, especially while they're stealing our resources.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71766" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're building a starship; these cores would give them a perfect energy source and enough power to obliterate Voss-Ka.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71768" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you really want to help us, get those power cores back. The Republic didn't come here to start a war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71769" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak can't have gone far. I should have your cores back soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71769" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find your power cores.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71770" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those cores could secure our alliance with the Voss. I'll find them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71770" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything to build support.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71771" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those cores are a threat as long as the Gormak have them. That won't be much longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71771" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider the mission done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71772" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you understand the urgency, thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71774" id2="17" version="1065353216">If nothing else, they'll be worth a fortune on the black market.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71774" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find your gizmos for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71775" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic will make it worth your while if you recover them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71777" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see if I find the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71778" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's the best I can hope for, I'll have to accept it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71780" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak have been camping along the ridge. That's probably the best place to look for the raiders that attacked us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71782" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you've got all the power cores, please bring them back here. I'll see to it they're put to their proper use.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71784" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have time to go looking for your research equipment, but I wish you luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71784" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Luck won't save any of us if the Gormak can bomb targets with impunity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, but the Gormak left us quite a mess to clean up. I've got to take inventory and see what we've got left.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
