<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/bronze/imperial/deconstruction_efforts/corporal_xeleste.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="538325" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's back to being blind, deaf and mute like everyone else on Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="538327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those explosives I gave you should be enough to take out the comm array.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="538328" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was supposed to be a simple assignment. You'd think disrupting enemy communications on Hoth would be easy, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="538329" id2="17" version="1065353216">The broadcasting range here is terrible. Better off just shouting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="538331" id2="17" version="1065353216">The weather alone makes transmitting a logistical nightmare. Figured my work was all but done for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="538334" id2="17" version="1065353216">And here I was afraid I'd sent you to your death, pitting you against Aegis Company like that. Felt bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742197" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't count on the Republic building a giant communications array to boost their transmissions. Solved all their broadcasting problems overnight!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thought maybe we could tap into the array, piggyback the signal to boost our own transmissions. But the encryption's too good.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pretty much helpless at this point. Weather's so bad, we'd need a comm array of our own just to transmit a decent jamming signal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best option is to blow the array up, but Aegis Company is garrisoned there. Probably be safer attacking Coruscant with a freighter.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aegis Company hasn't lost an objective in fifteen years. They'll defend the comm array to their dying breaths--or ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742604" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got to disrupt the Republic's communications or they will win this planet. But that means getting past Aegis Company.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742663" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm running out of options, here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742673" id2="17" version="1065353216">That seems too easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742674" id2="17" version="1065353216">The array's antennae amplify and focus the Republic's comm signals--cuts right through all the environmental interference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742794" id2="17" version="1065353216">How will you stop them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tough luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742831" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Aegis troopers are masters of tactical defense. They've held back attacking forces ten times their size with minimal casualties.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742867" id2="17" version="1065353216">You destroyed the comm array? That--that's incredible!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742892" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742893" id2="17" version="1065353216">That array probably cost millions of credits. Doesn't quite gel with the Empire's &quot;minimal effort, maximum gains&quot; strategy on Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you've failed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, my superiors are not going to be happy about this one.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then a suicide run like this was tailor made for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742910" id2="17" version="1065353216">I may have underestimated the Republic's resourcefulness, yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't help you. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742929" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I figured.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742932" id2="17" version="1065353216">I already had the demolitions team rig up some charges. Just plant these on the array and let the explosions handle the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742933" id2="17" version="1065353216">That could be fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742936" id2="17" version="1065353216">I look forward to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me the details.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742938" id2="17" version="1065353216">And here I was afraid I'd sent you to your deaths, pitting you against Aegis Company like that. Felt bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742940" id2="17" version="1065353216">That comm array was a huge investment for the Republic. Can't imagine they'll be eager to build another. Good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742942" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's your problem, not mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="743086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do you say that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="743095" id2="17" version="1065353216">This job won't come free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="743096" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were careless.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="743217" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can pay. Seems worth it to level a multimillion credit structure.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
