<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>99</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/trooper/chapter_3/intro/general_garza.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491894" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've won a major victory, but the war is just beginning. Your squad will be playing a vital role in our campaign against Rakton.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491895" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad is ready to serve, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491895" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're always prepared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad is going to win this war, General. No matter what.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491896" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imps don't stand a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491897" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're counting on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491899" id2="17" version="1065353216">With a record like mine, you get used to the big ops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491899" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm used to the spotlight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right now, we need every advantage we can get--every available force must be put to work to counter the Empire's moves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some of our top military units are bogged down on backwater planets instead of serving on the front lines where they belong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491904" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad is going to get our top forces where they need to be, starting with a group of elite pilots trapped on Belsavis. Understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491905" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll do whatever it takes to get those men into the fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491905" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491906" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's why you're the best in the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you give me any intel on Belsavis, General?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491909" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll discuss the details once you've arrived in orbit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't send me to free up resources, send me to kill Rakton!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491911" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a waste of time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491912" id2="17" version="1065353216">As soon as we know his location, you'll be the first person I contact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our forces are still spread thin. Saving our allies has relieved some pressure, but to turn the tide, we need every advantage we can get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491916" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will not accept defeat at the hands of the Empire. We will defeat them--utterly and completely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491917" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, General!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491918" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to find out what medal they hand out for winning a war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491918" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491919" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not stopping until every last Imp is facedown in the dirt. Time to get started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491919" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was always my plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491922" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major! Stand at ease. It's good to see you again, welcome back!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491924" id2="17" version="1065353216">You remember Supreme Commander Rans. We were reviewing the results of your mission--you did an excellent job on Outpost 256. Congratulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491925" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just glad we could intervene.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491926" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our allies are glad, too. I'll see that Helik receives a commendation of some kind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakton was on the holo when I rescued the heads of state.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491928" id2="17" version="1065353216">I spoke to General Rakton.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. Let him see what you're capable of--let him wonder when it will be his office that you're blasting your way through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491931" id2="17" version="1065353216">If our supposed allies had stood strong for once, I wouldn't have had to waste my time out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491931" id2="17" version="1065353216">It should never have happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491932" id2="17" version="1065353216">Securing the Republic's alliances and saving important heads of state is never a waste of time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491934" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's unfortunate that the Imperials executed Premier Vonn and Archduke Kailur. They were both very popular with their people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491936" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've... ensured their people will remember them as heroes who died defying the Empire. Their memory will set the example for their citizens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491938" id2="17" version="1065353216">As soon as they heard what happened on Outpost 256, our allies began full-scale strikes against the Imperials in their territories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491940" id2="17" version="1065353216">The plan worked just like we'd hoped. When word of the rescue got out, our allies began immediate strikes against the Empire's forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491942" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have your assignment, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491943" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major. Stand at ease. Let's get straight to the situation at hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491945" id2="17" version="1065353216">After we destroyed the Gauntlet, General Rakton called a &quot;diplomatic summit&quot; with the heads of state of several Republic-allied planets along our borders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491947" id2="17" version="1065353216">The summit was held aboard a neutral space station, where Rakton's troops seized the heads of state by force. They are now hostages of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491948" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want Havoc to get the heads of state out of there alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491948" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is a rescue op.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Correct. It's the only way to stop Rakton's plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491951" id2="17" version="1065353216">How does this tie into Rakton's invasion plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491951" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why take hostages?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491952" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Rakton's invasion plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491954" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't have expected anyone to fall for peace talks with the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491954" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a bunch of morons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Public pressure to attend peace talks is quite high. This war has people understandably terrified.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491957" id2="17" version="1065353216">With their leaders held hostage, our allies are allowing Imperial troops to pass through their systems and strike us where we're vulnerable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our forces are at their limit. The Imperials will overwhelm us unless we rescue these heads of state and block Rakton's invasion routes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491960" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's our intel on the hostages' location?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's make it happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we count on our allies to fight once their leaders are safe?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will this rescue really help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once their leaders are back to guide them, I'm confident our allies will fight harder for our cause than ever before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491964" id2="17" version="1065353216">No hostages are worth allowing an invasion, no matter how important they are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our allies gave up too easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491965" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree, but this is the situation we are presented with. &quot;Let them die&quot; isn't the solution our allies want to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491967" id2="17" version="1065353216">The station where the heads of state are being held is called Outpost 256. Imperial security is tight, but we've developed an entry plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Helik, a diplomat for one of these worlds, is flying there to surrender his government's security codes. He's volunteered to sneak your team aboard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491970" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can we minimize the risk to the hostages when we storm the station?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491970" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the plan once aboard?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491971" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Yuun will be responsible for that portion of the plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491973" id2="17" version="1065353216">It takes a lot of guts to fly into a hostage situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491973" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a brave diplomat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, he's taking a great risk for us. Let's make the most of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491976" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like relying on a diplomat with no combat experience.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds risky to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491977" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are no other options. Time is critical, and Helik is an opportunity we can't afford to pass up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your ship will ride alongside Helik's, detaching at the last second and landing in an unused maintenance hangar aboard the station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Yuun will slice into the station's security and stop any alarms from sounding while you storm the crew area and secure the hostages. Understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491982" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready to begin immediately, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491983" id2="17" version="1065353216">This one will be easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491984" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fighting through the elite commandos that have seized the station should give you plenty of exercise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those fat bureaucrats will be back in their palaces in no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get this over with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491987" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are valued allies of the Republic, Major. Try to show them some respect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Helik will rendezvous with you at these coordinates. The Imperials are expecting him to deliver his security codes very soon, so move quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember: The safety of the Republic depends entirely on the safety of these men. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major. This is General Garza. I need you to report to my office on Coruscant immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491995" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Rakton made his move--the Imperials have invaded dozens of Republic planets. Havoc Squad is needed--immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there a plan for dealing with this invasion, General?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491996" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's our counteroffensive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would've been nice to have a real break for once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="491997" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was just starting to relax.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="491998" id2="17" version="1065353216">The real breaks come when this invasion ends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492000" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should be with our troops on the ground, not chatting in your office!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="492000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send me to the fight!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let the standard forces handle the standard fighting. Havoc has a more specific target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492003" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll brief you on the details when you arrive. Move quickly. Garza out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="492005" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you've just completed another major operation, but our situation is critical.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
