<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>26</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/trooper/chapter_3/intro/yuun.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511357" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have reached the passage from maintenance to the crew area. Yuun now controls this door and all others, along with all security measures.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511359" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will be the only one able to pass from each room to the next. All Imperials will experience... technical difficulties.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Life-sign scanners show many, many guards within the crew area. The battle to reach the hostages we seek is sure to be fierce, Major--please journey cautiously.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="511362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for the heads-up, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="511362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will do.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511363" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is Yuun's honor to contribute.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="511365" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready for anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="511366" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you've got full control, couldn't you vent the atmosphere in the guards' rooms?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="511366" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't you thin their numbers?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, the station's systems lack such precision. Yuun could vent the atmosphere from the entire crew area, but this would be undesirable.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511369" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun will contact you in case of any developments. Good luck--Yuun out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our work reaches full fruition. You may proceed to the crew area access door, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511375" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another success. You are as the landslide obstructing a river's flow, sending its waters into the path we dictate. Our work will soon be complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511377" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admirably done, Major. The first system components now fall into our control.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511379" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major. Our landing has concluded successfully without gaining enemy attentions. Yuun is now prepared to carry out this mission's technical requirements.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511381" id2="17" version="1065353216">The terminal Yuun requires lies just outside of our ship. It will grant Yuun preliminary access to the station's security systems.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511383" id2="17" version="1065353216">However, to gain full control, other terminals nearby must be destroyed, so that their functions will be routed here. For this, Yuun relies on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="511384" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find the other terminals and take them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="511384" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="511385" id2="17" version="1065353216">Huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511386" id2="17" version="1065353216">To prevent discovery of our rescue attempt and subsequent injury to the hostages we seek, several terminals here in the maintenance area must be destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="511388" id2="17" version="1065353216">Garza didn't say anything about destroying terminals, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="511388" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't part of the plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511389" id2="17" version="1065353216">A map does not always show exactly how a path might turn. The signs are clear--we must deviate from the details of our plan to accomplish its essence.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun will ensure that the terminals' destruction goes unnoticed. Do not fear alerting the Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="511393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun is prepared to begin when you are, Major. May our path lead us to victory.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
