<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>267</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/war_world/quesh/world/imperial/venemous_war/moff_dracen.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505152" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to you, Quesh is nearly under Imperial rule. All that remains is the Republic army's complete annihilation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505156" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi and his Hutt are dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505157" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent! The Republic will be furious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505160" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Fraal's dead. Broga's still breathing, but is sworn to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505161" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent! I'd prefer the Hutt dead, but his cooperation will further infuriate the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505163" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have my thanks, and that of my council. We'd still be fighting over Quesh's mines if not for your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505164" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to thank me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your dedication won't be ignored. And if you're still invested in our war, there's more work to be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505167" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does the Empire have something in store for this planet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505167" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happens to Quesh now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505168" id2="17" version="1065353216">In time we will take over the Quesh venom industry. As for our military, there's still plenty to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505170" id2="17" version="1065353216">My talents are unsurpassed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505171" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't agree more. That is why Quesh still needs you.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="505173" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's still fighting. Help us pile up enough bodies here, they'll retaliate on other planets. Then we'll have our war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505175" id2="17" version="1065353216">But first enjoy your victory. Quesh will soon be ours, and the Republic grows more furious by the day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505179" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic thinks Master Fraal can save them. Prove them wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505182" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have a Hutt on the loose--Broga, the last leader of the Three Families. He escaped before your assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505184" id2="17" version="1065353216">As if losing that Hutt slime wasn't enough, we have a new problem. A powerful Jedi Master named Berin Fraal just landed on Quesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fraal was talking to the Hutts when I arrived. He didn't appreciate the interruption.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505185" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know. I met the Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505186" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must have scared him. Master Fraal is wasting no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505188" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're digging in for something big. We better hit them first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505188" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's regrouping.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505189" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll deploy our army at once. Master Fraal mustn't have time to strike.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505191" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's already amassing forces with Broga the Hutt. Slay them both, and the Republic's stranglehold on Quesh will crumble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505192" id2="17" version="1065353216">They will bow to my power. Then they will die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505192" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you wish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505193" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, my lord. Show the Republic how weak they are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505195" id2="17" version="1065353216">This planet will soon belong to the Empire. Leave the details to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505195" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't live another day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505196" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll bag the Jedi and his Hutt pet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505196" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're as good as dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505197" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll give it a shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505198" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do your best to kill them. That's all I ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505200" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll kill 'em for the credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505201" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assure you, the Empire will pay well for their deaths.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505203" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quesh deserves some peace. If that means killing these agitators, so be it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505203" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything to end this battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505204" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't forget--we're here to spark war, not extinguish it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505206" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find Master Fraal and Broga in the Quesh venom plant. Tear the facility apart. Make sure they don't leave the place alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505207" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll both die by my hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505208" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was hoping you'd jump at their throats.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Fraal's hiding out with Broga the Hutt. They're in the central Quesh venom processing plant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505212" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tear that plant apart. Kill the Jedi and his Hutt friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505223" id2="17" version="1065353216">Moff Dracen--I'm patched in to the Hutt's mainframe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505224" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is it--everything the Three Families knew about processing Quesh venom. We can erase the Republic's head-start in minutes!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505225" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fantastic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505226" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire owes you much. Thanks to you, the Republic is quickly losing control of Quesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505228" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take your word for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505229" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me. Our top researchers will pour over these findings. I can't thank you enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505231" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where's your gratitude?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, of course. The Republic will be furious once we use this data to ramp up our own Quesh venom operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505236" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see you've killed Jeelta and Portho. Outstanding. I wish there was time to celebrate, but our fight's not over yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505238" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see you've killed Jeelta and... Portho? You're still alive?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505240" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? Oh, hello, Moff. Just took a few adrenals. Care to join me?</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="505242" id2="17" version="1065353216">Foolish slug. I suppose we can use him--after we fix his adrenal habit. But our fight's not over yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505244" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kill the Republic's Hutt friends, and the Three Families will fall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505245" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without adrenals or their Quesh venom supply, the Republic is finally vulnerable! We must hit the Three Families with everything we have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Slay the Hutt slime, their secrets die with them--the Republic can't process Quesh venom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505249" id2="17" version="1065353216">And they'll be pushed to the brink of galactic war. All we must do is kill the leaders of the Three Families.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505250" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts will fall under my lightsaber.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505250" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will lead the assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505251" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I'm through, the Hutts will beg me to kill them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505251" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll slay them myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505252" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you're so eager, my lord. We'll prepare for your attack at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505254" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hutts make easy targets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505254" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll execute them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505255" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one is better equipped for the job. We'll prepare for your operation immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505257" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want these Hutts dead? Pay me their weight in credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505257" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three bounties will cost you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505258" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see that your payment matches the prey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505260" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got the Republic on edge. The Hutts will be well-guarded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505260" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll anticipate our attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505261" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed. We have an inside contact who should help us level the playing field.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is killing them necessary?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505264" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have no choice. Showing the Three Families mercy weakens our position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel, wake Portho the Hutt from whatever adrenal-addled haze he's drowning in.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Moff Dracen? Should've known you'd attack soon--and during my afternoon adrenals!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad my compatriots just upped security. There's no getting past the front doors now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your pathetic Hutt defenses can't stop a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing will hold me back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505272" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even the best security can be bypassed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505272" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll see about that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505273" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could try taking out the main gate's shields. But there's another way...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505275" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've busted down plenty of doors. This won't be any different.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wanna bet?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505276" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't mean it's impossible. There's just another way you could get in...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prove your worth, Portho. There must be another entrance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there an alternate way in?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well--I suppose there is one thing we could try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505281" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember, Portho: A useless Hutt is a dead Hutt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505281" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then why do we need you alive?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505282" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be hasty! I can work something out!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505284" id2="17" version="1065353216">My Chevin adviser, Norvaan Kel--he could smuggle a small group past security using my best adrenals.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505286" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're strong enough for Hutts--you'll be knocked out cold. Norvaan can give you the adrenal then sneak you in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505287" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather not be comatose in the middle of a firefight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505287" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems risky.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505288" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be awakened once inside. And the after effects are clean, I promise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505290" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll pay if this is a trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505291" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's the truth. Hutt's honor!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505293" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could use some shut-eye before slaughtering your friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505293" id2="17" version="1065353216">I love a nap before murder.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505294" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so. I'll make the arrangements, just in case.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505296" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll take your recommendation under advisement, Portho. Use your adrenals. When you awake, you'll be the only surviving member of the Three Families.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505298" id2="17" version="1065353216">You heard the fool: either fight through the front, or take Portho's adrenals and be smuggled in. Your choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505299" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutt can keep his concoction. I'd rather fight on my feet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505299" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer a direct fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505300" id2="17" version="1065353216">Portho gave us schematics on the palace's security. You'll need these EMP charges to scramble the generators shielding the main door.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505302" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. Once you're inside, kill the leaders of the Three Families--Portho, too. Then upload their data on Quesh venom processing to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505304" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take the Hutt's concoction. Best to save my energy for the fight inside the palace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505304" id2="17" version="1065353216">The adrenal's the safest path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505305" id2="17" version="1065353216">Norvaan Kel's hiding out behind the palace grounds. Security should be light during the battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505307" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take that Chevin's adrenal to infiltrate the palace. Once inside, kill the leaders of the Three Families--including Portho. Then transmit their data on Quesh venom processing to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505311" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just spoke with Graag. He said you shut down the factories, and the fight's under control. Well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505313" id2="17" version="1065353216">The factories won't fall without you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505314" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our next move is to hit the Republic again. Hard.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, Imps. Graag the Hutt is here. You ready?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505318" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send him in. Quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Graag is a leader of the Hutt Cartel. He keeps repulsive company, but he's proven a valuable ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505321" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can take down the next target without Hutt interference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505321" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need his help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505322" id2="17" version="1065353216">That may be. But we can't afford to turn away Graag's support just yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505324" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is a Hutt working with the Empire?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505324" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's an ally?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505325" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could say Graag was forced to cooperate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never trust a Hutt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry--Graag is dependable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505330" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's here to make amends for the Three Families, a band of venom-sniffing Hutts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505332" id2="17" version="1065353216">They violated the Cartel's neutrality to help the Republic's mining operation on Quesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such favoritism deeply upset the Empire. The Cartel claimed ignorance and disowned the Three Families.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505335" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the rogue Hutts isolated, all that's left is the killing blow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505335" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Three Families are doomed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505336" id2="17" version="1065353216">But first we must sever their source of income: the Republic's adrenal factories. Only then can we destroy the Three Families.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505337" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure they took kickbacks from the Three Families and looked the other way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505337" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Cartel must have known.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505338" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're probably right. To make amends, the Cartel sent Graag--one of their finest leaders--to help us punish the Three Families.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spare me the Hutt trivia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505340" id2="17" version="1065353216">I simply remind you that the Empire's not alone. As a Cartel leader, Graag kindly &quot;volunteered&quot; to help us punish the Three Families.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't mention those traitors! They make my blood boil!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505344" id2="17" version="1065353216">Graag, good of you to join us! Allow me to introduce our newest allies on Quesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gaze upon me, Hutt. You won't see someone so powerful again in your lifetime.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505345" id2="17" version="1065353216">The honor is yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505346" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd ask you to bow to my magnificence, but... well, you know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505346" id2="17" version="1065353216">The honor is yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505347" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've made quite the impression on Quesh, Sith. Finally, we'll have the Force on our side as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505349" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a pleasure, Graag. Imperial Intelligence will be glad to hear of your cooperation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505349" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm watching you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505350" id2="17" version="1065353216">I--I understand. Good to have your organization's support.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505352" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've dealt with your kind before. Don't try me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505352" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch yourself, slug.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505353" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought I recognized you. Nem'ro's friend, right? If his stories are true, I'm glad you're on our side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505355" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, Graag.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505356" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pleasure's mine. But I'm afraid I bring bad news--our forces are in trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505358" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't sign on for handshakes. What's the next target?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505358" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's stick to business.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="505359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi have joined the defense of the Republic's factories. Even the Cartel's droid army can't maintain the assault for long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505361" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Three Families won't be vulnerable until we sever their income. Are you ready to kill these Jedi and cripple the Republic's adrenal production?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to hit the Republic where it hurts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505363" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess I'm ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get too excited.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505366" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will be too easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't discount the Republic's strength. They're far more familiar with Quesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505369" id2="17" version="1065353216">Graag--have your army hold the factories. Don't allow the Republic a second's rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505371" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cut down the Jedi defenders. Then either destroy the adrenal production lines or kill the Selkath scientists operating them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505372" id2="17" version="1065353216">The scientists chose the wrong day to show up for work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505372" id2="17" version="1065353216">No Selkath will survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505373" id2="17" version="1065353216">The scientists are just doing their job. I'll cripple their equipment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505373" id2="17" version="1065353216">The machinery will fail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505374" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's your choice. Just don't return until those factories have ground to a halt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505376" id2="17" version="1065353216">Graag, you finally grace us with your presence! Let me introduce the Empire's greatest weapon on Quesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505380" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mines are poisoned. The Republic's running scared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505381" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent work. You also did a fine job razing their emplacements. My forces will have no trouble cleaning up your scraps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505383" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fantastic. We won't give them a chance to recover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505385" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's held Quesh for too long. Rip those mines from their grasp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505388" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire can't afford another loss, major. We must crush the Republic immediately!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505390" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've been on Quesh for years--we can't destroy their entire mining operation overnight!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505392" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gentlemen. We have company.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505394" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Moff Dracen. Head of Quesh Imperial forces. You're here to join our war against the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505395" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lightsaber's itching for Republic victims.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505395" id2="17" version="1065353216">War? I can't wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not just join--I'll win it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider me your best weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505397" id2="17" version="1065353216">This operation's under control. We don't need Sith running wild down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505398" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insult the dark side. Sith love that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505398" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh good. I smell a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505399" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't pass up the Empire's favorite pastime.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Correct, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505400" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperial military has the situation well in hand. We don't need Intelligence down here playing games!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505401" id2="17" version="1065353216">No games. Just tell me who to kill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505401" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep things simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505402" id2="17" version="1065353216">My rates skyrocket during wartime.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505402" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure, but it'll cost you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505403" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure we can work out a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505405" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire has the situation in hand. We don't need stinking mercenaries to win!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your forces are nothing compared to the power of the dark side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505406" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you do need a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505407" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, Major. I keep my companions on a tight leash.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505407" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep my people in line.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505408" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not my point. The Empire can win this war!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505410" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire must use all of its assets to crush the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505412" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the conflict.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quesh is a valuable planet, if you can believe it. We're here to stop the Republic's operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505415" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's your war, not mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quesh is valuable. To the Republic, and to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505418" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is absurd! We don't need their kind interfering with our war!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505419" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's more power in my fist than in your entire army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh really? [Force Choke]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me remind you of the dark side's power, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh really? [Shock him]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your manners need polish, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that so? [Punch him]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505427" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe a broken jaw will improve your perspective.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505427" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh really? [Punch him]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough. Save it for the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505432" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose you have your own victory plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505432" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go on, major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505433" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right. My men take the mines, make the Republic panic. Then we propose a truce and ambush their leaders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quaint theatrics won't work. Brutality, carnage--that's how you break the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505437" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a pitiful display.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505438" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't stand for this outrage!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505440" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, you will, major. Take your anger out on the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505442" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're responsible for our assignment to this toxic rock. The Republic went digging and found the source of this planet's poison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505444" id2="17" version="1065353216">The miners call it &quot;Quesh venom.&quot; Lies just below the planet's surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505446" id2="17" version="1065353216">We distill the stuff into Quell, a lethal poison. But the Republic knows how to refine it into high-grade adrenals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505448" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've been processing the toxins into adrenals for years, with Hutt help no less. We've come to conquer their operation and claim Quesh's venom for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505449" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tear down the Republic. Grind them into Quesh's soil.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505449" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroy them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turn Quesh into a monument of Imperial cruelty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make the Republic suffer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505451" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you'd have the appetite for this work. The Republic's defeat must be devastating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Carve their defeat into Quesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make a show of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505454" id2="17" version="1065353216">My goal exactly. Their ruin must be cataclysmic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505456" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this is Republic territory, they won't go down easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505456" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a tall order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505457" id2="17" version="1065353216">But they will be ruined. The Empire won't settle for less.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505459" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire wouldn't wage war on this scale just for resources.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505459" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're after something else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Correct. The adrenals are a bonus. Our primary goal is to test the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yet the Republic's still here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505463" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's downfall must be cataclysmic. Devastation on that level takes time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Push them enough on Quesh, and the Republic will be provoked into open warfare across the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once they violate the Treaty of Coruscant, the Empire can strike without risking neutral worlds joining in. We must rile their temper.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505468" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a talent for rousing the Republic's fury.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me anger them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505469" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't wait to see you test their restraint.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Provoking them to all-out war won't be easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505471" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll be hard to push.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505472" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's why we must bend them to their breaking point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Politics aren't my concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me rephrase. We must goad the Republic into open warfare. Help, and you'll be compensated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505477" id2="17" version="1065353216">First, we strike the Republic's venom mines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505479" id2="17" version="1065353216">The venom produces noxious gas. That's why Quesh is so lovely. It's most lethal in the mines, so the Republic installed specialized filters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505481" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroy those filters, release the poisonous gas, and the Republic will have to flee the mines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505482" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll declare the mines a disaster site when I'm finished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505483" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm kind of busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't delay. Our forces already siege the mines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take out every weapon emplacement you can, then get inside and destroy the filtration units. Don't stop until the mines are choked with poison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="505488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count me out. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'll proceed according to plan. Enjoy your time on Quesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough! We don't need his help!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't waste your energy on her. A woman has no place on the battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505493" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a private council. Leave us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful--the Republic's discovered Portho's treachery. Hurry, before the Hutts escape!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="505497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Portho fulfilled his promise, for once. Consider these mercenaries his payment for your mercy.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
