<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>54</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/jedi_knight/chapter_1/the_defector/master_satele_shan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640972" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did well bringing Kira to us, but you're needed elsewhere. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele, my mission has become more complicated. Masters Orgus and Kiwiiks have disappeared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640976" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm headed for Tatooine and Alderaan to find them, but first, my Padawan has something important to tell you. Kira?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640977" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was born on Dromund Kaas. My parents were Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whew! Much easier the second time. There's more, obviously.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640981" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should hope so. Give me time to assemble the Council. Most of us are still offworld....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640983" id2="17" version="1065353216">...and then my Master convinced me to come here and tell you. That's pretty much everything</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640985" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've heard rumors about these Children of the Emperor before, but this finally confirms their existence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Troubling, that we never sensed the truth about Kira when Master Kiwiiks brought her to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640989" id2="17" version="1065353216">That makes her especially dangerous. She's can't be allowed to remain free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kira's Master should have a voice in this. What do you recommend?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640992" id2="17" version="1065353216">The situation doesn't require a reaction. I just thought you should know the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640993" id2="17" version="1065353216">And now that we know, we can't ignore the threat she represents to our entire order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640995" id2="17" version="1065353216">I brought her to you because I wasn't sure what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Honestly, I don't know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our path is clear. The girl is dangerous. She lied to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640998" id2="17" version="1065353216">To allow her to remain a Padawan--become a Jedi Knight? It's inconceivable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it? Did we not first learn of the Children of the Emperor from a Sith turned to the light?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Braga speaks the truth. No one is beyond redemption.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arrest and interrogate her. Find out what she's still hiding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="641003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imprison her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly. Contain the threat until we understand it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi are not jailers, Master Kaedan. It's obvious she's told us everything she knows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641008" id2="17" version="1065353216">I reached out through the Force while Kira spoke. I detected sadness and confusion. Not malice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. Despite her origins, I feel no trace of the dark side within her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641012" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was natural for you to fear our reaction, considering your upbringing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641014" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's important now is that you leave your past behind and devote yourself to the Jedi. Can you do that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641016" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been trying to ever since Master Kiwiiks found me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kira's a good Padawan. I trust her with my life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="641017" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641018" id2="17" version="1065353216">There you have it. I need no further proof of Kira's loyalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641020" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you think, Masters? Should Kira remain my Padawan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="641020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should Kira stay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641021" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see no reason to punish a student who admits her error.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641023" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have time for debates. I need you people to make a decision.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="641023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get this over with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641024" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's right. Darth Angral is still out there. We must act.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641026" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's right. Darth Angral is still out there. We must act.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed--and I believe the best course of action is to leave Kira where she is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641030" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a mistake. If Master Kiwiiks were here, she'd tell you the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641032" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until she returns, this Council's ruling stands. Kira is safest in your care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641033" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate you giving her another chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="641033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641034" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're right about this, Master Satele.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="641034" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Release your worries. Kira has earned our trust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641037" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Emperor's Children hunt her again, what do you expect from me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="641037" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if more Sith come?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641038" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must learn more. Seize every opportunity to acquire knowledge about these people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641040" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's how I can make amends, I'll do whatever it takes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641042" id2="17" version="1065353216">I promise I'll make you all proud... even you, Master Kaedan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641044" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did well bringing this to us, but you should return to your mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="641046" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you on Tatooine and Alderaan....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
