<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>25</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/bonus_series/republic/jace_malcolm.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work taking out those mercs. If there's one thing I can't stand, it's thugs pretending they're soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103745" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're leaving a big impression on the mercenary forces. We're intercepting panic transmissions. Makes my day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice op. There's nothing wrong with these mercs a few kilos of detonite can't fix.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast those mercs... not even the Empire treats slaves that badly. We'll evac the survivors to Keylander Station for emergency medical treatment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103748" id2="17" version="1065353216">My scouts report merc forces abandoning their posts at the other slave camps. They're running scared--and the civilians are running to evac shuttles.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103749" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Science Office big brains are receiving sensor readings from the planet's core. Let's hope they can explain why Makeb isn't an asteroid field.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103752" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you just insured you'll be getting fan mail for the rest of your life. We'll get the civilians to an evac zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad you could free those civilians before the mercs got to them. Those people have been through enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103754" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was one tough merc leader--but he picked the wrong fight. I hope the other scum are paying attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103755" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice work. Just ID'd that merc leader. He was on the SIS &quot;most wanted&quot; list. I'll make sure you get the credit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work gathering that intel. The more we know about Imperial forces on Makeb, the harder we can hit them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103757" id2="17" version="1065353216">Getting solid intel on Imperial movements, thanks to you. My Stratcom team is already analyzing it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103760" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least we know the mesa isn't collapsing anytime soon. Your work on that detection grid paid off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get in there and be quick. There's no telling when that mesa will collapse!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103764" id2="17" version="1065353216">The data you found in that merc base revealed a location where civilian survivors are trapped. Get to those people before the mercs do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work uploading that data on Aboro Mesa. It revealed coordinates to supply depots. We can use what's there to aid our rescue efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103770" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scouts report the mercs diverted forces to those drilling platforms you disrupted. That should make this op easier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice work liberating all those mercenary speeders. We're transporting them to the mesa now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those manifests you secured show trapped civilians nearby. The mercs are leaving them cooped-up there like banthas. Let's get them free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103779" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got the mercs chasing their own tails. They moved a bunch of defense turrets from this zone to that abandoned drill site you already secured. Too bad for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use the flare gun you picked up and signal for reinforcements. They'll come running.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103783" id2="17" version="1065353216">Outstanding mission success. We've put the mercs on notice--now it's time to drive the point home. I'm transmitting special mission coordinates. Get there ASAP.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103784" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've made it clear Makeb is a Republic world. Now let's finish what we started here. My team has found a major target. Follow the coordinates I'm sending.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103787" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Nice work&quot; doesn't even cover it. They'll be teaching this op at the officer academy. I'm transmitting new mission orders and coordinates. Stay alert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work! You've earned some downtime after this op. Head back to the station for a full debriefing.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
