<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>13</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/bonus_series/republic/mission_terminal.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111893" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

Reports of suspected Imperial activity have tended to revolve around Makeb's abandoned mining mesa.

See what they were up to there, if anything, and if they're still active in the area. Reconfigure security measures on the site to look for signs of humanoid activity, and then pull the operations log from the drill's computers.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111894" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

Former Regulators are closely guarding records that detail the locations of their military assets on Makeb. These records can be accessed from one of three locations on Aboro Mesa, but signal jammers prevent data transmission offworld.

Gain access to a Regulator orbital platform to call down strikes on one of these jammers and then transmit the data to Keylander Station.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111895" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

Republic scientists have been unable to determine exactly why Makeb has stabilized. The best means of gathering data will be to access the planet's core via the mining drill sites on the former Cartel Mining Mesa.

Dispatch probes to scan the sites and then relay their data back to Keylander Station.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111896" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

A group of former Regulators on Makeb have called on various extraplanetary forces--Mandalorians, assassin droids and fallen Jedi, mostly--to help them take control of the planet. These forces are reaching the planet via a ground-to-atmosphere turbolift called a &quot;gravity hook.&quot;

Ambush the potential Regulator allies arriving at Gravity Hook Four before they can make their way off the mesa.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111897" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

According to debriefs from Protector rescue squads, Perekta Mesa was among those hardest hit by Makeb's groundquakes, and its citizens were least likely to have made it to the Ark.

Check the mesa's current state of stability and look for signs of life. Armed with your findings, the Protectors will be able to mount an effective rescue mission.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111898" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

Many of Makeb's citizens were unable to reach the Ark before its launch. Some couldn't make it because they were shot down by ex-Regulator forces on Telemur Mesa, who are keeping the civilians imprisoned.

Retrieve the shuttle manifests from the Regulators while doing what you can to limit these mercenaries' capabilities in the area.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111899" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

Information obtained from Aboro Mesa has revealed that former Regulators are using Stronghold One--Makeb's former treasury vault--as the information hub of their civilian slaving operations. 

Infiltrate Stronghold One, which is built into a volcanic mesa. Download the tracking data being used to capture and enslave the people of Makeb, and then destroy the facility.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111900" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

A particularly heinous band of former Regulators situated on the Fingers has been shooting down and looting civilian shuttles headed for a refugee camp.

Draw out these Regulators by fabricating and activating a shuttle distress beacon at one of the shuttle wreckage sites to keep them from doing harm to any more civilians.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111901" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

Due to the heavy presence of former Regulator forces in the area, a remote village located on Frinn Mesa remains almost entirely unevacuated. These civilians need our help.

Commandeer speeder bikes from the Regulator forces and go door to door to release the civilians from their homes so they can flee to safety.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111903" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

Protector scouting reports indicate that some civilians living on Perekta Mesa are still trapped inside their homes. Due to the mesa's continued state of instability, these civilians may not have much time left.

Clear the debris that is blocking the civilians' escape so that the Protectors can mount an operation to evacuate them from Perekta Mesa.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111904" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

The information you obtained from the abandoned drill site suggests that Imperials have been operating in and around the estate of mining executive Solida Hesk. A Republic scouting team was sent to investigate, but has not been heard from since.

Complete the original team's investigation, and also locate the missing scouts if you can.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111905" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

The Regulators who once protected Talaos City are now using civilian shuttles loaded with evacuees as target practice fodder. Our forces are ready to perform missile strikes on the Regulators' anti-air guns, but precise guidance will be needed to remove the possibility of harming any remaining civilians.

Visit shuttle crash sites to determine the location of the anti-air guns and target them using the macrobinoculars provided at the Republic landing zone outside Talaos City.

-- END --</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111906" id2="17" version="1065353216">-- REPUBLIC MISSION ALERT -- OFFICIAL --
-- By Authority of Supr. Cmdr. Jace Malcom --

Pollus Avesta, a prominent resistance fighter and brother of Shalim Avesta, is being held hostage by former Regulators who are aware of Avesta's political value. It is important that we rescue Avesta and his extended family from captivity in the Westwater settlements.

Destroy and scan Regulator hovertanks for any relevant data that may reveal the Avestas' whereabouts. Also be sure to have transportation ready for their escape.

-- END --</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
