<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>58</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/bonus_series/republic/t6d4.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1103241" id2="17" version="1065353216">T6-D4 = patching you through // Supreme Commander Jace Malcom = standing by!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103243" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was impressive soldiering you did on Makeb. Lot of former slaves would like to shake your hand right now. Lot of former mercenaries are wishing they'd never met you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103244" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a big planet. I doubt we found every mercenary outpost and refugee zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103244" id2="17" version="1065353216">We didn't get everyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103245" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed, which is why my scouts won't stop looking until they've ID'd them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we know what stopped Makeb from tearing itself apart?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did we solve Makeb's mystery?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103248" id2="17" version="1065353216">The big brains will be analyzing the data for months. A shame we haven't got that much time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103250" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did we figure out why Imperial forces are sniffing around?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103250" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the Empire?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103251" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think they're still after Isotope-5. One more reason we won't be leaving anytime soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103253" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now the bad news... sensors detect toxic gas from the core filling Makeb's atmosphere. We're projecting the planet's air will be unbreathable in weeks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103255" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can forget about resettling Makeb--but there's still plenty of work to do down there. Hope you'll stick around and lend a hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103257" id2="17" version="1065353216">I look forward to serving with you again. Supreme Commander Malcom out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1103260" id2="17" version="1065353216">You + Supreme Commander Jace Malcom = T6 favorite heroes!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1103262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your team = Heroes of Makeb + greatest Republic warriors // T6 = not worthy of this interaction!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1103264" id2="17" version="1065353216">You = Hero of Makeb + great Republic champion // T6 = not worthy of this interaction!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1103266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Priority incoming transmission = Supreme Commander Jace Malcom // You = stand by?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lucky I caught you bunch, before the Propaganda Office commandeers you for every morning news holovid from Coruscant to Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi... I've never paid my proper respects for all the beat-downs you've handed the enemy. Hoping you can spare a few more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103272" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi... I'm told you're the Order's expert on unexplained mysteries. Got a doozy for you. Hoping you can solve it quick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major... I need you to form up Havoc Squad, pack all the ammo your troops can carry and prep for immediate transport.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103276" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain... I'm sure you'd like to get back to whatever it is you do for a living, but the Republic still needs your service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad I caught you before the holovid chat circuit did. We might want to hold off giving interviews about our latest operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103280" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something's happened on Makeb. More accurately, it didn't happen. Scout teams report the planet has stabilized. The groundquakes and volcanic eruptions have all subsided.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103282" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Science Office big brains can't explain it. All we know is, Makeb isn't tearing itself apart anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103283" id2="17" version="1065353216">We wouldn't be talking if you were calling with good news. There's a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103283" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's still trouble, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103284" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lots of problems, actually.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103286" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps we won't need to find Makeb's people a new homeworld, after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103286" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's good news for refugees.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103287" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think that's what Madame Chancellor is hoping, but the planet's already being resettled.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103289" id2="17" version="1065353216">All due respect, Supreme Commander, but what are you expecting Havoc Squad to do? Point blasters at Makeb until it starts talking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103289" id2="17" version="1065353216">So send a science team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Answers aren't the only things I need. You'll have plenty to keep you busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103292" id2="17" version="1065353216">You would not believe all the valuables I was forced to leave behind just in Toborro's Palace alone. I'm gonna need a bigger ship....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great! I can loot the place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103293" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not calling you for a salvage run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103295" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ark barely escaped before that mesa blew sky-high.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103295" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we saw it exploding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103296" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turns out that was an isolated incident. Good thing, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103298" id2="17" version="1065353216">All that means is, it's probably waiting to blow up when we least expect it. I'm not risking my life there again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103298" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not going back there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103299" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if I told you there were people still alive on Makeb?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103301" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Hutts swallowed that treaty you forced down their throats, they abandoned their mercs planetside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103303" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mercs are making the most of having survived. They've taken over Makeb and enslaved thousands of civilian refugees who we thought were dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those people were counting on us to get them to safety. We have to finish what we started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103304" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't leave them behind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103305" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you might take a personal interest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103307" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even if we free the slaves, we have no way to get them off the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103307" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we evacuate them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103308" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought the impossible was your specialty. Don't worry, there's a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Typical mercenaries. The moment they're unemployed, they turn into exactly the kind of people they're hired to shoot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1103310" id2="17" version="1065353216">That filthy merc scum!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103311" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure the irony isn't lost on their victims. It's time we put these akk dogs down permanently.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103313" id2="17" version="1065353216">One more thing... scouts report Imperial forces are on Makeb. That's why I'm commanding this mission personally. I want answers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1103315" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've sliced the planet's comm network. When you land on Makeb, I'll keep in touch. Head to the coordinates I'm transmitting for further orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1103318" id2="17" version="1065353216">T6-D4 = big fan // You = hero!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
