<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/spvp/announcers/deathmatch.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128363" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let this be a reminder to our enemies: the Empire does not lose. Excellent work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128364" id2="17" version="1065353216">The wargame is now complete. Your squadron gets the win. Excellent work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128365" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been routed! Get out of there! Now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128366" id2="17" version="1065353216">That did not go well for your squadron. You'll have to try harder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128367" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's it. The wargame's done. You did your best, but it just wasn't enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128368" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone, fall back! We can fight this fight another day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128369" id2="17" version="1065353216">The results of this wargame will provide crucial data to Imperial strategists. Move in and tear them apart!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your enemy's gaining the upper hand!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast it! You're letting the odds turn in their favor!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128379" id2="17" version="1065353216">You cannot allow them to hold that advantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128386" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let their new advantage rattle you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128387" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their fighters took an objective. Buckle down, team!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128388" id2="17" version="1065353216">They just got an edge on you, but I know you can weather it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128402" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aygo here. Sometimes there's nothing like a good old-fashioned blast-'em-up. Two squadrons and one goal: take the other team down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128403" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Fleet Admiral Aygo. We can deal a major blow to the enemy here if we just take out their squadron.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128411" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've identified key objectives that will be of some help, but your real targets are those fighters--remember that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128422" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're almost there. Press the attack!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128424" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's nearly over. You have to turn the tide!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128435" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're just about done here. Don't let up!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128438" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can still win this thing, but there isn't much time!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128442" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victory's almost yours--keep fighting!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time is running short. Annihilate them!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay strong out there and watch each other's backs! Show them what you're made of!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128452" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got some leverage now, team. Don't let it go to waste!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch for helpful objectives along the way, but don't get hung up on them. Your skill on offense is what's being tested here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128455" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take this advantage and run with it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let the wargame commence, and may the best squad win!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128458" id2="17" version="1065353216">Objective secured. Now go get 'em!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128459" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Admiral Ranken. Our moment to truly demoralize the enemy has come. Prepare to engage in a full-on assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128461" id2="17" version="1065353216">The objectives marked on your displays will add to your advantage, but your primary task is to obliterate enemy fighters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128466" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a greater advantage. Use it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show no mercy and win this day for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admiral Ranken here. Your mission in this wargame is to wipe out the opposing squadron. Safety protocols are not in effect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take advantage of area objectives for leverage against your opponent, but do not lose sight of your ultimate goal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Objective secured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128481" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've earned some leverage. Now take down those fighters!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great job, squadron. Wargame's over, and the win goes to you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128483" id2="17" version="1065353216">We did it! You really took it to them. Way to go!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
