<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>28</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/daily_area/kuat/republic/breadcrumb.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be alarmed. I'm with the Republic Strategic Information Service, deeply embedded. I took a gamble you'd be curious enough about the &quot;malfunction&quot; I devised to stop a moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123853" id2="17" version="1065353216">A serious problem's brewing. The Empire is about to violate the Treaty of Coruscant by attacking Kuat Drive Yards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123855" id2="17" version="1065353216">A serious problem's brewing. One of the Empire's most feared admirals is about to launch an attack on Kuat Drive Yards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123857" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kuat provides the bulk of the Republic's warship production. If the Empire takes control, we're in bad shape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123858" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire won't take control of a single wrench if I have anything to say about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Point me to the problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123859" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have your work cut out for you, Jedi, but with you on board, I like our chances.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absent a healthy armada, the Republic would be crushed, and the Empire would be free to menace the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123861" id2="17" version="1065353216">An understatement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123862" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave it to a well-spoken Jedi like yourself to drive the point home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123864" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire won't take a thing--not if Havoc Squad has anything to say about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123864" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. The Drive Yards operation could use a stronger military presence, even if it isn't entirely by the book.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123867" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire isn't exactly good for business. Tell me what I can do to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123867" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would be bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Had a feeling I wouldn't have to work hard to persuade a smart entrepreneur.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123870" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Empire is on the attack, we should be doing all we can, not sneaking around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123870" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why so secretive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123871" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire might attempt to claim Kuat under the Treaty due to its proximity to Balmorra. Better to keep silent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123873" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. Unfortunately, the politics surrounding Kuat are such that no one likes having attention drawn to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123875" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't even know you. How am I supposed to know that what you're saying is true?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123875" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't trust you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123876" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have to take my word for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123878" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no official call to arms, but if you were to... simply show up, I 'm sure Fleet Admiral Aygo will be relieved to see you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123879" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't think the admiral will ask questions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123880" id2="17" version="1065353216">This channel won't be secure much longer. I should go. Best of luck keeping Kuat Drive Yards in Republic hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not by then, he won't; he'll have his hands full. Just be sure to get the proper clearance codes for safe travel to the Kuati fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125732" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
