<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>36</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/daily_area/kuat/republic/fleet_admiral_aygo.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123811" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must do everything to ensure Kuat Drive Yards remains in Republic control. Good luck out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123813" id2="17" version="1065353216">The First Fleet is on high alert status.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123890" id2="17" version="1065353216">There you are! I was told of your arrival. Fleet Admiral Bey'wan Aygo. You honor me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most fortunate, your timing, but before we get into that: I take it you're aware of the importance of Kuat Drive Yards?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kuat provides the Republic with the bulk of its ships. I'm here to see that arrangement doesn't change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123893" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's why I came.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123894" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you were connected, but to have learned of recent events and be here already--I don't impress easy, but well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123896" id2="17" version="1065353216">I try to stay up on these things; bring me up to speed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remind me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since the dawn of the Republic, Kuat Drive Yards has been the exclusive supplier of many of our greatest warships.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123899" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without Kuat to make and repair our fleets, we're vulnerable. Give the planet to the Imperials, and we're finished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123901" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was told there'd be Imperial heads to crack. That's why I'm here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't care. Just let me fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surprising point of view from a Jedi--not that I have any qualms. By all means, crack away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123904" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good news: You won't have to wait very long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123906" id2="17" version="1065353216">As we speak, the Imps are mounting an attack on Kuat's main defensive control station. Their starfighters have also targeted related assets in Kuati space.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you asking for help with the space station, or out there in a ship?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123928" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to get back to it now, but on behalf of the Republic First Fleet, thank you. May the Force be with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124923" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take your assistance however you'd like to provide it. Bottom line: we can't let the Empire take that station, and we won't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scramble all ships defending platforms fifty through seventy five. The Imps won't stand a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell the Minedrome squad leader to stand by for revised objectives. Those Imps won't know what hit them!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some of our own have been taken alive, and I'm sure you can guess how Imps treat their prisoners. Let's get them to safety!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imps are using the station's defensive ordnance to fire at our fleet. We need to take control of those cannons!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125602" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the unlikely event that we lose here, details of Kuati fighter production will be vital for the Republic going forward. Get what data you can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125604" id2="17" version="1065353216">All of Kuat will be in danger if the Imps sabotage that station's power core. Need to keep them at bay!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125606" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Imps get hold of that station's weapons cache, we're done for. There's no time for a reclamation crew, so start smashing!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125608" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imps need this hangar to bring in reinforcements. Don't let them take control!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125610" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got a Sith Lord who thinks he's claimed a zone for the Imps, but he wasn't expecting you. Go get him!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125612" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imps reprogrammed a company droid to attack our forces on sight. Take that thing out!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reports are coming in of a vicious Imp trooper who's routing our forces. Show him what you've got!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just what we needed. Great work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125618" id2="17" version="1065353216">With you on that station, we can't lose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Notch another score for the Republic. Nice going!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doing all of us proud in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125621" id2="17" version="1065353216">On behalf of the Republic First Fleet, you have my thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Way to go. We'll win this struggle yet!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
