<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>101</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/rishi/hub_2/the_revanites_revealed/shared/arankau.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131792" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're new.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131793" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you in charge here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131794" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't really operate that way, but I can act as that sort of figure if you require it of me. How might I help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131795" id2="17" version="1065353216">My allies and I would like to stay here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1131795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will you provide sanctuary?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do what you like. No Rishii will have an issue with your presence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131797" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you call this place?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1131797" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131798" id2="17" version="1065353216">The village doesn't have a name. It's just where we Rishii live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rishii or otherwise, anyone living here chooses when and for how long of their own accord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131801" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm taking over here. You can help by not getting in the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1131801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surrender control to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131802" id2="17" version="1065353216">There really is nothing to take over in the village; no ownership or hierarchy. You're welcome to do as you will.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1131804" id2="17" version="1065353216">More bird people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131806" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose now that we've left Raider's Cove, you're going to start complaining about them instead of the pirates?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1131808" id2="17" version="1065353216">No--those pirates are still the worst!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131810" id2="17" version="1065353216">You cleared the path well. And made a friend?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131812" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am called Arankau.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131813" id2="17" version="1065353216">The other inhabitants on this island--are you in contact with them? Do you know what they're up to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131814" id2="17" version="1065353216">If an individual Rishii chooses to get involved with others, that's that Rishii's choice. Otherwise, we tend to see no reason to inquire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131816" id2="17" version="1065353216">These other inhabitants, they have also kept to themselves. Strangely, their encampment appears to be segregated. One group looks like her. The other is less... intense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial and Republic traitors working side by side but still wary of one another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1131817" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131818" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they have more of you in their roster, I might be joining the Revanites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1131818" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Multiple Lanas?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131819" id2="17" version="1065353216">You flatter me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131821" id2="17" version="1065353216">If their Sith Lords are anywhere near as deadly as Lana, we're in deeper trouble than when we almost became fish food on Manaan!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131823" id2="17" version="1065353216">No matter what they look like, they're as good as dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1131823" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're all enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131824" id2="17" version="1065353216">So--there's a camp for Imperial traitors and one for Republic Revanites. And they're not exactly friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131826" id2="17" version="1065353216">This may provide an opportunity--either to exact atonement for their deception, or to employ a little deception of our own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131828" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's an opportunity to thin the ranks, is what it is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your zeal for making heads roll never ceases to surprise me, Deefour. Don't worry yourself; it may yet come to that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131831" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take a closer look at these Revanite camps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131832" id2="17" version="1065353216">And we'll attempt to establish a better grasp of their activities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131834" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope we can establish where Agent Shan is being held.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131836" id2="17" version="1065353216">As do I....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131838" id2="17" version="1065353216">We Rishii would be grateful for your help around the village--if you choose to provide it, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Savor your travels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1131850" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thank you. The village thanks you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings! We watched you fighting on the beach--the other offworlders were very unkind. We are much friendlier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you come to trade? Do you need lodgings? Outsiders are always welcome here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134575" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for the warm welcome. I'm surprised you're so open to outsiders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134575" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's very kind of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134576" id2="17" version="1065353216">We love outsiders. You all have such interesting things to say.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134578" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seem a little too friendly to be believed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody is this friendly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134579" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been told our ways are strange, but we don't see why that should be so. Shouldn't everyone be kind to neighbors and guests?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134581" id2="17" version="1065353216">My friends and I are going to be staying here a while. Do yourself a favor and stay out of our way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut up and step aside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134582" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so. As long as you don't trouble our people, we'll be happy to leave you to your business.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1134584" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place is a dump! Intelligent creatures actually live here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134586" id2="17" version="1065353216">An entirely new offworlder! We've never encountered your language--please, speak more!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, there's no need for that, I assure you. I can speak quite well for both of us! Allow me to introduce--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134590" id2="17" version="1065353216">The second head speaks too! I assumed it was decorative, how fascinating!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134591" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mentioned the other offworlders earlier--the ones who attacked me. What do you know about them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134592" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't know much, I'm afraid--they usually avoid us. It seems a little rude, but we know that our ways are different.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134594" id2="17" version="1065353216">They have some camps on the island. They wear different colors--dark in one, light in the other--but they all work together. Like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revanites. Some from the Republic, some from the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134596" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you're right. I'm still going over the data Theron decoded from the Nova Blades--go to those camps and interfere any way you can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134597" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll break up the Revanites' plans before they do any serious damage. I'm sure of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134598" id2="17" version="1065353216">It may still be possible to turn them away from Revan's teachings--if so, I'll find a way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps we can turn them back?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever works. Just don't take too long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a plan. I'll contact you once I've put a dent in their operations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134600" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134602" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got this. All I need are some stilts and a giant Revan mask....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134602" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mess with some cultists? Easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please feel free to take a more direct approach as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Save the reading for later. It'd be nice to have you along for once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134604" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Join the fun!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134605" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd like to, but... I really don't think you'll need my help. My time is better spent here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134607" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force serve you well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134608" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do not command me, Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't tell me what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134609" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't take orders from you, Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't tell me what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134610" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not one of your slaves. You don't tell me what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't boss me around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then stay here and waste time while our enemies move against us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever hospitality we can give is yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141585" id2="17" version="1065353216">The creature that preyed on Rishii is dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh! You bring most excellent news. Our fallen will glide on a warm breeze to their fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, outsider. Let us feast on the beast's remains, and prize your triumph today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go with our best wishes to your hunt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, for the days when I could rip apart a tonitran with my beak! But She Who Greedily Devours is yours, if you wish it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141596" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you do not, a hunting flock must be gathered... before our whole village becomes prey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes... the leavings of the beast! I know the hunter's signs--it must be near.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141604" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must locate the beast that hunts Rishii. It will leave a trail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141607" id2="17" version="1065353216">There have been sightings of a great beast--&quot;She Who Greedily Devours.&quot; Now we know her ferocity outstrips our scouts and hunters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141609" id2="17" version="1065353216">With your eyes so close to the ground, will you seek the beast's spoor? She must be tracked for the sake of the village.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141611" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found your scouts. They're dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141612" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is terrible news. The fledglings will grieve the most. Yet for you and I, there is no time for grief.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should you encounter our scouts, do let me know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141620" id2="17" version="1065353216">My outsider friend, perhaps you would like to trade? We have shared what we've seen with you; consider sharing your eyes with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141621" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is it you're looking for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Several of our scouts have not returned. We don't believe outsiders are involved, but we're puzzled nonetheless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our scouts are quick on their wings, sharp with their talons--delay is unusual. Kindly alert us if you encounter them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your company is appreciated and respected, as always.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
