<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>213</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/ilum/world/republic/the_last_battle/commander_rans.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500780" id2="17" version="1065353216">At last the Republic can rest easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500781" id2="17" version="1065353216">The council wants to congratulate you. I'll meet you there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cole Cantarus will fly you to battle when you're ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500787" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must plan our next move carefully.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500788" id2="17" version="1065353216">I intercepted this message as it was being broadcast across all standard Imperial communications channels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500790" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fellow Sith. Citizens of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500792" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too long the strength of the Empire has been beholden to the in-fighting of the Dark Council and the disappearance of an apathetic Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500794" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith, children of Sith and warriors everywhere, I declare a new Empire, open to all who long for conquest, freedom from inhibition and the right to follow their passions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500796" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suspected he'd betray us, but this is something else....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500798" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dark Council is dissolved. Those who would join Darth Serevin in supporting me, cast aside your titles and let me lead you to victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those who will not, prepare to face our stealth armada. The Emperor is gone. His station and power are mine. We will conquer the galaxy while the Emperor sleeps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500801" id2="17" version="1065353216">He had us eliminate his strongest rival so he could seize power for himself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Malgus staged a coup!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500802" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll say this for Darth Malgus: He's got charisma.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500802" id2="17" version="1065353216">He knows how to make a speech.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500803" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what makes him so dangerous. If he unites the surviving Imperial commanders, this war will start up all over again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you really believe Malgus was on our side? I'd hate to think the supreme commander was that gullible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't say I'm surprised.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500806" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not like we had a choice. Malgus had information we needed to stop Darth Arho. I'd hoped that would buy us a few years of peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500808" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're getting chatter from the Imperial comms. Malgus has the stealth technology, the fleet and the Emperor's space station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500810" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know I've asked too much of you already, but we have to take Darth Malgus out. And soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500811" id2="17" version="1065353216">Malgus has revealed his true countenance. And like all servants of the dark side, he must be stopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500811" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi live to serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Evil never rests, and neither can we.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500814" id2="17" version="1065353216">I defeated the Emperor. There's no way I'll let some want-to-be take his place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500814" id2="17" version="1065353216">He won't stand a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't underestimate him. He wouldn't have made this power play if he didn't have the strength to back it up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500817" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm keeping a list of everything I've done to help the Republic. When this is over, I'll send you a bill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess I'll be the hero. Again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever the cost, you're worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500820" id2="17" version="1065353216">Taking out Darths never gets old.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500820" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looking forward to it, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you should enjoy yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500823" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith stab each other in the back every chance they get. If we sit back and do nothing, one of his own people will take him out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let another Darth do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not right away. You heard the message. Malgus has the support of too many other Sith Lords.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500826" id2="17" version="1065353216">And once he consolidates his position, his stealth armada is sure to challenge the Republic. We have to take him out before that happens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500828" id2="17" version="1065353216">In case you forgot, I just defeated Darth Arho and saved Ilum. I could use a little downtime to recover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500828" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was hoping for a vacation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time is of the essence. Malgus is gaining support. We have to strike before he can fortify his position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500831" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must confer with our top military minds. Equip yourself for battle, then hurry to join our meeting. The fate of the galaxy is at stake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victory is ours! All Imperials on Ilum have surrendered. But success was costly.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too many Ongree fell beneath the blades of Arho's Sith troops. Jiyan Dar gave his life battling Arho's Sith troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500856" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will mourn Jiyan Dar, and honor his heroic sacrifice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500856" id2="17" version="1065353216">His death is a great loss.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500857" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every soldier understands he might give his life in service to the Republic, but it is good to know you appreciate the sacrifice Jiyan Dar made.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500859" id2="17" version="1065353216">We knew there would be casualties, and we needed the Ongree to hold off the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500859" id2="17" version="1065353216">A necessary price to pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jiyan Dar understood this. That is why he held his ground against the Sith, knowing it would cost him his life. Such courage must not be taken for granted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500862" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess the Ongree aren't really warriors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500862" id2="17" version="1065353216">He was weak.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jiyan Dar gave his life to help you! Now you mock his memory?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500865" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't deserve to wear a Republic uniform!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500867" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're just a greedy, self-centered opportunist. You know nothing about the honor of service to a higher cause. You disgust me!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="500869" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think you're better than the soldiers just because you're a Jedi?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone just calm down. We've been through a lot, but we can't turn against each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500873" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Rans is right. We must set aside emotion and take rational stock of where we are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500899" id2="17" version="1065353216">The names of all who gave their lives on Ilum will never be forgotten.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many soldiers were lost, and many artifacts in the temple were destroyed during the Sullustan bombing runs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500905" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know as a Jedi you expect no reward, but I want to give you something for your efforts to save the artifacts inside the Jedi Temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500907" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to give you a reward for your heroic efforts to save the artifacts inside the Jedi Temple. The order is forever grateful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander? You read me? Just picked up a transmission from Darth Malgus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500910" id2="17" version="1065353216">He wanted Darth Arho out of the picture, and we delivered. I wouldn't be shocked if he wants to offer us some kind of reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Probably calling to thank us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh... not even close. You better take a listen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Haven't we done enough for him already?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500912" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does he want now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500913" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd say we've done plenty. You better take a listen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Malgus is dangerous. With Darth Arho out of the picture, it won't be long before he starts looking for a new enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500914" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should take him out next.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like his search is over. You better take a listen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500919" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use the tunnel to sneak into the Jedi Temple while we engage the Imperial forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Incoming call, Commander. Looks like it's your Imperial friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to see you alive and well, Supreme Commander. With you back at the helm, Darth Arho's becoming desperate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501022" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's ordering his ships to land on Ilum's surface, to be equipped with prototype versions of the stealth technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501023" id2="17" version="1065353216">The battlefield's not secure. Landing ships here gives us a chance to take out his entire fleet!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501023" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's taking a huge risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only if you know where to find them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501026" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no way he pulled up enough resources to equip his fleet before I disabled the deep-miners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where'd he get the crystals?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even with prototypes in only a handful of ships, Arho will have a weapon to lash out at Republic worlds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501029" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can deal with his ships.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501030" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arho knows someone in the Empire is working against him. He's keeping the location of the landing sites secret.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501032" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is all I can tell you. I won't contact you again. Arho grows suspicious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Figures. As soon as there's any risk to himself, our &quot;ally&quot; leaves us out in the cold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Malgus is covering his tracks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501034" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's a servant of the dark side. Self-preservation will always be his first priority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501036" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we reveal Darth Malgus is the one who helped us, maybe Arho will focus all his efforts on destroying the traitor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's tell Arho about Malgus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501037" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. We have to think long-term. If we expose Malgus, we can forget about other Imperials helping the Republic again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501039" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's giving us an impossible mission. We don't have the resources to defend an entire planet. Arho's ships could land anywhere!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Malgus wants us to fail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501040" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's only a few spots on Ilum where a ship larger than a shuttle could even attempt to touch down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501042" id2="17" version="1065353216">We just have to take out those landing strips. If we can disable the ships already on the ground, nobody else will be able to land.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501043" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, we all know who's going to end up doing this. I'm used to it by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501043" id2="17" version="1065353216">By &quot;we&quot; you mean &quot;me,&quot; right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, we all know who's going to end up doing this. Ever since we landed, it's been one impossible mission after another. It's getting a little old.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501044" id2="17" version="1065353216">By &quot;we&quot; you mean &quot;us,&quot; right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501045" id2="17" version="1065353216">From those who give the most, the most is always asked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wise words, Master Boudyn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501047" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope they will give you comfort in the difficult time ahead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arguing with you is just going to give me a headache, isn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah. That makes no sense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501050" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501050" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. I get it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501051" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. I get it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad is ready, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just give the order, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our team is ready, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just give the order, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501054" id2="17" version="1065353216">I came here to stop Darth Arho. Might as well let me finish the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501054" id2="17" version="1065353216">No point sending anyone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501055" id2="17" version="1065353216">We came here to stop Darth Arho. Might as well let us finish the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501055" id2="17" version="1065353216">No point sending anyone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501056" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd send someone else if I could. But Caroowar and Jiyan Dar are leading all available troops against key Imperial installations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Caroowar and Jiyan Dar are missing. I'm guessing they're leading troops against key Imperial targets. That means this mission is up to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501058" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll help you however I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501059" id2="17" version="1065353216">Caroowar and Jiyan Dar are missing. I'm guessing they're leading troops against key Imperial targets. That means this mission is up to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501059" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll help you however we can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501060" id2="17" version="1065353216">A very astute--and accurate--observation. I don't have anyone else to spare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know what the temperature is out there? I've got frostbite on my... somewhere you really don't want to get frostbite.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Back to freezing our... toes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501063" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know this has been hard, but Caroowar and Jiyan Dar are already leading troops against key Imperial installations. I can't afford to send anyone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501065" id2="17" version="1065353216">This sounds like a mission the regular troops can handle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501065" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send somebody else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501066" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have any troops to spare. Caroowar and Jiyan are already leading our soldiers against key Imperial targets. It has to be you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501068" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll give you the location of the landing strips. Use these ion grenades against the ships already on the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501071" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made it back alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501072" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only because of you. I'm running out of ways to say thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501073" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just glad we got you back, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just following orders, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad really went above and beyond this time, Major. I won't forget it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your team really went above and beyond, Major. I won't forget it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501078" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're on the same side, Commander. I know you'd have done the same for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501078" id2="17" version="1065353216">No thanks necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501079" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know we'd try. But nobody else can do what you do. So do us all a favor and try not to get captured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501081" id2="17" version="1065353216">Plenty of ways to show your appreciation. Credits. Ship upgrades. A blanket pardon from the Senate I can hang onto, just in case.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501081" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll think of something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501082" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll look into it. Until then, you'll have to make do with my gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501084" id2="17" version="1065353216">My order is sworn to defend the Republic, Commander. We will always be here when you need us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501084" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi live to serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501085" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just wish we didn't need you so often. But Dark Lords are usually more than my troops can handle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did the rest of the Republic prisoners make it back?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where are the other POWs?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501088" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every last one of them. Our medics are looking them over; some of them were in pretty bad shape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501090" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a key military asset. The Republic needs your expertise. Ilum won't be the last time we battle with the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501090" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're too valuable to lose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501091" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right, unfortunately. They're down now, but they always seem to rise again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501099" id2="17" version="1065353216">I owe you my life. We all do.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="501101" id2="17" version="1065353216">The things those monsters did to us....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arho knows we're here. He's going to send reinforcements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501102" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to get moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501103" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right... I can hear them coming down the hall!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501105" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can't hurt you anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501105" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're safe now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501106" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've done enough already. Wait... what was that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501108" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever doesn't kill you makes you stronger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501108" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're alive. That's enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501109" id2="17" version="1065353216">Easy for you to say. You can't even imagine... wait! What was that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501111" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone coming down the hall. Arho must have sent reinforcements!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501113" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have no armor. No weapons. You have to hold them off and give us a chance to escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501115" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll meet you back at the Republic command post. Good luck, and thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. You're here. We're going to need your help--all of you--if we're going to defeat the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501123" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. You're here. As you can see, we need all the help we can get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501125" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me introduce our allies: Master Boudyn of the Jedi and Commanders Caroowar, Jiyan Dar and Yet Jub.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="501127" id2="17" version="1065353216">The introductions are over. Now we strike back! Retake the temple--no more retreating like cowards!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501129" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, Caroowar. The attack on the temple is to distract us from Darth Arho's true goal... just as the peace talks blinded us before the Sacking of Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501130" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Arho's a Sith. Seizing the temple is a direct challenge to our honor. He's throwing it in our face!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501130" id2="17" version="1065353216">He insulted our entire order!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501131" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must not rise to his bait. There is no emotion, there is peace. Let Supreme Commander Rans do his job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501133" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are still secrets in the temple worth guarding, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501133" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are the temple's secrets safe?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501134" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sealed the archives in the temple's vault during the attack. It would take them days to cut their way through the durasteel doors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arho's not here for the archives; he wants Ilum's crystals. They're using deep-miners to drill into the very core of the planet!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Caroowar has a point. We should go after Darth Arho, first. Without their leader, the Imperials won't stand a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501138" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Wookiee's right, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501139" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have to look at the big picture, Major. Ilum's crystals should be our focus. The Imperials are using deep-miners to drill into the planet's core!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501141" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like you Republic folks, but it always seems like you're two steps behind the Empire with your plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501141" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Imperials are crafty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501142" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which is why we can't fall prey to their tricks. The Imperials want Ilum's crystals. They're using deep-miners to drill into the planet's core!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501144" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we don't hit them at the temple, then where do we strike?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501144" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the plan, Commander?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501146" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like to learn from my mistakes. You should try it sometime.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501148" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials want Ilum's crystals. They're using deep-miners to drill into the planet's core!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501150" id2="17" version="1065353216">The excavations leave massive sink holes. The entire world's becoming unstable. If we don't stop them, Ilum could literally crack in two.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="501152" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll engage the bulk of the Imperial forces while you go to the excavation sites and disable the deep-miners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501154" id2="17" version="1065353216">After you've cleared each mine, call us and we'll send reinforcements in to hold the area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501155" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the kind of mission we live for, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501155" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on Havoc Squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501157" id2="17" version="1065353216">This base doesn't seem very secure. Maybe you and the other commanders should retreat to one of the ships in orbit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501157" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will you be safe here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501158" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't do that. The best place to oversee the efforts of our troops is right here on the surface. We're staying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501160" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was afraid my days of battling the Imperials were over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="501160" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to enjoy this!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501161" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stopping the deep-miners won't end this. Unless we locate the Imperial command post, they'll figure out another way to harvest Ilum's crystals.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="501163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Each mine must have a communications terminal to receive orders. We could locate the Imperial command center using data from the outgoing transmissions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good idea. After you disable each deep-miner, download the mine's terminal datalog. Bring all the data to Agent Samm Bradber at the communications center for analysis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501167" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fate of Ilum is in your hands. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501169" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't rest until the Empire is driven off Ilum for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501191" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials are taking heavy losses. Caroowar has broken their front lines, and Jiyan Dar has caved in their flank.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501198" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith are inflicting heavy casualties on the Ongree regiments, but Jiyan Dar refuses to fall back!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501203" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials are in full retreat! Republic troops are storming the temple. We have to find Darth Arho before he escapes!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501210" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've secured the first excavation site and scanned the communications terminal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501211" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done. We'll send a team to secure the mine while you head to the next one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501218" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm at the last mine. Everything's all clear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501219" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get that transmission data to Samm Bradber. He's waiting for you at the Republic communications center.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="766957" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd better take cover, sir. We can run for base camp once they're gone. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="767504" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not afraid of Malgus.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="930624" id2="17" version="1065353216">My forces will secure the Jedi Temple and make certain every Imperial soldier inside is sent packing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="930626" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Wookiees will join the Ongree in securing the Temple. The Imperials will run screaming from Ilum!</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="946762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now you're being stupid.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
