<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>55</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/ilum/world/republic/the_last_battle/lieutenant_halaa.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major, this is Supreme Commander Rans. I want to commend Havoc Squad for all you've done to help the Republic cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177845" id2="17" version="1065353216">Defeating General Rakton has left the Empire's military in ruins. You single-handedly turned the tide of the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177847" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Supreme Commander Rans of the Republic. It's an honor to speak with someone who's done so much to help the cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177849" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've had great success in tracking down the last of the Children of the Emperor. You single-handedly turned the tide of this war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177851" id2="17" version="1065353216">By defeating the Emperor, you've dealt a crippling blow to his followers. You single-handedly turned the tide of this war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Defeating the Voidwolf was a crushing blow to the Empire. You single-handedly turned the tide of the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177855" id2="17" version="1065353216">I read the reports from Corellia. Very impressive. You single-handedly turned the tide of this war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177857" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic already owes you a debt it can never repay. But I'm calling because we need your help again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, let me guess: impossible odds, fate of the galaxy, death at every turn?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="177858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course you do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh... more or less. Have you heard of Ilum? It's a remote, ice-covered world. It's also the galaxy's primary source of lightsaber crystals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad is ready and able, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="177861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Awaiting orders, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177862" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me the mission and I'll get right on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="177862" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do whatever I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177863" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's in total disarray. What threat can they pose now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="177863" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought the war was over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't underestimate the Empire. We made that mistake once, and Coruscant was nearly destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems like anytime there's a critical mission, the Republic needs me to step in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="177866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is everyone else useless?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177867" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the burden of being a hero. You get the jobs nobody else can handle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177869" id2="17" version="1065353216">As a Jedi, I'm sure you're familiar with the ice world of Ilum. It's one of the galaxy's primary sources of lightsaber crystals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you familiar with Ilum? It's a remote, ice-covered world... and one of the galaxy's primary sources of lightsaber crystals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177873" id2="17" version="1065353216">The remnants of the Empire's forces have invaded Ilum en masse. We sent reinforcements, but they're getting overwhelmed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once I get there, we'll drive the Empire off Ilum... just like we drove them off Corellia!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="177874" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll turn the battle around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177875" id2="17" version="1065353216">This mission's different. The Empire's not trying to capture Ilum. This is a raid, and they'll strip the planet bare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177877" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this is the Empire's last gasp, I would have expected them to strike at a more populated world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="177877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ilum's an unusual target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ilum's not your typical target. This is a raid, pure and simple. They're trying to strip the planet bare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177880" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire doesn't have the numbers to capture a strategically important world anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="177880" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll never hold it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177881" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're not trying to capture Ilum. This is a raid, pure and simple. They're going to strip the planet bare unless we stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177883" id2="17" version="1065353216">The crystals on Ilum are unique, and the Empire has found a way to use them to amplify cloaking systems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177885" id2="17" version="1065353216">With enough crystals, they could build an invisible armada: an entire fleet capable of striking any Republic world without warning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177886" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're leaving for Ilum right now, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="177886" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177887" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please hurry. The Imperials are led by a man named Darth Arho. He's throwing everything they've got at us. We can't hold out much longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177889" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me a breakdown of the enemy forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="177889" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are we up against?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Arho is leading the assault. He's hitting us with everything they've got: elite military units, mercenaries, bounty hunters... and Sith Lords.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since the Empire lacks the numbers to hold any planets, they're going to devastate them instead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="177892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Terror instead of conquest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Arho is leading the assault, and he'd rather destroy a world than see it live free. We can't let those crystals fall into his hands!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177895" id2="17" version="1065353216">Report to the Republic space station orbiting Ilum ASAP. A shuttle will take you down to the surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="177897" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're using the Jedi Temple as a makeshift headquarters for our operations. Meet me there and I'll give you a full briefing. Rans out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="554612" id2="17" version="1065353216">First Corellia, then Ilum. Looks like you've got two statues coming your way.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="554613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia's ready to fly the Republic flag again. Get to Ilum and do the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="554616" id2="17" version="1065353216">There they are! The squad of the hour! Or you will be, once Corellia's free.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="554618" id2="17" version="1065353216">There he is! The hero of the Republic! Or you will be, once Corellia's free.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="554620" id2="17" version="1065353216">There she is! The hero of the Republic! Or you will be, once Corellia's free.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="554622" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you're fresh off the battlefield, but I have an urgent message from Supreme Commander Rans.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="554624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not surprised, after your victory. Takes me back to my own fighting days...well, no time for that now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="554647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Star maps to Ilum, ready for your ship's nav system. Give those Imps what you gave 'em on Corellia and worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="554649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia needs every man fighting for her. Wish I could be out there myself.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
