<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>125</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/ilum/world/republic/the_last_battle/samm_bradber.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Arho refuses to surrender. He knows it could take weeks before we break the Imperial defenses and reclaim the temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fortunately, there is another way in--an underground escape tunnel built centuries ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500927" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need you to infiltrate the temple through the escape tunnel while we engage the Imperials outside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500928" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials have had plenty of time to search the temple. I doubt that tunnel's still undefended.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500928" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if they found it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500929" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're probably right. Our offensive will draw most of the defenders away, but I'm sure you'll still have plenty of Imps to deal with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500931" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about our man on the inside? Is he going to help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any word from Malgus?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500932" id2="17" version="1065353216">No recent contact. Malgus seems to have disappeared. But at least we know his followers aren't supporting Arho.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Troops are massing now, along with all available Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500937" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the temple well. If you clear the way, I can lead a team of Jedi to capture key strategic locations, like the armory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without Master Boudyn's Jedi, our troops will suffer greater casualties. But it might be worth it to get your hands on the armory equipment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500940" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't sacrifice lives just so I can get my hands on some Imperial weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Protect the troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500941" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'll engage Darth Arho's Sith followers while the rest of the troops take on the Imperial soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500943" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those weapons could swing this entire battle. Our troops understand that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500943" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want that armory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500944" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Jedi are going to help secure the temple, someone is going to have to engage Darth Arho's Sith followers on the battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500949" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree with Caroowar. At least they have a fighting chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500949" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's right. Send the Wookiees.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful, Caroowar. The Sith are unlike any enemy you have ever faced. You only have to distract them, not defeat them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500953" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give the Sith a taste of that famous Wookiee battle fury!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500953" id2="17" version="1065353216">So don't hold back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500956" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can handle a few extra Sith. You just worry about keeping your regiment alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't throw your lives away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500957" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can handle a few extra Sith. You just worry about keeping your regiment alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't throw your lives away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500958" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's an order, Caroowar! Do whatever is necessary to minimize Wookiee casualties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep the Wookiees as part of the main army and let Jiyan Dar's regiment face the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500960" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Ongree can handle this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful, Jiyan. The Sith are unlike any enemy you have ever faced. You only have to distract them, not defeat them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show the Sith the Ongree are warriors to be feared!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500964" id2="17" version="1065353216">So don't hold back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500967" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can handle a few extra Sith. You just worry about keeping your regiment alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't throw your lives away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500968" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can handle a few extra Sith. You just worry about keeping your regiment alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500968" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't throw your lives away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500969" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's an order, Jiyan! Do whatever is necessary to minimize Ongree casualties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500971" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about air support, Commander? The Sullustan pilots are itching for a chance to avenge Yet Jub.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500973" id2="17" version="1065353216">I share their pain. But the temple houses many irreplaceable artifacts that are unlikely to survive a series of air strikes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500975" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's your call. Your mission to infiltrate the temple will be a lot harder without air support.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500978" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must do everything in our power to preserve the teachings and treasures of the great Jedi Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500978" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must protect the temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those artifacts could turn out to be useful in our war against the Empire. We can't risk having them destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500979" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must protect the temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500980" id2="17" version="1065353216">You heard the Jedi, Bradber. Keep the Sullustans grounded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, the pilots can get a little reckless with their targets. This mission calls for more of a surgical strike.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500982" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to protect the temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500983" id2="17" version="1065353216">You heard the major, Bradber. Keep the Sullustans grounded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500985" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd hate to see all that treasure get blown to worthless bits. Kind of offends me just on principle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500985" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's protect the temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting point of view.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, Bradber. Keep those Sullustans grounded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Air support could save Republic lives. As valuable as the temple artifacts may be, they cannot be measured against a living being.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send in air support.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Arho's a Sith Lord. We need to seize every advantage we can get over him and his followers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send in air support.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500994" id2="17" version="1065353216">You heard the Jedi, Bradber. Get those Sullustans in the air!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Winning the battle's more important than saving some artifacts, sir. Let the Sullustans have their revenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send in air support.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500997" id2="17" version="1065353216">You heard the major, Bradber. Get those Sullustans in the air!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500999" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it makes my life easier, then I say: bombs away!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send in air support.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bradber--get those Sullustans in the air!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Copy that, Supreme Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here is the location of the escape tunnel into the Jedi Temple. Go there now; my people will follow once you've cleared the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here is the location of the escape tunnel into the Jedi Temple. Go there now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501008" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll send you updates on the progress of the battle. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="501012" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're just in time. We're discussing our final attack plans. The Imperial troops have fallen back inside the Jedi Temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arho's troops just raided our command post. Massive casualties on both sides.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our boys drove them off, but the Imps captured Supreme Commander Rans. Jiyan Dar's ordered everyone back to the command post.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662006" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to get back to the base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662006" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll need my help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this a retreat, or is he massing troops for a counterattack?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662007" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's Jiyan Dar planning?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your guess is as good as mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662010" id2="17" version="1065353216">The supreme commander sent too many troops to secure the mines. He left himself vulnerable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rans screwed up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rans had plenty of troops on hand. But Arho's insane. He sent his people into a massacre.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662013" id2="17" version="1065353216">They lost twice as many soldiers as we did. He sacrificed hundreds just to capture Rans. Probably figured we'd fall apart without him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grab your gear and head back. Jiyan and the others will want to speak with you. We'll be right behind you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take whatever you can carry! Wipe everything else clean. Let's go--we're mobile in five minutes!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662020" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's going on?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Report back to me after you take out Lord Loyat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent Bradber? I've got the data from all the mine terminals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662027" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't usually like working with civilians, but Rans was smart to put you on this. Let me contact him while this data's decrypting....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662029" id2="17" version="1065353216">You Jedi types do good work. Rans was smart to put you on this. Let me contact him while this data's decrypting....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662031" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can always count on Havoc Squad. Let me contact Rans while this data's decrypting....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rans knew what he was doing when he put you on this. Let me contact him while this data's decrypting....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Supreme Commander Rans here. Master Boudyn is with me, too. Do we have the location of the Imperial command center?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just got the coordinates. Looks like the orders were coming from a small Imperial base on the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662039" id2="17" version="1065353216">SIS scouted it before, but didn't think it was important enough to have priority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662040" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the whole planet under siege, Arho knew Republic intelligence would overlook something so minor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hiding in plain sight. Clever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take out that base, and we can end the assault on Ilum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send in the troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662042" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galaxy is about to have one less Sith Lord in it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to pay Arho a visit!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662043" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doubt Darth Arho's actually there. SIS reports show he likes to stay clear while someone else handles things on the front lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662045" id2="17" version="1065353216">He probably put his personal apprentice in charge. Lord Loyat is every bit as cruel and ruthless as her master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662047" id2="17" version="1065353216">SIS has a file on her. Pretty good with a lightsaber. Killed at least a dozen other Sith during her time on Korriban. Never punished for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arho protected Loyat. Their relationship goes deeper than master and apprentice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662050" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're not the type of Sith who've been physically corrupted by the dark side, are they? You know how their skin gets all wrinkled and gray and gross?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662050" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eww....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662051" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh... I don't really know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Loyat may be a Sith Lord, but she's no match for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662053" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll deal with Loyat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662054" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we capture Loyat, maybe we can use her as leverage against Darth Arho.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662054" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're lovers? Interesting...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662055" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Arho is consumed by the dark side. He will cast her aside when she ceases to be useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662057" id2="17" version="1065353216">She sounds dangerous. Be sure to send plenty of reinforcements when you move against that base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="662057" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better send extra troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662058" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we send troops in, Lord Loyat might evacuate to a new location. Our best chance is for you to go in alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662060" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can try to arrest her if you think that's best. But I won't miss her if she winds up dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once the base is out of commission, report back to Agent Bradber. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="662066" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rans told me to help you out. But first, I need the data from all the mine terminals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="918421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="918426" id2="17" version="1065353216">I volunteer to lead the Ongree regiment against the Sith, Supreme Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="918428" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, Supreme Commander. Jiyan's regiment will be slaughtered. Let me lead the Wookiees against the Sith instead!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="918430" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we hold back, the Sith will send reinforcements to help protect the temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="918432" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally, a real battle! The Sith's blood will stain the snow!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="918435" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we hold back, the Sith will send reinforcements to help protect the temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="918437" id2="17" version="1065353216">We may not look it, but the Ongree are warriors too. This will be a triumph remembered through the ages!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="918441" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send in air support.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="918446" id2="17" version="1065353216">Protect the Temple.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
