<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>110</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/imperial/hub_1/countdown_to_doomsday/r_c92.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010657" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always a pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010658" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is a shuttle awaiting you in the docking bay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010659" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have come for Darth Marr. Is he here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mighty Wrath. Follow me, please.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010661" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dark Lord. Follow me, please.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Marr sent for me. Has he arrived?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010663" id2="17" version="1065353216">He will be here presently, Commander. Follow me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010664" id2="17" version="1065353216">He is on his way. Please follow me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shuttle Fuliginous en route to docking bay eight. Nonessential personnel must clear the area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010668" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is strength in this chamber. Let it suffice for the task ahead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell no one of this meeting, hunter. You are about to hear a truth that very few are aware of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010693" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our last chance--our only chance--is far from the front lines. The planet Makeb is the secret to victory, and its responsibility is yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010694" id2="17" version="1065353216">An unaligned colony world on the edge of Hutt Space... why does it matter? And why now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010694" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not familiar with Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010708" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's not the only place I can find work. What if I don't want your responsibility?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010708" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I should switch sides.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010709" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you intended to leave, you would have done so. Depart now, and I may still allow it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010711" id2="17" version="1065353216">You summoned me. Why not take charge of this operation yourself?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010711" id2="17" version="1065353216">My responsibility? Not yours?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010712" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tens of thousands die to buy us time here, and I must lead the fleet. It is not as I would wish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010714" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb grew rich from mining and trade, becoming a neutral paradise for wealthy cretins. It escaped the war due to its tactical insignificance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010716" id2="17" version="1065353216">But now the Hutt Cartel has seized Makeb for itself. The Hutts believe that with our &quot;imminent defeat,&quot; the time has come to chase glory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010717" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts are greedy, but they're not fools. Makeb is important to them somehow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010717" id2="17" version="1065353216">They chose Makeb for a reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010718" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Cartel's former Supreme Mogul tried to claim new territory. He gave the Cartel a taste for conquest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010718" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the Hutts' ambitions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. But there's more to it this time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010721" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts are ambitious, but they're not militant. What's the Cartel thinking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010721" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts? Going to war?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010722" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts had an empire long ago. Many dream of its return.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010724" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why worry about a future threat when the Republic is on the verge of taking Korriban?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010724" id2="17" version="1065353216">That isn't our concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010725" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because what no one knows is this:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010727" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts chose Makeb not for its wealth, but for a substance called &quot;isotope-5&quot;--a mineral capable of twisting gravity and electromagnetic fields.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010729" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts have kept it a secret, but one gram could provide a near-infinite power source. Isotope-5 could remake the Hutts into a force to rival the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010730" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts find isotope-5, we take it from them... and the Empire gains a new weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010730" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then isotope-5 must be ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010731" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Hutts are keeping isotope-5 a secret, where did you get this information?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010731" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you learn this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010732" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire has been monitoring Hutt activity on the planet. This effort has borne fruit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010734" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said the former Minister of Intelligence set up surveillance on Makeb. Was that our source?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010734" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people discovered this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010735" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. Both electronic wiretaps and human informants provided this information; we are confident.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010737" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic can't be defeated with technology alone. If it could, we'd have won by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010737" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tactics win wars, not weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010738" id2="17" version="1065353216">A fair complaint, but now only a combination of tactics and weaponry can save us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010740" id2="17" version="1065353216">Despite the efforts of the Hutts' mercenaries, Makeb's leaders are requesting aid from the Republic, and the planet is on the verge of chaos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010742" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must steal the Hutts' stockpile of isotope-5 under cover of the conflict. Stealth is paramount--if the Hutts and Republic realize your intent, they will deploy overwhelming force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010743" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am the Wrath of the Emperor. There is no soldier, Sith or machine that is my equal. Send me to Makeb, and that world will fall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010743" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm the only army we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010744" id2="17" version="1065353216">The military is under your control, Lord Marr. Do not make me regret leaving the galaxy in your hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010744" id2="17" version="1065353216">See to the war while I'm gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010745" id2="17" version="1065353216">We both have much to lose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010747" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't survived this long by making my actions public. But you know that already.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010747" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer stealth, anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010748" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have learned what you are capable of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010750" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stealing from the Hutt Cartel earns you a galactic death mark. I'm in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010750" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never liked Hutts anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010751" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about allies? A base of operations?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will I have any backup?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010752" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will have a limited support team--specialists capable of performing their duty and willing to serve you unto death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010754" id2="17" version="1065353216">But in short, you will be alone on a hostile world. With our lines crumbling, we cannot mount a full-scale invasion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sending me to an isolated planet on a secret mission, surrounded by foes? You want me out of the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010756" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're arranging my death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010757" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were destroyed by paranoia and infighting once! I will not allow that to happen again! Not with the Emperor silent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010759" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord. You're needed with the Khar Delban fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010761" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is a cloaked shuttle waiting to deliver you to the surface. You may establish an uplink to your team once you land.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be wary, and move with subtlety. If you fail, the Empire's last stand will be over before it begins.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me. I have no instructions related to your arrival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039725" id2="17" version="1065353216">So it shall be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1045825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Nox. Time is short, so let us begin with truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1045826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Occlus. Time is short, so let us begin with truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1045827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Imperius. Time is short, so let us begin with truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1045830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Malgus the Betrayer and the Dread Masters were cracks in the Empire's steel; the Republic is the coming hammer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1045832" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire is losing this war. Barring the unexpected or the miraculous, our total defeat will occur within the year.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1045874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Between infighting among the Sith and military incompetence, it's sheer luck the Empire survived this long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1045874" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's no surprise to anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1045875" id2="17" version="1065353216">We won the battles on Corellia and Ilum. We should be stronger than ever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1045875" id2="17" version="1065353216">How is that possible?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1045876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our victories were glorious. But infighting among the Sith has taken its toll.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046052" id2="17" version="1065353216">That may have been true once. But now I sit on the Dark Council, and I will bring the unexpected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046052" id2="17" version="1065353216">My ascension changes things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your tone is not welcome. Your sentiment is correct.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046055" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Malgus sought to usurp the Emperor, and caused division when unity was required. The Republic sees an opportunity to strike.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046057" id2="17" version="1065353216">Power plays have diminished the Dark Council. The Republic stands united while we bicker amongst ourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confidence is not strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046060" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Empire is this close to falling, why hasn't the Emperor intervened? Darth Malgus claimed he was dead....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046060" id2="17" version="1065353216">What of the Emperor himself?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046067" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Empire is this close to falling, why hasn't the Emperor intervened? Darth Malgus claimed he was dead....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046067" id2="17" version="1065353216">What of the Emperor himself?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Malgus claimed many things. The Emperor remains silent, as is his right--but rumors of his demise have made our enemies bold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046070" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor has been silent for many years, and that is his prerogative. But rumors of his absence have made our enemies bold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wrath. Time is short, so I will be blunt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046106" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire does not fall easily. You dare much, to accuse us of weakness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046106" id2="17" version="1065353216">You come speaking treason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or we die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046140" id2="17" version="1065353216">So why am I here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046141" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won on Corellia and Ilum. I was there. You should be stronger than ever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046141" id2="17" version="1065353216">How is that possible?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046143" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's bad news. But you need an army, not one woman.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046144" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's bad news. But you need an army, not one man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046145" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are not here to fight the war at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046544" id2="17" version="1065353216">None must know what I am here to say. I will trust your discretion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046550" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least you're being candid. But I assume we're not here to surrender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046550" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate your honesty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Death before surrender. But today is not our day to die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046682" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did not expect such candor from the Dark Council. We must move swiftly, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046682" id2="17" version="1065353216">A bold admission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046683" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith slaughter one another while our people are leaderless. That is weakness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046687" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. But the obstacles are many.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
