<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>27</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/daily_area/ziost/world_arc/shared/for_ziost/holoterminal.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chancellor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Marr. You wanted a word?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150603" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you have questions for me about the status of our invasion, but first I have questions for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150605" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't make that out. Could you repeat?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't hear you, Marr. Probably on your end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150610" id2="17" version="1065353216">What can you tell me about these possessions? Theron Shan seems to think that, while it was an isolated matter at first--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150612" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm curious: Do you really believe you've accomplished anything here? What do you think you've stopped?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1150613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your bid for immortality.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150614" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let you butcher innocent people--or anyone else, for that matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1150614" id2="17" version="1065353216">The endless bloodshed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1150615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing--but I had to try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150616" id2="17" version="1065353216">You feed on all the deaths you cause. I'm doing everything I can to take that away from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1150616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your power supply.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150618" id2="17" version="1065353216">You would feed on every last life in the galaxy to become immortal. I won't let that happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150619" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not going to let you kill every living thing just so you can live forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150621" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know how powerful you've become. But if I do nothing, what good am I?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like I'm really just going to kick back and take a load off while you eat the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Power-hungry maniacs can't be left to just do whatever they want.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150624" id2="17" version="1065353216">You might as well, for all the actual progress you have made here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150626" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have decided that life is more interesting with you in it. If you wish to keep railing against me, then so be it. Your interference changes nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150628" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I am finished here--when every life on this world has been exhausted--I want you to be alive. To know that I succeeded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150629" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have already cheated death. I have other plans now--as you will see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150630" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could be so much more if you would let go your quaint morality. I'll even give you the chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150631" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Everything you can&quot; will never be enough. You would be wise to remember that from now on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Noble. Pointless, but noble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed--what good are you? It is a question I have asked myself--and have finally answered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Goodbye.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
