<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>4</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/heroic_weekly/mission_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174164" id2="17" version="1065353216">CORUSCANT SECURITY ALERT 

Criminal gang &quot;The Fondor Five&quot; confirmed active in Old Galactic Market sector. Last seen entering Fartrader Lounge. All five gang members carry death sentences and substantial bounties from numerous violent felony convictions. 

Bounty payment to be rendered contingent upon substantive proof of gang members' final status. 

CITIZENS STRONGLY DISCOURAGED FROM PURSUING BOUNTY - SUSPECTS CONSIDERED ARMED AND EXTREMELY DANGEROUS!

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Security Officer Stansum has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Black Sun Territory sector of Coruscant. For additional details about the mission, Security Officer Stansum may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174166" id2="17" version="1065353216">Luran Gonthor has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Justicar Territory sector on Coruscant. For additional details about the mission, Luran Gonthor may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174167" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ensign Belkan has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jedi Temple sector of Coruscant. For additional details about the mission, Ensign Belkan may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
