<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>29</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/war_world/quesh/bronze/imperial/blood_and_venom/sergeant_molvar.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry about me. I can hold this area until reinforcements arrive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71393" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic soldiers that killed your squad are no longer a threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71394" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've called headquarters for reinforcements. Next squad should be here soon to hold the place, but we couldn't have secured it without you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't thank you enough. Payback is satisfying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71398" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teach those adrenal-chugging Republic scum a lesson.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71401" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord. Sergeant Molvar. Had a cousin who was Sith. Very powerful. Died young. Wish he was here now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71403" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunter. A sergeant's operating budget isn't befitting a duchess or anything, but I'll pay you good to make some Republic dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71405" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent, sir! Sergeant Molvar reporting. I can't candy-coat this one. Nothing's going to make this op taste any better, except maybe Republic blood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71407" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, your help is critical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Operation was to move in, secure the area for a supply depot, move troops and equipment deeper into the mines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71411" id2="17" version="1065353216">Casualties: Thirteen. Dead: Twelve. And I count six broken ribs, one shattered kneecap and one Hutt-sized headache.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71412" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happened here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71413" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could just put you out of your misery right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would you rather be dead?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71414" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure, after we take care of the Republic scum that wiped out my unit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are you telling me this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71417" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic worms guarding the area were jacked up on some kind of adrenals. They weren't human. They were animals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71419" id2="17" version="1065353216">They shrugged off blaster fire like bug bites and then tore into my squad. I only survived because a grenade knocked me senseless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71421" id2="17" version="1065353216">My plan was to rush in there, take all the adrenals I could find, and complete the mission, but you might have better success. We need that supply depot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71422" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure. Won't do the rest of my squad any good, but I'll take a lesson.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71425" id2="17" version="1065353216">From the way you describe these Republic soldiers, I'm not sure I'd do any better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71425" id2="17" version="1065353216">This sounds dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71426" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic soldiers are only good because they have an edge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71428" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll give you the coordinates to the Republic's adrenal stashes. If they can play that game, so can the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Secure the area for the new supply depot and make sure Alpha Squad didn't die for nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71432" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not interested. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71433" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, then. Back to Plan A. At the very least, the adrenals should help me get rid of this headache.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71435" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's going to pay. Soon as the ringing in my ears stops.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
