<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>43</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/rishi/hub_1/the_cove_crier/shared/crier_droid.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings to you! Would you like to hear a true story about the legendary Howling Tempest Gang?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132414" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh--I beg your pardon! I didn't realize it was you! How exciting! Such a pleasure to make your acquaintance!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132416" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should consider yourself honored and fortunate to have this opportunity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aren't I the greatest?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed, I do! My master did not prepare me for the sheer measure of awe I would be required to process!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132419" id2="17" version="1065353216">What exactly is your purpose?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are you doing this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132420" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been assigned by my master to spread word of your many accomplishments throughout all of Raider's Cove!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoever put you up to all this lied to you. I'm not who you think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not the pirate thing again....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132423" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought my master told me everything, but I had no idea you were so modest!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why, in the time since your arrival, you have already defeated the illustrious Gorro, brought fear to the Corellian Run Scoundrels and Carida Corsairs....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132427" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even the Nova Blades have taken notice of you! My master would be most impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arrange a meeting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132430" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're going to take me to your master--whether you'd like to or not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132432" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should like to confer with your master. You will arrange an introduction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't suppose there's any chance of your master coming around to chat?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132436" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know, I wouldn't mind a face-to-face with your master so I can get to the bottom of all this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132437" id2="17" version="1065353216">It just so happens that my master would like very much to see you, and has authorized me to direct you to a point of contact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is that impressive? What's so special about the Nova Blades?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132439" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Nova Blades?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132440" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid you would need to ask my master. Fortunately, I've been authorized to direct you to a rendezvous point so you can do just that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132442" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to know who has you broadcasting these stories about me. Give me a name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132442" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your master's identity--now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132443" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may direct any and all questions to my master, as I have been authorized to arrange an introduction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh--do be careful in your travels. Legend or no, Gorro's brother Grumm is severely displeased as to Gorro's fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be wary, people of Raider's Cove--the Howling Tempest Gang has come to Rishi!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132454" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will know true fear when you cast your eyes upon the Howling Tempest Gang!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132455" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic can't touch the Howling Tempest Gang, and the Empire is afraid to even try!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who has Kai Zykken so scared he won't even go outside? It's the Howling Tempest Gang!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132457" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Howling Tempest Gang's a perilous pack of pirates whose prowess rivals that of the Nova Blades!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132463" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look out, Raider's Cove! The Red Hulls are coming, and they've got an appetite for murder!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133582" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right, a pirate crew so vicious that they paint their ships with the blood of their victims! The Red Hulls!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it true that members of the Red Hulls actually eat their victims? Find out when they arrive on Rishi!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133584" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you consider yourself easily startled or especially delicious, steer clear of the Red Hulls!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you heard the terrifying tale of the Red Hulls? What about you? Or you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134094" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, gentlebeing! Let me regale you with the tale of the dread Red Hulls, and their monstrous, flesh-eating captain!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134096" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, my! You are the monstrous, flesh-eating captain of the Red Hulls! What a singular pleasure to meet you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134097" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who programmed you to say these things about me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134098" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd be happy to tell you! They're eager to meet you, after all! Big fans!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134100" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can find them at these coordinates. But do be careful! After your magnificent duel with Gorro, there may be others out for revenge!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me! You there! Have you heard of the dread Red Hulls, and their monstrous, flesh-eating captain?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
