<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>13</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/pvp/warzone/quests/empire_pvp_bounty_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="939406" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Ministry of War reports record-setting response to their recent call to arms. Citizens from across the Empire have answered the call to stamp out the insurrections along our borders and they have met with victory at every turn. Despite these notable accomplishments, there are still those who fail to realize the futility of raising their fists against our Empire.

Though they show the spine so many of their kind are lacking, their bravery is that of the animal, for they lack the sense to know their place in the galaxy. It is our duty to remind them.

Glory for the Empire!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="939414" id2="17" version="1065353216">Loyal servants of the Empire, press the attack and claim what is rightfully ours. Though our enemy may be giving ground, the Republic will fight us for every meter. It is only through tireless, unyielding, effort that we will pry every last world from their cold bloodless fingers.

Our forces continue to assault the enemy on every front and constant reinforcement is required. Veteran units are at a premium and can expected to be called to hold the line on active fronts all across the galaxy. Do not falter now, our birthright awaits.

Glory for the Empire!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="939415" id2="17" version="1065353216">War is upon us and make no mistake, there will be no merciful cessation to this slaughter. The time for diplomacy has passed.

Now is the time where your resolve will be tested and we will learn who among us are merely exceptional and who are without peer. Fight tirelessly and fight brilliantly, servants of the Empire, because it is to the victor that goes the spoils.

Glory for the Empire!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="982535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention Imperial personnel!

Region 29-2987, informally known as &quot;Outlaw's Den&quot; by the locals, should be considered a restricted area.

Rumors aside, disappearances in the region are not exaggerated. Aside from a few suspicious travelers, no one who has entered the region has returned.

Enter at your own risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1112863" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Minister of War has mustered a new swift action division to deliver swift and decisive response to emerging threats across the galaxy.

By volunteering you will be expected to deploy to warzones and battle for victory against the opposing forces.

- Click the Warzone Icon on your Mini-Map.
- Queue for a Warzone and Complete It.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1112864" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Minister of War has mustered a new swift action division to deliver swift and decisive response to emerging threats across the galaxy.

By volunteering you will be expected to deploy to warzones and battle for victory against the opposing forces.

Queue for Warzones and Win Three Matches.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1128113" id2="17" version="1065353216">PRIORITY MESSAGE: IMPERIAL FORWARD COMMAND

Enemy starfighter squadrons have become a nuisance to our fleet operations in several sectors. The eradication of these forces is now a priority.

Qualified pilots should report via terminal interface immediately to carry out their duty to the Empire.

- Click the Starfighter Icon on your Mini-Map.
- Complete Your Starfighter Ship Loadout.
- Click BATTLE to Begin!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1128115" id2="17" version="1065353216">PRIORITY MESSAGE: IMPERIAL FORWARD COMMAND

Enemy starfighter squadrons have become a nuisance to our fleet operations in several sectors. The eradication of these forces is now a priority.

Qualified pilots should report via terminal interface immediately to carry out their duty to the Empire.

- Click the Starfighter Icon on your Mini-Map.
- Complete Your Starfighter Ship Loadout.
- Click BATTLE to Begin!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1128116" id2="17" version="1065353216">PRIORITY MESSAGE: IMPERIAL FORWARD COMMAND

The Empire's campaigns are proceeding according to plan. Additional recruitment of qualified starfighter pilots has been approved to ensure the fastest possible success for our ongoing operations.

Serve the Empire--report immediately.

- Click the Starfighter Icon on your Mini-Map.
- Complete Your Starfighter Ship Loadout.
- Click BATTLE to Begin!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1144003" id2="17" version="1065353216">The magnanimous Giradda the Hutt has graciously invited you to entertain him in his Arena of Death! Join the arena by toggling the holographic signal at the bottom right of your mini-map overlay. Remember to fight with honor and always pay respect to your host Giradda!

-Baron Deathmark</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144122" id2="17" version="1065353216">The magnanimous Giradda the Hutt has graciously invited you to entertain him in his Arena of Death! Join the arena by toggling the holographic signal at the bottom right of your mini-map overlay. Remember to fight with honor and always pay respect to your host Giradda!

-Baron Deathmark</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1220088" id2="17" version="1065353216">The magnanimous Giradda the Hutt has graciously invited you to entertain him in his Arena of Death! Join the arena by toggling the holographic signal at the bottom right of your mini-map overlay. Remember to fight with honor and always pay respect to your host Giradda!

-Baron Deathmark</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220089" id2="17" version="1065353216">The magnanimous Giradda the Hutt has graciously invited you to entertain him in his Arena of Death! Join the arena by toggling the holographic signal at the bottom right of your mini-map overlay. Remember to fight with honor and always pay respect to your host Giradda!

-Baron Deathmark</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
