<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>13</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/pvp/warzone/quests/republic_pvp_bounty_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="941766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Peacekeepers. The office of the Supreme Chancellor would like to report that you are in good company. Enlistment is occurring in record numbers across the galaxy. From the Deep Core to Outer Rim, brave citizens are stepping up to the challenge of defending our borders. The Republic owes each of you a debt of gratitude.

Reports of border skirmishes are also on the rise, many of you can expect to be called upon for deployment. Be prepared and be vigilant.

For the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="941774" id2="17" version="1065353216">We face a prideful enemy. The Empire is a foe that will not accept defeat, surrender or peace. No matter how hopeless their cause is, they will fight us to the bitter end. To defeat them, we must exceed their resolve, face them wherever they choose to make a stand and knock them to their knees. Make no apologies and seek no forgiveness for those you cast down, mercy is a courtesy the Empire never extended us when they sacked our homes and enslaved our citizens.
  
The time for civility has passed. Show the enemies of freedom that we will be pushed no farther.

For the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="941775" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have no shortage of heroes, volunteers and enlisted alike, who have been willing to take up arms and defend this Republic with everything they've got. Those of you who still have more to give, do not falter now, your Republic needs proven veterans to lead our onward march.

Your leadership, your endurance, and your dedication will be tested to their brink. Not all of you will be up to the task, but when history asks how you will be remembered, how will you answer?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="982425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Militia advisory!

Disappearances are up near the Outlaw's Den again. Count's fifteen just this week, including patrols.

Nobody head out that way. Spread the word and get travelers to steer clear.

Whatever you people think is out there, it ain't worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1112865" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senate has authorized a new force of volunteer peacekeepers to stand vigil against emerging threats across the galaxy.

By volunteering you will be expected to deploy to warzones and battle for victory against the opposing forces.

- Click the Warzone Icon on your Mini-Map.
- Queue for a Warzone and Complete It.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1112866" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senate has authorized a new force of volunteer peacekeepers to stand vigil against emerging threats across the galaxy.

By volunteering you will be expected to deploy to warzones and battle for victory against the opposing forces.

Queue for Warzones and Win Three Matches.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1128117" id2="17" version="1065353216">REPUBLIC FIRST FLEET DISPATCH//PRIORITY CODE AUREK

Long-range sensors show increased Imperial starfighter activity near several key strategic locations. Additional flight-certified personnel will be needed to counter this imminent threat.

All volunteers should submit credentials via terminal interface ASAP. The Republic is counting on you!

- Click the Starfighter Icon on your Mini-Map.
- Complete Your Starfighter Ship Loadout.
- Click BATTLE to Begin!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1128118" id2="17" version="1065353216">REPUBLIC FIRST FLEET DISPATCH//PRIORITY CODE AUREK

Long-range sensors show increased Imperial starfighter activity near several key strategic locations. Additional flight-certified personnel will be needed to counter this imminent threat.

All volunteers should submit credentials via terminal interface ASAP. The Republic is counting on you!

- Click the Starfighter Icon on your Mini-Map.
- Complete Your Starfighter Ship Loadout.
- Click BATTLE to Begin!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1128119" id2="17" version="1065353216">REPUBLIC FIRST FLEET DISPATCH//PRIORITY CODE AUREK

Repeated engagements with Imperial starfighter forces have taken a heavy toll, but victory is still within reach! Our campaign against the Empire can still succeed with the help of brave volunteers!

Sign up now--for the Republic!

- Click the Starfighter Icon on your Mini-Map.
- Complete Your Starfighter Ship Loadout.
- Click BATTLE to Begin!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144124" id2="17" version="1065353216">The magnanimous Giradda the Hutt has graciously invited you to entertain him in his Arena of Death! Join the arena by toggling the holographic signal at the bottom right of your mini-map overlay. Remember to fight with honor and always pay respect to your host Giradda!

-Baron Deathmark</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144125" id2="17" version="1065353216">The magnanimous Giradda the Hutt has graciously invited you to entertain him in his Arena of Death! Join the arena by toggling the holographic signal at the bottom right of your mini-map overlay. Remember to fight with honor and always pay respect to your host Giradda!

-Baron Deathmark</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1220086" id2="17" version="1065353216">The magnanimous Giradda the Hutt has graciously invited you to entertain him in his Arena of Death! Join the arena by toggling the holographic signal at the bottom right of your mini-map overlay. Remember to fight with honor and always pay respect to your host Giradda!

-Baron Deathmark</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1220087" id2="17" version="1065353216">The magnanimous Giradda the Hutt has graciously invited you to entertain him in his Arena of Death! Join the arena by toggling the holographic signal at the bottom right of your mini-map overlay. Remember to fight with honor and always pay respect to your host Giradda!

-Baron Deathmark</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
