<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/dromund_kaas/world/sport_hunting/weng_wrightsyn.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550308" id2="17" version="1065353216">No new murders, and that bounty hunter seems to have disappeared. I knew I was right about him!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550309" id2="17" version="1065353216">The murderer's name is Renegin. He's hiding in the Mandalorian enclave. Go look if you don't believe me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seven brutal, bloody murders. Seven! And the killer is allowed to walk free?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550312" id2="17" version="1065353216">Decent, law-abiding citizens--loyal servants of the Emperor--are being slaughtered. And what do our security forces do? Nothing!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550314" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen the killer myself, but the authorities say I don't have enough proof. I demand justice!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are you yelling at me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="550315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm down!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550316" id2="17" version="1065353216">I apologize for raising my voice, my lord. But these murders cannot go unpunished--not when the killer is so obvious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550318" id2="17" version="1065353216">You haven't heard about the horrible murders? Ghastly crimes--and I know who committed them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because you probably know the killer. He's a professional manhunter, like you! Well, hopefully not just like you....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550324" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must be heard. I'm the only one who knows the truth!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, I'm--I'm not fit to confront such an individual. But someone has to!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Several days ago, I spotted a bounty hunter following people seemingly at random--but pointing a strange device at them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550331" id2="17" version="1065353216">The descriptions of the murder victims exactly match the people the hunter was following. He's behind these brutal killings--I know it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only a coward kills defenseless people from the shadows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="550332" id2="17" version="1065353216">He sounds like scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550333" id2="17" version="1065353216">And only a brave guardian like you can bring that coward to justice, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550335" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admire any killer who leaves so faint a trail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="550335" id2="17" version="1065353216">How interesting....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, but he didn't elude detection, my lord, I saw him--and now I'll make certain everyone knows his name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bounty hunters--so unsubtle. A real professional wouldn't be detected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="550338" id2="17" version="1065353216">What an obvious fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550339" id2="17" version="1065353216">And he never saw me watching him. He must think he's invincible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550341" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lots of bounty hunters kill for a living. Me, for instance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="550341" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe it's just a job?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550342" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing professional about these murders. They're sickening--depraved, even.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, what a relief. I've been trying to get someone--anyone--to listen to me for days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550348" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. I know what I saw. I--I made no mistakes, I'm sure of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550350" id2="17" version="1065353216">I followed the killer this morning. Saw him skulking into the Mandalorian enclave. Someone called him by name--Renegin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550352" id2="17" version="1065353216">I followed the killer this morning. Saw the filthy alien skulking into the Mandalorian enclave. Someone called him by name--Renegin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550354" id2="17" version="1065353216">This bounty hunter must learn the Empire doesn't tolerate gutter scum like him killing its citizens. He needs to be punished!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550355" id2="17" version="1065353216">This bounty hunter must learn the Empire doesn't tolerate alien scum like him killing its citizens. He needs to be punished!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="550357" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please excuse me. I'm waiting to speak with a security commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="935962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Obsess much?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="935963" id2="17" version="1065353216">You certainly are loud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="935966" id2="17" version="1065353216">From me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="935984" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then let's punish him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="935987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your evidence is thin.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
