<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>82</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/intro/imperial.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoa. You look like Jaesa did that time she tried exoboar soup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey. You okay? You look like me after we went out for shaclaw on Voss and you had to hold my lekku.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142826" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had a vision. There was a galaxy neighboring our own, and then... nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every star went dim, both in that galaxy and our own. The end of everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142829" id2="17" version="1065353216">See? Probably just something you ate. Maybe? I hope?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142831" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another galaxy? Would you say it was a dwarf galaxy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, my lov--my lord, I didn't mean to eavesdrop.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me, my lord; I couldn't help but overhear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142837" id2="17" version="1065353216">A dwarf galaxy sounds right. What do you know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142838" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is such a galaxy off the Outer Rim, known as the Rishi Maze.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143257" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rishi? I've heard of Rishi. It's a planet. Some kind of pirate resort? Sounds like a real dive. I've kinda always wanted to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1143259" id2="17" version="1065353216">We get strange datamails from Rishi. We do not ask for them. Offers of free travel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143260" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've started receiving these recently?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1143261" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. Sith understands. And there is no sender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quinn, set a course. We're going to Rishi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reach out with your emotions. Let them guide you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143267" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes... that's it....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ahh!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ashara, tell me: what did you see?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143272" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was... it was you. You were in a jungle. Roots and vines, they took you, bound you, and then....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143274" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were torn apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143277" id2="17" version="1065353216">You saw the future. One of many possible futures, but a probable one, at the very least.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I heard a voice. A woman. She reached out to me through the Force. She told me you had to go to Rishi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143314" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rishi. You said Rishi?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143317" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't want you to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rishi's been coming up on the navicomputer. Thought it was some kind of glitch. Nothing out there but my kind of people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143320" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is no glitch. It is a message.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me guess: you're thinking of walking straight into a trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143326" id2="17" version="1065353216">An invitation for you and me to go off on a little pirate holiday? Heh, no, I know better than that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps it is a trap. What of it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell the crew there's been a change of schedule. I should very much like to visit this &quot;Rishi&quot;....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1143615" id2="17" version="1065353216">It not Blizz's fault!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143617" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you did it, Blizz. I always catch you messing with stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1143621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blizz not know what Torian mean, but boss take love-love Torian word over Blizz any day.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1143625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blizz not know what Torian mean. Blizz not mess with any stuff, ever!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, you two. Someone care to explain?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone plotted a course on the Mantis's navcom without running it by anyone. We were about to make the jump when I caught it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1143629" id2="17" version="1065353216">How Blizz do that? Blizz never even hear of... what planet name?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rishi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143633" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think it was Blizz. In fact, I'm pretty sure it wasn't anyone on the ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Telling me we were sliced? How were you not on top of that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, I don't know. Maybe because you've been keeping me, uh, busy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never saw a data routine like it before. Looks like Republic spy stuff, but modified. And that's just part of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143644" id2="17" version="1065353216">Been up on the Blacklist lately? Every listing claims Rishi was the mark's last known location, including....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143646" id2="17" version="1065353216">A bounty. On him. Right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess someone wants me to go to Rishi. Well....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143649" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of gal would I be if I disappointed them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143651" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of guy would I be if I disappointed them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143657" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, agent. Was kinda hoping to find you in bed. Guess you're busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143661" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, agent. Doing a little research, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143662" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's nothing that can't wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, good, 'cause I did that sweep like you asked. Found something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143665" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are we looking at?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143666" id2="17" version="1065353216">A homing beacon sends a broadcast, not a direct signal, so we can't discover directly who's tracking us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Transceivers along our route pick up the beacon's signal. If I triangulate the origin of someone collecting the beacon's data from those transceivers....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143671" id2="17" version="1065353216">As ever, we are enthralled with your mind. But we don't believe we have ever heard of this planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143676" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are impressed. But we don't believe we have ever heard of this planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rishi. I know it. Pirates and all that. Never been, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143679" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then it's your lucky day, Kaliyo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143681" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're going to Rishi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Wrath. Per your instructions, I am transmitting the navigational coordinates for the planet Rishi now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144357" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're mistaken. I haven't requested any navigational data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144358" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... oh. Rishi? Abrion sector? Outer Rim? No?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144360" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please forgive this error, my lord. The computer system must have suffered a failure of some kind. It won't happen again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh... good day, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, my lord. It is an honor to provide the coordinates for the planet Rishi, as you requested.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144365" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've made no such request.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144366" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... hm. You have my sincerest apologies, my lord. We must be suffering from a computer error.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144368" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rishi, Abrion sector, Outer Rim... a very strange glitch. With your leave, I will investigate at once. Farewell, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144370" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings... citizen. The navigational data you requested is being transmitted now: planet Rishi, Abrion sector, Outer Rim.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144371" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you talking about? I never ordered any nav data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you quite sure? I have your name and contact details listed quite plainly here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah. I'm sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144374" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh. Well, my apologies then. I won't trouble you any further--good day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144376" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good day, Commander. Per your request, I am transmitting all navigational information available for the planet Rishi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144377" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't request any navigational data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144378" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... hm. That's very strange. Your credentials and request are quite clear here: planet Rishi, Abrion sector, Outer Rim.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1144382" id2="17" version="1065353216">Must be some kind of computer error. I will ensure that it doesn't happen again--apologies for the inconvenience, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1145891" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was no mistake. We must go to Rishi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1145893" id2="17" version="1065353216">If someone is trying to get my attention... they have succeeded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1145896" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm either being messed with or sent a message--I don't care which. We're going to Rishi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1145899" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Computer error.&quot; No, I don't think so.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
