<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>88</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/the_tomb_opens/republic/master_satele_shan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="514524" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514526" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Carrick Station. The threat on Athiss is over, Master Satele. We gathered all the Sith artifacts we could.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514527" id2="17" version="1065353216">More importantly, you returned home safe. The Council no longer feels any disturbance in the Force coming from that world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Based on your discoveries, we now believe the ruins were once a great city built by a renegade Sith alchemist: Vodal Kressh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514531" id2="17" version="1065353216">According to these artifacts, Vodal Kressh raised an army to challenge the Emperor's rule. The beings you fought in the ruins were their descendants.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514532" id2="17" version="1065353216">The man who was controlling everyone was a powerful Force user. He'd had training.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their leader was a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many Sith refuse to merge with the Force when they die. It's possible Vodal Kressh still led his remaining followers, but you've ended that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe the Sith stranded Kressh and his followers on Athiss and abandoned them there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that why the Empire left?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kressh must have been a considerable threat, if the Emperor's solution was to leave the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514538" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care what they were. I'm just glad they're all dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514538" id2="17" version="1065353216">What matters is, they're done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Death and destruction should never be celebrated--but there is some good to come out of this evil.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514541" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Darth Malgus had secured these artifacts--and recruited the enemies you fought--it would have been disastrous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514543" id2="17" version="1065353216">These corrupted things will be sealed away where the Sith will never find them. We owe you a great debt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514544" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just returning the favors you paid me during my training.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anytime, Master Satele.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514545" id2="17" version="1065353216">That seems so long ago now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surely we stand to learn something from what we recovered. Must we hide the artifacts unexamined?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514547" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should study the artifacts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even the most experienced Jedi Master hesitates to work with Sith creations. Knowledge is power, but corrupted knowledge is deadly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514550" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can help me file a report with Command. They owe me hazard pay for this, but I'm not sure they'll believe my story.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talk to my superiors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514551" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will assure the Republic's military leaders of your valor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meet me for a meal at the Dealer's Den on Coruscant, and I'll forget all about what you owe me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514553" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Have dinner with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514554" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't accept such a generous offer, Captain. I have you at a disadvantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing says &quot;thank you&quot; like hard currency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514556" id2="17" version="1065353216">I gladly accept credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514557" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be rewarded for your efforts, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514559" id2="17" version="1065353216">You owe me nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514560" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a noble gesture. I'll make sure your payment is donated to the needy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514562" id2="17" version="1065353216">A little fame would be nice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your name is already known to those who matter most.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514565" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must report to the Jedi Council and inform them of what we've learned. Thank you again--and may the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="514567" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514569" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Carrick Station on secure channel &quot;ion eight.&quot; Do you read?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514570" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm receiving--and grateful you answered my call. I couldn't have asked for better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514572" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are one of the order's strongest champions. May your connection to the Force carry us to victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514574" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've earned a reputation for bravery. I hope that strength of spirit will be enough for this mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514576" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your team must face a powerful dark side presence. Failure to resist its influence could condemn you all to madness... or worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514577" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must face a powerful dark side presence and resist its influence. To fail could destroy your sanity... or worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever this evil is, I'll face it. I'm not afraid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514578" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't fear the dark side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514579" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514581" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's something more terrible than dying, or losing my mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514581" id2="17" version="1065353216">What could be worse?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many things. Let's hope you never discover them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514584" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've beaten everything else. I wouldn't mind adding &quot;insanity&quot; to the list.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally, a real challenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514585" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is no time for boasting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514587" id2="17" version="1065353216">We received a distress signal from the planet Athiss. Archaeological survey teams were excavating Sith ruins there. They awakened something while gathering ancient artifacts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514589" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dark side grows strong within those Sith ruins. And now the Jedi Council senses a profound disturbance in the Force there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would anyone explore Sith ruins in the first place?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514590" id2="17" version="1065353216">People shouldn't be there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their discovery was accidental. By the time anyone on the survey team realized exactly what they'd found, it was already too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did this planet once belong to the Sith? Why is the dark side so powerful there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about Athiss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514594" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith Empire colonized Athiss millennia ago, but abandoned it for unknown reasons. The explorers thought the world was uninhabited.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514596" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the situation is that bad, shouldn't Jedi Masters be handling it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is the Council going, then?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514597" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galaxy is growing unstable. Council members have their own emergencies to deal with. This one is mine--and yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514599" id2="17" version="1065353216">The survey team leader said his people were driven mad before being overwhelmed by something inside the ruins. He warned us to quarantine Athiss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514601" id2="17" version="1065353216">But now, intelligence reports indicate the Sith Empire intercepted those transmissions. Darth Malgus is putting together a strike team as we speak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514602" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll put an end to that evil presence before Malgus's lackeys can get anywhere near it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514602" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll be too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514603" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe our enemy wants to harness this evil presence. Don't let him succeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514605" id2="17" version="1065353216">Malgus must believe whatever is on that world can be useful to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514605" id2="17" version="1065353216">Malgus wants something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514606" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fear he's correct. The Empire has the advantage of knowledge we don't possess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514608" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should just wait for them to land and flatten the site from orbit. Problem solved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's bomb the ruins.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Members of the survey team may still be alive--and whatever infests the ruins will not be destroyed so easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514611" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've hired the right spacer, lady. Being first to the prize is what I'm famous for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514611" id2="17" version="1065353216">I always win races.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any relics in those ruins will be corrupted by the dark side. Please don't try to sell them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514614" id2="17" version="1065353216">That Sith name sounds familiar, but I can't put a face to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who is Darth Malgus?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Malgus is a formidable enemy who will stop at nothing to destroy us. That is all you need know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514617" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sick of the Empire always being one step ahead of us. Whoever is in charge of keeping our secrets is fired.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our security is worthless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514618" id2="17" version="1065353216">In moments like these, I cannot disagree with your assessment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever evil presence has been unleashed on Athiss must not be allowed to escape--or worse, become a weapon of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="514622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take a shuttle, end the dark side threat and gather all the Sith relics you find for study and containment. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="514623" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start Veteran Mode]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="514624" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1111989" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start Master Mode]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
