<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>6</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/heroic_weekly/imperial/mission_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Duke Keldas Thul has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Kaamos Territory sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Duke Keldas Thul may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Malichose has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Elysium above the Glarus Valley sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Lord Mailichose may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178296" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corporal Lanoyo has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Kaamos Territory sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Corporal Lanoyo may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178297" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rehmar Thul has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Kaamos Territory sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Rehmar Thul may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178298" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fannatex has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Kaamos Territory sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Fannatex may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gevin Thul has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Kaamos Territory sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Gevin Thul may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
