<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>145</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/world/imperial/expansion_plan/captain_revar.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see the Republic try to get in here now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670549" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's over. The reactor is secure, but you'll need someone to run it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good, good. I arranged for a contingency such as this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670552" id2="17" version="1065353216">Command is sending technicians and guards on the next shuttle down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670554" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's over. The reactor is secure, and the Empire now has a deal with the Ortolans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670555" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was hoping they'd stay on. The last time we took over a reactor, we had to translate all their labels into Basic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670557" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll ask Command to send reinforcements there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like we're going to be holding some ground after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670560" id2="17" version="1065353216">This planet should be about winning instead of stalemates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670560" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670561" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, who knows, maybe others will follow in your footsteps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670563" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670565" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm fond of the exhaustion strategy myself. We've cost the Republic ten times what we're worth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670567" id2="17" version="1065353216">But let's not talk theory when the real world demands our attention. The captain of Thesh Outpost on the glacier requires help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's move on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670570" id2="17" version="1065353216">We require no further assistance, but I would like to ask a personal favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670572" id2="17" version="1065353216">The captain of Thesh Outpost on the glacier is what you might call a friend. We went through the Academy together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670574" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said pirate outposts are hooked up to the reactor. What happens to them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670574" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the pirates?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670575" id2="17" version="1065353216">We cut their power and watch them run to a shelter with heat. They're easy pickings then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670577" id2="17" version="1065353216">But such trifles are our duty, not yours. You would be more useful at Thesh Outpost, on the glacier. The captain there is a friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670579" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's been wounded, and his outpost is battling a group of survivalist fanatics called the Hailstorm Brotherhood. You could make the difference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670580" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll go at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670580" id2="17" version="1065353216">Done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. I'll send word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670582" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670583" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is as much as I can ask. We must all look out for ourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670584" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have other matters in mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670584" id2="17" version="1065353216">My obligations come first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670585" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see. Well, too much to be hoped for, I suppose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670587" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you'll excuse me, I need to go check on the installation process for our guns. Good day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry! They're setting bombs in the reactor!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670590" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've already begun the installation of our defense systems, and we're on schedule to be done before nightfall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670592" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir? The Republic frequencies are alive with chatter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670594" id2="17" version="1065353216">They somehow knew we had a power surge just now, so I swept for bugs, and I found this: an energy monitor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we have a spy or a traitor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone's been in the base?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Based on the Republic's internal communications, they had this installed long before we took over this outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670598" id2="17" version="1065353216">I only looked because the Republic chatter was so obviously shocked by the influx of power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670601" id2="17" version="1065353216">The key thing is, they saw our power readouts and were shocked into action. And that's not good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670603" id2="17" version="1065353216">So they know about our new power source. What good will it do them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670603" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670604" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll look to cut us off at the root.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670606" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't attack here; they'll bomb the main geothermal reactor to black out the entire sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you agree that's the most likely target?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does that make sense, Captain?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670608" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the grid goes cold, it'll get rid of all the pirates plugged into it, too. It's a solid win for the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670610" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got my attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670611" id2="17" version="1065353216">It sounds like they figure with us and a lot of pirates all on the same grid, one fatal blow is better than trying to take the reactor over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670613" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll have to cut through the Ortolan workers there and the White Maw pirates, but they're sending Zero Squad snowtroopers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670615" id2="17" version="1065353216">How well-defended is this reactor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can they do it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670616" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's an Ortolan community that keeps the mechanics running, and they won't put up much resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670618" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're too used to knuckling under the White Maw pirates there. But the Republic is sending snowtroopers from Zero Squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670620" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I were a gambler like the captain here, I'd bet on them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not bet so hastily. I will put a stop to this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670621" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take over the reactor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very good, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670624" id2="17" version="1065353216">My name alone will destroy them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670624" id2="17" version="1065353216">They don't have long to live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, uh, I'm sure your confidence will serve you well, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Put a bounty on their heads, and you'll have them soon enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me a price.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. I thought you'd see it my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670630" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the installation is so key, I'll go myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670630" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, we can't have that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670631" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's central to our functioning, and the White Maw's. They aren't allies, but if they're stirred up, it's trouble for everyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670633" id2="17" version="1065353216">But concentrate on Zero Squad. They're the best cold-weather troopers the Republic has. Any defeat will humiliate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I should go quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zero Squad is the Republic's best. If you defeat them, just think of the humiliation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could someone explain to me why we aren't in control of this reactor to begin with?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670636" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't believe this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Part of the big Hoth plan. We were told to be efficient, and living on a small generator or your enemy's fuel is plenty efficient.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670639" id2="17" version="1065353216">But this is something new. The Republic destroying the reactor rather than capturing it--they're learning to fight like us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670641" id2="17" version="1065353216">All the more reason to humiliate them by taking out Zero Squad--let them see their heroes die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670643" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did it. We're running on geothermal power now. We blew a circuit when it came on, but that was easily fixed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did the Houks prove difficult?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670646" id2="17" version="1065353216">They proved clumsy and stupid. I could have fought twice that number.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670646" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670647" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's odd none of you are injured given their accuracy. But I won't refuse good news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670648" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought as much. Sith have an extremely high success rate in combat against irregular forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670649" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought as much. The White Maw have a good kill ratio versus regular troops, but nonstandard tactics like yours eat them up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670650" id2="17" version="1065353216">They would have killed me if I let them. I believe a &quot;thank you&quot; is in order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes... now show some respect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670651" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, I thought it went without saying that everyone in this base owes you a debt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670652" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, and it's time I was paid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670653" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't believe we discussed credits... but if that's the price for the outpost's survival, we can accommodate you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, if you'll excuse me, I need to oversee the deployment of our sensors and weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670657" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can stomp out those Houks and power the guns, our odds go up to fifty-fifty at least.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670658" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is this? I asked not to be disturbed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670660" id2="17" version="1065353216">No matter. It is a rare sight to see a stranger here, let alone more than one. I trust you have come to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, it is you. Commander Tritan and that Chiss fellow spoke well of you. Make yourself at home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670664" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, my apologies, my lord. I did not see it was you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me. I have had enough of interruptions today. You are, of course, welcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670668" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was busy calculating our chances in case the Republic attacks. It looks grim. If they bring a force of any real size, we're doomed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't focus on possibilities. Focus on what we will do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Control your own destiny.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670670" id2="17" version="1065353216">The best force multiplier would be installing more automated guns--which we have. However, they eat power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670672" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you have enemies, send me at them. You will be safe soon enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670672" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not with me here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our skeleton crew is willing to fight, but we need automated guns to make up for the lack of numbers. And those eat power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Troubling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670676" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's an understatement. We're understaffed, Dorn Base can't send us reinforcements, and our automated turrets eat too much power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670678" id2="17" version="1065353216">What we really need is to tap into the nearby geothermal power substation, but it's been taken by the White Maw.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670680" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have the manpower to take on those pirates, and we've got a base that'll black out in any sustained fight with the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Criminals are no threat to me, frozen ones less so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670681" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll kill the pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670682" id2="17" version="1065353216">The White Maw's Houks are more like an army than criminals. Our kill ratio for them is about one to ten.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670684" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never heard of Imperials backing down from a fight with pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pirates too tough for you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670685" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're Houks, part of a group called the White Maw--two and a half meters of muscle each.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670687" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last time they captured our men, they made them dig their graves in the ice using only their hands. Then they buried them alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670689" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't chance that happening again, so we haven't attacked their power substation. But you... your odds look good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670690" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you know you can't kill them? Have you tried?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670690" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're sure you'd fail?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670691" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've run mathematical models on a few battle scenarios, and the numbers don't look good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670693" id2="17" version="1065353216">We stand less than a six percent chance to clear the Houks off the substation without drastic casualties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670695" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the chance for capture or total loss is in the mid-thirties. That's far too high. You, on the other hand... your odds look good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670696" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can take out these monstrosities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670696" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670697" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no doubt of that. But you will need this energy coupling to restore the flow back toward the outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670699" id2="17" version="1065353216">These vagabonds will see what power truly is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670699" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of that I am certain. But take this energy coupling with you. You'll need it to switch the flow back toward the outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Install it when you have eliminated all resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670704" id2="17" version="1065353216">A pirate is a pirate. I've dealt with their kind before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670704" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670705" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't lose sleep over dead Houks. Now, you'll need this energy coupling to divert power back to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670707" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can get in there with no one being the wiser. Getting out... I make no promises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670707" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670708" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have to eliminate large numbers of them. They would certainly notice if you hooked up our energy coupling again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take this and install it when you've eliminated all resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670712" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've gambled on my future before, but rarely have I seen the math.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670712" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you think I can win, sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670713" id2="17" version="1065353216">My method has flaws, to be sure, but the soldiers here don't like to bet against me. Let me give you what you'll need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670715" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could do it, but in a Republic attack, they will cut your power first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670715" id2="17" version="1065353216">But your goal is flawed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670716" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mean like at Dorn Base? We've thought of that. Once it's ours, half of our turrets will be installed to cover the power substation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670718" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is an energy coupling you'll need to install when you've eliminated all resistance. It should divert flow back to the outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670720" id2="17" version="1065353216">With that power, our guns will be operational and give us a fighting chance. Go in strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Number crunching won't convince me to take a fool's errand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670722" id2="17" version="1065353216">No way. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670723" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's how you see it, I won't change your mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670725" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am assessing the situation. Leave me.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
