<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>47</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/class/bounty_hunter/crysta_markon.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="717856" id2="17" version="1065353216">PLACEHOLDER: Bark indicating that you cannot turn in/start Balmorra/Nar Shaddaa.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717857" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Balmorra, hunter. Your target is the right impressive Admiral Ivernus, they call him &quot;Admiral Untouchable.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spends all his time on a fancy flagship surrounded by armed soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't kill what you can't touch, hunter. You gotta lure Admiral Ivernus off his flyin' fortress and down to Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717863" id2="17" version="1065353216">To make things even more interestin', no friendly contacts here. You gotta figure this out yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717865" id2="17" version="1065353216">And don't forget--the job ain't done 'til you're the only hunter left standin'. Good luck!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mako, get me everything you can find on Admiral Ivernus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="717866" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Already on it. Logging in to the Imperial network now....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="717868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't need it, Crysta.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717869" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I like most about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717870" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's kidding, right? This is a suicide mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="717870" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was that a joke?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never stopped you before. Consider this a chance to show you've got more in your arsenal than a blaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717873" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm logging into the Imperial network. Let's see what I can dig up about this Admiral Ivernus....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717875" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's a war hero, all right. Actually won some battles against the Mandalorians. Wonder if that's how he got on the list?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm, this is interesting. Turns out, one of the admiral's toadies is in the market for a bounty hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get every piece of information on them you can pull down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="717878" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's our in. We got a name?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717879" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the job this toadie wants done?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="717879" id2="17" version="1065353216">Details?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717880" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing specific, but it's a high priority encoded message. Only top bounty hunters can access it--I had to hack it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="717882" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sure this is solid?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717883" id2="17" version="1065353216">You get rid of people's problems. I find out what they are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717885" id2="17" version="1065353216">The job listing contact is Lieutenant Major Pirrell. And get this--&quot;discretion is of the utmost importance.&quot; Whatever this is, Pirrell wants it secret.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's apply for a job and see if we can't work our way up to the admiral.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="717886" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a start.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717887" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Major Pirrell's office is at the Imperial base in Sobrik. Let's go impress him and see where it leads.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717888" id2="17" version="1065353216">How does this secret job help us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="717888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think we should follow up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717889" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's all I've got. Better than nothing, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperials have the best dirty little secrets. Remember Dromund Kaas?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="717891" id2="17" version="1065353216">If nothing else, it'll be fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dirty is right. I don't think I'll ever forget that poor admiral and his horrible daughter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717894" id2="17" version="1065353216">How 'bout we go have a chat with Lieutenant Major Pirrell at his office at the Imperial base in Sobrik--find out what he wants?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717898" id2="17" version="1065353216">You notice the Great Hunt never sends us anywhere nice?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717900" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's been fighting for control of Balmorra for years. Death toll's in the high seven figures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717901" id2="17" version="1065353216">War or no war, I've got a job to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="717901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717902" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm really starting to admire this professional attitude of yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717904" id2="17" version="1065353216">How is there anything left to fight over?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="717904" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a lot of war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717905" id2="17" version="1065353216">The weapons factories are built to withstand attack. The people aren't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess that death toll isn't high enough, if they're still fighting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="717907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Must still be resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717908" id2="17" version="1065353216">The resistance fighters have a lot of support. Rumor is, the Republic never really left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="717910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see what Crysta has to say about our job here. Starting the holo now....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
