<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>196</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_2/multi/shalim.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052891" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to the ark. When you're ready to leave Makeb, take the shuttle here at the camp. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052893" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ark's fuel rods, as promised. Toborro's gone--along with his entire supply of isotope-5.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052894" id2="17" version="1065353216">The whole planet felt it. Lemda says the explosion triggered a chain reaction in the planet's core.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052896" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you have unfinished business, better make it quick. I'll take the fuel rods and get our people to work installing them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052898" id2="17" version="1065353216">I left a shielded shuttle here at the camp. It's your ticket off Makeb. The rest of us are taking the ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052899" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're sure there's nothing else that needs to be done? Have all the planet's refugees made it aboard the ark?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052899" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you need any more help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052900" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ship is full and ready to fly. Thanks to you, we're about to achieve the fastest planetary evacuation in galactic history.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052905" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're in this together. If there's trouble, you'll need help. I'm sure the ark can seat a few extra people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052905" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's all ride the ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052906" id2="17" version="1065353216">The space is tighter than you can imagine. I appreciate the offer, but you've done more than enough for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052908" id2="17" version="1065353216">This has been quite a vacation, but I think it's time to go home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052908" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm leaving now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052909" id2="17" version="1065353216">And for us to find a new one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052911" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope we meet again on Keylander Station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052915" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we don't get those fuel rods from Toborro, my people are doomed. Our fates rest with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052918" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Cartel has deserted you, Toborro. You have no allies left--don't be a fool! Give us the fuel rods.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1052920" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never! The entire galaxy plots against me, but I still hold the ultimate power!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1052922" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let this planet tear itself apart! My fortress can withstand anything. When you are all dead, Toborro will still remain! This galaxy is mine!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toborro, there's something very wrong with you. Listen to what you're saying--it doesn't make sense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052923" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need psychological help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1052924" id2="17" version="1065353216">No more words! Now, only death!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052925" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you're overestimating your real estate, Toborro. When this planet goes, you're going with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you really want to die?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1052926" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am eternal! I am invincible!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052927" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're done negotiating with that insane Hutt. Cut the comm and stop wasting time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Switch off this crazy fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052928" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought I could appeal to the businessman in him. Apparently, that part of Toborro no longer exists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052930" id2="17" version="1065353216">That inbred imbecile has abandoned all sanity. You will have to take the ark's fuel rods by force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052932" id2="17" version="1065353216">His palace is a testament to my artistry. I poured my spirit into designing lethal defenses. I also left myself a private entrance inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052933" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finding a way inside the palace is the least of our problems. We're heading into the heart of a lunatic's private playground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052933" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's good, but only a start.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052934" id2="17" version="1065353216">A secret back door? I'm starting to like you, Oggurobb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052934" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sneaky little Hutt--I approve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052935" id2="17" version="1065353216">My charms are legion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroying your creations is always a blast. Those droids look terrific engulfed in flames.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052937" id2="17" version="1065353216">I enjoy trashing your work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052938" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is by design. Color! Vibrancy! Impact! Destruction should never be dull.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toborro will have far more than my inspired designs guarding him. His most lethal soldiers and isotope-5 droids patrol every corridor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052942" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll hold this position until you get back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052944" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without those fuel rods, millions will die. If you can't get them... I'm canceling your parade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell your people not to worry. We'll get those fuel rods no matter what.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052945" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll return, I promise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052946" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052948" id2="17" version="1065353216">Parades are nice, but I'd rather have a kiss for luck before I go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052948" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] I like you, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052949" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate flying into certain death with dry lips. Help me out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052949" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Kiss for luck, Lemda?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052952" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why not....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052954" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have people with blasters. Throw a few of them at Toborro for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052954" id2="17" version="1065353216">No backup from your citizens?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052955" id2="17" version="1065353216">My followers aren't soldiers. They'd only get in your way--and die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052957" id2="17" version="1065353216">You now have coordinates and the security code to my secret entrance. Once you're inside, contact me for more information. Don't die!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052961" id2="17" version="1065353216">A shuttle will fly you to the mining platforms. We must shut down those drilling lasers before it's too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor, it's such an honor. I'm so glad we weren't forced to kill you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052965" id2="17" version="1065353216">We held up our end of the bargain and got you to safety. Tell us about isotope-5--and how to fuel the ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052965" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't make our guest any more nervous than he already is. The Republic only kills in self-defense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052966" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was never the plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052967" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I saw on our flight from Sanctuary, you specialize in artful property damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052969" id2="17" version="1065353216">The jury's still out on that. If he doesn't start being useful quick, he'll be a permanent resident.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get his hopes up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052970" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am a living repository of boundless knowledge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that you're here... what can you tell us about isotope-5? How does it fuel the ark?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isotope-5... Toborro's great discovery at the center of Makeb. Something truly unique in all the galaxy--and worth destroying this planet to obtain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imagine a substance as light as shimmersilk but stronger than durasteel. It distorts gravity and electromagnetic fields so predictably that it can be refined into fuel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isotope-5 has limitless potential to remake this galaxy. Those droids you battled were first-generation prototypes. Playthings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052979" id2="17" version="1065353216">In Toborro's hands these weapons will oppress entire sectors. The Cartel will become as bad as the Empire--maybe worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deadly toys for conquest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052980" id2="17" version="1065353216">More profitable than the Imperials, one would hope. Honestly, we don't know how they support themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isotope-5 is the Cartel's key to becoming a galactic superpower. That's why they invaded Makeb and why Toborro won't back down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052982" id2="17" version="1065353216">It all makes sense now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052983" id2="17" version="1065353216">He has staked the Cartel's entire future on this world. He cannot fail here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052985" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Toborro gets off Makeb with his droids and all the isotope-5, he'll topple the Republic and Empire both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052985" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is bad news for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, good--you're following the logic. No need for me to elaborate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052988" id2="17" version="1065353216">With an isotope-5-powered army, Toborro could squash half the galaxy. No wonder he isn't giving up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052988" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is very, very bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052989" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you have become the itch mite in his soup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you saying there are even more advanced versions of those droids? How many? What are their capabilities?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are there upgraded droids too?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toborro has dozens of prototype weapons. Their capabilities vary based on whatever creative inspiration moved me that day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop making excuses for your shoddy workmanship. I trashed your playthings, and I'll break anything else Toborro throws at me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052994" id2="17" version="1065353216">I broke them easily enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sadly, I doubt you will encounter my more advanced designs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052997" id2="17" version="1065353216">I crafted a beautiful set of isotope-5 fuel rods to power Toborro's ark. Some of my finest work, but you'll never see it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052999" id2="17" version="1065353216">According to my datastream, Toborro has increased mining production to maximum levels. Makeb's destruction will arrive far ahead of schedule. You have a spacecraft, yes? We should depart immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053000" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not leaving our people behind. If Toborro's drilling has accelerated Makeb's destruction, turning it off should slow it back down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053000" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll shut down the mining.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053001" id2="17" version="1065353216">We won't abandon millions of Makeb refugees. You said you could help us get the fuel rods back!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053001" id2="17" version="1065353216">We only leave with the ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053002" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was before I saw the latest updates on Toborro's drilling operations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053004" id2="17" version="1065353216">You never intended to help us. All you wanted was a way off Makeb before Toborro sent a hit squad after you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053004" id2="17" version="1065353216">You lying sack of filth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053005" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, no. I only became aware of the drilling increase during our voyage here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053007" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mining platforms are massive lasers drilling directly into the planet. Shutting them down would release core pressure and buy us time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attacking the mining platforms would be suicidal. Even worse, it might kill me. Wait... why do I get the feeling you're serious?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053010" id2="17" version="1065353216">You just confirmed our next move. Stay put and hope we make it back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053010" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are seriously desperate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Death by Toborro or slow suicide with the Republic. Perhaps I have chosen poorly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053013" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does Toborro have guarding these mining platforms?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Define &quot;suicidal.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053014" id2="17" version="1065353216">With a steady supply of raw isotope-5, my former employer can power a multitude of devices designed to exterminate all trespassers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053016" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't trust this mound of flab as far as I can throw him. Stick him someplace secure--and small.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone lock up this Hutt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053017" id2="17" version="1065353216">An orbit-capable shuttle would do nicely. Joking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053019" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to deactivate all of Toborro's mining platforms. That's the only way to slow Makeb's destruction until we can get the ark's fuel rods.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053021" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fear it won't be as easy as flipping switches. The platforms and their control rooms will be heavily defended.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything on this planet has been an ordeal--I'd hate to break our perfect record. But don't worry, those drilling lasers are going offline.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053022" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expect a challenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053023" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they don't, I doubt we'll see each other again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053025" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surely Toborro has the platforms rigged to shoot down any incoming shuttles.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053025" id2="17" version="1065353216">How will we get to them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to Doctor Oggurobb's craft, we know what transponder frequency Toborro uses to identify &quot;friendly&quot; airspeeders. We'll fake them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053028" id2="17" version="1065353216">When it comes to body count, Makeb's groundquakes have nothing on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053028" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll kill the defenders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053029" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suspect that's not an exaggeration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053031" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have a transport to the mining platforms prepped for you immediately. Keep us apprised of your progress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get to the Sanctuary research base and capture Doctor Oggurobb. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, you're here. Good news: Tarlam's refugees evacuated safely--and no fresh reports of Toborro's droids. You bought us time... and we'll need it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053040" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Gez Addar, one of the Republic's top engineers and a brave man for coming down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Couldn't pass up a chance to thank the legendary Jedi who saved Coruscant. I was there when you stopped the Planet Prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053043" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised you know anything about that. It wasn't common knowledge at the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053043" id2="17" version="1065353216">That mission was top secret.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053044" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard about it well after the fact. Nothing like belatedly realizing you escaped certain doom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of all the Jedi, you're the one I've been most excited to meet. I'd love to pick your brain about holocron design.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Holocrons are more than merely technology. I'll happily discuss them with you--once we're all safely off Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Later, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053048" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll need time to think up questions, anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053050" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major, it's an honor. I have a complete collection of Havoc Squad holovids. Your army's victory on Corellia? Amazing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053051" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just a soldier doing a job. Some jobs are bigger than others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053051" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was only doing my duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053052" id2="17" version="1065353216">From what I hear, this job's your biggest yet. Evacuating a whole planet... incredible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053054" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, I was working at the Republic shipyards you saved from the Voidwolf. Any chance I can get your autograph--or a few hours to explore your ship?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053055" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like people poking around my ship. Autographs are no problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053055" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll sign something, sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053056" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fantastic. Here, you can scratch the screen on this datapad....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never thought I'd get to meet one of the Republic's top ten most famous heroes. Somebody pinch me.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1053059" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather just say hello.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053060" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the high point of my year. They called me crazy for volunteering to come down. Who's laughing now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053062" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't tell you what an incredible honor it is to meet you all. They stream holovids of you constantly to the fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053063" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a lot more to what we do than battling the Empire. My friends and I help people in need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053063" id2="17" version="1065353216">More than combat, I hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053064" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's why I'm here. Can't let you take all that risk alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053066" id2="17" version="1065353216">By risking your life to land on Makeb, you've shown great courage. Such acts inspire others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053066" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're all heroes here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think I'll wind up in a holovid, too? Give my parents something to show the neighbors? That'd be something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trust me, they edit those things to make us look good. We're just people fighting for the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those vids are embellished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure, and Coruscant's just a planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053072" id2="17" version="1065353216">How often do you see my face, on average? I really need to get a talent agent collecting credits on these things....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053072" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should be earning royalties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053073" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the most legendary privateer in the galaxy. People should be paying you to dock at their stations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053074" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been saying the same thing for years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053075" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you verified Toborro's claim that the ark will only run on isotope-5?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053075" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you tell us about the ark?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053076" id2="17" version="1065353216">I analyzed the ark schematics. Despite them being borderline incomprehensible, I can now say with authority that they reveal Toborro's threat is authentic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053078" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you were a scientist. Sounds more like you're running for the Senate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053078" id2="17" version="1065353216">Boy, you're a slick one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053079" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm good with machines, but people are my real passion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053081" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gez just made it through the analysis of the ark schematics. I'm sad to report that Toborro wasn't lying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053083" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ark was specifically built to run on isotope-5. It's the only energy source capable of pushing that massive vessel through Makeb's atmosphere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053084" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still haven't heard a decent explanation for what that substance is. What makes isotope-5 so special?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053084" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you explain isotope-5?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053085" id2="17" version="1065353216">It appears to be a radioactive variant of illerium unique to Makeb's planetary core. From what little I've examined, it's nearly a template element.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isotope-5 can be modified into all manner of useful configurations, including a potent fuel source. But I'm no expert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053088" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those war droids Toborro sent to attack Tarlam also ran on isotope-5. Maybe we could convert their power cores into fuel?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053088" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toborro's droids run on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053089" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd be acquiring it in such small amounts that we'd never get enough before Makeb's core goes critical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053090" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's it? You don't have a plan to fix it? What kind of engineer are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053090" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some help you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053091" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to be realistic. Makeb's days are numbered, and dropping quickly. Isotope-5 is our only solution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053093" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we need the real brains behind the Hutt Cartel's operations here: Doctor Juvard Illip Oggurobb. And we know where he is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053095" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoa--the only five-time winner of the Bao-Dur Science Prize is on Makeb? Are you saying he designed the ark?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053097" id2="17" version="1065353216">Probably those droids, too. Doctor Oggurobb has been holed up at the Sanctuary research complex since before his people invaded. If anyone knows about isotope-5, it's him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053098" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like we're headed for Sanctuary. We need a full briefing, and quick. I can feel the ground shifting while we stand here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053098" id2="17" version="1065353216">Point me at him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053099" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would a Hutt scientist help us at all? Isn't he with the Cartel?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053099" id2="17" version="1065353216">This doctor is a Hutt, too?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053100" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Oggurobb is well respected across the galaxy. For a Hutt, he's pretty reasonable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053102" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never met a Hutt who had a spine. I'll get this Doctor Oggurobb on our side--in pieces, if that's what it takes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053102" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'll talk, or die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053103" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt it'll come to that. Smart people know when to surrender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053105" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sanctuary research complex is one of the most advanced experimental laboratories in the galaxy. It's on an isolated mesa completely under Hutt control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053107" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no telling what sort of defenses a genius like Doctor Oggurobb has there, and you'll be going in blind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053109" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are data access terminals on Sanctuary's testing grounds. Try accessing one--it might let you disable any unwelcome surprises. Otherwise, good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053110" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care how well defended Sanctuary is--I'm tougher. I'll have Doctor Oggurobb back in time for dinner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053110" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to kidnap a Hutt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053111" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no plans to feed him. It would cost a fortune.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053113" id2="17" version="1065353216">I promise to stay alive. You'll be worried sick the whole time I'm gone, won't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053113" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Will you miss me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053114" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been worried sick since before you landed on Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why can't we just go after Toborro? He's the one with the ark's fuel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1053116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure about all this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053117" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're only getting one chance at this--we can't afford to be wrong about anything. Doctor Oggurobb has the knowledge we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1053119" id2="17" version="1065353216">And please, for the love of science--don't hurt Doctor Oggurobb. I didn't bring a way to preserve his brain.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
