<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>16</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/imperial_spy/chapter_1/a_new_epoch_of_fear/messages.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Message intercepted from Citadel command:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478789" id2="17" version="1065353216">It looks like Intelligence failed to catch the Eradicators in time. We'll have to declare a state of emergency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478791" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a miracle the Citadel hasn't been hit. I don't know if those terrorists wanted to spare us, but it gives us a fighting chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478793" id2="17" version="1065353216">Message intercepted from the Kwenn system, source unknown:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478795" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're burning up! We need authorization to evacuate--Lord Phaaral will kill us if we abandon station, but we can't last....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478797" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please. My name is Thranc Roulus. I have family in Kaas City. Give us the order to evacuate....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Message intercepted from Sernpidal City:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478801" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know if anyone's receiving this. It may be too late anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478803" id2="17" version="1065353216">They hit the bunker first. There couldn't have been more than a dozen soldiers inside, mostly civilians. But they blew the whole thing up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478805" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's going on? Is it terrorists? Is it Republic? What's happening?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Message intercepted from Moff Lett-Shara:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478809" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's going on? I'm getting reports of three separate attacks--two on Sith training grounds, one on a blasted hospital!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478811" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was told we'd be warned if the Eradicators couldn't be stopped! Get me the Intelligence Minister now--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Message intercepted from Rinn mining colony:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something's happening--we're under attack, but there aren't any ships. The command post was cut in half by a beam from the sky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone who receives this--help us. Our defenses are minimal, we can't--</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
