<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>58</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/voss/world/imperial/settling_scores/lieutenant_quorr.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600879" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've sent those plans you recovered to my superiors. Soon the Jedi won't have any secrets left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600883" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found these while I was clearing out the Jedi outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600884" id2="17" version="1065353216">This looks like part of the Jedi's defensive strategy for Voss! I'll get this to my superiors immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Between these plans and annihilating their base, you've struck a real blow against the Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600889" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi won't be using their little outpost anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600890" id2="17" version="1065353216">We intercepted a distress call; I wondered if it might be your handiwork.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600892" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll be too busy trying to rebuild to interfere much with our truce with the Voss. Nice work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600893" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate to think of it as work; taking care of the Jedi is fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="600893" id2="17" version="1065353216">I enjoyed that too much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fun? If you say so, but I'm glad you handled them instead of us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600895" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any responsible citizen could see the Jedi were a threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="600895" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did what had to be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600896" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll be less of a concern now, thanks to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="600897" id2="17" version="1065353216">My part in this is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600898" id2="17" version="1065353216">With their communications disrupted, we should be able to handle anything the Jedi can organize. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600902" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've picked up some distress signals from the outpost I mentioned--I thought you might like to know there're still survivors up there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600905" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you're here, my lord, I've just received important news from our spies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, I've just received important intel from one of our advance recon teams.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me, I don't want to seem presumptuous, but I've got important intelligence that needs to be shared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600911" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've uncovered a hidden Jedi outpost in the cliffs not far from here; they don't know we've found them yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600912" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi must be dealt with, immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="600912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ready your men for an attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600913" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, I can't send troops out there. My commander has really tied my hands on this one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600915" id2="17" version="1065353216">This sort of information is vital to the Empire's plans; your commander needs to be informed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="600915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you told your commander?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600916" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's busy dealing with the Voss. I'm telling you because you might be able to do something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="600918" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me you've dealt with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600919" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's just it, I'm telling you about it because I can't deal with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600921" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not allowed to initiate an attack. The higher-ups say we can't breach the supposed peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600923" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been told it's important to keep the Voss happy, but this is a special circumstance--surely something can be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave it to me. The Jedi will regret ever coming to Voss, and the natives won't ever know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="600924" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle this quietly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600925" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're asking me to defy your superiors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="600925" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to break the peace?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="600926" id2="17" version="1065353216">This sounds like your problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600927" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was hoping you'd be able to do what I can't. I said I'm not allowed to send troops to attack the base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600929" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi think we won't risk the truce, my lord, but you could wipe them out without the Voss ever knowing. It's perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, a Sith of your skill and authority could handle the Jedi, and the Voss would never know about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, as an independent operator, you're not technically bound by the truce. You could go after the Jedi yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600932" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'd be improper to suggest abandoning regulations, sir, but you've freedom enough to attack the Jedi yourself--the Voss'd never know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600933" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't rule out an independent strike, however--you'd have the advantage of surprise; they'd be defenseless against you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600934" id2="17" version="1065353216">They think they're safe from the Empire. They're wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="600934" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave the Jedi to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600935" id2="17" version="1065353216">The &quot;peace&quot; is amusing, but it shouldn't define our actions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="600935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Treachery is my business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Taking out their outpost should disrupt their activities for a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="600936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makes sense tactically.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hitting a hidden Jedi outpost sounds like my kind of fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="600937" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600938" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't envy them having to face you in a closed space. They'll wish we'd never found them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="600940" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it if I find the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600941" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand. I'm just passing the information along to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600943" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, if you find anything that hints at the Jedi's activities, Captain Mereel will want to see it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600947" id2="17" version="1065353216">When your commander decides what to do, you can take care of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="600947" id2="17" version="1065353216">Await orders. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600948" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand. I'll compile my report for Captain Mereel's return and hope the Jedi don't pull up stakes before he gets back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600950" id2="17" version="1065353216">These earthquakes are driving me crazy. I've swallowed enough dust to build Voss another moon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="600951" id2="17" version="1065353216">With their outpost destroyed, the Jedi can't interfere with our negotiations with the Voss.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
