<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>15</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/daily_area/ziost/world_arc/shared/a_presence_on_ziost/console.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149264" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can feel your presence... Vitiate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone there? Theron?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149269" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had foreseen your arrival, but I didn't believe it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, my Wrath. I foresaw your arrival, but I didn't quite believe it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149271" id2="17" version="1065353216">My little insect, no doubt here to drone and flutter once more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149273" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought, after bearing witness to my rebirth on the Yavin moon, why? Why would you stand in the face of certain death?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149275" id2="17" version="1065353216">And then I realized: you're a simple one. Not terribly bright. But that's fine--I'm rather pleased you're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149278" id2="17" version="1065353216">I promised on the Yavin moon that I would devour you last, and yet here you are. So impatient.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149280" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you've lived as long as I have, patience comes far more easily--but that's neither here nor there. I must say, I'm glad you're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149282" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dromund Kaas, the Yavin moon... It must not be clear to you yet. There is nothing you can do to stop me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149284" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll bear witness to a world's end if you survive long enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149289" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's all right, though. Seeing you, it's like visiting with a forgotten friend. I'm oddly pleased you're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana? Are you there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149293" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're far from stupid, I know that much. Overly ambitious, perhaps. Well, regardless, I do hope you find your time on Ziost enlightening.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
