<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>55</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/bronze/hasty_exit/resistance_fighter.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to know we can count on the Republic again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296845" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have the data files. The encampment is without a commander as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice work. I said I'd throw in a bonus if you got rid of him, and I'm as good as my word.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296848" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said you don't work cheap, and I promised a bonus if you took him out. And I honor my promises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296850" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have the data files.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never thought I'd say this to someone from the Republic, but I'm impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296853" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're expensive, but at least you're worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296855" id2="17" version="1065353216">You saved a lot of lives by doing this. My friends and I owe you. Thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bring me the intel files from the encampment before the Imperials decode them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296863" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi? Don't see too many of your kind on Balmorra these days.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to see you Republic soldiers back on Balmorra. Kinda wished you'd never left.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296867" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't look like you're part of the resistance. You must be with the Republic, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Name's Taya Rinn. Been fighting the Imperials here on Balmorra since I learned to walk.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296871" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, you in this for the long haul? Or is the Republic going to cut and run again as soon as things get tough?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296872" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic has got your back. Count on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296872" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will support you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296873" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd like to believe that. But actions speak louder than words.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296875" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you'd be a little more appreciative of all the help we're giving you now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296875" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sound pretty bitter.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296876" id2="17" version="1065353216">We put our trust in the Republic, and they left us high and dry. But I know how you can make amends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296878" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand your frustration.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296879" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't want sympathy. We want help. And if you're serious, now's your chance to prove it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296881" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was at a nearby encampment when the Imperials hit us. Barely got out alive. Had to leave our intel files behind.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296883" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we don't get those data files back before the Imperials decode them, the resistance is in real trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296884" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's on those files, exactly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296884" id2="17" version="1065353216">They sound important.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Locations of resistance outposts. Names of spies and sympathizers inside the Imperial ranks. Stuff we don't want to fall into the wrong hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296887" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296888" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm willing to pay good credits for this job. A lot of resistance lives will be lost if you can't recover those files.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take out the leader of the Imperial forces at the Neebray encampment, and I'll throw in a nice bonus, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Taking out Imperials is part of my job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296891" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd help you anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to meet a Jedi who prefers action over meditation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296894" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi is not motivated by material wealth. I will help you because it is the right thing to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296894" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would help you anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296895" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very noble of you. I guess the stories about the Jedi are true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296897" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're on the same side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296897" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd help you anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296898" id2="17" version="1065353216">If all the Republic soldiers shared your attitude, we'd have driven the Imperials off Balmorra years ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296900" id2="17" version="1065353216">I figure the Republic owes you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296900" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd help you anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry. Just figured you were a mercenary. It's nice to see somebody here for the right reasons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296904" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're not stingy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296905" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't think the Jedi were into material wealth. Don't worry, though; you'll get plenty. After the mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't think you'd be so mercenary about it. Don't worry, though; you'll get plenty. After the mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Break into the encampment and get the data files from the main computer, then bring them back to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296911" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll pass. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should have known better than to expect help from the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296916" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not in the mood to talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="486804" id2="17" version="1065353216">The old encampment isn't too far off. There's an army of Imperial special ops camped out inside. Parasites.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="486805" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have to beat their leader to make it out with the intel. He won't be easy, but that's why I'm paying.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="486806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Break into the recon encampment, take out their leader, and get the data files from the main computer.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="486808" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can get those files back here. I'll have plenty of payoff waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="486811" id2="17" version="1065353216">Break into the recon encampment and get the data files from the main computer, then bring them back to me.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
