<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>8</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/heroic_weekly/imperial/mission_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Heedley has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Corellian Sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Captain Heedley may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178269" id2="17" version="1065353216">IMPERIAL TERMINATION INCENTIVE
BOUNTY LISTING #X489J2

Several Jedi combatants have invaded this sector. They are secretly lending support to the rebel alien refugees opposing Imperial interests. Loyal servants of the Emperor are encouraged to confront these Republic meddlers and eliminate them with extreme prejudice.

Reward will be delivered upon verification that the Jedi at key coordinates have all been neutralized.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Skav Mora has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Industrial Sector sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Skav Mora may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178271" id2="17" version="1065353216">HUTT CARTEL EMERGENCY BOUNTY POSTING

The Cartel seeks combat-worthy individuals who value Hutt generosity! A large pack of savage vrblthers has infested Network Access. These deadly predators are wreaking havoc at the power station. Trillions of important data files are at risk. The entire HoloNet itself may cease functioning!

The Cartel will lavishly reward any who eradicate the vrblthers and repair the damage before it is too late. Please be advised, several security teams have indicated the presence of unusually large vrblther pack elders. Additional information is unavailable, as the security teams have since disappeared.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178272" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Sharoleigh has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Industrial Sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Lord Sharoleigh may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178273" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gorn Sweevas has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Industrial Sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Gorn Sweevas may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent Ryleah has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Network Access sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Agent Ryleah may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glort has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Network Access sector of Nar Shaddaa. For additional details about the mission, Glort may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
