<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>169</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/world/republic/the_war_for_nar_shaddaa/deera_ulyette.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always good to see you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646647" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's over. Our people are safe from the Empire's threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646648" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hear that, Bareesh? How does it feel to back the winning team?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your victory was never in doubt--and now the Hutt Cartel has taken notice of your power. You've earned respect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Change is coming, Bareesh. The Cartel would be smart to recognize that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646651" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a good start.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646652" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one disagrees things will be different. The real question is, different for whom?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646654" id2="17" version="1065353216">Respect easily becomes fear in the weak-minded. The Cartel must see us as allies, not potential rivals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646654" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're here to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646655" id2="17" version="1065353216">You understand much about respect, Jedi--but little about Hutts. Every ally is a potential rival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646657" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell your friends if they even think about joining the Empire, Havoc Squad will be back for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646657" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd blasted well better have.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646658" id2="17" version="1065353216">They are not my friends--and the voices speaking in favor of your enemy have all gone quiet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anybody who doesn't respect me by now really hasn't been paying attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646660" id2="17" version="1065353216">I already had that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646661" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like you, Captain. Perhaps we can do business, someday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that the Cartel has seen what we can do, are they ready to kick the Empire off Nar Shaddaa and join our side?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646663" id2="17" version="1065353216">How about an alliance?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646664" id2="17" version="1065353216">You ask too much, too soon. Give things time. I will continue championing your people to the Cartel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646666" id2="17" version="1065353216">We didn't do this for your idiot government's approval, Bareesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646666" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Cartel can go hang itself.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly--and that is why they respect you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646669" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a major victory for the Republic. It's a shame we can't go public with it. Not yet, anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646671" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your actions here may go unreported, but you've certainly earned our sincere appreciation. Please accept this gift in recognition of your service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646672" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a generous reward. If you'll excuse me, my ship is waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646672" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're too kind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Material possessions don't mean much. I'd rather we spent some time together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646673" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] I only need you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646674" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seem to have more than enough company. Maybe some other time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646676" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather have the pleasure of your company. You could show me the nice parts of Nar Shaddaa.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646676" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Let's go someplace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Winning makes you bold, doesn't it? I like that. Say goodbye, Bareesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646679" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell, great hero! Enjoy your reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now it's just us. Follow me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646683" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know about you, but I'm enjoying Nar Shaddaa a lot more now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646684" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a shame I have to leave. I was just getting to know you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646684" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] This was wonderful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe someday we'll finish what we started. Take care of yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like my work here is done. Be careful, all right? I won't be around to protect you anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646686" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time for me to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646687" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're sweet. Stay safe out there. We'll see each other again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Feel free to keep enjoying yourself without me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646688" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least someone is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks, I'll do that. I'm sure you have someplace else to be. Somewhere far, far away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646690" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a bit... abrupt. This really isn't the best time. Maybe we'll see each other again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646692" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire doesn't accept defeat gracefully. Stay safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646692" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take care of yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646693" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be spending a lot more time here in the spaceport--and close to my ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646695" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's it? Next time I'll quote you a price in advance. And if you can't pay....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646695" id2="17" version="1065353216">War pays poorly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646696" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll be prepared to meet any price, should we need you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646698" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will be remembered as great heroes! I will see to it!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646699" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will be remembered as a great hero! I will see to it personally!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646703" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you doing back here? Your mission isn't over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646706" id2="17" version="1065353216">A who's who of Republic heroes. I'm glad I caught you before anyone left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646708" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're leaving quite a mark on Nar Shaddaa, Master Jedi--but I'm afraid your services are still needed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not every day I meet a Republic war hero. Wish I wasn't about to beg you for a favor....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646712" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the infamous freighter captain who crashed Drooga's party? Not leaving already, I hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646714" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it isn't Nar Shaddaa's newest celebrity. This place loves a winner. You should stick around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646716" id2="17" version="1065353216">Name's Deera Ulyette, Senate Special Liaison to the Hutt Cartel. I work with Hutts who are friendly to the Republic. Yes, they do exist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646718" id2="17" version="1065353216">An old pal of yours is making good on his promise to aid our cause: Bareesh Fenn'ak Torill. Remember him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646719" id2="17" version="1065353216">A gangster turned legitimate businessman--or so he says.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646720" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's working overtime to rehabilitate his image. We're liking what we see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646722" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've met a lot of Hutts, and they all have unusual names.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646722" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, I don't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646723" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'd be crushed you forgot him, especially after all the hard work he's done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646725" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does that festering blob of criminal filth want now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646725" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's a piece of scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ex-criminal filth. He's making amends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bareesh Fenn'ak Torill sends his regards. You were working with him and Ambassador Averdon to stop the Kintan Kings gang. Never finished the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646729" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had other business, but it's done now. Do they still need help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646729" id2="17" version="1065353216">My own mission came first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646730" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have bigger problems than gangsters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646732" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did Ambassador Averdon and Bareesh manage to get rid of those gangsters?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646732" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did things turn out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646733" id2="17" version="1065353216">No idea--but we have a much bigger problem on our hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646735" id2="17" version="1065353216">None of those names rings a bell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646735" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't remember any of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646736" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Hutt who didn't leave an impression. That's a first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bareesh Fenn'ak Torill has deep connections in the Hutt Cartel. He's been feeding us valuable information on the Empire's dealings here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646739" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't know the Hutts were taking sides. Nar Shaddaa does business with both the Republic and Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646739" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hutts are supposedly neutral.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646740" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some Hutts are developing an enlightened perspective. They know if the Empire defeats us, the Hutt Cartel is next on the list.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just how valuable is this data?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646742" id2="17" version="1065353216">How good is the information?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Valuable enough that you shouldn't leave this planet before you hear it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hutts never help anyone out of good will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646745" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't trust your contact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646746" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never said Bareesh was motivated by altruism. He's looking to keep his customers alive. But we can work with that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646748" id2="17" version="1065353216">Through his Cartel sources, Bareesh obtained classified Imperial intel. The enemy is training mercenaries to conduct sneak attacks on our civilian forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646750" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire will deny involvement while their mercenary army destroys us. We need to shut down the enemy's operations--all of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646751" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't leave Nar Shaddaa until this threat is ended.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646751" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on my help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646752" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not one to hesitate. Good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once again, the Force has guided me where I can do the most good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646754" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on my help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646755" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're prepared to offer more than sage advice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646757" id2="17" version="1065353216">We shouldn't wait for the Empire to strike first. If they want a surprise attack, let's give it to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646757" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on my help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646758" id2="17" version="1065353216">You certainly live up to your reputation, soldier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every time bad guys try to blow up the Republic, I get real popular.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646760" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on my help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646761" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a knack for battlefield heroics. Those are always in demand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646763" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're suggesting we declare war against the Empire?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646763" id2="17" version="1065353216">And break the treaty?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646764" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Hutt space. We aren't declaring anything--and the Empire is in no position to accuse us of breaking the treaty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646766" id2="17" version="1065353216">My ship's fueled and ready for departure. Let me know how things work out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, but I'm leaving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why waste time on your cozy starship when you can stay here and save innocent lives? Whatever you're doing, it can wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646768" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess Nar Shaddaa isn't finished with me just yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646768" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose you're right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646769" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you see it that way, because you're our best hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646771" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not making any promises--but I'll listen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646771" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll see about that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bareesh is standing by. He wanted to speak with you personally.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646774" id2="17" version="1065353216">I placed myself at great personal risk to obtain the coordinates of your enemy's staging area. I can only imagine the danger awaiting you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646776" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire trains mercenary killers, builds devastating weapons and operates a horrific interrogation center. Its villainy knows no limit!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646777" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Hutt Cartel formed an alliance with the Republic, we could easily defeat the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646777" id2="17" version="1065353216">Help us defeat them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646778" id2="17" version="1065353216">What goes on in these interrogation centers? Does the Empire have prisoners?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interrogation centers?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone the Empire believes may possess valuable information goes to the interrogation center for &quot;processing.&quot; Their process is one-hundred percent fatal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646781" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire needs to learn there's a limit to everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646781" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough is enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes! Crush those scum! They deserve whatever fate they receive.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too few among the Cartel share my disgust of the Empire. They cling to their foolish neutrality and refuse to commit forces to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646786" id2="17" version="1065353216">If only I could provide you more than information... I wish you good fortune stopping the Empire's abominable campaign to destroy you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your information is most appreciated. We'll take things from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646788" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you fail to stop this threat, I shudder to think of the damage to the galaxy's economy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646790" id2="17" version="1065353216">You give us all this information, but you won't lend a hand to clean up your own planet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646790" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won't help us at all?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646791" id2="17" version="1065353216">The politics are complicated. If you only knew what I went through to obtain these secrets. I will be repaying favors for years--decades!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646793" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calling you coward would be an insult to the spineless. Thanks for nothing, Hutt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646793" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a pathetic worm you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646794" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insult me if you like! If the Cartel knew I shared this information with you, they'd slow-roast me over the sun!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646796" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure no offense was intended, Bareesh. The Republic is prepared to fight its own battles.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646798" id2="17" version="1065353216">SIS reconnaissance located an enemy industrial complex swarming with heavily armed mercenaries. If that army is unleashed on us, we're done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our only hope is scattering those mercenaries and destroying the Imperial interrogation facility. Defeat the enemy before it can mount any attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646801" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do everything in my power to protect the Republic. The Empire won't drive us off Nar Shaddaa.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646801" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646802" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need this world's technology. Losing is not an option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646804" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are few; they are many. But the Force is our ally--and a powerful one. We will not fail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646804" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victory will be ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646805" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never had a reason to say this before, but... may the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646807" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't mind a good fight, but I'll settle for overwhelming victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646808" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate you lowering your standards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646810" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you knew how many armies I've single-handedly defeated, you wouldn't be worried.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646811" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just remember there are no reinforcements. You're all we've got.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646813" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was looking forward to some R &amp; R. Stomping the Empire with a beautiful woman sounds relaxing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646813" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] You only had to ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646814" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I may have to broaden your horizons. First things first....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646816" id2="17" version="1065353216">You almost make it sound fun--but people are going to die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646816" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is no game.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646817" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know that--and I appreciate the risk you're taking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646819" id2="17" version="1065353216">The longer you flap your lips, the more time the Empire has to prepare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646819" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're wasting time talking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646820" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take a speeder to the Empire's industrial complex. Look for the droid that isn't shooting at you. That's your contact.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry, my heroic friends! The Empire could launch its attack against your people at any time!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="646823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not delay, my friend. Once the Empire chooses to attack, it moves swiftly. This may be your only chance!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646825" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can handle this without me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646825" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, it can't. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646826" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that were true, do you think I'd be begging for your help? Go on, then....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646830" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're cute--but I'm busy. Maybe another time....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646831" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice outfit. You'll fit right in.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="962249" id2="17" version="1065353216">I got you the best in the galaxy, Deera. And here they are. Remember, all of you, I wasn't part of this.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
