<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>118</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/world/republic/the_war_for_nar_shaddaa/ik_4c.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646834" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am pro--pro--programmed against my will to direct you to the turbolift. Farewell, friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wel--wel--welcome back. My master is awaiting you on the holo....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646839" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was able to monitor some of your progress. You've put the Empire in full panic mode. They're reeling from the damage you inflicted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646840" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've put an end to their plans on Nar Shaddaa, but they'll be back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646840" id2="17" version="1065353216">The threat is over, for now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646841" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire is already threatening more of our people. This attack stirred things up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646843" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would've preferred to resolve matters without taking lives, but the enemy left us no choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646843" id2="17" version="1065353216">I regret violence was needed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646844" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire doesn't share your aversion to killing. We're not done here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646846" id2="17" version="1065353216">No reason to stop now. Still got plenty of ammo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's keep it up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646847" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll need it, but not here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646849" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you managed to record my amazing heroics, I wouldn't mind a copy. For sentimental reasons, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have any footage of me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646850" id2="17" version="1065353216">I destroyed every holocam down there before it could record your face. This isn't over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sending messages from Imperial Intelligence headquarters is a big risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you safe where you are?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646853" id2="17" version="1065353216">No choice. We've got a new problem that can't wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody needs a pat on the back from you. Are we done here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop being a suck-up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646856" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's surprise attack is officially canceled, but we've got new problems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646858" id2="17" version="1065353216">I recently discovered a hidden annex of the Empire's Shadow Town prison complex. When I alerted SIS, they sent teams to investigate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646860" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's keeping Republic POWs in the annex. Your attack threw the Imperials into a frenzy. They're about to execute our people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646861" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to stop the executions. How do we get inside this prison annex?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those monsters!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646862" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can get you there easily from where you are. This droid has supplies you'll need to take with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would the Empire keep Republic prisoners on Nar Shaddaa? Are these soldiers who fought in the war?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are these POWs?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646865" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been fighting in the shadows ever since the Treaty of Coruscant. These POWs are spies and saboteurs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646867" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been to Shadow Town. Those people are as good as dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646867" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing we can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646868" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, we can save them. These prisoners haven't been fitted with cranial bombs yet. SIS agents are already moving to free them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646870" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need you to infiltrate the prison annex. Get our people out of there. This droid has supplies our agents will need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deliver the supplies to one of my remote droid units, and it will... oh... oh, no... Imperial Intelligence is on to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646873" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure you're not just being paranoid?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646873" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't panic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646874" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you said you could avoid detection.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646874" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? How?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646875" id2="17" version="1065353216">Paranoia is a survival trait in this business. Trouble is, it works both ways.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646877" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're transmitting from inside their headquarters. It was only a matter of time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646877" id2="17" version="1065353216">That isn't exactly a surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646878" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they'd identified me, I'd already be dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646880" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been slicing my superior's private logs. His latest entries are all about hunting for a mole inside his division.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646882" id2="17" version="1065353216">After everything that's happened today, I have to be one of his prime suspects. What do I do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't wait to be discovered. He'll kill you--or worse. You've served the Republic well. It's time to come home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Run for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Slip out quietly. Get off Nar Shaddaa as fast as you can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast... there was so much more I could do here, but you're right. I'll use the chaos to cover my escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646888" id2="17" version="1065353216">He doesn't know it's you, so there must be other suspects. Get him alone and take him out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kill him and get creative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make it look like another agent murdered him. There has to be someone who can take the fall for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe... maybe the Chiss. No one trusts her. Can't believe it's come to this, but you're right. I don't have any choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Droid, hand over the supplies and provide coordinates to the prison annex turbolift. I've reprogrammed an astromech unit down there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646895" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find the astromech, deliver the supplies, and it will signal your contact. Logging off. Hope we see each other again....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646897" id2="17" version="1065353216">The turbolift will take you directly to the prison annex. Goo--goo--good luck, Republic citizen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646903" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should co--co--coordinate with the rebellious workers in this facility. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Combat sequence engaging, weapons arming.... War--war--warning: systems failure. Remote override prohibiting mayhem protocol activation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi target will be stored in memory, to be terminated at a future date.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even the Empire's droids believe they're superior. Are you programmed for arrogance?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646909" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're overconfident.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Negative. I am programmed to render you into component molecules.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646911" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's polite of you to inform me of my imminent demise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for the warning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Settle your affairs, Republic scum. Your end is coming soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Special Forces target will be stored in memory for later termination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pipe down, rust bucket. My combat droid's spare parts are bigger than you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck with that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spare parts provide insufficient cover against explosive attacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646916" id2="17" version="1065353216">Target will be filed as &quot;unidentified spacer&quot; and cached in memory for future termination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646917" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're planning to kill me, you should at least get my name right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646917" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get properly introduced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646918" id2="17" version="1065353216">Irrelevant. There will be no record of your passing. Your component organic parts will be recycled upon death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646919" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your target profile has been saved to memory for termination at a later date.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646920" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attacking me would be foolish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646921" id2="17" version="1065353216">You lack a core combat processor. You overestimate your odds of survival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646922" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suggest you stop threatening my friend. Droids don't stand up well against lightsabers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646922" id2="17" version="1065353216">That won't be happening.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your weapon is ineffective against high-yield explosives. If only I could trigger the one in my arsenal....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps you haven't noticed, but the Force is with your target. You should rethink your ambitions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646924" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're slightly outnumbered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your presence is noted, Jedi. I will terminate you first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646926" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mess with my friend and you mess with Havoc Squad. Got it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646926" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have to go through me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646927" id2="17" version="1065353216">I possess area-effect weaponry. Multiple targets should not pose any difficulty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646928" id2="17" version="1065353216">You planning to terminate all of us, or just my friend? Just wondering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does that include me, too?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646929" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am capable of targeting multiple adversaries. There will be no delays when my terminations resume.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646930" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was told you work for the Republic. Is that any way to greet an ally?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646930" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a rude way to say hello.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your information is incorrect. I am an Imperial assassination droid. My inability to carry out programmed functions is due to external interference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646932" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't normally attack defenseless enemies, but I'll make an exception for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646932" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prepare to be scrapped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646933" id2="17" version="1065353216">Engaging self-defense protocols... fai--fai--failure. Permanent deactivation imminent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646935" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's enough, droid. Vocabulator switched off....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry about that. Had a little trouble overriding that stubborn droid's holo-emitter. I'm your contact. Republic SIS.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wish I could meet you in person, but I'm at a comm station in the middle of Imperial Intelligence headquarters. Long story.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you insane? If they trace this signal, you're dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get out of there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646941" id2="17" version="1065353216">My job is to maintain droids like this one. It's a perfect cover. Nobody's watching me... I think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646943" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't drop a bomb like that and not give details. What are you doing in Imperial Intelligence?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646943" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to hear this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646944" id2="17" version="1065353216">As far as the enemy knows, I'm just an entry-level tech analyst. I'm trying to keep it that way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646946" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have time for stories. What's the mission?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646946" id2="17" version="1065353216">Skip to the briefing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646947" id2="17" version="1065353216">My security access here is limited, but I've been able to coordinate with a resistance cell working inside the Imperial factory zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those people are practically slaves. They're ready to revolt. They'll help you pinpoint critical Imperial targets. Stop the enemy before they can attack us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646950" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I need are their names and locations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646951" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're sure these workers aren't leading us into a trap?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646951" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we trust them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646952" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know how the Empire treats any species other than human. Believe me, they want us to win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646954" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the people down here were worth anything, they wouldn't be with the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="646954" id2="17" version="1065353216">These people are useless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most didn't realize what they were getting themselves into when they took the jobs. Give them a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646957" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm uploading the profiles of people you should talk to. You'll find them nearby.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh-oh--gotta cut the channel. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vocabulator functions have re--re--resumed with limited language options. Have a caring day, Republic citizen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="646965" id2="17" version="1065353216">My attack protocols have failed. Con--con--consider yourself lucky, Republic scum!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
