<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>17</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x2/event/imperial_announcer.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033192" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alert: this is an Imperial News Network special bulletin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033193" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warning: this is an Imperial News Network emergency alert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033197" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is an Imperial News Network travel ban alert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033201" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is an official reminder from the Ministry of Logistics: per Imperial Edict 1968Z, lethal force is authorized against rakghouls and rakghoul plague carriers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033266" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are multiple confirmed reports of the Taris rakghoul plague spreading to other inhabited systems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victims of rakghoul plague suffer full-body physical mutations and become highly aggressive. They pose an extreme risk of infection or death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033270" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you encounter evidence of a rakghoul plague outbreak, report it immediately to the nearest Imperial military station. Failure to comply is considered treason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033272" id2="17" version="1065353216">This has been an Imperial News Network special bulletin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033274" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are increasing reports of rakghoul plague outbreaks in Imperial space and bordering systems. The infection rate is growing exponentially.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033276" id2="17" version="1065353216">For your own safety, interstellar travel has been restricted by the Ministry of Logistics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033279" id2="17" version="1065353216">A rakghoul plague outbreak is confirmed on the planet Tatooine. The system is now considered a Level Omega hazard to all travelers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033281" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial citizens are urged to avoid Tatooine. Do not attempt to contact anyone currently on the planet or offer aid to the native population.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033283" id2="17" version="1065353216">Authorities will advise when the travel ban expires. Once again, all citizens are urged to avoid planet Tatooine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033293" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remain vigilant, keep calm, and report all suspicious activity to the nearest Imperial military post. Failure to comply is treason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033305" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you or anyone you know exhibits symptoms of rakghoul plague, it is your Imperial duty to eliminate the threat by any means necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033307" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not hesitate. The Empire's security depends on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Officials indicate the death toll exceeds ten thousand, with many infected still at large. Anyone mutated by the rakghoul plague represents an extreme threat.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
