<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>14</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x2/event/republic_announcer.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033203" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention Republic citizens... the Galactic Senate Health and Safety Council has issued an infectious disease alert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033204" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention Republic citizens... the Galactic Senate Health and Safety Council has updated its infectious disease alert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033207" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention Republic citizens... the Interstellar Travel Council has issued a Level One Emergency Alert for the planet Tatooine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033211" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention Republic citizens... the Health and Safety Council reminds you that victims of rakghoul plague are a danger to your well-being.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033508" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are unconfirmed reports that the rakghoul plague has spread beyond the Taris system.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victims of rakghoul plague suffer fever, body aches and genetic mutation. If left untreated, the victim becomes dangerous to nearby life forms.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033512" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you see anyone suffering from rakghoul plague, do not approach. Report the victim's location to the Health and Safety Council immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakghoul plague outbreaks are now confirmed in Republic, Imperial and unaligned systems. A complete list of infected planets will be released shortly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Citizens are encouraged to remain in their homes or aboard their starships. Anyone displaying symptoms of rakghoul plague should be quarantined immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once again, a major rakghoul plague outbreak has been confirmed in multiple systems. Citizens are advised to use extreme caution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033522" id2="17" version="1065353216">A serious rakghoul plague outbreak has been confirmed on the planet. Tatooine officials report significant loss of life and a high rate of infection.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033524" id2="17" version="1065353216">For their own safety and the safety of others,  all citizens are warned to avoid Tatooine until further notice. Thank you for your cooperation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033534" id2="17" version="1065353216">In extreme cases of infection, rakghoul plague victims will attack and attempt to devour their own loved ones.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1033536" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you cannot restrain or isolate a rakghoul, run away. If you cannot escape, use appropriate force to defend yourself against infection.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
