<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>39</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/ilum/bronze/republic/crystal_clear_sabotage/captain_sarmuk.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179118" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm putting in a requisition order for new equipment, today. A destroyed ion disruptor has to count for something.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179119" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't need my lousy standard-issue scanner to see that explosion. Nice work!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179120" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179121" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have business elsewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179122" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I've earned a reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179123" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knew there had to be a catch somewhere. I hope this'll be enough for you--and thanks, I guess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179124" id2="17" version="1065353216">Next time, fix this yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179125" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Operational self-reliance,&quot; huh? The brass says that, too. We'll keep trying.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179127" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh hey--take this with you. Not every day someone goes out of their way for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179129" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep the Imperials off the ion disruptor once you've planted the bomb, or it's all for nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179132" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know how hard it is to get decent equipment out here? Hmm, I guess not--all you Jedi need is a lightsaber.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179134" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be grateful you're Havoc Squad, sir. Special Forces are always prioritized for new gear; we're lucky to get equipment once a month.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph. Let me guess, independent starship captain? I bet you never have trouble getting the equipment you need, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take my advice, all of you. Conserve your equipment while you've got it. We're lucky to get resupplied once a month.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179140" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were sent diagnostic gear, to find those big crystal deposits, but the blasted Empire's set up an ion disruptor nearby.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179142" id2="17" version="1065353216">That disruptor fries our diagnostic systems, no one sends us proper shielding.... The Empire's going to get those crystal deposits first, all because we're &quot;lower priority.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179143" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could go on the offensive.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179144" id2="17" version="1065353216">That diagnostic equipment is what matters, Master Jedi; it can only take so much damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179146" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic wouldn't do this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179147" id2="17" version="1065353216">The sacrifices have to be made somewhere, Master Jedi. We make do--most of the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179149" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want to be treated like the best, Captain, prove you're worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make yourself high priority.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179150" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm doing my best, sir, but you know what it's like, doing operations on shoestring resources.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179152" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stuck with bureaucrats, eh?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179153" id2="17" version="1065353216">And even when I can see a way out, something else goes wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179155" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get rid of the Empire's ion disruptor, and it won't matter what priority you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179155" id2="17" version="1065353216">The disruptor is the problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179156" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been trying to trash that thing, believe me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Complain to someone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179159" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just hoping for a sympathetic ear.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179161" id2="17" version="1065353216">I cobbled together a bomb to destroy the disruptor, but the Empire has some of their best technicians on site. They'll only defuse it before it goes off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179162" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not if I stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Really? Huh. Never thought anyone'd care about us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179165" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you use this bomb?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179166" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're serious about helping, just find the ion disruptor and plant the bomb; it self-activates.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179168" id2="17" version="1065353216">The real problem is the Imperials. Keep them away from the bomb or they'll shut it off. But you can handle them, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179170" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have to go. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179171" id2="17" version="1065353216">When will they get it? We can't find their crystals if they don't give us the tools!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blasted Imperials and their gadgets. This is a losing battle.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
