<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>35</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/imperial/hub_1/to_pierce_the_heavens/bunker_console.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010998" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Gravity Hook Seven to Regulator post 2X4. Receiving the all-clear signal now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Last one. You should be able to hit the gravity hook without anyone sounding alarms. Play this right, the Hutts will never know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011002" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have to assault the hook's base, then take a lift to the docking ring. That's where the command crew will be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011003" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the command crew gone, the gravity hook will be ours. Wait for my signal to dock.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1011003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Simple enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011004" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not in any hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011006" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the gravity hook is secure, I assume you join me? I'd like to put a face to that voice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1011006" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Then do we meet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011007" id2="17" version="1065353216">My... team and I will be joining you, yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where are you and the rest of the support team now? Still in orbit?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1011009" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's your current status?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Affirmative. As soon as you've secured the docking ring, though, we'll come on board.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your voice is grating. Show that you're useful to me, and do it soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1011012" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been worthless so far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once the docking ring is secure, my team will come aboard. Maybe we'll be more to your liking then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011015" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have identified a member of the opposition: The mercenaries' overseer is the &quot;pet project&quot; of one of the Hutts running Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011017" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's an alien Whiphid, trained from the time he was a cub to be a Hutt Cartel enforcer. Big and brutal; thought you should know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011021" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Raspard to Regulator post 2X9. The Archon's pet freak is cracking down on security, so we still need that all-clear. Over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coming in now... got it. I'll let you get back to playing pazaak, or however you pass the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011025" id2="17" version="1065353216">Support team to ground. Remember I mentioned the quakes? That was a minor one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any idea what's causing these groundquakes? Could they cause a problem?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1011026" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's behind the quakes?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb's always been volatile, but local reports say it's been especially bad this year. Geologic shifts of some sort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011029" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not too worried, but I'll keep an eye out. I'll check in at the next bunker.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011030" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing like having a planet move beneath you to keep you awake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1011030" id2="17" version="1065353216">They keep things interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess the mercenaries aren't enough opposition, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011033" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll check in at the next bunker. Keep moving, and be sure not to leave survivors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011034" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need a support team to notice the obvious. Stay off the line until you have something useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1011034" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're wasting my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011039" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Gravity Hook Seven to Regulator post 2X3--we have not received an all-clear signal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011041" id2="17" version="1065353216">A strike team is on its way--ah, nevermind. Signal just came through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011043" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, Commander--some sort of comm disruption. Must've been another groundquake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011045" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is support team to ground. That's one clear. Whoever you are... keep doing what you're doing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1047032" id2="17" version="1065353216">Name is Commander J'Ruush, trained from birth to be a Hutt Cartel enforcer. Big and brutal; thought you should know.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
