<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>16</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/open_worlds/class/jedi_consular/unforeseen_circumstances/altean.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083723" id2="17" version="1065353216">I tried, sir, but they're still mopping up Ulgo forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083725" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, then if we can't keep the Voss commandos, we might--One moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083770" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, Master Jedi, how rude of me. Altean, of the Great House of Estaria. I'm glad your Council sent someone; my father's life might hang on this summit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083771" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not just a representative of the Council, I'm their military liaison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1083771" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not just &quot;someone.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083772" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does your father have to do with the Voss commando issue?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1083772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083773" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never been to Estaria. What's it like? Have you been affected by the war?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1083773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about your world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083776" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're more fortunate than you thought. You're speaking directly to a member of the Council itself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1083776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Actually, I'm on the Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083780" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid I don't know the protocol, but I'm honored to meet you. This situation's going from bad to worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Estaria's the capital of the Indrexu Sector: lots of old trading families, with vintage grudges. The Empire tried manipulation rather than invading.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083931" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I may: Stand up to Haftan-Ke. He's created a lot of resentment, and he could use a lesson in protocol.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083932" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a pleasure speaking with you. But if it's alright, I should check on my father. Just in case.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083934" id2="17" version="1065353216">Haftan-Ke seems to think I should already know all about &quot;Voss-Ka&quot; and &quot;Gormak.&quot; How can anyone negotiate like this?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
