<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>26</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/open_worlds/class/jedi_consular/unforeseen_circumstances/steward_droid.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, Master Jedi, feel free to signal with the intercom whenever you're ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, Master Jedi! How very, very grateful I am to see you. Welcome to the Noble Answer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083620" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Republic steward droid S3-N9, programmed to assist the Voss in their, ah, diplomatic endeavors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083622" id2="17" version="1065353216">So who else is attending? I might recognize some of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1083622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are the other delegates?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele Shan said the Voss need their commandos to fight the war back home, is that correct?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1083623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go over the situation again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083624" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure we'll all resolve this Voss commando question and get through the summit in one piece. Metaphorically speaking! Ha.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083625" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss are used to getting their own way, but they're becoming part of the galactic community now. It's time they acted like it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1083625" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss need to grow up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083628" id2="17" version="1065353216">My programmed response is that the Voss are valuable friends and allies, and the Republic is fully committed to assisting them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083629" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss say that the Gormak are becoming more dangerous, and they need their commandos--which, of course, is absolutely their right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083630" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Zabrak is Master Judhu Faan, a trader and entrepreneur. Master Altean is a nobleman, from Estaria, I believe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083633" id2="17" version="1065353216">But many Republic worlds rely on Voss commando support. And the Voss are being very... Voss, about the commando withdrawal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083636" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Nikto gentleman, Master Kef-Ditas-Rai, defends Republic mining properties. He, um, he seems very angry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Obviously the other delegates are, um, eager to resolve this--all of them rely on the Voss commandos. It's rather awkward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Awkward, but not unsolvable. Don't worry, S3, I've handled worse situations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1083641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Relax. I'll fix this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083643" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done enough, droid. Someone needs to straighten out this mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1083643" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just let me handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who's running this summit? Is it one of the Three, the Voss leaders?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1083645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who's in charge here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083646" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Three sent a gentleman called Haftan-Ke to represent them, with two Voss Mystics. I'm, er, not sure where Master Ke is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083650" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's time if you'd like to speak to the other delegates. Please, signal whenever you're ready; I'm sure Master Haftan-Ke will get things started soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083653" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Master Haftan-Ke, and two Voss Mystics, are running the summit. If you'd like to speak with the other delegates, there's still time; just signal whenever you're ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1083656" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you'd like to speak with them, there's still time. Please, signal whenever you're ready; I'm sure Master Haftan-Ke will get things started soon.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
