<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>43</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/ilum/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I ever tell you I have a fear of being shot to death on a forsaken frozen world?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179444" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic won't surrender their resources easily. We might have to kill every last one of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179445" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy is entrenched here. They are determined to repel any attack to their frozen resources.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179446" id2="17" version="1065353216">I feel our enemy's determination and fear--we will leave them frozen in the ice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another frozen Republic base about to bite the dust. I'm jacked and ready to bring it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our enemy waits inside! We bring death!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179449" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deeper, deeper into darkness. We are the Republic's nightmare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing like taking shots at the Republic to get the blood going. Good thing I spent all that time training my eyes for low-light combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get in and out quickly, with minimal casualties. I'm still a little uneasy about fighting Republic soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fascinating construction, building a base like this so quickly after arriving on Ilum. It won't last, of course. That's the tragedy. In ancient times, building was slow, but those buildings lasted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Move swiftly and silently. The night and the snow are our allies. My people know Ilum well. Watch for ambushes from the cliffs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember when attacking a Jedi fortress seemed like a bad idea? Yeah, me, neither.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179455" id2="17" version="1065353216">We go to fight Jedi on a lost and distant world. A moment to remember.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179456" id2="17" version="1065353216">I really am too old to be assaulting Jedi bases. But we rise to the challenges of our time....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever happens, I'm proud to be a part of this assault. It'll go down in history.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179458" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you do not survive this attack, I will retain a recording of the event for later analysis. Perhaps I will broadcast it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179459" id2="17" version="1065353216">According to the HoloNet, Ilum's over ninety percent ice. After Hoth, though, this actually seems kind of cozy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179460" id2="17" version="1065353216">This planet's supposed to be loaded with crystal formations, valuable crystal formations. Keep an eye out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179461" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi've been on Ilum for ages. Don't know why, but it's time to serve an eviction.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blizz think this like when Blizz work for Slam.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179463" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like we ain't gettin' a warm welcome 'til we torch the place.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi Temple = invaded by Sith // Jedi + T7 = flush out that filth!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's show the Sith what happens when they squat in a Jedi Temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure which is worse, Ilum or Hoth. Scratch that--I'm going with Ilum, because I'm on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody invades a Jedi stronghold and gets away with it. Not on my watch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look on the bright side. The last time we attacked a Jedi Temple, we left you nothing to reclaim.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is not like temple on Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179474" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know Jedi like to go without, but building a temple on such a frozen world is going too far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great defensive position wasted on a temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Carved right out of the stone. Guess the Jedi have architects as well as ambassadors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179477" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imagine training here. Going through that arch every day and looking up at the stars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fighting for a Jedi temple? What have we gotten ourselves into?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fighting the Sith on Ilum is an honor. Bowdaar's legend grows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179480" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope there's profit in this fight. We're risking a lot to help out the Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179481" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Jedi were true warriors, they would not have let this temple fall into Sith hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, Sith! Just so we're clear, I'm not an actual Jedi. I only dress like one!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179483" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi Temple. Nice to see one that's almost in one piece.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179484" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the Jedi Temple. Files show that it's stood here for centuries--it's a very important structure in the Jedi Order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179485" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi Temple! Quite impressive, as one would expect from our noble allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess that's the Jedi Temple--pretty impressive. Never guessed I'd be spending time in places like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179487" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Jedi Temple shows the marks of centuries. Falling now would be a great shame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023383" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commentary: The Republic undesirables are well-fortified here. I almost feel sorry for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lament: The Jedi have proved remarkably incapable of holding their temples, master. Am I the only one bothered by this?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
