<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>40</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tatooine/bronze/republic/show_of_force/professor_larcoh.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615302" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be certain to include your name in my research documentation... somewhere, at any rate.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615305" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was right! My hypothesis was utterly correct!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615307" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since you left, there have already been reports of Sand People carefully avoiding the local settlements--they now respect our strength, just as I'd thought!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615308" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615309" id2="17" version="1065353216">These fools will probably never appreciate what I've done for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615311" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get to my reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615312" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, yes, fine--here. Though participating in my achievement should be reward enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615314" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't I get any gratitude?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your contribution was important, certainly. You should feel very proud to have helped.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615317" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will be a tremendous boon to my research--I must begin my formal documentation immediately!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show the Sand People our strength! Make them respect us!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615322" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm telling you people that we can save lives! Why won't any of you rubes listen to me?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615324" id2="17" version="1065353216">These &quot;Sand People&quot; may be violent, but they have a society and customs. I know ways to make them leave you alone, if you weren't too ignorant to listen!</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="615325" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll never stir people to action by berating them.</text>
		<text bitflag="5456" id1="615325" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insults won't serve you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615326" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi? Hmph. You're probably right--these fools are a lost cause. But perhaps you will act, even if they will not.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="615328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you saying that diplomacy with the Sand People is possible?</text>
		<text bitflag="5456" id1="615328" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a peaceful solution?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615329" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi? No, I'm afraid the Sand People are no more interested in listening to reason than these backward fools. But perhaps you will!</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="615331" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to need you to calm down, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="5456" id1="615331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take it easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615332" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll calm down when somebody actually agrees to listen to reason. How about you?</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="615334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody likes a loudmouth. You've got to play it smooth.</text>
		<text bitflag="5456" id1="615334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yelling won't convince anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615335" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is no time for jokes, you--wait. You aren't a local. Perhaps you can actually help this situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="5456" id1="615337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally, someone smart enough to listen!</text>
		<text bitflag="5456" id1="615340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get over yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615341" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone who ignores an enlightened voice at the risk of their own safety is a fool. The point cannot be argued.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615343" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been studying the Sand People for some time and, while their attacks are savage, they are not mindless beasts. They merely respect strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rival Sand People tribes often send warriors into each other's camps to fight ritual challenges and prove their strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615347" id2="17" version="1065353216">If someone here--you, perhaps--were to undertake such a ritual challenge, I'm confident that it would earn their respect and end their attacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615348" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm always up for a challenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615349" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a clever idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615350" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is good to finally have my work suitably appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="7489" id1="615352" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take this--the Sand People I observed carried a similar object. Plant it in the midst of their camp, and defeat all who come to challenge you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615354" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will save these dull-minded dregs yet!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not interested. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615357" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then leave me to my fruitless task of convincing these morons to save themselves!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615359" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have nothing to discuss.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
