<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>5</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/dromund_kaas/heroic_weekly/mission_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172388" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vort Norman has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Jungle Valley sector of Dromund Kaas. For additional details about the mission, Vort Norman may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172389" id2="17" version="1065353216">By order of the Dark Council, the legendary Mandalorian bounty hunter Valen Korik is wanted for betraying the Imperial-Mandalorian alliance and murdering two Sith Lords in Kaas City in open combat. He is considered extremely dangerous and is believed to have fled into the Dark Temple. 

Only persons authorized to enter the Dark Temple should give pursuit. Korik is believed to be heavily armed, and the situation in the Dark Temple remains unpredictable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172390" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vol Kolla has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Nalis Quarry sector of Dromund Kaas. For additional details about the mission, Vol Kolla may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Sunder has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Malignant Bog sector of Dromund Kaas. For additional details about the mission, Lord Sunder may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172392" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major Shellaster has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Dark Temple Approach sector of Dromund Kaas. For additional details about the mission, Major Shellaster may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
