<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>126</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/rishi/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135558" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Rishi. Gorgeous beaches, pirate hideouts, and over six hundred open bounties. Too bad the HoloNet signal's weak--otherwise, it's perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Raider's Cove. Shoddy defenses. Lots of hiding spots. Pretty beach.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135561" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know I like my beach resorts with character, but this particular character seems a little less &quot;eccentric&quot; and a little more &quot;spice-addled.&quot; Welcome to Rishi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take a slice of Nar Shaddaa and drop it on the beach, and you've got Raider's Cove. Don't lean against anything--it might collapse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135563" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is Rishi. Heard a little about it back on Hoth--pirates talked about it like it was some vacation hangout. Got to admit, the view's not bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every planet we visit--I still feel a thrill when we land. Look at the ocean! Does this ever get old?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135565" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have seen many things, but never a black beach on a golden sea. This will be an excellent world for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135566" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spent a week on Rishi once. Nasty bunch, even for pirates. Did things I don't like to think about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135567" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a beautiful planet for such an ugly spaceport. I wish we could do something about it--but that's not why we're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Smell that, my lord? That's the smell of low-quality blaster cartridges leaking tibanna gas. That's who we're dealing with on Rishi--very cheap, very violent people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135569" id2="17" version="1065353216">This may be the saddest, most run-down port I've ever seen. I've said that before, but you keep surprising me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135570" id2="17" version="1065353216">Viidu used to talk about retiring to Rishii. Never was sure if he was serious--always seemed he was a little scared of the place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135571" id2="17" version="1065353216">My father took me to Rishi once when I was a little girl. I was scared of the black sand, but by the end... it was a good trip.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess this is Rishi. I think I might've been here before--it was a long week, I was trashed for most of it, but that skyline looks familiar....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warm sun on black sand. We've seen sights like this in the memories of the nest, but never with our own eyes. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135574" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Raider's Cove.&quot; Name like that tells you something--the locals don't even bother to pretend they're not scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135575" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's so little about Rishi in our databanks--it's all secondhand accounts from smugglers and raiders. People who go this far from civilization like their privacy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135576" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observation: This spaceport appears to be in dire need of maintenance. Stripped wires, spilled oil, and unsound construction may all be to our advantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135579" id2="17" version="1065353216">Query: Why bother caging and feeding the prisoners instead of working them indefinitely? Surely their resale value cannot be high after much use.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135580" id2="17" version="1065353216">To capture a prisoner is a great thing! A happy event to be celebrated with a feast! These Nova Blades have no joy or respect for victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Slaves--the cargo of the stupid and sadistic. Way too bulky and way more trouble than they're worth. Most of the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135582" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't know what the political answer is to slavery. But here and now, we can set these people free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135583" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I was a kid, I'd sometimes slice bounty boards and put bounties on slavers. I felt bad for not paying out, but slavers are jerks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Slaving is like hunting mice. No challenge. No honor. Cruel to the mice. Shoot to kill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135585" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's good money in slaving, but it's a business I won't touch. If there's one thing you've taught me, Sith, it's that slaves can get mean.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Were you really a slave once? I just can't imagine you in one of these cages. I can't imagine you... helpless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135587" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe there's a place for slavery in the galaxy--I won't deny that. But certain standards should be upheld. These men lack standards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135588" id2="17" version="1065353216">No jokes, no smart comments... every slaver here--every scumbag who treats people like property--has to die. We have to kill them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at these people. We'll do what we can, but they need a good two, three months of physical and nutritional therapy to recover. Not even counting the psychological damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every day we're out fighting the Empire is a day we could have been stopping slaver scumbags. Just another thing to hate the Sith for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135591" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know it's not why we're on Rishi, Jedi, but blast it... no innocent person deserves to be in a cage like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135592" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not the cruelty that surprises me. It's that this goes on, ignored, in so many corners of the galaxy. Let's help these people, if we can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, look at these people, Captain. Even outlaws need to have limits. Slaving goes way past respectable crime.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone in the Nova Blades must be very proud of enslaving instead of killing the people who refuse to pay protection. They probably think it's ethical. I don't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Had a run-in with slavers second year out of training. I still can't forget the smell--unwashed, unfed people caged in their own dirt. Blast it all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135596" id2="17" version="1065353216">My family owned slaves. I don't want to admit how long it took me to realize that was wrong. Let's do this properly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis: Overloading the Nova Blades' ship reactor will likely not prove feasible. Unfortunate, as a full-scale meltdown would prove quite spectacular.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look! Had a ship so large crashed on my homeworld, I would have brought my whole tribe to the stars. We would have won battles endless!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at that ship. Imagine being on the bridge when it went down. We have got to try that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135602" id2="17" version="1065353216">The hive-ship burrows into the heart of the world, bearing life and sickness in equal measure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135603" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been doing some research. The Nova Blades used to let their members marry and raise kids--they had their own culture. Now it's mostly just killing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heavy defenses. Clean, though. Not used to frontal attacks. Let's go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135605" id2="17" version="1065353216">Had a friend or two in the Nova Blades. Better shooters and better flyers than I was. Don't mind killing them now--if we can pull it off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135606" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never thought a pirate crew could rival the White Maw. These guys may not be an army, but they've sure got the firepower of one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135607" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Project Meteorite&quot; proposed ramming Imperial cruisers through Republic blockades and using them as staging grounds once they crashed. It seems the Nova Blades beat us to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135608" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Nova Blades.&quot; &quot;Nova Blades.&quot; If I ever start a pirate crew, I'm going to call them the &quot;Star Stabbers.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, if you crashed your ship more than a decade ago and you're still living in the mess, it's time to grow up. Get an apartment and a housekeeper.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135610" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Nova Blades,&quot; huh? Takes a lot of guts to name yourself after a fiery sword when you don't carry lightsabers. Guts, but not smarts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135611" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a mean-looking ship, but looks are all it's got. Nova Blades have it jury-rigged to all get-out--we do this smart, we can take them on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135612" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should feel sorry for the Nova Blades--they're only pawns here. But the things they do for greed are hard to forgive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Says something about the Nova Blades that they didn't join the White Maw or the Voidwolf. Says something about how much firepower they've got, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135614" id2="17" version="1065353216">It doesn't matter how big or fast a pirate band grows--egos grow bigger and faster. The Nova Blades could use a lesson in humility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135615" id2="17" version="1065353216">One thing about fighting pirates: They keep you on your toes. No tactics, no discipline, and a lot of messy surprises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135616" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand this used to be the bread-and-butter of the Republic Army: large-scale action against militarized pirates. Pity the tactical reports are all outdated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warning: I am not programmed with biological data for the Rishii, master. Should engagement prove necessary, my approach may seem grisly and inelegant.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not trust these creatures, Chief. Too big, talons endless. They will hunt us for sure, but I will wear their beaks with pride!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135621" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd think their feathers would be worth something, but... nah. If they were, someone would already be poaching 'em.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135622" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could spend a year among the Rishii and still leave unsatisfied. What do they believe? How do they organize their families? What can the Empire learn from them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135623" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think the Rishii ever rent their homes to tourists? Tell me you don't want to come back next time we get a week off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rishii are predators. Good eyes. Sharp beaks. I'd like to meet a Rishii Mandalorian.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wouldn't mind having wings, living in a place like this. Some people are born with all the luck, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135626" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do the Rishii stand having those pirates on their world? There's so much beauty here. Why don't they fight?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135627" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Rishii could make fine allies for the Empire. Of the alien species we've recruited, few have natural aerial attack capacity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, I admit it--the Rishii terrify me. Just look at those beaks! I'm going to have nightmares about being snapped up and eaten.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135629" id2="17" version="1065353216">You ever met a Mrlssi before? Talk about feathers... this one woman loved to have the down on her neck scratched. But I'm not saying try that with the Rishii.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135630" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm always nervous in places like this. I know the Rishii aren't exactly primitive, but they're not cosmopolitan either. One wrong word and they'll hate the Jedi forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't say I envy the job, but it's always a joy seeing you play goodwill ambassador to a new species. Let's hope these Rishii stay friendly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you think there are Force-sensitives among the Rishii? I bet there are. I'd like to see a Rishii Jedi fly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say, Captain--think it would be wrong to take a feather as a souvenir? I won't pluck it off a Rishii or anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135634" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't get to see the Rishii last time I was here. Not up close--but I saw one gliding, once. Glad to get a second chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad there's not more time. Give me a month, I'd have these Rishii running a militia that would terrify the pirates. They're natural predators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135636" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's something admirable about the way the Rishii just ignore the outsiders on their world. There's a confidence about them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Request: I have previously attempted to avoid &quot;friendly fire&quot; incidents, master--but as traditional politics do not apply here, I would like to deactivate that program.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135640" id2="17" version="1065353216">All this because they think Revan is a great chief? But the great chief is hiding! He is not such a great chief.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Joining a cult is basically admitting you have no idea how to live. Fine with me, but don't shoot back when I come gunning for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135642" id2="17" version="1065353216">These people have found a home, and it pains us to oppose them. But their belief is not justification for their acts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135643" id2="17" version="1065353216">You see this? Republic and Empire working together for a common delusion? This is why I don't believe in people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135644" id2="17" version="1065353216">Empire. Republic. Together but still separate. That's their weakness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135645" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you appreciate a good cult, Sith, but these people seem deluded to me. Guess that's kind of the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135646" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to feel happy, seeing Republic and Empire working together. But it's all just a lie.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135647" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is madness, my lord. This is not a convenient alliance or negotiated truce--these are Imperial and Republic soldiers who have forgotten the very reason they once fought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135648" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess the good news is: the Empire and the Republic can get along! The bad news is we have to join a murder cult.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never thought I'd wish people would quit working together and just fight, but--I wish these guys would quit working together and just fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135650" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can this many people be so convinced that the Revanites are the real thing? There's got to be a way to make them see reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135651" id2="17" version="1065353216">I almost don't want to look too close--I'm afraid of seeing people I served with in this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135652" id2="17" version="1065353216">Beliefs, alliances--they can be so fickle sometimes. If you joined the Revanites, would I stay on the right path? I don't know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Takes a strong man to bring the Republic and Empire together. Not a good man, but a strong one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135654" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know a thing or two about leaders. This sort of devotion looks good, but it can't be sustained--zealots break, die, or kill their own idols.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135655" id2="17" version="1065353216">What bugs me most about the Revanites isn't that they're defectors--it's that they do it in secret. What Dorne did was brave. These guys and Tavus? Not so much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135656" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials here would betray their nation for Revan's ideology, but not for true justice. I don't understand it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135659" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reflection: That particular cave is perfectly sized to hold a top level predator. If desired, I can list the possibilities in alphabetical order.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, Chief! That cave is large enough to house a Gorax! Maybe nothing on Rishi is as fierce as a Gorax, but we must always hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135661" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something smells in that cave. My guess? A lot of dead big game hunters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135662" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is a scent here. It is old and powerful, and the nest grows restless at its memory. Be wary of that cave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't that cave remind you of the one on Dromund Kaas? The one where you killed &quot;the Beast in the Darkness&quot;? Let's not go in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135664" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cave's inhabited. Scratch marks, scent, spoor. Big prey. Good hunt. Your call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135665" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bet you could hide a lot of things in that cave. Guns, cash, maybe even a ship. Given it's Rishi, someone must have tried.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135666" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sense that? There's danger here. Look at that cave. Should we... you know. Do what Jedi and Sith do best?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Note the cave entrance, my lord. Easily large enough to admit a terentatek or similar predator--if Rishi has anything of the sort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you hear breathing coming from that cave? Cave-sized breathing? Let's not get any closer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey--I may not have Jedi senses, but even I know that cave looks bad. Not &quot;interesting bad,&quot; either, but just &quot;bad-bad.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135670" id2="17" version="1065353216">They never tell you when you're a Padawan to avoid big, dangerous-looking caves. Guess that's something every Jedi learns on her own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135671" id2="17" version="1065353216">Check that cave. If Qyzen were here, he'd be molting at the chance to go in. Me, I'm not keeping score.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135672" id2="17" version="1065353216">That cave houses a predator--you can see the marks in the stone. They're beautiful in their way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mark that cave on your map for me, will you, Captain? I'd love to come back here one day, make a camp and go exploring.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135674" id2="17" version="1065353216">How big do you figure the predators get on Rishi? I only ask because that's a very big cave....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135675" id2="17" version="1065353216">That cave's a good hiding spot. Problem is, I bet something's already using it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135676" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think we should avoid that cave, sir. Unnecessary elimination of native predatory species is discouraged by the Unaligned Worlds Protocol Handbook.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135679" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lamentation: The Order of Revan has clearly not understood the secret of Revan's success--proper application of adaptable hunter-killer units.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135680" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sometimes I think of claiming a new ship. But if I take the ship of an enemy, he must be truly great. These ships are not enough for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135681" id2="17" version="1065353216">An army of drooling morons and enough blaster stockpiles to keep us shooting for days. You remembered my birthday!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135682" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is beauty in a swarm of ships rising and dancing in the air. Considerably less so when the pilots wish us dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135683" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. So we're not just fighting an army--we're fighting an armada. If you don't ask for a bonus, I will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough ships to wage war. One way to win: stop them on the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at those ships. Wouldn't mind having a fleet like that. Don't much want to fight one, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scores of ships and ten times as many cultists. I'm ready for this if you are, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135687" id2="17" version="1065353216">At a glance, these ships have enough firepower to breach Rishi's crust. They cannot be allowed offworld.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently we could have just landed here. Everyone else did. They wouldn't notice one more, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will you look at those ships? Good news is, if the Revanites decide to pack up and go home, we won't have to give them a ride.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135690" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow! I know those ships are going to kill everyone we care about, but--wow! If we save the galaxy, can we go joyriding?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wouldn't mind having an army to back us up on this one. Lots of ships and lots of troops ahead. At least tell me the Force is with us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135692" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to lift up those ships and toss them into the sea--then we wouldn't have to fight this battle. But no one's that strong in the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135693" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those are some good-looking ships out there. I know we've got work to do, but I bet we could strip a few parts quick enough...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always wanted to get my hands on a fleet. Tuning one ship is a joy--synchronizing a hundred sounds like a challenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135695" id2="17" version="1065353216">Haven't seen a fleet on the ground like that since Corellia. That many ships could put up a fight against any planet's defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135696" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll try to record as many images of these ships as I can, sir--even if we win, Republic authorities will want a record of any that escape.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
