<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>52</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/bronze/imperial/bugs_and_bombs/captain_ascercia.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319149" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are still so many... I'm going to need more explosives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319150" id2="17" version="1065353216">Set the charges around the nest, then hunt down their queen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319151" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where are you? Come out! I know you're there, you brain-stealing vermin! Oh! Uh... sorry. I didn't see you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319153" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Ascercia of House Thul. Can't speak now, got to keep an eye out. Killiks are everywhere....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319155" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll turn us all into mindless drones to serve in their hives. They must be stopped!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319156" id2="17" version="1065353216">I lack the patience to listen to your raving. Just tell me what's going on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop ranting and speak sense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319157" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, the Killiks are a menace! Giant insects that can take control of your thoughts! And they are spreading.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319159" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hardly see what it matters if this miserable planet is overrun by Killiks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319159" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319160" id2="17" version="1065353216">They control your mind, my lord! They'll worm their way into your brain, too....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319162" id2="17" version="1065353216">You looking to hire me for some bug-stomping?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319162" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a job offer to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319163" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you'd understand! You want to kill them, too, don't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319165" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are plenty of bigger threats on Alderaan than the Killiks. Why are you so worried?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319165" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't seem likely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319166" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why aren't you worried? There are countless Killiks out there just looking for a way to dig into your mind....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319168" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think they're going to keep spreading?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are they a serious threat?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their numbers increase daily. They're trying to burrow into my thoughts, I know it....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319171" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scared of a few bugs?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319172" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are bugs on this planet twice the size of men, who can steal your mind! You don't find that unsettling?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319174" id2="17" version="1065353216">When they overrun our world, House Thul will be powerless to aid the Empire!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319176" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got demolition charges. We can strap them to the Killik hive to draw their queen out of hiding! Help me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319177" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me the charges.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explosives? To kill bugs?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319179" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm the only sane one left! The only one who knows what the monsters are up to!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319181" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attach the charges, then seek the queen. Tell my commander we succeeded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319183" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kill them all. Kill them with fire!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319185" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've snapped. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319186" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll cover this planet with their hives, and then you'll see....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319188" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you see that? Was it a Killik? This place is crawling with bugs....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="485276" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, maybe you should look over our battle plans again. I can handle the debriefing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="485278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, forgive the captain. He hasn't been the same since the Imperial squad we were traveling with was attacked by the Killiks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="485280" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were their field guides, helping to install a long-range sensor array. Prototype technology, all the way from Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="485282" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Killiks overwhelmed us. The Imperials had the sensors on their backs. The Killiks...attached them to their hives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="485283" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attached them how?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="485284" id2="17" version="1065353216">The men were cocooned. Some kind of sticky, woven material. More Killik filth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="485286" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're crazy too.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="485287" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know what I saw. The men were cocooned, wrapped up and stuck to the hive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="485289" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have all day.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="485290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't you get it? Those men were put in cocoons. Now the Killiks have our sensors.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="485292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ever since, I've been working on a way to get even. Now I have it-- these liquid grenades. Special formula, dissolves the cocoons on contact.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="485294" id2="17" version="1065353216">With these grenades, we could get those sensors, avenge those men, and win this war. But with the captain's...illness, I can't leave him alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="485295" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say no more, friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="485296" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. House Thul will owe you a great debt if you make it out alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="485298" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where are the sensors?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="485299" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Killik hives are just over this ridge. The men and the sensors are...well, you won't miss them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="485301" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you get yourself and the sensors out, take them to Major Pharoth, our CO at Outpost Bolym.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="485303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe the captain will improve when he hears what you're doing. Good luck out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="485305" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your problem. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="485306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just be careful out there, then. The captain and I have seen what the Killiks can do.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
