<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/bronze/republic/the_terror_brigade/lieutenant_calia.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="537824" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear you made quick work of that Onslaught. The Terror Brigade delivered the Imperial Moff, as promised. Nicely done.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="537826" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't envy you having to face that Onslaught. But you've got my thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="537827" id2="17" version="1065353216">This has to be a joke. No way command would throw us a mission like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="537828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems I've been downgraded to &quot;expendable.&quot; Go figure.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="553286" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Terror Brigade is always looking for a new combat thrill: unarmed ambushes, wrestling wampas, they've done it all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="554610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recently assaulted an Imperial base for kicks. Captured Moff Yoren, one of the Empire's chief strategists. Now they're offering to ransom him off to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="554650" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got the right of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="554991" id2="17" version="1065353216">You familiar with the Terror Brigade? Group of ex-Mandalorians, all crazy as a snow cat with heatstroke.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="554993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently they found the mercenary lifestyle on Hoth too boring, if you can believe it. Now they'll fight anything with a pulse: Republic, Imperial, doesn't matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="555277" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll face this Onslaught.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="555278" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've beaten Mandalorians.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="740420" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure. But these aren't your typical Mandos.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="740424" id2="17" version="1065353216">Disappointing, but I can't say I blame you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="741099" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I don't do it, no one will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="741345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me guess--there's a catch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="741347" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's generous of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741571" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Terror Brigade wants us to pass something called &quot;the Onslaught&quot; before they hand over the Moff.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heard rumors about this Onslaught--chock-full of wild beasts and Terror Brigade wackos. Command has given my squad permission to try, but I doubt our odds are good.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741576" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, hand over some credits, get an Imperial military genius--sounds like a good deal, right? Wish it was that simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="741578" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's suicide.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741579" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;For the Republic.&quot; You know how it is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="741581" id2="17" version="1065353216">You going through with it?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure. Probably turn my back on the whole thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Moff Yoren has intel on every major Imperial campaign. We need him. But I'd rather not lead my people into some Mandalorian death trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="741624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't put up with that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Already got our hands plenty full fighting off the Hailstorm Brotherhood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="741665" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="741668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then pay them. Simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turns out the Mandos aren't interested in credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741672" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard some impressive things about Havoc Squad. Sounds like this mission is right up your alley. Up for it?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741673" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got a reputation for surviving the impossible. Perfect candidate for the Onslaught, I'd say. Think you can handle it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="741674" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want me to do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Er, yes, actually.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741678" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi's got a better chance of surviving this Onslaught than anyone. We need you to tackle this one for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="741680" id2="17" version="1065353216">No way. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only survived because they were using makeshift weapons. Can't imagine the damage they'd do with a real arsenal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741683" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember, that Onslaught was designed to break their strongest warriors. You watch yourself in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Appreciate it. I've fought the Terror Brigade before. Not too eager to relive the experience.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
