<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>5</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/heroic_weekly/republic/mission_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Obatt has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Apalis sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Lieutenant Obatt may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Urgent! House Organa seeks aid! Despite our diplomatic efforts, House Thul has brought chaos and bloodshed to Alderaan. We have received reports of Imperial probe droids in the area, further evidence that House Thul has allied themselves with the Empire.

If these reports are true, the Empire's intel must not be allowed to reach House Thul. Organa forces brought down a probe droid in the area, but were overwhelmed by Thul forces during recovery. Hazard pay is offered to any volunteers able to overcome these invaders and reach the wreckage. Proceed with caution: Thul forces appear to have advanced reconnaissance and combat training.

If successful, deliver any intel recovered to Rickard Organa. For House Organa!

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178300" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent Essor has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the King's Pass sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Agent Essor may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178301" id2="17" version="1065353216">Elz Organa has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the King's Pass sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Elz Organa may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178302" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dolin Organa has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the King's Pass sector of Alderaan. For additional details about the mission, Dolin Organa may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
