<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>15</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/02/ep_06/transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1206210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alarms disabled in your area, but you may run into security. Engage at will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1206213" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah... We seem to have run into a minor complication. With very large teeth. Mind lending a hand?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1215849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, honored guests! Tonight we celebrate our glorious leader, the one and only Empress Vaylin!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1215853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scene 3 int</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1215854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exiting the party is strictly forbidden--but, honestly, who'd ever want to cut such a fantastic evening short!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1215855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Complimentary holograms of Empress Vaylin can be picked up in the reception area. Let her light up your home today!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1215856" id2="17" version="1065353216">The moment we've been waiting for is almost here! Remember, speaking during a royal address is punishable by death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217119" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vaylin's on the roof. You can reach her if you hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander. We've cracked the intel you secured earlier. Standby while I open a shortcut...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217817" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the server room. Lift the lockdown, and you'll be able to access the valuable data within.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217818" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've lifted the lockdown, Commander. Pay the server room a visit, and secure Vaylin's precious data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1218160" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the server room. There should be valuable data within. Try to establish an uplink.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1219013" id2="17" version="1065353216">The palace is in absolute chaos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1219015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vaylin's guests are stampeding for the exits, and Arcann's loyalists are blasting anything that moves. The entire district is on lockdown!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1219017" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid you'll need to get creative if you want to reach the skydeck.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
