<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>57</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/republic/revan/doctor_narem.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200926" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic butchers! You've invaded a sovereign Imperial world! Slaughtered dozens of innocents to, what, steal our research?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200928" id2="17" version="1065353216">This facility is on a mission of peace. We're charting the Maelstrom Nebula for the good of all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surrender the technology you're using to navigate the nebula, and you won't be harmed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hand over the Gree computer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like the other personnel you spared? I'm no fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200932" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have warships in orbit and battalions on the surface. If this is your version of a peace mission... you're doing it wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200932" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain the military forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200933" id2="17" version="1065353216">We knew once you discovered our research you'd attempt to steal it--and here you are!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spare me your lies. The Empire has a prison inside the Maelstrom Nebula. A Jedi Master is held captive there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200935" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're guarding a prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200936" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have nothing to do with that--and the Empire has every right to imprison anyone who threatens its security.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200938" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the rest of the galaxy hears of this unprovoked assault, the Republic's evil will finally be exposed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your names will become synonymous with your government's extermination campaign against us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200941" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will surprise no one when the Jedi are revealed as warmongers. All you've ever sought is my culture's extermination!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your Empire started this war. Before that, it was the Sith who tried to enslave the Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200942" id2="17" version="1065353216">You confuse us with the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200944" id2="17" version="1065353216">We take no pleasure in killing, but we do what we must to protect the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spare me your platitudes. I see you for what you are: a murderer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200947" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are the guardians of peace and justice in the galaxy--but there can be no peace without justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200947" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi seek only peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your Empire oppresses, enslaves and murders all who don't submit. I cannot permit that to continue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200950" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've only ever defended ourselves. It's you who oppress us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200952" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are they paying you to exterminate us? What price was your conscience worth?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200953" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we give your Empire the chance, you'll wipe us out. Destroy whole worlds and enslave the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200953" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm protecting my people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200955" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I can save the Republic by killing you people, so be it. I won't shed any tears.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think you're a hero, don't you? All I see is a murderer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200958" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know who you are, but I know what you serve--a campaign to eradicate the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200959" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm keeping the galaxy safe for independent entrepreneurs. No offense, but the Republic made me the better offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200959" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is just business, pal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell yourself whatever you want. You're nothing but mercenary scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Save your accusations. Gree technology isn't easy to come by. Where did the Empire find it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200962" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you get the computer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200963" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Malgus obtained the computer during an expedition to the Outer Rim. I don't know more than that--and I don't care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200965" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't even dignify that with a response. I want to hear everything you know about the nebula.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200965" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the Maelstrom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200966" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a massive expanse of cosmic dust and highly charged energy particles. Ship sensors are useless beyond a few kilometers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200968" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're condemning hundreds of civilian science vessels exploring the Maelstrom Nebula. Electromagnetic radiation alters the safe navigation routes every moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200970" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without precise and timely coordinates from the Gree computer, thousands of good people--innocent scientists--will be trapped there forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200971" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic doesn't leave civilians to die. Transmit fresh coordinates to your science vessels and order them home. Then, the computer's ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200971" id2="17" version="1065353216">Call back your civilians now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200972" id2="17" version="1065353216">But our research! All that dangerous exploration will have been for nothing without a complete map....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Transmitting the coordinates now. The computer is yours. I hope it breaks the first time you use it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200975" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are no good or innocent people in the Empire. Your scientist friends work for the Emperor, just like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperials die. I'm happy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those crews don't have supplies to last more than a few weeks. They'll starve to death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200978" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let you kill them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200979" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't stop what's happening--but you can run away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be a fool. Just leave.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="200980" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... I... Emperor forgive me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200982" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should've taken &quot;no&quot; for an answer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Idiot. [Kill Doctor Narem]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aaaaah!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200985" id2="17" version="1065353216">...come in, repeat, come in! My fleet's taking heavy losses, and the fortress defenses are crumbling. There's no more time!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take the computer to the fortress shuttle bay! You can fly out in one of their ships. We'll rendezvous in Republic space. Now go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200989" id2="17" version="1065353216">You people are nothing but thieves and butchers!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="673598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Idiot. [Kill Doctor Narem]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
