<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>32</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/republic/revan/grand_moff_kilran_holo_maelstrom_prison.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your persistence is impressive. Most of my foes have the decency to die quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes... I arrived before you. Bided my time in the nebula.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201051" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oteg spread his forces too thin. It will cost him his life--and yours. Darth Malgus will be most pleased.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201052" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find Master Oteg and I can survive anything you dish out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi aren't easy to kill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Feeling invincible, are we? Good--makes my victory even sweeter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201055" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Oteg and I have outwitted you at every turn. You're counting your victories too soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201055" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're smarter than you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201056" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not this time. I planned our battle down to the last detail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroying a fleet is one thing. Killing Havoc Squad is much harder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't underestimate us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201059" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is truth to that, soldier--but not enough to save you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201061" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is it with you? It's always kill, kill, kill. Can't we settle this with an insult contest? I'll even let you go first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201061" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's just rude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201062" id2="17" version="1065353216">I actually look forward to some well-earned silence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should your master's name mean anything to me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who is Darth Malgus?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201065" id2="17" version="1065353216">What short memories you people have. Darth Malgus is the Empire's greatest hero. He led the assault on Coruscant's Jedi Temple. Killed its leaders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201067" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should meet in person. I can make both sides of your face match.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come and get me, ugly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes... this ought to be personal, shouldn't it? I'll see the light in your eyes extinguished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scurry about our prison. After I destroy your fleet, I'll find you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201072" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Oteg. We've sliced the enemy's comm frequency. Kilran's got us pinched between his fleet and the prison's auto-cannons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201074" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi prisoner must be freed, even if it means losing the fleet. As long as we're between you and Kilran, you're protected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201075" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you stay here, you'll die. Fall back. Kilran can't stop this rescue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201075" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need to retreat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201076" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll make a tactical retreat. Draw off enemy warships. Divide their forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201078" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep the comm channel open. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201079" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your sacrifice won't be in vain. Take those Imperial ships with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201079" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fight and die well, Oteg.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201080" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep the comm channel open so you know the situation. Goodbye, my friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201081" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep the comm channel open so you know what's happening. Goodbye, my friend.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
