<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>28</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/republic/revan/grand_moff_kilran_holo_taral_v.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201085" id2="17" version="1065353216">You. On my doorstep. Fortune has always favored me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201087" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've all made quite an impression on the galaxy since our last meeting. Congratulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201089" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been busy since our last meeting. Saved Coruscant... Tython. Pity about Uphrades, but you can't win them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201091" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Intelligence has kept me appraised of your career since our last meeting. Strange plagues and dark secrets... you lead an interesting life, Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201093" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since our last meeting, you've become a rising star in the Republic Special Forces. I've read your file. Quite respectable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201095" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've followed your growing infamy since our last meeting. You've made a name for yourself among the galaxy's mongrels. Congratulations, I suppose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201097" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sadly, your victories end here. My fleet is about to bombard your position from orbit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201098" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place is designed to withstand a lot of firepower.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201098" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thing I'm in a fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201099" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fortress shields have been deactivated. You're standing in a tomb, and I'm burying you in it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201101" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're being foolish, Kilran. Blind strikes rarely find their target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201101" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a hopeless strategy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201102" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make up for inaccuracy with sheer quantity. It served me well on Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you insane? You'd wipe this fortress off the map just to get revenge?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201104" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll kill your own people!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201105" id2="17" version="1065353216">My orders are to safeguard the fortress's contents at any cost. I've adopted a liberal interpretation of that command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be hasty, chief. We can both walk away from this. Name your price.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's make a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201108" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only restitution that will satisfy me is your ashes scattered to the wind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201110" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who the blazes are you? What's got you angry enough to blow up your own fortress?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201110" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have we met before?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201111" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grand Moff Rycus Kilran. We sparred during the Esseles incident. I was hunting the Twi'lek ambassador, Vyn Asara. You interfered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201113" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've survived worse. Seeing your face, for starters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201113" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give it your best shot, ugly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Schoolyard insults? Tsk, I expected better from the Republic's so-called finest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201116" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been a pleasure catching up... but you won't escape this time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201120" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's Oteg. Do you read me? I monitored that transmission. My fleet is moving to intercept the bombardment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201122" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do my best to keep the Grand Moff busy, but you need to hurry. Find that Gree computer and get out of there!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
