<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>14</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/republic/revan/maelstrom_prison_transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201144" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oteg lives to fight another day--through cowardice, of course. Now you're all alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201146" id2="17" version="1065353216">So much for Oteg. With his death, the Republic's little misadventure here comes to an end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201148" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd hoped to finish you myself, but Lord Vanithrast beat me to your position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201150" id2="17" version="1065353216">There won't be much left after he's finished. Pity. I so enjoy collecting trophies....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201154" id2="17" version="1065353216">All vessels, retreat. Repeat: All vessels retreat immediately. Over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201155" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cruisers Nova and Farstar--pull in the rear guard. The enemy's taking the bait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Draw the enemy fleet into the Maelstrom. Buy our friends more time....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rear guard's taking heavy fire! Cruisers Nova and Farstar--close that gap!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201159" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Onasi's gone. Concentrate firepower on the Emperor's Glory! Don't let it through!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201160" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial bombers strafing the Telos. All fighter wings, break and attack. Fire at--aaaaah!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201163" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Scarred Man followed you. Hatred. Master Oteg in flames. Mercy is the Jedi's defense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201166" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha! Caught the enemy on a caf break. Prison defenses might as well be made of flimsiplast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find the security control center. Deactivate the internal safeguards. The computer system will reveal the Jedi prisoner's location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201170" id2="17" version="1065353216">My fleet will move in and provide any support you need. Good luck!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
