<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>24</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/republic/revan/master_oteg_holo.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201324" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done, my friends. We now have access to the Empire's communications. Do you read me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201325" id2="17" version="1065353216">Outstanding. You've given us access to the Empire's communications. Are you there, my friend?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our data slicers are quietly shutting down the Empire's security grid. The enemy's in for an unpleasant surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201329" id2="17" version="1065353216">The time for subtlety is almost over. Make your way carefully to the fortress... but once you arrive, strike quickly and hard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201330" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no pleasant way to make a frontal assault on an Imperial fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201330" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't have any choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Normally, I'd advise you to minimize the casualties, but our objective is too important.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201333" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather not hurt anyone I don't have to. Is there a way to enter the fortress without fighting?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201333" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer less violent methods.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201334" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry we have to be the aggressors here, but we have no choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201336" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't the first time I've crashed one of the Empire's parties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201336" id2="17" version="1065353216">I plan to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201337" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may find this particular celebration more intense than normal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Making a big entrance is my specialty, little guy. Relax and enjoy the show.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201339" id2="17" version="1065353216">I always do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your confidence inspires many feelings, young one. Let's hope the enemy is more frightened than amused.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201342" id2="17" version="1065353216">How fast will those ships in orbit respond once they hear what's happening at the fortress?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201342" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the Imperial fleet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201343" id2="17" version="1065353216">The sentry ships aren't prepared for a ground invasion. They shouldn't be a factor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201345" id2="17" version="1065353216">This would be easier if you weren't jabbering at me all the time. You're the worst backseat driver I've ever met.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201345" id2="17" version="1065353216">You talk too much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha. Normally, people are stepping on my toes. Point taken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201348" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sending coordinates to the fortress. The Gree computer is amazingly compact. You'll have no trouble carrying it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201350" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep quiet from here on, unless it's an emergency. Oteg out....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
