<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>128</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/republic/revan/master_oteg.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201172" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll be dropping out of hyperspace shortly. Be ready to launch that assault shuttle when we arrive at Maelstrom Prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cut your escape awfully close. Grand Moff Kilran destroyed the fortress just moments after you left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201175" id2="17" version="1065353216">We suffered heavy losses at Taral Five: the Dantooine, the Serroco... more starfighters than I care to count.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201177" id2="17" version="1065353216">But there's no time to mourn the dead. We must strike the Empire's prison before the enemy bolsters its defense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Down on Taral Five, your Jedi friend sent us warnings. We couldn't see her, but it was definitely her voice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201178" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dead Jedi contacted us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201179" id2="17" version="1065353216">Extraordinary. Your team has a powerful ally. The Force is with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201181" id2="17" version="1065353216">Down on Taral Five, your Jedi friend sent warnings. She didn't appear, but it was definitely her voice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201181" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dead Jedi contacted me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201182" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. She's a powerful ally, and her counsel is useful--always listen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201184" id2="17" version="1065353216">You aren't a Force user. That's extraordinary--and wonderful. Heed her advice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201186" id2="17" version="1065353216">What defenses are protecting the prison? How hard will it be to crack into?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201186" id2="17" version="1065353216">How tough will this be?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201187" id2="17" version="1065353216">The prison's location is its primary defense. Difficult to attack what you can't find. More than that, we don't know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201189" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grand Moff Kilran has to know what we're up to. His fleet is probably on its way there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201189" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need reinforcements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201190" id2="17" version="1065353216">All the more reason to move quickly while we have one advantage he doesn't: the latest coordinates through the nebula.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201192" id2="17" version="1065353216">My technicians have plugged the Gree computer into the Telos's hyperdrive. We're already calculating a safe route to Maelstrom Prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201194" id2="17" version="1065353216">When we arrive, I need my best people leading the raid. You're the Jedi prisoner's only hope of escaping alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201195" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll carve open every blast door in the prison by hand, if that's what it takes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201195" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on me, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201196" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even with a lightsaber, that might be time consuming. I recommend searching for the keys, first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201198" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force has brought us together. I will see this through, wherever it leads.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201198" id2="17" version="1065353216">I feel the pull of destiny.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201199" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let the Force be your guide--but keep your eyes open, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201201" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad gets the job done every time, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201201" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood, Admiral.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201202" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've asked too much of you, young one. Too much of everyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201204" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there's one thing I'm known for, it's daring rescues. That, and impeccable timing. Snappy comebacks are a close third....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201204" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course I am.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201205" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heh... the spirit of youth. Hard to believe it's been two-hundred years since I was your age....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201207" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we have a plan to free the rest of the captives? We're not just leaving them there, are we?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201207" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about other prisoners?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201208" id2="17" version="1065353216">The facility was specifically built for the Jedi prisoner. The good news is, you should only have to break open one cell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201210" id2="17" version="1065353216">It would be helpful to know who I'm rescuing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we even know his name?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201211" id2="17" version="1065353216">I asked my source the same thing. She said revealing too much could jeopardize his rescue. You'll know everything before I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201213" id2="17" version="1065353216">This mission will cost more lives before it's done, but it's a necessary sacrifice. The Jedi prisoner can end this war--save countless worlds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201215" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll be jumping to hyperspace soon. Head for the shuttle bays. Be ready to launch on my signal. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201219" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperial shuttle will take you to Taral Five--but I will be in constant communication. Now go....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201222" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, friends. You're even more impressive in person. Forgive me for not shaking hands, but I forgot my hover seat today. Heh....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201224" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, my friend. I appreciate you coming all this way. Oh, do forgive me for not shaking hands. My hospitality exceeds my reach, heh....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201226" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before we begin, I'll ask that you keep an open mind to what you're about to hear. The source of my information is... unconventional.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201227" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi is prepared to accept help from any source.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201227" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't bother me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201228" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such wisdom in one so young. Master Satele's faith is well placed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201230" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the feeling this isn't a standard military operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201230" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now you're intriguing me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201231" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your instincts are one of the many reasons you were summoned for this mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201233" id2="17" version="1065353216">A good source of intel only needs to be reliable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201233" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine--but is it trustworthy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201234" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assure you, the information couldn't be from a more legitimate origin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201236" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should see the sources I usually rely on. They redefine &quot;disreputable.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201236" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201237" id2="17" version="1065353216">Despite its unusual nature, my source is of the highest integrity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201239" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm already worried.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201240" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Unconventional&quot; does not mean &quot;unreliable.&quot; Let go of your prejudices.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201242" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're wasting my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201243" id2="17" version="1065353216">Patience, young one. Understanding comes only to a clear mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201245" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will share with all of you what I have seen. Come--stand together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201246" id2="17" version="1065353216">As a Jedi, you are already attuned to the Force. But you must deepen your connection to see as I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201247" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are not a Jedi, but you can still experience the Force's mysteries--with my help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201249" id2="17" version="1065353216">Concentrate with me. Focus your mind. Feel the Force around us. Hear its echoes....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201250" id2="17" version="1065353216">Follow Oteg's lead. This is important.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201250" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone work together.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="201251" id2="17" version="1065353216">[You concentrate with Master Oteg, opening your mind.]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="201251" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Remain silent]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201252" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes... the Force is with us....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201253" id2="17" version="1065353216">Am I listening for anything particular?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201253" id2="17" version="1065353216">What will I hear?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201254" id2="17" version="1065353216">A voice that seeks to be heard. It was silenced long ago, but now it returns....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201255" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't come here to stand in a circle and chant nonsense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201255" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is ridiculous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201256" id2="17" version="1065353216">Control your emotions. Release your fear. Then, you will see....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201258" id2="17" version="1065353216">She is here... a Jedi without physical form. Her body is long dead, but her wisdom--her essence--lives on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201259" id2="17" version="1065353216">My Master died, but his voice still speaks to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201259" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've experienced this before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201260" id2="17" version="1065353216">One Jedi persisting beyond death is almost unheard-of. But two? These are strange, dark times indeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201262" id2="17" version="1065353216">I encountered a fallen Jedi who did this--and a Sith whose will lived on long after death. He could possess another living being.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201262" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've experienced this before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith who persist beyond death are aberrations. Expressions of greed and pride. For a pure Jedi to do this... something terrible has happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201265" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you said your source was unconventional, I wasn't picturing a... whatever that is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201265" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wasn't expecting that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most Jedi go their entire lives without experiencing anything like this. You are special.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201268" id2="17" version="1065353216">What I really need are the winners of the next major swoop circuit. She have those?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201268" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm all ears.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201269" id2="17" version="1065353216">Put aside worldly concerns. Open your heart as well as your mind. Jedi who persist beyond death have suffered greatly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201271" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dead shouldn't be able to speak, much less appear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201271" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can that be?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201272" id2="17" version="1065353216">And yet, she does. Her death must have been a terrible thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201274" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dead don't speak. I should know--I've killed plenty of people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201274" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is impossible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not deny what your feelings tell you is true. She is real--and she needs our help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201277" id2="17" version="1065353216">The darkness will consume all it touches. Stars will burn black, ashes raining on lifeless worlds. Everything ends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201279" id2="17" version="1065353216">The prisoner holds the darkness at bay, lost inside it for three-hundred years. His strength will fail. Then, he will become the darkness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201280" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our team will free your friend, no matter what it takes. That's a promise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201280" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will save this prisoner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201281" id2="17" version="1065353216">I promise the prisoner will be freed, no matter what it takes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201281" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will save this prisoner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201282" id2="17" version="1065353216">This prisoner has been fighting the Empire for centuries? How is he still alive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201282" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three-hundred years?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201283" id2="17" version="1065353216">No more riddles. If you want help, start speaking Basic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201283" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop babbling and make sense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201284" id2="17" version="1065353216">The bond weakens, my friend. I'll take things from here....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201286" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's told me many things. Revealed the existence of an Imperial prison in the constantly shifting Maelstrom Nebula--and a way to get there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201288" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only way to navigate the Maelstrom is using a Gree computer hidden at an Imperial fortress. We need that computer to free the Jedi prisoner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201289" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201290" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's a &quot;Gree,&quot; and how are its computers so special?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201290" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Gree&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201291" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gree are an ancient civilization, rarely seen anymore. How the Empire obtained their technology is a mystery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201293" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial fortresses are bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201294" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would not throw you into the fire unless I had no other option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201296" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fortress we're invading is on the planet Taral Five. Enemy territory, protected by Imperial warships. Too many to fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201298" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we have a captured Imperial shuttle that can sneak past the sentries. It's waiting for you in the hangar.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201299" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can fill me in on the rest while we travel. There's no time to waste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then let's get started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201300" id2="17" version="1065353216">No offense, but I'd feel a lot more comfortable invading Imperial space in my own starship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201300" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather take my own ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201301" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wouldn't make it past the first Imperial cruiser. This is the only way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201303" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a powerful Jedi Master. Shouldn't you be part of this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aren't you coming with me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201304" id2="17" version="1065353216">My strength is strategy, not fighting. I would simply be underfoot, heh....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our fleet will hide at the system's edge so I can monitor your mission and guide you. If something goes wrong, we'll come running.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201308" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go to the shuttle, my friends. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201309" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now go to the shuttle, my friend--and may the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="673636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone work together.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="673638" id2="17" version="1065353216">What will I hear?</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="673664" id2="17" version="1065353216">What will I hear?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
