<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>45</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/republic/revan/mp_77.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Admiral Jedi Master Oteg requires your assistance. Meet him aboard the Republic dreadnaught Telos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scanning group facial features and matching to identifile records. Please do not move until this process is complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Identities confirmed. All of you are listed on Republic High Command's approved agents list.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201363" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scanning facial features and matching to identifile records. Stand by... identity confirmed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201365" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are the Jedi Knight who defeated Darth Angral and saved multiple Republic worlds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201367" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are the individual designated &quot;Barsen'thor&quot; by the Jedi Council. This rank indicates a supreme level of trust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201369" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are leader of Republic Special Forces unit Havoc Squad. You are cleared for Indigo-level mission recruitment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201371" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your accomplishments are on record with Republic High Command. You are listed among its few recommended agents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Opening holochannel to Republic Fleet Admiral Jedi Master Oteg. Stand by... channel open.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201375" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello. My name is Oteg. I serve the Jedi Order and lead the Republic's First Expeditionary Fleet. I need your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201376" id2="17" version="1065353216">If a Jedi Master and fleet admiral needs me, the situation can't be good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201376" id2="17" version="1065353216">This must be bad news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201377" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good and bad are relative. Let's just say the situation is &quot;interesting.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201379" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll help you if I'm able, but military operations aren't my specialty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201379" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not a soldier, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201380" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't underestimate yourself. My officers sometimes trip over me, but I'm still fleet admiral.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201382" id2="17" version="1065353216">Expeditionary fleets operate outside Republic territory, sir. Have we invaded Imperial space?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201382" id2="17" version="1065353216">This sounds big.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201383" id2="17" version="1065353216">My fleet is at the Imperial border. Whether we cross it or not depends on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201385" id2="17" version="1065353216">You caught me between jobs, pal. Start talking--I'll stop you when I've calculated my fee.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201385" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds profitable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201386" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you'll give me a patriotic discount.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201388" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't know you could be a fleet admiral and Jedi Master at the same time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201388" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a Jedi admiral?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201389" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've had many titles in my lifetime. I prefer being called Oteg--it's shorter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201391" id2="17" version="1065353216">You didn't need to send a droid to loiter around the spaceport. My holofrequency is always open.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why didn't you just call me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201392" id2="17" version="1065353216">My MP droids are equipped with advanced holochannel scramblers. We can speak more freely than over an open channel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201394" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've received intelligence that the Empire has a secret prison inside the Maelstrom Nebula. It's a dangerous region--impossible to safely navigate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201396" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi prisoner possessing vital information is held captive there. I need your help to navigate the Maelstrom Nebula and free him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201397" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can tell me all the details in person. Give me your coordinates, and I'll meet you there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201397" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201398" id2="17" version="1065353216">What could this Jedi prisoner know that would be worth such a risky operation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201398" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sort of information?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Direct knowledge of the Emperor's plans. Insights the Republic will need to win the coming war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201401" id2="17" version="1065353216">Potential suicide missions aren't something I take on lightly--or for free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="201401" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's going to cost you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201402" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had hoped for heroes--but I can afford mercenaries, too. You'll all be compensated for your efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201404" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admit it's been some time since I visited Tython, but I don't remember the order being quite so mercenary. Very well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201406" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew the Republic military's budget was stretched thin, but I had no idea it was this bad. Very well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201408" id2="17" version="1065353216">The thing about being a Jedi is, you never need credits for yourself. That leaves plenty to share with others. You'll be well compensated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201410" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm aboard the First Expeditionary Fleet's command ship, the dreadnaught Telos. Transmitting coordinates now--and please keep them to yourself. Oteg out....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201414" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good day, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good day, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="201416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good day, citizen.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
