<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>123</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/directive_7/republic/director_rigel.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200484" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need a vacation....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200485" id2="17" version="1065353216">What in blazes happened down there? The entire moon is breaking apart as we speak!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200487" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was a very serious threat, of course, but... I think this goes a bit beyond our acceptable degree of force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, destroying Directive Seven meant destroying the moon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200488" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did what I had to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200489" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know, Master Jedi. This was very extreme.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200491" id2="17" version="1065353216">I only struck our enemies, but they carried a heavy cost even in death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200491" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was regrettable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200492" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Heavy cost&quot; and &quot;blew up a moon&quot; aren't the same thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destruction of the primary target--the leader of Directive Seven--resulted in unintended consequences.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200494" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can explain, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200495" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unintended consequences? Would your CO buy that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200497" id2="17" version="1065353216">This level of service is normally extra--but I like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200497" id2="17" version="1065353216">And at no additional charge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you lost your mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200500" id2="17" version="1065353216">I stop the biggest genocide in history, and you're upset about that worthless rock?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200500" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just saved the galaxy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200501" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did what I was sent to. Collateral damage isn't my problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Back off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200502" id2="17" version="1065353216">Collateral damage? You blew up a moon!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200504" id2="17" version="1065353216">The moon was destroyed through Mentor's carelessness, not your agent. Cast blame where it belongs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200506" id2="17" version="1065353216">The moon's destruction was purely a result of Directive Seven's actions. Your agents are blameless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugh. I'm sorry. I just wasn't expecting... this situation has been very difficult. But you faced that difficulty and succeeded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200510" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've saved more lives than anyone will ever know. The people of the Republic--of the entire galaxy--are alive today because of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Protecting innocent people is what the Jedi live for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200511" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200512" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't mean you don't deserve gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200514" id2="17" version="1065353216">I simply acted as the Force guided me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200514" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was the will of the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, good thing the Force was on our side, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad is always happy to serve, Director.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just doing my duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200518" id2="17" version="1065353216">And serve you have. I won't forget it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200520" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want to give me some kind of certificate to that effect....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I get that in writing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200521" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid not. This op stays strictly off the record. People will sleep better not knowing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those droids came a lot closer to having their revolution than I would've liked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200523" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just glad it's over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Close or not, it didn't happen. That's all that matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200526" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume that someone who saves the entire galaxy receives a great deal of... gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200526" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what's my reward?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given that we can never reveal this situation to anyone, your reward will have to stay under the table. But it will be substantial.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200529" id2="17" version="1065353216">We also owe you a great debt of thanks--C5-M3, was it? Without you, we would never have had a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200531" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would be proud to offer you an assignment here in the Republic fleet as soon as you've had some standard maintenance checks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assignment? Nonsense. I belong to no one--I will leave and go where I please.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200535" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm... sorry, but I'm not sure I can allow that. You have the same programming as the other renegades--letting you roam free would be extremely dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200536" id2="17" version="1065353216">C5 is no threat to us, Director. He's earned the right to do as he wishes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let C5 go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200537" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're willing to take responsibility for the matter... by all means. C5, you are free to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200539" id2="17" version="1065353216">As if I needed your leave....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for speaking on my behalf. It's good to know that some organics can understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200543" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've actually enjoyed meeting you, despite the circumstances. Perhaps we'll meet again someday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks again for your help. It's been... interesting. Take care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200547" id2="17" version="1065353216">This droid has the potential to repeat the entire situation. He can't be released.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200547" id2="17" version="1065353216">C5 is too dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200548" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I gave everything I have to protect you....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200550" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am a free being....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200552" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's for the best--we'll treat him well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200554" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope the next time we meet is under better circumstances. Thanks again for your assistance--take care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your shuttle is waiting--and time is running out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200557" id2="17" version="1065353216">...Targets of opportunity are AA, comms and shields. But remember: We're diversions first and hotshots second. Questions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there a reason you're not telling us who we're hitting, sir? I mean, if it's just more Imps, I don't see why--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200561" id2="17" version="1065353216">The target is classified, the mission is classified, you being here is classified. Everything is classified. Just get to your fighters and do your job, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surely those men deserve to know what they're fighting against?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why hide the truth?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your tension will only distract you from our task, my friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Release your apprehensions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200564" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll relax when we're done, Master Jedi. I won't promise anything beforehand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200566" id2="17" version="1065353216">If those men are going to fight and die out there, they deserve to know what it's for, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200566" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't send them in blind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200567" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't have this situation leaking out and starting a panic. They're protecting the Republic--that's all they should need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200569" id2="17" version="1065353216">With charms like that, I'm surprised you chose to work as a shadowy government agent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not very smooth, are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200570" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is no time for sarcasm. We have a job to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you ready to get started, Director?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's begin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, yes--thank you for coming. Let's get right into it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200575" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listening to pointless briefings is a waste of my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200575" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't come here to wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200576" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, all right... just let me make sure the doors are sealed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200578" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know the basics: A faction of renegade droids called &quot;Directive Seven&quot; is planning to exterminate every form of biological life in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200580" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not all of the renegades agree, though. Someone inside the movement wants us to take them down. He, she or it has been our primary source of intel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200581" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't even know this traitor's identity?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200581" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;He, she or it&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Directive Seven only accepts droids, as far as we know, but the traitor never gave personal information--just intel on the movement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Having someone on the inside will give us a big advantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200584" id2="17" version="1065353216">One ally is better than none.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200585" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's our hope, at least. So far, all of the intelligence has checked out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200587" id2="17" version="1065353216">This could easily be nothing but a huge ambush.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200588" id2="17" version="1065353216">We aren't new at this. We've triple-checked every piece of information--it's all solid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to our unnamed friend, we know Directive Seven's ultimate weapon: a coded signal that can forcibly convert any droid to their cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200592" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's how they're planning to wipe us out--they're going to transmit that signal across the entire galaxy, turning every droid into a mindless killing machine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200593" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll start a galaxy-wide revolution in a matter of seconds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Incredible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly. Our only chance is to strike now, before it's too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200596" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we block the droids' transmissions, their plan won't work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't we jam the signal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200597" id2="17" version="1065353216">No such luck--their tech is too sophisticated. Our only option is to destroy the source.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Droids turning other droids into killers just like that? Seems farfetched.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200599" id2="17" version="1065353216">That can't be true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200600" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've already used their signal to decimate three entire colonies. We can't afford to wait--we have to strike now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200602" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their headquarters is on a moon called Zadd, in the Unknown Regions. But the defenses are too thick for any kind of orbital attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200604" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only way to stop Directive Seven's plan is on the ground: Make a big diversion and slip a strike team through their defenses. That's where you come in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200605" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will not allow these droids to harm another living creature.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200605" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Subtlety and precision are a Jedi's specialty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get me on the ground, and I'll do what needs to be done, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like everything I heard about you was right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200610" id2="17" version="1065353216">I kinda figured I wouldn't be part of the diversion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makes sense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ahem. No. That would be a waste of time, wouldn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200613" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess our options are this, or a galaxy-wide droid massacre....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200613" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's what it takes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200614" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the situation we're faced with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200616" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should've known that taking down an entire revolution wouldn't be easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="200616" id2="17" version="1065353216">This doesn't sound fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200617" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a reason I only called the best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200619" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got a shuttle ready to take you in and starfighters to cover you. But I'm afraid that's as much as we can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200621" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are trillions of lives on the line here. Everything we have--the entire Republic--depends on you. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry. This isn't a good time.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
