<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>91</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/world/killed_in_custody/paus.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks again for all your help, buddy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683321" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been hearing some serious comm chatter, pal! Sounds like you made a mess in the Justicar tower!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you find any recordings of Rikael? Don't keep me in suspense!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683324" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here you go, Paus--straight out of the Justicar detention center.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683324" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found a holovid of Rikael.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683325" id2="17" version="1065353216">Terrific. Let's see what you found.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rikael's story didn't unfold quite the way you thought it did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683327" id2="17" version="1065353216">You aren't going to like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, that doesn't sound too good. Let me see what you've got here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683330" id2="17" version="1065353216">This recording will reveal to all of Coruscant the truth about the Justicars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683330" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got quite a story here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683331" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew it! We're going to take these Justicars to the curb! Let's see what you found.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683333" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about my pay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, buddy, come on, it's me. Don't worry. Your credits are right here. Let's have a look.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh no! Rikael, you snake! No wonder your parents won't talk about you, you little thug!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. My whole story, shot to pieces. That little jerk was my best lead. Now I've got nothing to go on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even if this lead didn't work out, you're still right about the Justicars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't give up, Paus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tough break.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683341" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not my fault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683342" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, no, you were great, buddy. I know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683344" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let this keep me down. I'll find the proof. Just got to stick it out a little longer down here, that's all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyways, thanks for all your help. Keep fighting the good fight! I'll see you around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683347" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is perfect! This is going to change the world, baby, the whole galaxy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683349" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once everyone sees the truth about the Justicars, the Republic will squash them like bugs, and freedom will reign! All thanks to you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683350" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683351" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was just one more victory for freedom over tyranny.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683351" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know, I know--I'm a hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683352" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah! That's a great opening line! You're a natural, baby. I'll see you around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683353" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, that's really great, Paus. Really great.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683353" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever you say.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683354" id2="17" version="1065353216">I gotta think of a story title right away... hope I see you around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look for interrogation droids in the Justicar tower, and find one with recordings of Rikael. They'll be in the detention center. For freedom, buddy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, man! A Jedi, in the flesh! Perfect, this is perfect!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683361" id2="17" version="1065353216">A soldier? Special Forces? Oh, beautiful, baby, beautiful! Just what I need!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683363" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoa, look at you! You're perfect, just perfect!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683365" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, my name's Paus, right, and I'm a journalist. The only journalist down here who isn't afraid to dig up the truth!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683367" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on to something major with these Justicars. I'm gonna blow the lid on all their tyranny and oppression, and show all of Coruscant what they really are!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683368" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a noble goal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683369" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you think so, too, my friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683371" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you know about the Justicars, Paus?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683371" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are the Justicars?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683372" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're all about abuse of power. They're the big guy, pushing the little guy down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683374" id2="17" version="1065353216">I try not to argue with lunatics. If you say you're onto something, that's great.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683374" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever you say.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683375" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, if it's crazy to love freedom and hate totalitarian thugs like the Justicars, then yeah, I'm plenty crazy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683377" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm working on a major scoop. A clear-cut case of wrongful arrest, illegal imprisonment and unjust execution!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683379" id2="17" version="1065353216">Proof I need is just out of reach, though. I need a fearless hero to get that evidence. I need you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683380" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me what needs to be done, Paus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683380" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd be glad to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683381" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you were the one! You're a fighter, baby, fighting the good fight!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683383" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683384" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because I can tell! You're brave, you're tough! Everything a hero of freedom and justice should be!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683386" id2="17" version="1065353216">No way--too dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683387" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nah! You can wipe the floor with these Justicars, trust me. You can go all the way, I just know it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683389" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rikael Lysannis. Son of a wealthy family, arrested and executed without trial or explanation. He's the key to everything--the catalyst, the dirty little secret.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody's talking about Rikael's death. Not the Justicars, not his family, nobody. So I need the facts, straight from the source: the Justicar tower. And that's where you come in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683392" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find out the true circumstances of this poor boy's death, Paus. Perhaps then, justice can be served.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683392" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will uncover the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah! And not the Justicars' jack-booted justice, either--the real thing!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Odd. Why do you think the boy's parents won't speak on the matter?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rikael's family isn't talking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683396" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure the Justicars got to them--told them they were dead meat if they talked to anybody.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683398" id2="17" version="1065353216">Infiltrate, search and seize--understood. What will I be looking for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683398" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm always ready for duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's be clear--my expertise comes at a price.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683399" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't work for free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, hey, of course, no problem. We've all got to cover the bills, right? I'll make it worth your while, don't worry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683402" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's in the Justicars' tower that will prove your suspicions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683402" id2="17" version="1065353216">What needs to be done?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683403" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want me to charge into a highly secure facility to do what, exactly? Look around?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683403" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would I do this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683404" id2="17" version="1065353216">You better believe it, buddy. We're going all the way, here, all the way!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interrogation droids. They're the key. Justicars use 'em all the time, and they record everything they see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683408" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find the droid that recorded Rikael, smash it and yank the memory core. You can check the core on the Justicar computers, to make sure you've got the right one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683409" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take care of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Couldn't I bring the memory core back to you? Can't you read the thing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why can't you check it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683411" id2="17" version="1065353216">But what if you end up with the wrong one? You wouldn't want to have to fight your way back in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683413" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you need to find someone else to get your evidence, Paus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683413" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't do this for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683414" id2="17" version="1065353216">But what about freedom? Striking a blow against tyranny and evil? The oppressed masses need you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683415" id2="17" version="1065353216">If innocent people are suffering, then something must be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683415" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right--let's do this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683416" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess I could help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah! You're going to make this happen, I know it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683419" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, then. Soon as you've got the recording  I need, bring it back here and we'll show Coruscant the truth about these Justicars! Good luck, buddy, good luck!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683421" id2="17" version="1065353216">No way, Paus. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, no! Right through the heart, buddy, right through the heart!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683424" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. The truth will come out, one way or another. Forget you, pal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, pal, I'm busy.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
