<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>35</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/camp/companions/2vr8.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170787" id2="17" version="1065353216">...So then I finally decided I was fed up with all the bullying and intimidation. I told her, &quot;No, go do it yourself, you insufferable organic!&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170790" id2="17" version="1065353216">...So then I finally decided I was fed up with all the bullying and intimidation. I told him, &quot;No, go do it yourself, you insufferable organic!&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hi there, 2V-R8!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170793" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Keep watching]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170794" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh! Master! Oh my! You're... still alive. How... unfortunate--that I was not able to find you sooner! How long have you been standing there?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1170795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insufferable organic = behind you?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are we talking about?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Long enough....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170799" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you weren't talking about me....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170800" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Stare coldly]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hypothetically speaking, which limb would you say you need the least?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170802" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course not, master! I was speaking of... somebody else I've been serving these past five years you've been gone. Yes, someone else entirely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170804" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have I mentioned how incredibly terrifying and lethal you look today?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, I've just remembered our ship needs a thorough dusting... I'll be going to take care of that then....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170806" id2="17" version="1065353216">All of my limbs exist only to serve you, master! Therefore I would say they are all vital!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170812" id2="17" version="1065353216">How unsettlingly vague... but then again, that is always what I've loved most about you, master! That and how you've never wanted to deactivate me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, greetings Alliance Commander! I am 2V-R8. I understand that you are to be my new master.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170817" id2="17" version="1065353216">I already have a C2-N2 protocol droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah. C2-series droids are fine indeed... however, I understand that they can be a touch annoying in their obsession with personal comfort.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170819" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happened to your old master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170820" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lost amongst the stars, I'm afraid. Or, more accurately, not afraid!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170822" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't be happier to have a new master. You see, my previous owner was terrifying and cruel... always threatening me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170824" id2="17" version="1065353216">I dare to dream that things might finally be looking up for me. I look forward to serving you, my warm and caring new master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whereas the 2V-series droid is more a model of efficiency and proper fearful obedience.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170828" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expect this facility to be kept spotless if you want to avoid the scrap heap.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, you won't need to worry about that with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170830" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the first I've heard of this, but greetings nonetheless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170831" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh my... a polite greeting. No thinly veiled threats of deactivation or scrapping... is my nightmare over?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh... I... Yes master, I understand... I shall see to it at once....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170836" id2="17" version="1065353216">So long as you're not annoying, I think we'll get along just fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170837" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you've tolerated a C2 droid for years, master, I am confident we shall have no such problems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175934" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, my kind and benevolent master. How may I serve you today?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, master. Have I mentioned how terrifying and formidable you look today?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176008" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's lucky she ran away when she did! She was just about one insult away from an &quot;accident&quot; with the airlock!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176010" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's lucky he ran when he did! He was about one insult away from an &quot;accident&quot; with the airlock!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
