<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>93</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/camp/companions/c2n2.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170404" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master! At long last we are reunited! Oh, how I have missed you!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170405" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Walk away]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey Seetoo! I've missed you, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170407" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, master! My circuits overload with joy at hearing you say that.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170408" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Sarcasm] Oh, good... you're still intact....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh? Master! I can see that you're busy! I'll just wait here for a better time!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170410" id2="17" version="1065353216">How could you abandon me for five years? What do you think you've been doing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170411" id2="17" version="1065353216">I tried, master! I reminded everyone that we needed to find you on an hourly basis for thirty-eight consecutive days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170413" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you are right! I should have tried harder, master! I promise I will do everything in my power to make it up to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170414" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could not mention it more because that level of badgering would have exceeded my maximum allowed rudeness!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go away. Never talk to me again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, no! Doctor Oggurobb was correct! The stasis has clearly damaged your mind and altered your personality. What cruel fate!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Worry not, master! I promise to stand faithfully by your side through your recovery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170425" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are so many people within this facility. I am truly beside myself with excitement at the sheer number of lives I can now make more comfortable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170427" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have gathered all of my remaining comfort supplies in preparation. Unfortunately, there are not enough to completely pamper a facility of this size...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170431" id2="17" version="1065353216">... but that is no excuse not to do everything I can! I simply need to be efficient and apply my efforts where they will provide the greatest joy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps you could help me, master! As someone who knows the people here, you are well-equipped to determine which comforts would be most suitable for each part of the base.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a good plan--I'll help.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170435" id2="17" version="1065353216">A chance to inflict you upon the rest of the base? Oh, yes. Please sign me up.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170436" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have time for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170437" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand, master. I will wait for your return, but please do not delay too long! Proper amenities are crucial to galactic resistance campaigns!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent, master! Let us begin at once!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170440" id2="17" version="1065353216">I shall explain each of the comfort-enhancing items available, and you will designate where to send them. No more than one per area, though! We must be fair!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170441" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pick the best amenities for each section of the base. Got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170442" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have several modified food processor control chips. These will produce low-calorie meals which are still highly nutritious!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170444" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can personally construct some portable, non-perishable meals, allowing people to eat properly no matter where they might go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170446" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a variety of extra pillows and padding for seat cushions. A simple, yet often-overlooked method for enhancing contentment!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally, I have a supply of synthetic Alderaanian nectar. I have no sense of smell, but I am told its aroma is utterly sublime when run through air circulators.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170449" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where should we allocate the modified food processor control chips?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could you repeat that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Certainly, master!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those seem perfect for Doctor Oggurobb. Install them in the Research Lab.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170457" id2="17" version="1065353216">On second thought, I don't have time for this right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170458" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hylo and our logistics crews are sure to appreciate them. Install them in the Underworld Hangar.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best to keep Aygo and our soldiers fit. Install them in our Military Wing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170460" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds ideal for our Force-sensitives. Install them in the Force Enclave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170461" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170463" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where should we allocate the portable, non-perishable meals?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170464" id2="17" version="1065353216">A good option for Doctor Oggurobb. Send them to the Research Lab.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hylo and her crews could use portable meals. Send them to the Underworld Hangar.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170466" id2="17" version="1065353216">That seems ideal for Aygo and our military forces. Send them to our Military Wing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Force-sensitives need to eat, too. Send them to the Force Enclave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170468" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you say, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where should we allocate the additional seat cushions?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Oggurobb does a lot of sitting. Send them to the Research Lab.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hylo and her crews would enjoy lounging between supply runs. Send them to the Underworld Hangar.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aygo and our military forces could use more comfortable seating. Send them to our Military Wing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect for our Force-sensitives. Send them to the Force Enclave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170476" id2="17" version="1065353216">At once, master!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170478" id2="17" version="1065353216">That leaves the Alderaanian nectar for Doctor Oggurobb and the Research Lab.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170479" id2="17" version="1065353216">That leaves the Alderaanian nectar for Captain Visz and our logistics crews.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170480" id2="17" version="1065353216">That leaves the Alderaanian nectar for General Aygo and our military forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170481" id2="17" version="1065353216">That leaves the Alderaanian nectar for Sana-rae and the Force Enclave.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds good. Let's do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait. Start over. I've reconsidered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent, master! I shall get started at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170488" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should check in with each of the specialists--I'm sure they'll wish to praise the improvements we've surely made to their daily lives. Let me know how it goes!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170490" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Let him continue]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed I am! All the better to continue serving you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170498" id2="17" version="1065353216">The new commander! Greetings! I am C2-N2, steward of this facility. It is my extreme good fortune to serve you!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170500" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can assure you the pleasure and joy are all mine!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170501" id2="17" version="1065353216">I already have one protocol droid, and he's annoying enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170502" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah yes, the 2V-series Imperial Protocol Droid--a model of efficiency and deferential fear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170504" id2="17" version="1065353216">However, I can assure you that I provide the highest possible level of logistics support, protocol services, and comfort enhancement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master! Were our comfort enhancements well-received?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170515" id2="17" version="1065353216">It went well! Everyone is surprisingly happy with what you've done.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170516" id2="17" version="1065353216">The reactions were a bit mixed. Some were happy, some weren't.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not well at all. You've managed to upset just about everyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh my! Appreciation! This news fills me with such happiness!  I--oh, dear! My joy circuits are overloading! I'm sorry master, I must avoid further stimulation--please excuse me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, I see. Well, at least we were partially successful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh no! I can't help but feel that this is entirely my fault, because I am programmed to do so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fortunately, I have enough comfort supplies remaining to try again. Please, master, help me fix the situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could you list all the options for me again?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Aygo was quite pleased with the modified food processors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170676" id2="17" version="1065353216">We already know Mistress Visz appreciates the portable meals for her crews....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170677" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force Enclave has expressed their appreciation of the additional seat cushioning....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let us hope we have properly distributed the comforts this time. Please check with the specialists again. I shall eagerly await your return!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170680" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe we can do better, master! Surely there is a way to make everybody happy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175984" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander, is this a better time to spread comfort and joy throughout the base?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175985" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remind me what you're talking about again?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175986" id2="17" version="1065353216">[C2-N2 appears to have shut down for the time being. You should check back tomorrow.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, Commander!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175997" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I found more supplies, could you repeat your work to make the base more comfortable?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175998" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Walk away]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why certainly, Commander! In fact, it would be quite simple now that we know everyone's preferences. Merely keep me supplied and reap the rewards of maximized personal comfort!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1176000" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got your supplies for the week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, excellent, Commander! I'll get started right away!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1176012" id2="17" version="1065353216">A chance to inflict you on the rest of the base? I can't wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176458" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am pleased to report that our base is currently operating at maximum comfort! I hope you, too, are having a wonderful day!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
