<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>85</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/camp/companions/m1_4x.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi, the numerous reports of your gleaming saber cutting a swath through Imperial scum would overwhelm any lesser droid's processors!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171276" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, I've been hearing no end of your actions across the galaxy. Your talents as a soldier almost outshine your abilities as a pilot!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171278" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be happy to know that victories involving you were referenced by a statistically significant number of new recruits as their inspiration for joining!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171280" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to our efforts, recruitment is at an all-time high!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171281" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does this mean the Republic will turn their attention to the Eternal Empire now?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171282" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm happy to stomp Imperials just for the sake of it, but that's good to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171283" id2="17" version="1065353216">Being a lover of totalitarian subjugation is reason enough for a sound beating! Something the people of Zakuul should learn.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171285" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't take satisfaction in these victories when they've done nothing to stop the greater threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171286" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic stands stronger thanks to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171288" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't say whether command is ready to counter-strike our new enemy, but this droid is ready to get back in the fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171290" id2="17" version="1065353216">With my assignment complete here, I could request a transfer to join your Alliance as an attache from the Republic military.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171291" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd greatly appreciate official support from the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Together we will be an unstoppable force of galactic liberation!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171294" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that includes turning Skytroopers to scrap, we'd be glad to have you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171295" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any droid that can be mass-produced can be mass-reduced!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171297" id2="17" version="1065353216">No more morale-boosting duties. You'll be strictly a combat droid. Preferably a quiet one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171298" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am not optimized for stealth operations, but I'm certain my versatile design can adapt as needed!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171300" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing will halt my onslaught straight to the Eternal Throne! Onward!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those dirty Imps are scattering like vermin. Filthy, totalitarian vermin!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171305" id2="17" version="1065353216">Against the stalwart spirit of the Republic, those spineless Imperials are all but on the run!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171306" id2="17" version="1065353216">The march to victory is a long, hard climb over a mountain of Imperial bodies. I'm happy to report the mounds are growing!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171307" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171308" id2="17" version="1065353216">There truly is no rest for the wicked. The Imperial hordes continue their suicide march into our territory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171309" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Requires Participation in 20 Warzones] You're needed in the field more than you are here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171310" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll help when I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Two tyrannical Empires straddle our beloved galaxy, seeking to stamp out the virtues of democracy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171315" id2="17" version="1065353216">So we must be doubly prepared to deliver a righteous boot of our own against these oppressors!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171316" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Continue Listening]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171317" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the face of such depravity, more and more of our fellow citizens are exercising their right to enlist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cloaked in the enduring mantle of the armed forces, these proud recruits are nurtured in the chrysalis of liberty. Emerging from their training as glorious butterflies of... hmm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171321" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, pardon me! I was devoting one-hundred percent of my processing power to my inspirational protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why, sir! I always knew you'd be out there listening.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171325" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the one broadcasting all those messages for the Republic war effort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, Captain!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171330" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's some speech you're working on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171331" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's humbling to find that my calls to action resonate with such a renowned member of your order.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171333" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a sentiment I can get behind. Never underestimate the value of a well-placed boot!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171334" id2="17" version="1065353216">High praise coming from a member of the Coruscant Aegis!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171336" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's an honor to finally meet you. Your volunteer record is truly an inspiration to non-combatants everywhere!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171338" id2="17" version="1065353216">M1-4X, Republic Special Forces, on temporary assignment with the Press Corps.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to meet you, M1-4X.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Flattered as I am, I know a decorated hero such as yourself doesn't require my bracing speeches, but I have others I must reach.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171342" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's a battle droid doing composing propaganda?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171343" id2="17" version="1065353216">I may be a droid, but within this armored chassis hums the core of a patriot!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171345" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a waste of resources.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171346" id2="17" version="1065353216">While not my primary function, leadership and inspiration are core parts of my programming.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now there's a voice I could never forget.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171349" id2="17" version="1065353216">And one the Republic's enemies dread hearing, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171351" id2="17" version="1065353216">When did you go all talk and no action on me, Forex?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171352" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shortly after your unfortunate &quot;demise,&quot; sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Though my blaster cannons are silent, my vocoder has become another booming weapon for freedom. One meant to battle fear and complacency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171356" id2="17" version="1065353216">My duty here is to instill a greater sense of purpose in the people. Now more than ever, the Republic needs its citizens to stand up and fight!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171357" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does your duty include telling those people what they're really up against?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171358" id2="17" version="1065353216">The misdeeds of our vile enemies are as much a motivator as our own valorous conduct, but reports of Republic victories are what I long for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171360" id2="17" version="1065353216">With more veterans such as yourself returning to the fight, I'm certain the galaxy will be back in the hands of good without delay!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171362" id2="17" version="1065353216">My only regret is not being able to assist you on your top secret mission all these years.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171363" id2="17" version="1065353216">There was no mission, Forex. I was a POW.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aha, I understand now! I would choose a more believable cover story, but your secret is safe with me, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171366" id2="17" version="1065353216">Top secret mission?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surely you have been on a mission of utmost secrecy, and making our enemies believe that you were killed was vital for operational success.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171369" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could have used Havoc with me for all I've been through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171370" id2="17" version="1065353216">The strategic minds of our commanders must have had good reason to split us up as they did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171372" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you can see, my own reassignment was greatly needed. After the success of my Morale Initiative, command knew the Press Corps could count on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171374" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recruitment and voluntary redeployment are up fourteen percent since I joined. Soon, we will be able to finally drive out the forces of injustice!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171375" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything I could do to help with that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171376" id2="17" version="1065353216">Continue to lead by your unimpeachable example!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171378" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every time you deliver victory against our depraved enemies, the sovereignty of our Republic is planted firm.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171380" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on a recruitment drive of my own. I'm assembling an Alliance against the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171381" id2="17" version="1065353216">I, for one, would love to give the erroneously named &quot;Eternal&quot; Empire a taste of high-yield justice, but we can't show our backs to those treacherous Sith!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171383" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until the home front is secure, my place is here, making sure those Imps have to claw for every micrometer!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171385" id2="17" version="1065353216">And of course you thought of me, sir! I would be honored to serve under such a fine command as yours again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171387" id2="17" version="1065353216">Under your exemplary leadership I will have no shortage of valorous deeds to supply to the Press Corps.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171389" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never thought I'd see you so far from the front lines, Forex.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171390" id2="17" version="1065353216">It has felt like an unbearable amount of time since I've emancipated a world from the iron grip of despots.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171392" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir! It occurs to me that serving directly under you once again would provide the Press Corps with ample feats of heroism.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171394" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm certain I could persuade my superiors that a joint operation is the best course of action.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to have you back.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better shake off the rust. We're in for some serious fighting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a single component in my ingenious construction is susceptible to rust, corrosion, or cowardice, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alright, but you don't release details of our missions without my go-ahead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171400" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't dream of compromising your operational security, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171402" id2="17" version="1065353216">My actuators are shivering with anticipation. M1-4X is ready for action!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171404" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep up the good fight!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187867" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Requires Valor Rank 40] I've defeated countless enemies of the Republic already!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
