<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>91</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/camp/companions/pierce.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171407" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen some powerful Sith at work, my lord. And you'd give just about all of them a run for their money.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could have used a killer like you in black ops. Might've liked it. Didn't stand on rules and regulations, just bodies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171411" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never gave you Intelligence types much credit when it came to the real fighting. Glad to be wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victories outstripping defeats. Morale's out of the gutter. Logistics are in the black for the first time in years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tide's finally turning now.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then it's time for the Empire to turn its attention to Zakuul.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gonna tackle the real threat now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171418" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's back on the table, I wager.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171420" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic makes it too easy to hurt them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Must not have changed as much as I thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meanwhile the Eternal Empire has had time to gather its strength and dig in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171424" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear you. Would have been trying to squeeze blood from a stone though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171426" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm tired of sitting on the sidelines and Command's out of excuses to keep me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thinking I might assemble another black ops team. Start hitting the hardest targets again. Maybe attach myself to an outfit that can do real damage. Know anything like that?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171429" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Alliance could use you, Pierce.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171430" id2="17" version="1065353216">All the truly hard targets are controlled by the Eternal Empire. You ready for that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171431" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never been more ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171433" id2="17" version="1065353216">If being a desk jockey hasn't made you totally worthless, I might.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coming from anyone but you, that'd be a closed casket.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171436" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been waiting for this, sharpening my edge. Next time you see action, I want to be there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soon as I've got my transfer, I'll meet your people. My CO rejects it, I might put two in his chest as a resignation and come anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171442" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic's on the retreat. Not news to you I'll bet, but it's got the losing fronts stepping livelier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like the Pubs have worn themselves out. Losing more ground everyday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bloodied the Republic's nose with a few key victories. It's a start anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to hear it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171446" id2="17" version="1065353216">Between you and me, the only news we're getting is &quot;bad&quot; and &quot;worse.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171447" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Requires Participation in 20 Warzones] You're needed in the field, Pierce.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171448" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do what I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171451" id2="17" version="1065353216">We aren't here to drone on about facts and figures, Lieutenant. We report victories. Bloody, hard-won victories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get me one by twenty-two hundred or Kaas City will hear about your upcoming suicide mission to Coruscant. Dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171455" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a sight for sore eyes....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kept me waiting long enough, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have my dreams come true, or are you here to finally put me out of my misery?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171460" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've grown comfortable in my absence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171461" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was more comfortable neck-deep in muck on Taris.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171466" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't seem all that surprised to see me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Call it a hunch, but I knew you'd still be out there. Expected to see a report long before your face, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171469" id2="17" version="1065353216">A desk, Pierce. How the mighty have fallen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cruel as ever, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171472" id2="17" version="1065353216">This post is more of a fit for that bootlick of yours, Quinn, but I'm the war hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171474" id2="17" version="1065353216">My &quot;reward&quot; for cracking the Bastion. Promotion, medals, and being trotted out as a reminder of what every grunt should aspire to.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171475" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is no place for a soldier of your caliber.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171476" id2="17" version="1065353216">No it isn't, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171478" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were right to use you as an inspiration, but taking you off the battlefield was a mistake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't prove it, but I suspect Moff Hurdenn had a hand in that. Damned me with praise, I'm sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171481" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many would literally kill for your position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wish they'd hurry on with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Having to sit here and talk about the grand victories instead of being a part of them. It's a fate worse than death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bah, enough of my griping. You have business with the Outreach Bureau, or is this a personal call?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171487" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have organized an Alliance against the Eternal Empire. Join me in crushing it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like something you'd do. I'd love to, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171490" id2="17" version="1065353216">After seeing you alive and well, I wanted to offer you a place at my side once more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171491" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no place I'd rather be than fighting by your side, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171493" id2="17" version="1065353216">This visit was to reclaim something I had lost. You will serve me once again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gladly, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171496" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll inform my superiors of my reassignment. Doubt anyone would be fool enough to dispute it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Next time you see action, I want to be there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171500" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord. You served on the Dark Council alongside Darth Marr. Disappeared along with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171502" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're looking for leads, bounty hunter, I only hear about the action after it's happened these days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait--I know you. You were on the expedition for the Emperor. Not many survivors of that action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171506" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now this is interesting. You're the Intelligence officer that had Marr's ear before we made first contact with Zakuul.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major Pierce. What brings you to the Outreach Bureau?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171509" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've given a lot of speeches asking our people to go &quot;above and beyond&quot; the call of duty. How bad is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171512" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can spot a want ad when I see one. All those speeches tell me you Imps are shorthanded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shrewd.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your service record is quite impressive, by the look of you. It caught my interest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Caught a lot of people's interest. And saddled me with this sorry post.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171518" id2="17" version="1065353216">You look like you've seen more than your share of action, Major. That interests me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Planning to take a run at me for a quick credit? That'd actually interest me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pierce. I've heard that name. Why?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could be I led the op that cracked open the Bastion on Corellia. Could be I served under the Emperor's Wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171524" id2="17" version="1065353216">These days I'm only trotted out like a blasted trophy. Idiots up top think it's good for morale. Winning is good for morale.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems like the Republic's given up on Zakuul and dedicated everything they've got left to kicking our hinds.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171527" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic has had decades to nurture their hatred of us. Arcann's empire isn't nearly as appealing a target for their anger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Picked a fine time to find their backbones.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to bring in a specialist, Major. How much is good news worth to you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me something for the headlines and you can count on more than credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arcann will destroy us both unless we unite against him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171537" id2="17" version="1065353216">He won't have to, things don't start turning around.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then it's time we show them we will not fall so easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171540" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll take more than talk. Just makes being here even more frustrating.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Payback's a real mother, ain't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Goes both ways.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Empire won't be in any shape to tackle Zakuul without pushing back the Republic. Start putting wins on the board and maybe that'll change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope it does. Might get me out of this stuffed shirt and back in the action. Excuse me, the Ministers are waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope to hear more about you soon, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Start putting in your overtime, hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bring me a good op next time you're by.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless it's important, I've got more blasted reports to file.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187856" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Requires Valor Rank 40] I have crushed all of the Empire's enemies!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
