<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>87</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/class/sith_inquisitor/bolan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bolan, I need to disable some kind of Rakata security system. Can you help me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495968" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best slicers in the galaxy. We've been studying the readouts of the device you found earlier, and I think we've got a handle on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495970" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we can't do it, no one can. Patch us in when you're ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jackpot, Sith. Let's ride this droid home. Find that Rakata device and scan it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495973" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stuff you're looking for is at the Republic labs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495974" id2="17" version="1065353216">That diagram's ancient alien tech, all right. Never seen it in my life. But Grokan saw something like this part here in the Republic labs.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="495976" id2="17" version="1065353216">They used it for their tests, to get data off of me. Don't know what, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495978" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's rumors of the kind of crazy stuff those aliens built deeper in the prison. Advanced AIs, self-healing droids, living cities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495980" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said this is some kind of healing device? I can kind of see that. Hard to say, though, without a scan. Them Rakata freaks built some twisted stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495981" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would expect nothing less. How do I acquire this machine and then, how do I use it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds promising.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495982" id2="17" version="1065353216">What was the place your friend said he saw it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where was it again?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic labs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495985" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have time for guesses. I need to know it'll work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495985" id2="17" version="1065353216">But will it work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495986" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can scan that device, we can get you a better idea of what this thing is and how it works.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here. Data chip. It'll re-program the Republic security droids in the area to open up the labs so you can get in and scan the device.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495990" id2="17" version="1065353216">You find us this piece, we'll find you the mystery machine. No question.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495992" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are labs doing as part of a prison?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Labs?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't say for sure. Figure it's something crazy if the Republic's come all the way out to Belsavis to do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495995" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sure this will work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495996" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you think the Empire caused this break, huh? I had these droids figured from day one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take this with you. It'll let us analyze the Rakata prize without you having to drag it back here, yeah?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just watch the prisoners in the area. They're meaner than most.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice work on the beacon. Guess we owe you some info, huh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496004" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need that beacon set up. Can't help you 'til then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three hundred transistors. Three hundred. Sweet stuff, man. Sweet stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey hey. What's this? You bring something juicy? Processor chip? Crazy Sith crystal tech?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will trade for shuttle passes. No, just kidding. We love it here. Some real crazy tech. The droids don't even speak Basic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496010" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm looking for an ancient healing technology. What have you got?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496010" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to contain my power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you the ones that call yourselves the Circle?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nikto slicers, hmm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496012" id2="17" version="1065353216">You got it. Circle like circuit. Everything's connected. The galaxy is one big machine and all our cells are like tiny little droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496014" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never met a Nikto who could speak Basic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496014" id2="17" version="1065353216">You speak Basic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chip plus brain plus Basic language upgrade program equals sweet success. Might try Trandoshan, Shyriiwook someday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hear that? Bzzzzz. Sweet electrical music. Could listen to that all day. You need something?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496018" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Zash's apprentice. She said you would know how to find some tech for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496018" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard you could help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zash. Zash. Let me just pull it up in the old memory banks. Oh, yeah! Funny lady. Tell me what you're looking for....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496021" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm very sick, and I heard there was some ancient healing technology to be found on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496021" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm looking for Rakata tech.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got some old kolto injectors and a couple creepy-looking med droids, but nothing ancient. You got details?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496024" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need you to examine some writings for me and build me the thing they describe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take a look at this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496025" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can think it, we can build it. Let me have a look.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496027" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's some crazy-looking diagram. But I'm pretty sure we can help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Course when we helped Zash, she did something for us in return, yeah?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Course last time we helped one of you, she did something for us, yeah?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Freakish monstrosities. They won't talk to us like that. We are Sith!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496034" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you need me to do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496034" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not your call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496035" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need to take nonsense from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496035" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right. [Shock Nikto.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get out of my head!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut up!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Easy now. Nobody's in your head. We'll help you, all right? Just calm down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496039" id2="17" version="1065353216">A little trouble for a little tech?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496040" id2="17" version="1065353216">That depends on what you want me to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496040" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you need?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496041" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it's trouble you want, I have plenty to spare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trouble, eh. [Shock him.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aggghhh! All right, all right! Just don't fry my chip, okay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aggghhh! All right, all right. Cost my life stealings to get a Basic-language chip in my brain. I don't need it fried.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496046" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do what I must to buy your assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496047" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a state-of-the-art slicing hub in the making. Belsavis security protocols, HoloNet, we want it all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496049" id2="17" version="1065353216">The vault blows up our signal, makes it huge. Unbelievable. But we need a relay to carry it offworld. Go galactic or go home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496051" id2="17" version="1065353216">All we need is you to clear out a spot for our relay and protect it while we hook in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496052" id2="17" version="1065353216">You clear us out a spot for our relay and protect it while we hook in, we'll help you with your mystery machine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496053" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496054" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496055" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have better things to do. Give me what I want now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496055" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget it. [Shock him.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496056" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do this for us, the Circle will be everywhere. You won't regret it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496060" id2="17" version="1065353216">You just head to the Republic labs and zap the scientists like you zapped me. One of them'll point you the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496064" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been a long time since I've had a chance to torment a scientist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496064" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will be fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496065" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever expands your mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496067" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if I don't want to &quot;zap&quot; them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="496067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there another way?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="496068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now you find a conscience? Sorry, Sith, got nothing else for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="763972" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I must.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
