<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>42</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/class/sith_inquisitor/warden_gorshaa.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503263" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have done well, slave. The last Rakata thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503265" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have delivered upgrades for your droids to your ship, so that you do not assume that we are in your debt.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503267" id2="17" version="1065353216">We cannot help you unless you give your information to the mother machine.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503268" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Warden Gorshaa. We are the last of the true masters, the Rakata. We watch over this place, guarding it from intruding slaves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="503269" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear you have a device that could heal me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="503269" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you help me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="503270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps you haven't noticed, but your prisoners are escaping.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="503270" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done a terrible job.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503271" id2="17" version="1065353216">They are not what we guard. Nor do we care about the other slaves that meddle here. They have no imagination.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503273" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you found our machines and wondered &quot;why&quot; and that question led you to us. Nothing on this planet escapes our notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="503275" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care about your secrets. I want to be healed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="503275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why attack me?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503276" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah yes, you took power for yourself that you could not wield. Nothing on this planet escapes our notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503278" id2="17" version="1065353216">We cannot heal you, but we can rebuild you. First, though, you will do something for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="503279" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean, rebuild me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="503279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rebuild?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503280" id2="17" version="1065353216">As the Rakata lost our connection to the Force, we have performed many experiments on many species, including your own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="503282" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing's free, is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="503282" id2="17" version="1065353216">That figures.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503283" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is only fitting. Even as we lost our connection to the Force, the machines we made put your species' greatest monuments to shame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="503285" id2="17" version="1065353216">What can a slave like me do for such perfect beings?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="503285" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought I was below you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503286" id2="17" version="1065353216">Long ago, we Rakata began to lose our connection to the Force. We formed this place as a place of research.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503288" id2="17" version="1065353216">We planned to study the lesser species and see which could be modified for Force sensitivity. We would use that knowledge to save ourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503290" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is the reason we built the machine. It can rebuild you, but you must allow it to take an imprint of your pattern, so we may continue our research.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="503291" id2="17" version="1065353216">What horrible fate awaits me if I say &quot;no&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="503291" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if I refuse?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Collection of your pattern is part of the process. The machine cannot rebuild you without it. It is impossible to refuse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="503294" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="503295" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gladly.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503296" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is simple. Use this datakey to access the heart of the prison and access the machine.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503298" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is programmed to follow the instructions on the key. It will take your pattern and then rebuild you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503300" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have performed most acceptably. You might have turned away, you might have been killed. But here you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503302" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps there is hope for the slave races after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="503303" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find I'm far from powerless. Besides, condescension is unbecoming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="503303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch who you call a slave.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503304" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will not profit by denying your station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="503306" id2="17" version="1065353216">I take it you're the one who gave the cryptic warning in the lab.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="503306" id2="17" version="1065353216">You again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="503307" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you just try to kill me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="503307" id2="17" version="1065353216">What were those droids?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="503308" id2="17" version="1065353216">We had to be sure you were worthy. The other one held such promise, but he did not make it.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
