<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>56</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/world/imperial/zero_protocol/commander_stron.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649061" id2="17" version="1065353216">The network is secure, thanks to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649062" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe this. We follow the slime right to the slug himself and... and....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me. Eliminating Zero is no small feat, but I still don't understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649066" id2="17" version="1065353216">He was creative, he was personal, even vindictive. How could a droid replicate that behavior?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe malicious attacks aren't as creative as you think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649067" id2="17" version="1065353216">You gave him too much credit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649068" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose we could learn from his model.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649070" id2="17" version="1065353216">It also alerted us to the threat of this free droid enclave. We'll figure out who or what had a hand in his creation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649072" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where there's a droid, there's a creator. Or at least a missing restraining bolt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649072" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ask his maker.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649073" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a point. He was in the free droid enclave. They haven't proven to be a strategic threat before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649075" id2="17" version="1065353216">But this changes everything. We will raid them to ensure they harbor no more surprises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent work. If I can't have my day in the sun, I can at least appreciate yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649078" id2="17" version="1065353216">Credits are my concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649079" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I suppose you don't care to listen to the denials of an old man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649081" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've worried about my position being taken by a droid before, but never my enemy's.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649083" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will pay attention to the free droid enclave from now on. If this threat could come out of there, our next great gain might as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649085" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once we can trace him through the hubs, he'll have nowhere to hide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649088" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Stron here. Nice work with that slicer in the data center. I don't suppose you'd be up for more of that sort of thing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649090" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Stron here. I heard about some of your work for General Kolvin. Impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649092" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Stron here. I've heard from Agent Felth that it's good to have you on our side in tough times.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649094" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Stron here. The Shadow Syndicate's been passing word that you're willing to take on the tough fights.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649096" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Stron. I'm glad you're here. I've heard I can't meet any better for help in a tough situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649098" id2="17" version="1065353216">A slicer's compromising our computers. Only name we've got is &quot;Zero.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649100" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know that's normally below your notice, but this is Central Hub Prime. All our communications flow through here, including top secret military data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Normally, I wouldn't bother a Sith with this, my lord, but this is Central Hub Prime. All our communications, military data, it all goes through here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649104" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Central Hub Prime. All our communications go through here, including top secret military data. Imperial Intelligence, they want him stopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649106" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Central Hub Prime. All our communications go through here, including top secret military data. We'll pay well to protect it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649108" id2="17" version="1065353216">This slicer, this &quot;Zero,&quot; is dangerous. We sent a termination squad after him--none returned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649109" id2="17" version="1065353216">So we don't catch him, then what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649109" id2="17" version="1065353216">We care about one slicer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649110" id2="17" version="1065353216">Last time Zero surfaced, he got into spaceport traffic control. Two thousand casualties were traced to a code change he personally signed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649112" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649113" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649114" id2="17" version="1065353216">If a slicer killed your men, you need better men.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649114" id2="17" version="1065353216">So they failed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649115" id2="17" version="1065353216">The bodies all bore the marks of military-grade blasters. He's as dangerous on the ground as in the networks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649117" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only chance we have to track him is by implanting tracer spikes into some of the Hutts' most secure hubs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649119" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't support this officially, so there can be no witnesses, guards or otherwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649120" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire will not allow some rebellious child to humiliate us again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649120" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will find this slicer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649123" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the price is right, I'll get your slicer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649123" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll hunt him down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649124" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll pay scale plus fifty out of my own pocket.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649126" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rest assured, no one will trace our presence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649126" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649127" id2="17" version="1065353216">If your reputation holds, I have little to worry about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649129" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me the mission details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649130" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need you to physically plant tracer spikes in the computers through which Zero is sending his signal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649132" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll have a technician waiting on the ground to trace Zero through your spikes and give you his locale.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649134" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then, when you're finally face-to-face... make him beg.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649136" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you want someone more technical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649136" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't. [Refuse quest.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649137" id2="17" version="1065353216">We had several; unfortunately, they were on board a starship when Zero sliced the traffic control tower.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our networks are secure. None shall say otherwise.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
