<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>66</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/world/republic/the_perfect_carrier/doctor_brenna_fash.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your courage saved a lot of people. We all owe you thanks, especially the Gen'Dai.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706396" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish there had been another way, but at least the disease is under control. Thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706397" id2="17" version="1065353216">We aren't finding any more infected Gen'Dai on the scanners. With the carriers dead, the disease will die out pretty quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Fash is still upset that we had to sacrifice them, but she'll realize it had to be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706400" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish there had been another way, but we had to act quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our safety is worth the price.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706401" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll get no argument from me. As for Doctor Fash, well, she'll come around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706403" id2="17" version="1065353216">There wasn't a way around it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706404" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's never comfortable, having to choose who lives and dies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Saying thank you seems... crude. All the same, you deserve thanks. You've saved us from an agonizing death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706407" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your indecision disgusts me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706408" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never want to deal with anything like this again. And I certainly wouldn't trouble you with it. Good day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706410" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are no more infected Gen'Dai on the scanners. You've done it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706412" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew it could be done without sacrificing them. They're as much the victims as we are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706414" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just glad you stopped the disease. You've saved a lot of civilians today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706415" id2="17" version="1065353216">She came up with the vaccine. All I did was deliver it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Fash did the hard part.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706416" id2="17" version="1065353216">You had the more dangerous job by far, but thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706418" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad they could be saved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706419" id2="17" version="1065353216">You saved a lot of unnecessary bloodshed. I can't thank you enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706421" id2="17" version="1065353216">We all owe you our gratitude, especially the Gen'Dai. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pulling that off was brilliant, even for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706422" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're lucky I showed up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your modesty suits you. At least you kept us from having to sacrifice all those Gen'Dai.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706425" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't be finished yet. I'm certain there are plenty more Gen'Dai for you to butcher.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706427" id2="17" version="1065353216">She meant to say there are still more infected Gen'Dai out there. They all need to be removed before we're safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706429" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm still getting reports of infected Gen'Dai out there. Sorry, but you need to keep looking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706430" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm reasonably certain that the antidote will work at this new concentration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706432" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, doc, I won't risk our safety on &quot;reasonably certain.&quot; They've got to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706434" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't have the Gen'Dai butchered wholesale! At least let me try the antidote first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706436" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless the Force protects you from contamination and disease, I wouldn't get any closer to that body.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706437" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd step back if I were you, Major. That body's a class-two contamination hazard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless you've got a decontamination suit under that outfit, I'd steer clear of that body.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706439" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on Belsavis to assist. What seems to be the problem?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps I can help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706440" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now there's a loaded question... well, at the moment, we have a virus that's tearing through the sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706442" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it's that deadly, why is it just sitting out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706442" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't scare that easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706443" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the doctor's fault. She's trying to study this virus that's tearing up the sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706445" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not interested in catching whatever he had.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706445" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to tell me twice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706446" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good choice. This virus is tearing the whole sector apart. It's not pretty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706448" id2="17" version="1065353216">The disease is exceptional--it spent a millennia locked away, and when the Empire blew open its vault, it came out even deadlier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706450" id2="17" version="1065353216">It attacks the central nervous system. Seizures and agonizing death follow in hours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless you happen to be a Gen'Dai. Make sure you mention that, doc.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like the virus needed to be locked up forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Letting it out was a bad idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706454" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think the Empire knew what they were letting out, but we almost had it contained 'til the Gen'Dai got infected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are the Gen'Dai immune to the disease?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706456" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the Gen'Dai?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706457" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're immune to everything--disease, blasters, planetary bombardment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706459" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's more bad news. Great.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706460" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no good news when the Gen'Dai are involved. Imagine a giant killing machine, then make it immortal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706462" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were sent to Belsavis because their species is violent and almost impossible to kill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even the disease won't kill them, it just incubates in their tissues. They become carriers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706466" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need help to wipe out the infected Gen'Dai. If they aren't killed, they'll eventually infect the entire planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or we could cure them. Jansen doesn't agree, so that makes you these creatures' best hope--I can give you the antidote.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706469" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right, we should try to cure them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706469" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm here to save lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here you go. Just use it on the infected ones.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful. They're sluggish now, but once you cure them, they'll be back to their warlike selves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706474" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, doctor, but he's right. Killing them protects all of us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killing the Gen'Dai is safest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706475" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish there was another way. I'd hoped you would agree with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706477" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gen'Dai tend to cluster around the old vaults. You'll be able to find them there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, no time to talk. We're getting some strange reports from the field.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
