<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_10/scene_04_kaliyo_alianna.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159092" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay. We're set, but I've got to stick around a minute. Supposed to meet a contact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159093" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of contact?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159094" id2="17" version="1065353216">A local. Won't take long, but get too close and you'll scare her off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159098" id2="17" version="1065353216">Firebrand? Everything's ready. I've got the Overwatch data, and the rest... the rest is done, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159100" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good girl. Who says you can't get your hands dirty?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen, the others... they're out. They won't say anything, but they're getting their scars fixed. It's not fun anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, well, they're morons. We've got each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159106" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159108" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't forget... you cause me problems, those scars can get deeper!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159110" id2="17" version="1065353216">Idiots and cowards. Remember that girl in Kaas City whose dad you shot? She had spine compared to these people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159111" id2="17" version="1065353216">Idiots and cowards, every one of them. I've met Alderaanian nobles less pampered; more backbone, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159112" id2="17" version="1065353216">Care to explain what that exchange was about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159112" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who was that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159113" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd be surprised. I've seen Zakuulans fight as well as anyone. Knights, soldiers, allies and enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159113" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zakuulans aren't all cowards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe. But I'm not talking about Knights and soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159116" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people of Zakuul have been sheltered from just about everything. Even their soldiers are naive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159116" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're in agreement there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Haven't met many of the soldiers, but I believe it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159119" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've picked up a few fans over the years. That girl? Daughter of the Overwatch administrator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159120" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is she helping you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Same reason they all did. They're sheltered kids and rebellion is taboo. They don't really want Zakuul overthrown.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159123" id2="17" version="1065353216">But almost getting blown up? Getting a few scars before the droids make them pretty again? Oh, that's a mark of pride.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159124" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Skytroopers will find us soon. How many more junctions do you need to rig?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159124" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's keep moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159125" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just one. Real soon, we get to watch the show.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159126" id2="17" version="1065353216">That woman said the others were out. That they're getting their scars healed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159126" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yet they've abandoned you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159127" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently some Outlander turned up and soured my pals on rebellion. Hits too close to home now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159129" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you came to Zakuul without a support network and built one from your enemies? A Cipher agent couldn't do better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159129" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm impressed you found them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159130" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was always good at using people. You just showed me a few tricks to get the most out of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159131" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least our time together wasn't a waste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159132" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never said that. Come on--one more power conduit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159133" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're no more likely to bring down Zakuul than they are, and your defiance is just as petty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159133" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're all aimless rebels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159134" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't judge me. I've got reasons for what I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159136" id2="17" version="1065353216">One more power conduit. Then the show starts.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
