<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>32</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_10/scene_03_kaliyo.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159026" id2="17" version="1065353216">This &quot;Tayvor Slen&quot;--is he another Knight of Zakuul?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who's the administrator?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nah. Piece of work, but no powers. I plan to shoot him in the head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159079" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm in. I could use a blueprint of the Spire, and we always made a good team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159079" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to work together again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159080" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's just until the job is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159085" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just so we're clear: I think you're lying about something, even if I'm not sure what.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159085" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't trust you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Feeling's mutual.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159916" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep an eye out for Skytroopers. I've got to wire a jury-rigged ion grenade into the power junction. I mess up, we all fry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159918" id2="17" version="1065353216">That blackout you caused shows the whole system's vulnerable. You know about the Overwatch?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some sort of command center?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Smart girl.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Smart boy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Overwatch is where they run half the droids in the Spire. Skytroopers, building crews, med units, you name it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159931" id2="17" version="1065353216">We blow a couple junctions at once, Overwatch security goes down. Force fields, scanners... no power. We walk right in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159932" id2="17" version="1065353216">This whole city runs on machines. If we interfere with the Overwatch controls, the Spire will practically shut down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159933" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah. These people... the droids do everything for them. Most of the locals sit around drooling while their tech feeds and protects them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159935" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're going to show them real life for a day or two. No droids. Just until it's fixed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159936" id2="17" version="1065353216">The plan might work, but what's the goal? If the damage gets repaired, all we're doing is causing chaos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159936" id2="17" version="1065353216">For what purpose?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159937" id2="17" version="1065353216">We might be able to do more. What about reprogramming the droids from Overwatch command?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could we control the droids?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159938" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wasn't planning on spending long in there, and tech isn't my thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159940" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're playing into Arcann's hands. An attack like that will only unite Zakuul further.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your plan will backfire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159941" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, you came to me. You don't like my methods, I don't really care--but I'll throw in a bonus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159943" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tayvor Slen, the Overwatch administrator? The data he needs to run those droids is pretty much a blueprint for the city.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159945" id2="17" version="1065353216">You ever plan an attack here, you'll need that data--defenses, vulnerabilities, everything. So we get inside, we both get something good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159946" id2="17" version="1065353216">A blueprint of the Spire would be worth the effort. Let's keep moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159946" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159947" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on... we better get to the next junction before the Skytroopers show.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
