<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>47</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_10/scene_06_kaliyo_hologram.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159236" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is it. My fans bought the furniture. Let me show you something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159240" id2="17" version="1065353216">...You can see the Vankaysar Bridge burning from here. No one's saying what happened, but I haven't seen anything like it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159242" id2="17" version="1065353216">My father will kill me if he knows I'm recording this. Firebrand struck again. The spaceport this time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159244" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was so afraid, but I've never felt a rush like that before. Thank Valkorion the droids got me to safety....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gray market holos. They used to trade them, like it was a game. Now watch this:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159249" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Outlander's back. They say she's responsible for the meltdown. I still haven't heard from my brother....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159251" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Outlander's back. They say he's responsible for the meltdown. I still haven't heard from my brother....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159253" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Outlander's back. We were lucky she only caused a blackout, but what about next time?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159255" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Outlander's back. We were lucky he only caused a blackout, but what about next time?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159257" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zakuul should be safe. It's always been safe. What happens now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159259" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tone's a little different on that one, huh? Suddenly blowing up a building matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159260" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're awed by Firebrand, but they fear the Outlander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159261" id2="17" version="1065353216">You come back to life after everything I--after five years. Not only that, you do it by blowing up a building and humiliating me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159262" id2="17" version="1065353216">The woman I remember could never be humiliated. But if she saw a chance to up her game, she'd do it in a second.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Humiliated? You?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159263" id2="17" version="1065353216">The woman you remember isn't the woman in this room.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159265" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't mean to hurt you. Not by dying and not by coming back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159265" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know I'm sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159266" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't say hurt. I said humiliated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159267" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then what do you want from me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing you can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159272" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were my friend. You know me. Do you really think I'd humiliate you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159272" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know I'm sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159273" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not assigning blame. Things are what they are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Power junctions are set. Overwatch force fields cycle in an hour. Let's talk tactics until then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159278" id2="17" version="1065353216">I got lazy, figured there was no way through to these people. Set my sights low with bridges and spaceports.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159280" id2="17" version="1065353216">But if you scared them, I can too. Guess I owe you for the wake-up call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159281" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happens next?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159283" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that why you brought me to your apartment? Searching for a way to repay me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159283" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] You owe me, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159284" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, I can figure something out. Just not this second.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159286" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got an hour until the power cycles. That's when we detonate the junctions and hit the Overwatch. Let's kill some time and talk plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159287" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm here because you're a useful tool, not because we're equals fighting Zakuul together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1159287" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not on my level.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever. We'll get this job done, then you can decide if you still want an &quot;alliance.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159289" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that the power junctions are rigged, can we strike at the Overwatch?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pretty much. Force fields cycle in an hour, so we'll trigger the blackout then. Meantime, I've got maps and everything. Let's talk tactics....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159294" id2="17" version="1065353216">...Everything goes down in the droid control center. You grab your data, I blow the machinery. And hopefully shoot the administrator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159295" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're sure the data's complete? The full city schematic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159296" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every droid in the city runs on those specs. You ever go to war with the Spire, that's your winning card.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159298" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time. Step one: Blow the junctions!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159300" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like old times. Get ready to shoot droids, a few Knights... whatever Zakuul has to show.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159301" id2="17" version="1065353216">That feels good. Come on--expect droids, maybe a few Knights... a grand old time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Life is as empty without terror as without love.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159305" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would permit this creature's existence from my throne. She cannot truly threaten perfection, but only enhance it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1159899" id2="17" version="1065353216">But though chaos can be beautiful... it cannot last.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
