<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>177</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/class/bounty_hunter/baron_zacar.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494806" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got him now. I know it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494807" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I was saying... with House Rist unable to protect him, I have no doubt that Duke Corwin is seeking asylum with the Organas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494808" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Rists didn't know where he went. How do you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494808" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can you be sure?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makes sense, considering how buddy buddy they've been.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems likely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494810" id2="17" version="1065353216">The facts support that assumption as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thul scouts reported spotting a civilian shuttle headed into Organa territory shortly after you breached House Rist's compound.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494814" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've already crushed the best this planet has to offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494814" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't be able to stop me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494815" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Organas have offworld support as well, but let's not speculate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494817" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've more than demonstrated your talent for frontal assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494819" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nowhere left for my cousin to run. Go kick down House Organa's doors and give them hell. Expect a bonus for any additional Organa casualties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494821" id2="17" version="1065353216">I apologize for recalling you here, but I couldn't risk my cousin catching wind of this discussion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494823" id2="17" version="1065353216">If his retreat from House Rist is any indication, the Durasteel Duke is already running scared and I'd like him to stay right where he is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494825" id2="17" version="1065353216">It may not be our goal, but crippling House Rist is worth noting. Consider this payment for supporting the Thul war effort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494826" id2="17" version="1065353216">You didn't call me back just to pay me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494826" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to know why I'm here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your whole family is on the Rist's hit list.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rist isn't out of the picture.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. Thank you for the warning, but I don't think Rist is in any position to strike after your actions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Man after my own heart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494831" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better than nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494834" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is the meaning of this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494836" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just caught this little rake of yours in a dalliance with my wife!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494838" id2="17" version="1065353216">More like you caught your wife in a dalliance with me, cuckold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless you want half of House Thul questioning why we continue to keep you riffraff here, you'll grant me that winter haven of yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494842" id2="17" version="1065353216">My grandfather's estate? Are you mad? That's half my family's lands! Advocate, kill this petty extortionist and I'll double what I just gave you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494843" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're your credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Double? Deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494844" id2="17" version="1065353216">You picked a bad time to show up, buddy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494844" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure, I'll take a freebie.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494845" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd pay this thug to murder me? It's idiotic to think you'd actually get away with that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494847" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there is anything &quot;this thug&quot; has taught me, it's to handle threats directly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494849" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is a war going on, or hadn't you noticed? You've just become another unfortunate casualty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494851" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're insa--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494853" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was... liberating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Worth every last credit. Thank you, advocate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494857" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not some common thug to be sent at everyone who annoys you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494857" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jobs take planning, contracts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494858" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't even command authority over a hired goon? You're pathetic, Zacar! I'll expect that deed promptly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494860" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought if there was anyone on this damnable planet I could finally rely on, it was you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494862" id2="17" version="1065353216">Raffid, you're confined to your chambers--indefinitely. Hope I do not keep you there the rest of your natural life. Now get out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494864" id2="17" version="1065353216">My life or yours, Father?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Advocate, are you there? Damn this blasted thing! Can you hear me? I have news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494868" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't dare discuss the details on an insecure channel. Please return to House Girard as soon as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494873" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be exceptionally careful. House Rist is no place for recklessness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494874" id2="17" version="1065353216">My cousin is safe within the sanctuary of House Rist. If he's under their protection, it's little wonder why the Durasteel Duke always survives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494876" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Rists are a family of assassins who ascended into nobility through centuries of murder and sabotage. Duke Corwin is beyond our reach.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494877" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm gonna pay House Rist a visit, be back once the duke's a corpse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me, I have a job to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494878" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're determined, I'll give you that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does it look like I'm getting cold feet to you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quitting isn't an option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494881" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's your life, hunter, I've apprised you of the risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anybody who can't kill someone face-to-face ain't a concern of mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assassins are chumps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494884" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last bounty hunter I hired probably thought the same thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494886" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll need to find Duke Corwin's haven inside House Rist and stop whatever negotiations my cousin has underway, permanently.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494888" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm likely sending you to your death, but if you can manage to succeed, I will have a suitable payment waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you absolutely insane? House Alde just announced that mercenaries have pillaged the Royal Museum!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494894" id2="17" version="1065353216">They are calling for whoever is responsible for the attack to be brought up on war crimes. War crimes! I demand an explanation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494895" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do what has to be done to finish a job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494895" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was in a hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494896" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd better hope that the Organas lose this war, or we'll both be facing firing squads.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494898" id2="17" version="1065353216">The duke shouldn't have put the relics in danger in the first place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, we aren't to blame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494899" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt anyone will see matters that pragmatically.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep talking and I'll be penning your will in blood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494901" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't make demands of me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494902" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... I believe I can forgive this error, once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494904" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see if this was worth the backlash. Hmm, this is in Organa's &quot;house tongue.&quot; I'll need a moment to parse the details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your attack on House Alde certainly didn't go unnoticed, but you managed not to cause any unnecessary destruction. That merits a bonus, I think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Appreciated, Baron.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494907" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never say no to credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494908" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be certain to see more if you continue to perform with distinction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to be appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellence should never go unnoticed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494913" id2="17" version="1065353216">I ain't your pet, I don't need a treat for not going on the rug.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't patronize me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494914" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... I meant no offense. Keep it or not, your choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494916" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see what you've discovered. Hmm, this is in Organa's &quot;house tongue.&quot; Give me a moment to parse the details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494918" id2="17" version="1065353216">These houses... Thul vassals, Ulgo vassals, House Organa. Duke Corwin isn't just allying with the Organas, he's organizing an entire coalition against House Thul!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494919" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does that thing say where the duke is or not?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494919" id2="17" version="1065353216">Skip it, I want a location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494920" id2="17" version="1065353216">It does, but that information is of no further use to us now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494922" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like he's prepping you guys for a good beat down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494922" id2="17" version="1065353216">That can't be good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indelicate, but accurate, and there is nothing we can do about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494925" id2="17" version="1065353216">He won't be organizing squat when I'm done with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not for long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494926" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll never have the chance to make good on that threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember, damaging the Royal Museum could have disastrous consequences.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494929" id2="17" version="1065353216">According to Malfus's information, Duke Corwin is in negotiations with our enemy, House Organa. They're placing messages in phony relics at House Alde's Royal Museum for later retrieval.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Duke Corwin's placed an imposter relic in the museum recently; you'll have to forcibly enter House Alde and find it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494932" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get my gear together and head back out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494932" id2="17" version="1065353216">On my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494933" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Alde has the support of Organa and the Republic. Do not underestimate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't I just buy a ticket and take the tour?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why forcibly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494936" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Alde is a vassal house of Organa. They are at war with us as much as anyone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494938" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was thinking my rap sheet's a little light on breaking and entering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494938" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that's more my style.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494939" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is not playtime. You're to identify the fraudulent relic and bring me the message.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494941" id2="17" version="1065353216">And use extreme caution. The museum holds priceless cultural treasures. Nobody wants to be responsible for destroying that heritage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494943" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Priceless&quot; is something Alderaanians only use to describe things they still own. Catch my drift?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494944" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like we're getting to sightsee after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494945" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll look forward to hearing of your success.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494947" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is clear that you have plans in motion, nephew--ah, your newest lackey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me, did my nephew mention that he already hired a bounty hunter... and got him promptly killed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Past business dealings aren't my interest. Getting paid for this one is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not interested. Working.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494951" id2="17" version="1065353216">I recall Veeboo saying something similar... before you killed him. It's never a bad idea to show interest in your competition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494953" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's he talking about, Zacar?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494953" id2="17" version="1065353216">That true?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494954" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're already aware of Duke Corwin's reputation for survival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just saves me the trouble of taking him off the payroll.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494956" id2="17" version="1065353216">More credits for me, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think that was the you-know-who, here for the you-know-what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494959" id2="17" version="1065353216">That could have been our competition. Might've caught a lucky break.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494961" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you would please excuse yourself, uncle, I have business with my advocate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494963" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see how your brat Raffid learned to disgrace us. Advocate... pah.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494965" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just got a very impolite communication from Lord Malfus saying that you assaulted him. Is that true?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494966" id2="17" version="1065353216">I convinced him it'd be a bad idea to hold out on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494967" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know, I'm beginning to appreciate your particular brand of diplomacy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494969" id2="17" version="1065353216">I may have negotiated with his face a little.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494970" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've always thought that pompous nitwit could use a good straightening out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494972" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should have fed him my blaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494972" id2="17" version="1065353216">He got off lucky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494973" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get carried away. We were fortunate that your roughhousing didn't cost us the prize.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494975" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're back without incident. I'm surprised Lord Malfus didn't raise a stir. Insufferable man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494976" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is everything he gave me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's the data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494977" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't let chumps get me riled.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494977" id2="17" version="1065353216">He tried. I wasn't having it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494978" id2="17" version="1065353216">You performed admirably.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494980" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't ask me to do anything like that again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494980" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not doing anymore deals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come now, try not to act as if my credits are bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't keep Malfus waiting; this may be difficult enough as it is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494987" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a bounty hunter. I'm after the Durasteel Duke. Can you help or not?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right to the point, yes? I'm afraid the duke and his sister left House Girard some time ago under... unpleasant circumstances.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494990" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Girard now has a vested interest in finding the duke and having him meet an unpleasant end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494992" id2="17" version="1065353216">A minor noble claims to have a lead on the duke. However, he insists on meeting in person--which I'm not willing to do. Instead, I will employ you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Formalities aren't in my job description.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494993" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not a diplomat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494994" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're expecting a double-cross?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494994" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want a bodyguard, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494995" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's possible. Either way, I'm certainly not going out in that war zone, and none of my relatives can be trusted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me where to find this twerp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="494997" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll teach him some respect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494998" id2="17" version="1065353216">This transaction must be handled delicately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495000" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't expect you to navigate the intricacies of our society, but I can give you the authority to negotiate on my behalf.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495002" id2="17" version="1065353216">From this point on, you will act as House Girard's advocate. A role of honor. Come, I will walk you through the appointment ceremony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495003" id2="17" version="1065353216">After you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just set up this deal. The duke's not getting any deader.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's not and say we did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495005" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a point. Let us move with haste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just make it quick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495008" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is not to be taken lightly, bounty hunter. I am bestowing immense legal authority, even if it is temporary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please kneel. I, Baron Zacar Girard, do hereby bequeath my voice and my seal to this proxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now repeat after me: I humbly accept this honor and swear to carry my authority in a manner befitting the lord I serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495013" id2="17" version="1065353216">I humbly accept this honor and swear to carry my authority in a manner befitting the lord I serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495014" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may rise. Well done, there may be hope for you yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh-huh. I accept... you know the rest. So, we done?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, honor and all that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495017" id2="17" version="1065353216">What--no. You must... nevermind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495019" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have anything else to say or can I get back to shooting people?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quit wasting my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Already, I question putting my faith in you--but my options are limited.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495022" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is customary for information to be double-encrypted in these transactions, so Lord Malfus must enter his half of the key before you take the data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495024" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll let Malfus know you'll arrive at his encampment soon. Be on your best behavior.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
