<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>28</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/class/bounty_hunter/gault_rennow.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540326" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm so proud, I think you actually brought a tear to my eye.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quite the looker, that one... I hate it when they know it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540328" id2="17" version="1065353216">When do I get my turn?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540329" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like that kid. Reminds me of me, only uglier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540330" id2="17" version="1065353216">The old man's a bit stingy, but it was easy enough money, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540331" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I'd known the Organas could put up such a fight, I'd have said take the deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540332" id2="17" version="1065353216">I love negotiating with the upper hand. Let's get him back before he starts to smell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540333" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never really had any stomach for the Organas. Too straight and narrow for my taste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent timing, that one. Let's get going; it'll be a long walk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Next time you're going to tell off someone who's set an obvious trap, take Mako.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540336" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't feel my face. Tell me you brought a medpac.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540337" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess you made a good impression. The Rists aren't the sort for negotiating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, he's not here. How about we just turn around?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540339" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard of Rist, absolutely ruthless and unbelievably deadly. I'd stay behind you, but that's the direction they'll be coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have a nice walk? I had a lovely tour of my own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540341" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think she's warming up to you, keep at it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540342" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hadn't realized the Alderaanians started keeping their livestock indoors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540343" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess that confirms that you aren't in this business for the money.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540344" id2="17" version="1065353216">Old guy can't remember everything that's in here... oh, nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Royal Museum... that sounds promising.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540346" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's enough playing bagman for the day, yes?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Malfus is a popular fellow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540348" id2="17" version="1065353216">It really doesn't pay to be hired help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540349" id2="17" version="1065353216">He calls these bribes? I wouldn't get out of bed for half of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540350" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's the plan: You write the will, I'll forge the signature.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540351" id2="17" version="1065353216">That man's got ambitions. Could be worth talking to him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540352" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is going to be messy. Just smile and bite your tongue. A lot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540353" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never been to House Thul. I think they were still in exile the times I've been here.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
