<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>31</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/class/bounty_hunter/mako.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540247" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I've had my fill of Alderaan for awhile. We done here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, wipe that smirk off your face. Goof.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540249" id2="17" version="1065353216">She could use an attitude adjustment, but Aitalla wasn't that bad in the end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540250" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know you're going to have to fill me in on the juicy details, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540251" id2="17" version="1065353216">How long you think before Raffid bankrupts them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540252" id2="17" version="1065353216">Money's nice and all, but was putting Heitor in charge really a good idea?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540253" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe I lived through that... give me a breather, would you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540254" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better not tell the Huntmaster he was already dead... they might make us do another one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540255" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is starting to look a lot like Tatooine. I really hope the duke stays put this time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540256" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you think the baron wanted to tell you? Seemed pretty urgent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540257" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sneaky rats! Served them right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugh, are you nauseous? My head is spin--ulp. Oh boy... get me to a med center.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540259" id2="17" version="1065353216">It doesn't feel right... double-crossing Zacar. I hope that was just an act.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540260" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is so a trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540261" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do we always have to get sent to places like the &quot;House of Assassins&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540262" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know she actually sent a nursemaid? It was a nice touch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, aren't you Mister Chivalrous all of a sudden.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you see the size of that guy? What a porker.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540265" id2="17" version="1065353216">I kinda feel bad... making that old man cry. Oh well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gotta give him credit, that old timer was really devoted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540267" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know about you, but I'm really looking forward to seeing this Royal Museum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540268" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's all of them. Finally. Let's go get that info from Malfus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540269" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the feeling we aren't the only ones who think Malfus is a jerk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540270" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I actually heard the moment you broke his nose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Smooth, how much did you just pay that guy anyway?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540272" id2="17" version="1065353216">I feel bad for those guys... throwing their lives away to protect this colossal jerk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540273" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Tokens of respect.&quot; Hmph, guess &quot;bribes&quot; wasn't fancy enough for him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at you, all formal. Come on, &quot;advocate,&quot; Lord Malfus is waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, at least the baron's not rude. Stupid snobs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540276" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the feeling we're the main attraction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="540277" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on, maybe if we're lucky, the duke'll still be at House Girard.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
