<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>22</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/class/bounty_hunter/rist_messenger.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like Rist isn't happy about you going back on your contract.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those are Rist colors. I told you to take the deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rist sent someone to see you off. Hope she's packing a paycheck instead of a vibroblade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rist flunky dead ahead. Better watch your back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549045" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Girards are dead. You have my pay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, House Rist sends their thanks for your assistance in this matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549049" id2="17" version="1065353216">You looking for trouble?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549050" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to be alarmed. I'm only here to deliver a message.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549052" id2="17" version="1065353216">While House Rist regrets that you decided to renig on our agreement, it makes no real difference in the end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549054" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is unfortunate that our individual arrangements had us at odds earlier, but that's simply the nature of our business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549056" id2="17" version="1065353216">My master wishes to ensure that there is no ill will left between us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549057" id2="17" version="1065353216">Steer clear of me and we won't have any problems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549057" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just stay out of my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549058" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is acceptable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since you asked so nicely, I'll consider it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549060" id2="17" version="1065353216">No hard feelings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please do, hostilities between us would be an unnecessary expense for everyone involved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549063" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know, I can be real temperamental... I find credits help lighten my mood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good will's pricey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549064" id2="17" version="1065353216">My master anticipated this. Please accept a peace offering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549066" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Rist will no longer interfere with your affairs, news Tarro Blood will not take graciously I'm sure. He fronted a considerable sum to ensure his rivals were dealt with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549068" id2="17" version="1065353216">I imagine he'll threaten some reprisal, but I think we both know what Tarro Blood's word is worth.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
