<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>6</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/support/makeb/shared/bb_group_1_board_1.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1111965" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
ENCRYPTION CODING

Intelligence: a well-rounded military can't do without it. Our scientists have attempted to analyze the coded transmissions from mercenary forces situated at the Sanctuary on Makeb, but it's proven quite impossible. It appears the transmission towers themselves generate a wavelength component that compliments their encryption routines.

If you were to take detailed scans of these towers, we may be able to replicate this technology to provide a new level of data security.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111966" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
RARE METALS

The metallic alloy that served as the ultra-durable hide of Hutt Cartel's prototype droids on Makeb are particularly impressive. Our research concludes that this alloy consists of rare metals only found under the caverns of Makeb's volcanic mesa.

Procure samples of the alloy's components for our Metallurgical Division and we'll get to work on tough new battle droids and armaments.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111967" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
GROUNDQUAKE TECHNOLOGY

Few on Makeb foresaw the devastation that would result from the planet's increasing groundquakes. However, that didn't stop a team of scientists from designing and testing a system of subsurface vibration emitters that could be used to create discordant waves to combat the tremors. While promising, the project failed and was ultimately abandoned.

The vibration emitters work with data transmitters above ground to relay the data; they will help to approximate the emitters' locations. Dig up these faulty prevention devices for GSI's scientists, who believe they can fine-tune them into functional groundquake-making weapons.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111968" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
MAKRIN BARK SAMPLES

With its thick claws, tough hide and brilliant camouflage, the makrin creeper is Makeb's most fascinating creature--especially in the eyes of GSI's Biodesign Division. Born deep underground, the tree-like makrin young leave their proto-bark casings behind as they dig their way to the surface. 

We would like for you to obtain samples of this proto-bark, which will prove useful in creating damage-resistant gear for covert wilderness ops.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111969" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI ACTION ALERT:
PROTOTYPE SCHEMATICS

The mercenaries on Makeb hold in their possession full schematics for the remarkable prototype droids employed by the mad Hutt Toborro. Even without the unique energy source that powers the droids, GSI could use the schematics to build powerful new allies.

Once you've triangulated the data's location, you will undoubtedly have to make your way through some very tough customers--but we here at GSI have full faith!

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112014" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI OPPORTUNITY: VALUED PARTNER INITIATIVE

At Galactic Solutions Industries, we're always looking for ways to grow our partnerships. By accepting and completing multiple GSI assignments, you may qualify for GSI's Valued Partner Initiative. The VPI rewards your hard work with reputation above and beyond what you've earned for each individual commission.

Thank you for your consideration in becoming one of our most valued partners.

Addalar Hyland, founder and CEO
GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
