<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>26</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/02/ep_02/banter.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203251" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay alert. Deadly predators stalk these wilds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203252" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could say the same thing about your cities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203253" id2="17" version="1065353216">City predators won't eat our remains. Usually.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203256" id2="17" version="1065353216">The storms are fierce today. It will make a rescue attempt difficult.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203257" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never liked relying on others to save me anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203258" id2="17" version="1065353216">A sound philosophy, one the Sith Code embraces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203259" id2="17" version="1065353216">A small part of me is enjoying this. As Empress, I am rarely able to test my martial skills anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203260" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer to lead by example. Stay on the front lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203261" id2="17" version="1065353216">Among the Sith, being on the front lines just makes it easier for someone to stab you in the back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203264" id2="17" version="1065353216">I cannot decide which is stranger: that the GenoHaradan are real or that they're hunting us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203265" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should be flattered. The GenoHaradan only accept contracts worthy of their skills.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203266" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is one compliment I could do without.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203267" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fear the storm is getting worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. It'll cover our approach to the GenoHaradan camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203269" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see why the Alliance follows you. Where others see problems, you see opportunity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203275" id2="17" version="1065353216">This reminds me of my earliest trials as an apprentice: clearing vermin from tombs on Korriban.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203276" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you miss those days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203277" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remember those days, too. It's like our lives have come full circle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203278" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a simpler time, but I am not nostalgic for the past. I see a glorious future for us both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203279" id2="17" version="1065353216">No matter how much we change, some things remain the same. An important lesson, I suppose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203287" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ancient Sith Lords are revered on Dromund Kaas... but to move forward, we must abandon the old ways.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Easy to say, harder to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1203289" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand your skepticism, Outlander, but I will prove myself to you in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1213922" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand your skepticism, but I will prove myself to you in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1214643" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was too close. The lightning strikes can be deadly out here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1214645" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we recalibrate the electrical towers, they will draw in the power of the storm and keep us safe.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
