<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/world/imperial/head_that_wears_the_crown/captain_lieber.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724275" id2="17" version="1065353216">The crown is being hidden away. We will announce we have it at an expedient time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724276" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, I admire your principles, but it is clear Organa offers no help on what matters most to House Panteer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724278" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need not try to sell House Panteer on Thul alliances again, Fixer. But who are these?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724280" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do your lot want to do with the captain of the Queensguard?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724281" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need not try to sell me again on House Thul, Fixer. But who is this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724283" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you want with the Queensguard, stranger?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724284" id2="17" version="1065353216">I recovered this from the river. You know what it is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="724284" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have the Panteer crown.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724285" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's... that is, quite frankly, unbelievable. We will, of course, analyze it to determine if it is a fake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724287" id2="17" version="1065353216">I bring something from Sir Deris to Captain Lieber.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="724287" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir Deris sent me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724288" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know Deris, and I know that, were he able, he would deliver this prize himself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724290" id2="17" version="1065353216">First feast your eyes... then beg.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="724290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch and I will show you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724291" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is hardly the diplomatic way to--I see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724293" id2="17" version="1065353216">I came to sell you a planetary symbol of rulership. Slightly used.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="724293" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got something priceless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724294" id2="17" version="1065353216">You cannot be serious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724296" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that is genuine, it is worth the lives of every man here and then some.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724298" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, surely this will sway your vaunted neutrality? The Empire and House Thul giving you--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724300" id2="17" version="1065353216">The symbolism does not escape me, Fixer. But that crown has never changed hands without enormous cost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724302" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you seek in return for the crown? An alliance, or merely a deal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724303" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't put a price on peace. So, start handing me credits until I say &quot;stop.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="724303" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want personal compensation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724304" id2="17" version="1065353216">But what of House Thul? We require a Panteer alliance and your loyalty to our Empire--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724306" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have neither credits nor crown in your hands, Fixer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724308" id2="17" version="1065353216">What I see here are many mouths, many obligations. It is fair that this team will be... financed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724310" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had not imagined the Sith to be so... financially motivated, but credits are a lesser currency than blood and loyalty. I will pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724312" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have dealt with mercenary avarice before. We are not without means.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724314" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not think this independence will go unnoticed by the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ignore him. Yours are unlikely hands to have brought the crown home, but on such chances our future turns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724317" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the end, what I ask is that the crown go on a Thul head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="724317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Honor the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724318" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Thul's crimes are great, but Organa has proven itself no better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724320" id2="17" version="1065353216">To retrieve this must have taken courage. If Thul commands such virtue these days, perhaps we can look beyond old transgressions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724322" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are to be commended. Many in your position would have taken full financial advantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724324" id2="17" version="1065353216">How fortunate for the Empire it was you who held it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="724326" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are neither friend nor enemy. That is all you must know.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
