<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/war_world/quesh/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71512" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I ever mention I have a fear of being poisoned to death?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quesh is a critical planet in the war, my lord. I'm glad we're here to add our weight to the effort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71514" id2="17" version="1065353216">From the sky to the soil, the blight of war marks this world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71515" id2="17" version="1065353216">The embers of war are smoldering here. We will leave this world engulfed in flames!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71516" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire is thirsty to take Quesh. What say we quench that thirst.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our eyes water! Our lungs burn! Our heart quickens for war!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71518" id2="17" version="1065353216">The skies bleed, the air is sweet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71519" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I thought Hutta smelled bad. I guess it's true there's no good thing the Hutts can't spoil.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71520" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never seen such a disgusting place. Was it always like this, or have we made it that way with all our mining and industry?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Industry has a rather distinct odor, doesn't it? I might advise breathing through the mouth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Industrial landscape. Many ways to kill. Thick, dusty air makes good cover. Smell overpowering, have to rely on other senses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71523" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can see why no one's heard of this place. Think my eyes are burning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71524" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've never seen a sky so red before--not even under a red star. It must be the atmosphere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71525" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard rumors about Quesh, but very few details. I'd very much like to tour the venom mines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71526" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place makes Hutta look like a breath of fresh air... smells like I just put out a death stick with my nose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing like a breath of fresh toxins to really get you going in the morning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stinks worse than rakghouls. Gonna be nose deaf for a week.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Umm, Blizz feel kind of dizzy. Maybe sit down. Please?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ahh. Smells like burnin' spice and blood. Gonna like it here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quesh = hostile to organics // Droids = not much better off</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71536" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic wouldn't normally bother with a planet this disgusting, but we need Quesh's resources. We can't let the Empire have them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those inoculations we got better work. Ol' Doc isn't dying on a planet this ugly.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. Sky color reminds of blood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quesh is living proof of that age-old edict: Big money always smells bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71540" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remember this smell. From bioweapon attacks. Why are we here again?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71541" id2="17" version="1065353216">A whole world living on poison. There's a metaphor in there somewhere, I guess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you really sure it's safe to breathe here? I think my hair's starting to curl.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71543" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Quesh, huh? And I thought Nar Shaddaa was ugly....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hutts ruin everything they touch. Quesh is no different.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody mentioned Quesh was made of toxic mud. Should've worn my least-favorite boots.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71546" id2="17" version="1065353216">The air on Quesh smells like death. This is no place for the weak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71547" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're sure we're immune to the atmosphere on Quesh? My gills are itching.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71548" id2="17" version="1065353216">The faster we get our job done, the faster we can be off this rock. Let's move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even having taken precautions, we should attempt to limit our atmospheric exposure as much as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Compensating sensors for atmospheric interference... complete! Ready to proceed!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Swampy, nasty and filled with poisonous gas--no wonder Hutts live here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023353" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admiration: There are few things I love more than a poisoned atmosphere. Liquidations become so much simpler.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reassurance: Should your inoculation fail to protect you from the atmosphere, rest assured my deletions will continue in your name.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
