<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>100</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220087" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7's last chrono entry of Coruscant = destruction of Jedi Temple // Memory recall = unpleasant</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220088" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anybody who isn't inspired by that view needs to check his pulse.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220089" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is cold world. Both full and empty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220090" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coruscant sure is good at making a fella feel small. I guess it's kind of inspiring....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220091" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been to Coruscant twice, but it still amazes me. We're standing in the beating heart of the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220094" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senate tower = important + fancy // T7 = should have gotten oil bath before coming</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220095" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Kiwiiks always says we're fighting for the people inside the tower, not the tower itself. But I'm alright fighting for a tower that amazing, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220096" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why so large building, just for Republic's elders?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220097" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senators are mighty proud of their office building, aren't they? Can't say I blame them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220098" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senate tower. I've never actually been inside before--I'm looking forward to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220101" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senate tower = redecorated since T7's last visit // Results = impressive</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220102" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people in here decide the fate of the galaxy every day. Let's try to keep them alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220103" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is great honor you show your elders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220104" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know about you, but I'm feeling pretty underdressed. You suppose there's a place that rents formal wear around here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220105" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place is even more impressive than the holovids. Hard to believe we'll be reporting here from now on.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220108" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 sensors = detecting high levels of toxic chemicals being ingested by biologicals here</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220109" id2="17" version="1065353216">Smell that? Cheap Rodian ale and desperation. I'd recognize those aromas anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220110" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prey drown weakness here. Is no place for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220111" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow... even the cantinas here are big. Darmas says this is the best watering hole on the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220112" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guys on Ord Mantell used to tell stories about this place. They're supposed to have the best Corellian whiskey on Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220115" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic security forces = fighting armed hostiles // T7 + Jedi = lend assistance?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like Republic security could use a lightsaber or two. Good thing we're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why they cower here? Is points to be gained!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220118" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're having shootouts in the street? And here I thought Coruscant wouldn't be any fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220119" id2="17" version="1065353216">Barricades, armed standoffs... it feels like we're back on Ord Mantell, not the capital of the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220122" id2="17" version="1065353216">Justicars' sector = very clean compared to Black Sun sector</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220123" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate this place already. You just know this whole area's crawling with snipers.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220124" id2="17" version="1065353216">All confusion here for simple travel. Faster to walk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220125" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place makes me nervous, Captain. Feels like we're being watched by the Justicars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220126" id2="17" version="1065353216">So a bunch of ex-soldiers take over the streets and call themselves the &quot;Justicars.&quot; Sound like nutjobs to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220129" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 sensors = detecting unusual readings // Source = unknown + probably hostile</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220130" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our robes are going to smell like sewage and droid oil for weeks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220131" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fagh. Stinking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220132" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't believe we're actually going down into the Works. Skavak better be down here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220133" id2="17" version="1065353216">Machines and maintenance areas like this keep the whole planet going. Pretty incredible.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ruined Jedi Temple = T7's least favorite place</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220137" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith sure did a number on this place. Can't believe they got away with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuon spoke of this. Where Jedi fought bravely, stood against unstoppable foe. Is great honor to whole Jedi Order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Man... sad to see a place like this all busted up. Wonder how many Jedi died here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220140" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imps really messed this place up. The headquarters for the entire Jedi Order, and now it's just a pile of rubble.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220143" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 scanning starship registries // Many ships = reported as stolen</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220144" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess if things go bad here, we can always flee on one of the Black Sun's rides.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Black Sun deserve to be prey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220146" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Black Sun fools don't mess around. Look at all that hardware.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220147" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd better stay sharp down here--I doubt the Black Sun is very welcoming toward authority figures.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220150" id2="17" version="1065353216">Black Sun gangsters = everywhere // Jedi = proceed with caution</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220151" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's like a blasted free-for-all down here. Black Sun thugs everywhere. I'll watch your back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220152" id2="17" version="1065353216">Black Sun only hunt those weaker. Have no honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220153" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to roll up our sleeves and take out some trash. Let's show this Black Sun who's boss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220154" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess the Black Sun just care about holding the turf, not keeping it clean.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220157" id2="17" version="1065353216">Justicars' main base = close</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220158" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a nice skyline view. Explains why the Justicars settled here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220159" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is Justicar hunting ground. Go softly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220160" id2="17" version="1065353216">Man, the Justicars make the Black Sun's operation look like a kiddie park.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220161" id2="17" version="1065353216">All of these docks and loading equipment. What have the Justicars been up to?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220164" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 sensors =  multiple armed organics nearby</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220165" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Justicars aren't messing around. Lot of firepower here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220166" id2="17" version="1065353216">Justicars are busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220167" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like the Justicars are expanding their territory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220168" id2="17" version="1065353216">This looks like a full-scale military base, not some hideout for vigilantes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220171" id2="17" version="1065353216">Comm sensors = detecting multiple Justicar alarms</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice place to visit. Wouldn't want to live here. Justicars have more rules than the Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would be glory in destroying Justicars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Boy, this place just keeps getting bigger. Where'd the Justicars get this much hardware?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220175" id2="17" version="1065353216">This would actually be a nice part of the city if the Justicars weren't around.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Justicar prison = heavily guarded</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220179" id2="17" version="1065353216">This must be where the Justicars keep everyone they don't kill.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220180" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do Justicars cage prey, not kill?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220181" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kinda expected the Justicars' prison to be a lot dirtier--not to mention, smaller.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220182" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Justicars have their own prison... insane. The laws of the Republic don't mean a thing to these people.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rogue droids = hostile to organics</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220186" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't think there was any place on Coruscant worse than the Justicars' sector. Wrong again, Kira....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220187" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can feel electricity. Makes hide itching.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220188" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those droids don't look happy to see us. Then again, I'm not happy to be in the Works. Guess we're even.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220189" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lots of corners, lots of shadows--better keep our eyes open and watch for ambushes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220192" id2="17" version="1065353216">Water = bad for T7's servos</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220193" id2="17" version="1065353216">We found the one part of Black Sun territory that isn't on fire. Lucky us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220194" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lifeblood of Coruscant flows here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220195" id2="17" version="1065353216">This hydrosupply station better not rust my blasters. Figure I'll be needing them for a good long while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220196" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugh. Nothing like a water treatment plant to get those really memorable smells.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220199" id2="17" version="1065353216">Black Sun gangsters = attacking everyone</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220200" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Black Sun's getting target practice. Let's not give them any.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220201" id2="17" version="1065353216">Choosing to live here, no air, no sky. Is strange.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220202" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't recommend loitering. This looks to be Black Sun central.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220203" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tough to see slums like this when the people on the upper levels live just fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220206" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cargo crates = stolen merchandise</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220207" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure everything here was obtained legally. The Black Sun would never stoop to stealing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220208" id2="17" version="1065353216">Black Sun feed on blood and credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220209" id2="17" version="1065353216">I bet the Black Sun stole half these cargo crates right off the spaceport docks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better watch our step. No telling what the Black Sun has stored in here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220213" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi Code = forbids gambling // T7 = friendly reminder</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220214" id2="17" version="1065353216">The next drunken gambler who touches me loses a hand--and I don't mean pazaak.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220215" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seem even weaker from above.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220216" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care what Darmas says, I could live without all the flashy lights in here. Good cantinas don't need all this foofaraw.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220217" id2="17" version="1065353216">Big place. Not really my style, though. Corner cantinas with a good pack of regulars are more my speed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Center = top-quality medical care facility</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220221" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've got the best autodocs in the galaxy here. We could use a medcenter like this back on Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="220222" id2="17" version="1065353216">Had best treat Herald well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220223" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a mighty nice place to get patched up when a deal goes sour. Coruscant knows a thing or two about medcenters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220224" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pretty nice medcenter. Much better than the field hospitals I'm used to.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
