<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>61</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/world/gree_hydrosupply_leak/namakk.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683793" id2="17" version="1065353216">The clean life-waters flow upward, and my black sphere achieves purple parallel because of you. Gratefulness, black bisector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683794" id2="17" version="1065353216">I continue upgrading Coruscant systems and ensure the clean life-waters flow upward. Accept my unyielding gratefulness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683796" id2="17" version="1065353216">All Coruscant systems indicate clean life-waters flow upward. You flawlessly applied my crafted solution to the hydrosupply at the Black Sun level below. Adulation!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683797" id2="17" version="1065353216">No problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683798" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are unmarred by Black Sun green perpendiculars. I am gratified by this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683800" id2="17" version="1065353216">A group of children was collecting water from the broken hydrosupply and trading it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kids used the hydrosupply.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683801" id2="17" version="1065353216">A faulty hydrosupply is not suited for immature life cycles. Sealing the break promotes their safety.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Taking down Black Sun thugs was a lot of fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683803" id2="17" version="1065353216">I always enjoy a good fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683804" id2="17" version="1065353216">You took yellow equilateral to the green perpendicular? That is profoundly appropriate. My seared chassis feels justified.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clean life-waters flow and nurture upper levels. The Coruscant sufferer-beings achieve benefits of the enclave's Gree ingenuity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683808" id2="17" version="1065353216">My black sphere evolves to a purple parallel because of you. When I impart this development, Pat-aK will progress enthusiasm with the Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683809" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad life on Coruscant will be better now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683809" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's good to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683810" id2="17" version="1065353216">The city-planet's infrastructure expresses elementary designs. Additional upgrading is sternly recommended.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683812" id2="17" version="1065353216">You guys like things to be parallel, don't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Parallel is good, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your comprehension of Gree linguistics progresses favorably. You evolve accurate insights.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to hand over my reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683816" id2="17" version="1065353216">You exhibit numerous disagreeable traits, but black bisectors often do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683818" id2="17" version="1065353216">I pledged you a piece of Gree ingenuity. This solution was crafted specifically for your being. My acknowledgment and appreciations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683820" id2="17" version="1065353216">Convey my crafted solution to the broken hydrosupply at the Black Sun level below. Be alarmed to the Black Sun green perpendiculars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never going back... never going back to blue nonagon. Now, I am yellow concave. Injuries mark my chassis forever, and why? Ungrateful humans!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683824" id2="17" version="1065353216">How were you damaged?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683824" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been injured?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fire, smoke, blades. The occupants of level below committed numerous assaults. My safe return was improbable. Never going back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where's this &quot;blue nonagon&quot;? Why won't you go there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blue nonagon?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683828" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is difficult to impart. The level below is concentrated, strong, misery-wrongness. It is blue nonagon and horrible. Never going back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh... what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683831" id2="17" version="1065353216">I offer apologies. The fear courses in me, and I lose myself. I must verbalize more attentively.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coruscant's life-waters are sluggish-stagnant. Pat-aK commanded me, go to the level below, repair the broken hydrosupply, make clean life-waters flow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683835" id2="17" version="1065353216">I crafted a solution to achieve Pat-aK's command. All was orange sphere, until I arrived at the level below. Then, green perpendicular!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you run into trouble?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your language is insufficient to describe my suffering. Misery-wrongness, unprecedented perpendicularity... all too much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683839" id2="17" version="1065353216">How were you going to fix the hydrosupply?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the solution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683840" id2="17" version="1065353216">I crafted a durable object of Gree ingenuity, perfectly-aligned for the needed maintenance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Um... what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683843" id2="17" version="1065353216">I renew my atonement efforts and acknowledge your patience with this idea exchange.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683845" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pat-aK failed to impart the lethal conflict-enemies waiting on the level below. Many weapons and offenders despising my arrival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683847" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fled Black Sun with my crafted solution intact, but the repair progresses unresolved. Coruscant's life-waters remain sluggish-stagnant without repairs. The hydrosupply must have my crafted solution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I take your crafted solution to the hydrosupply?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683848" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683849" id2="17" version="1065353216">You offer yourself as a black bisector? That is a gratifying unpredicted announcement! I pledge to provide items of Gree ingenuity in return.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683851" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could fix that hydrosupply for you--for the right price.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you pay to make it happen?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683852" id2="17" version="1065353216">You would progress my black sphere for compensation? Agreed without contemplation! Items of Gree ingenuity I pledge, as consideration for this bargain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count me out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683855" id2="17" version="1065353216">You decline to help? But assistance would be rewarded with items of Gree ingenuity! Please, you must remedy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683856" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll go ahead and give it a try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683856" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, I've reconsidered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683857" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just can't say no to someone with a burned chassis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683857" id2="17" version="1065353216">How could I refuse?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683858" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I must.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take and apply my crafted solution to the hydrosupply. But do not apply before deactivating nearby flow-valves, or pressure-explosion-death will result!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be alerted, Black Sun green perpendicular will provide onslaught. May you experience blue tangent and return intact....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683863" id2="17" version="1065353216">The level below is blue nonagon, full of green perpendiculars. If you value your membrane, stay away....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a chance. [Refuse quest.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yellow vertex! Go, then!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
