<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>156</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Funny, people usually want to break out of prisons, not in to them. Guess everything's backwards with the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290394" id2="17" version="1065353216">There was nothing discreet about this prison break. I expect more of the same blunt tactics inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290395" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must be ready for anything, master. I sense chaos inside the prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290396" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's going to be a free-for-all inside this prison. Unpredictable, volatile, desperate. I can't wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prison riot. Shoot, first; toss grenades, second; call in an air strike, third--if anything's still moving, then ask questions.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290398" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our claws go in clean, come out bloodied!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our path is clear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice demolition job. Can't run a prison with a big hole in the wall, huh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290401" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever the Empire touches, it destroys. I can't defend the Republic's choice to keep a secret prison here, but that doesn't make this right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290402" id2="17" version="1065353216">It looks as if the Empire's begun the excavation without me. Heh. Little archaeologist humor there. That breach will lead us to the Republic prison, or what's left of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290403" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now this is a prison break. Think I'm gonna like this planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290404" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is where the first breakout occurred. These people are desperate, and violent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290405" id2="17" version="1065353216">A fine perimeter, though it lacks the elegance of Shadow Town. Don't you think?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290406" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's the breach in the prison defenses. It must've all started here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290407" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's the breach. Our only way in... and maybe our only way out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290408" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heck of a place the Republic's set up here. Wonder if they've got anyone I know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Subtle entrance. Fifty kilos of detonite, easy, or bomber strike maybe.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Empire people make super big hole over there!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I ever tell you I have a fear of being buried in a tunnel cave-in?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290414" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could easily be flanked in there. I'll cover our rear, make sure no one follows us in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290415" id2="17" version="1065353216">More trouble awaits, master. There are hostile thoughts inside this tunnel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Feeling jittery over here. Think I'm in withdrawal--let's kill something soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could be more Gand in there. Hate those buggish freaks. Time to exterminate them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290418" id2="17" version="1065353216">We enter now, kill all within, come out the other side with the stench of death.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tread lightly, little Sith. We are not among friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290420" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wonder what the Republic's using this tunnel for? And how all these aliens got here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290421" id2="17" version="1065353216">This facility's much larger than I imagined. And that tunnel? What was the Republic doing here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290422" id2="17" version="1065353216">A tunnel! Who knows what secrets it may hold. I hate to rush a job, but there's just so much here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spent some time in holding, but jail time is for chumps. Knew a lot of people in labor camps, though--fought each other more than the guards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290424" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop a moment. A thousand scents, a thousand songs... there's so much life here. And the Republic made it a prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290425" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had a Minder friend once who was captured by the SIS. I always assumed he'd been killed, but I hope he was imprisoned someplace like this. He'd have enjoyed the view.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290426" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place is fantastic. It shouldn't be a prison at all, it should be... I don't know. A garden for the Sith, a jewel for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290427" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is definitely not what I was thinking when I heard &quot;prison planet.&quot; I expected durasteel walls and deflector shields, not fields of flowers and trees.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's hoping this is a shortcut and not, say, some dead-end cell block we're going to get trapped in for the rest of our lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290429" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cross quickly, we're exposed out here. Good shooter could pick us off easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooh, look! Blizz can see far down!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290433" id2="17" version="1065353216">That must be where they keep the really bad criminals. Guess that means we're going in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290434" id2="17" version="1065353216">The deeper we go, the more difficult our extraction. My calculations are growing more unsure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290435" id2="17" version="1065353216">What was so terrible they needed to put it behind a river of lava?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290436" id2="17" version="1065353216">Murderers abound--I sense genocidal thoughts in there, sadistic cravings, unbelievable lust for vengeance and destruction. Yum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Love to visit strange new worlds, meet strange new people, kill them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290438" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can't build a cell that will hold us!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290439" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fire beneath us, no place to go but forward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290440" id2="17" version="1065353216">A particularly sadistic captain once tried to make me walk on hot coals, but I think I'll pass on swimming in magma. Let's stay away from the edge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290441" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful. We're entering the most ancient and most secure part of the old prison. Who knows what horrors the Rakata locked away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290442" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't flinch at danger, do you? Not that I'm frightened. Ahead lies maximum security and things unseen by any but the Rakata.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290443" id2="17" version="1065353216">New security zone. But you feel that? Soak up the steam and enjoy it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heat, in the middle of an ice world. It's extraordinary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290445" id2="17" version="1065353216">A crossing point between security zones. Somehow, I don't think this is where they keep the non-violent offenders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290446" id2="17" version="1065353216">New security zone, new types of prisoners. Not that they'll be any friendlier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290447" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see why they called it &quot;the tomb.&quot; Reminds me of all those old ruins I saw on Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do I let you drag me to these places? I say we sit right here and wait until Zale comes back out. If he doesn't, who's going to know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290449" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;The tomb,&quot; huh? No joke from the look of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, boss! Rock-river!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290453" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place keeps getting more surreal. I guess we're headed into the cave beneath the subterranean giant tree?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sophisticated alien technology built this place. There's no telling what we may face.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290455" id2="17" version="1065353216">This tree gives off a powerful essence. I've never felt anything like it before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290456" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are powerful secrets locked away here. I say we pry them out, painfully.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290457" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've fought on dozens of bizarre worlds on the fringes of the galaxy. Never seen nothing like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290458" id2="17" version="1065353216">We feel an ancient power in this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290459" id2="17" version="1065353216">The grave of a dead empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290460" id2="17" version="1065353216">You got a way of finding the craziest places, Sith. Who knew this place was under a tree. Let's just hope the folks who built this place are all dead, but I'm keeping my blaster handy just in case.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290461" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Rakata buildings make me uncomfortable. They ruled the galaxy, and then they just disappeared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this truly Rakata-built? I can't believe it. I can't--I'm sorry. I need a moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290463" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cripes. It's like the prison runs straight to the core... you could lock half the galaxy in here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290464" id2="17" version="1065353216">The nest remembers a place like this, long ago and far away. The creation of an ancient people... but not more ancient than us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such advanced technology. Such fine detail. The Empire is a great civilization, but we still have much to learn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290466" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never heard of anything like this, sir. Not beyond stories--Chiss fables about ancient species... be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290467" id2="17" version="1065353216">I--I think this place is Rakatan. They had some galaxy-spanning empire that makes the Sith's look like they're playing around. Seriously ancient.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290468" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't say this often, but whatever valuables are down here can stay. Let's just bug out while we can, all right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Path wasn't walked for a long time, until recently. Should've left it undisturbed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Boss know why people put funny heads on statues?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Energy generator station = providing power to prison sector</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis would be beautiful if it wasn't for all this ugly technology. The psychotic criminals don't help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290477" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I should guard that energy station for a while. It'd be safer, wouldn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290478" id2="17" version="1065353216">These energy stations have been left undefended. That's poor tactical planning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290479" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic placed too much faith in its technology. This shield generator could not withstand the Empire's might.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cannot trust shields. Better to rely on own strength and skill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290481" id2="17" version="1065353216">An oscillating shield network. Good luck to any prisoner who gets tangled up in that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290482" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's shielding the shield generator?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their shield generators better be more reliable than the ones we had on Hoth. Blasted things blew a fuse every other day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those shield generators are the only thing keeping the Empire from taking over this place completely.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290485" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must all defend the shield generators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290486" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear the Empire's been hitting power generators all over this area. Probably wouldn't hurt to discourage that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290487" id2="17" version="1065353216">An unsecured power facility. Typical Republic incompetence. This is why the Empire will win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290488" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got a bunch of old power packs back on the ship that need recharging. Knew I shoulda brought them with me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shield generators are still in one piece, at least. The Imps haven't smashed everything yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290490" id2="17" version="1065353216">These shield generators appear to still be functional. We're fortunate that Imperial commandos haven't destroyed them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic shield generators--the finest workmanship available! Particle field bulwarks for freedom!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290492" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never knew the Republic had a place like this. And I thought regular prison sounded rough....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290493" id2="17" version="1065353216">This world takes a strange path through history: known, then unknown; remembered, then forgotten.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290496" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = detecting evidence of Imperial forces // Jedi = be prepared</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290497" id2="17" version="1065353216">So much for keeping the bad guys locked up. Let's hope the prisoners who used to be here were just greedy Senators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't imagine why anybody would want to bust out of such a nice place. Are those turrets still working?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever happened here was over long before we arrived. The Empire knew exactly what it was doing when it came through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290500" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's plan of attack is to free as many prisoners as possible. Republic forces are easily confused by the chaos.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic cages. This is justice, Herald?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290502" id2="17" version="1065353216">Throwing away the key wasn't enough. Freedom will out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic got sloppy. Should have been best-defended positions on the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, yell if you see any good graffiti.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290505" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't figure this cell block should be wide open like that, do you?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290506" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will find no one good down there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290507" id2="17" version="1065353216">You spend more time deliberately running into prisons than anyone I know....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290508" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire has already been here. No telling how many prisoners they've released. This will be interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello down there? Any bad people home? No? All right, we're leaving. Think they bought it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope most of the prisoners have made a run for it. Anyone held here is bound to be tough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290511" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should be on our guard, sir. The occupants of these prisons are extremely dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290512" id2="17" version="1065353216">If these prisoners refuse to serve their mandated sentences, then they can face summary justice! Let them come!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's keep our eyes open, huh? Anybody they locked up in a place like this isn't gonna be too friendly.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290514" id2="17" version="1065353216">A path leading here is a path of violence and crimes beyond counting. Yuun advises caution.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alert! // T7 = detecting large + hostile predators nearby</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those are some awfully big prison cells. Maybe we don't want to know what lives here....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Check out the size of these prison cells. What are they keeping here, rancors?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any prisoner requiring this much security will take maximum firepower to bring down. I'll be ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290521" id2="17" version="1065353216">The things imprisoned here should not have been released. The Empire's forces have gone mad.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many cages. So many points lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imagine being trapped here, surrounded by heinous criminals--bruhh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wish we'd had a few cells like these for Imperial prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maximum security. Nothing to do but count snowflakes and think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those busted-open cells look even worse than the last batch. You ever get the feeling we're headed in the opposite direction of safe?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bowdaar smells strange things here. Be wary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290528" id2="17" version="1065353216">The comm channels are full of Republic soldiers yelling to send more troops to this cell block. That can't be good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at the size of those cells. I cannot wait to meet these prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen up, whatever ugly and large prisoners live here! I am a Jedi. Do not make me or my equally powerful friend hurt you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290531" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wonder how deep this place goes. It's just one prison block after another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290532" id2="17" version="1065353216">This complex seems to have no end. Prison block after prison block, with no end in sight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290533" id2="17" version="1065353216">The size and complexity of this prison is truly amazing! A true feat of Republic ingenuity!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290534" id2="17" version="1065353216">More prison blocks. Someday, you're going to run out of nasty places to drag me along to.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290535" id2="17" version="1065353216">This space reverberates with memories and thoughts of vengeance too terrible to speak.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prison technology = advanced + unknown</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290539" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's cold here--almost like the Force has been drained out of the place. The only presence here is death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything called the World Razer needs to stay down in its hole--forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some weapons should never be used. This World Razer is one of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you feel it? There is vast destructive power here. It's intoxicating.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something sleeps here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi, I can't help noticing the size of that vault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290545" id2="17" version="1065353216">That vault's too big. Something's wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just what kind of inmate needs a vault that huge?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't know what this World Razer is, but there's no such thing as a monster that eats planets. Is there?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bowdaar's battle skills are tested against the World Razer. Good!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would it really be so awful if this World Razer destroyed Belsavis? After we left, obviously.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Battles like this are the reason I stay with you. Not many Mandalorians can say they've faced the World Razer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wouldn't you rather have the Wookiee with you right now? I mean, he's taller--and he probably enjoys fighting things called the World Razer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290552" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever's behind that door, it's not good. Let's stay sharp, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290553" id2="17" version="1065353216">We cannot know with certainty what we'll face inside. I think a cautious approach might be advisable, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290554" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever danger may hide in these depths, it is no match for Havoc Squad! Onward!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290555" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seriously? This is where we're going? Are you crazy?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun can see the anguish of millions laid here. The regrets of deaths beyond counting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Praise: Sometime a giant hole is the most effective means of entry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alert: Beware the possibility of ambush by undesirables. It is how I would use this terrain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023269" id2="17" version="1065353216">Opinion: The security protocols for this level are quite thorough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023272" id2="17" version="1065353216">Approval: We could liquidate undesirables here indefinitely. How delightful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Judgment: A linked series of energy generators? Careless planning. No wonder the Empire invaded so easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023506" id2="17" version="1065353216">Witticism: I must remember to thank the Empire for releasing all these prisoners. I will not be bored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Estimation: Given the size of these prison cells, I predict we will encounter exciting new troublemakers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023512" id2="17" version="1065353216">Praise: One must admire the commitment to deleting troublemakers that is inherent in a name like &quot;World Razer.&quot;</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
