<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>6</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/support/tatooine/shared/bb_group_1_board_1.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1111848" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
SPACE DEBRIS RETRIEVAL

Meteoroids: they come in all manner of shapes, sizes and compositions. GSI's orbital sensors tell us that one particular meteoroid that broke apart over Tatooine exhibited the energy signature of a rare, especially dense phobium variant.

Locate and take detailed scans of this special rock. If it's made of the rare ore we hope it is, we can use it to create more dependable fuel cells for use on the field.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1111867" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
SCAVENGED PROTOTYPES

We are embarrassed to report that a shipment of starfighter repair droids has been lost in transit on Tatooine. At this time, the best we can determine is that the shipment was picked apart by Jawas. Trouble is, sandstorm activity has made orbital tracking impossible.

Pinpoint area sandcrawlers and we'll dispatch probe droids to check for signs of GSI technology. Once our droids are found, we'll take care of the rest.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1111887" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
KRAYT DRAGON EGGS

Of all the varied predators of Tatooine, few are as revered--and feared--as the krayt dragon. That is why our Animal Weaponization Division is looking to clone the great, rare beast and test its ferocity in a controlled laboratory setting.

Collect fossilized krayt dragon eggs for us, and your faction may soon have a scaly new ally on the front lines. You can usually find the eggs near clusters of penakin larvae, which feed on the fossil's unique nutrients.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1111888" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
EXAMINE VAPORATORS

The denizens of Tatooine are nothing if not resourceful. They have built not only quake-resistant settlements into various mesas and cliffs across the planet, but also scaled-down moisture vaporators that are nearly as powerful as the full-size models.

Take detailed scans of the moisture vaporators located on these &quot;cliff villages&quot; so GSI can replicate their unique design for the creation of comparatively portable vaporators for use in military deployments.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1111889" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI ACTION ALERT:
ROGUE DROID

Our latest battle droid prototype--fitted with proprietary GSI technology--has been reprogrammed by a thief who is presently directing the droid offworld. 

Unfortunately, the thief has employed subsurface scramblers to keep the droid's location from us. Pinpointing and disabling these scramblers will allow you to triangulate our costly--and powerful--droid's location. We are more concerned with the value of the tech than the state of the droid. Destroy it if you must.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1112012" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI OPPORTUNITY: VALUED PARTNER INITIATIVE

At Galactic Solutions Industries, we're always looking for ways to grow our partnerships. By accepting and completing multiple GSI assignments, you may qualify for GSI's Valued Partner Initiative. The VPI rewards your hard work with reputation above and beyond what you've earned for each individual commission.

Thank you for your consideration in becoming one of our most valued partners.

Addalar Hyland, founder and CEO
GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
