<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>19</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/uprisings/space/fracture/transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216582" id2="17" version="1065353216">You found us, Commander. Aren't you a clever one?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216584" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you would come. Your kind are smug and predictable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't mean we can't be hospitable. Tell us, Commander... how would you like to die?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216589" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have friends on those bases we destroyed? Loved ones? Loss is a terrible thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216591" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were weak. Vermin must be stamped out!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such a shame, Commander. You have so much power and not a clue what to do with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scum has no imagination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your Alliance is made of filth. It will fall--and so will you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216601" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid Lord Anril's right. It's almost time for you to say goodbye.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, we'll make your end nice and quick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216607" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've discovered a dangerous rogue faction within Sith Intelligence, led by a former Imperial Cipher and a powerful Sith Lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major Korven and Lord Anril are launching devastating attacks on Alliance settlements. By striking us, they're attempting to reclaim the glory days of the Sith Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216611" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've tracked their operations to Vanguard Station. Board the facility and end this threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive, Commander. By cutting off the head of this rogue faction, you've put an end to their attacks on our outposts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our Alliance is stronger with Anril and Korven pulverized and Vanguard Station out of play.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wiping out these traitors is a powerful reminder to the galaxy that we do not tolerate threats.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent job, Commander. Our allies can breathe safely knowing they're no longer the target of lunatics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216622" id2="17" version="1065353216">With Lord Anril and Major Korven out of the picture, we can once again rally others to our cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216624" id2="17" version="1065353216">You proved today that we protect our own. The galaxy won't soon forget this.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
