<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>27</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/bronze/republic/out_in_the_cold/corporal_loovi.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527556" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pirate attacks have started to ease up. Guess the Hailstorm Brotherhood needs to eat, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527559" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sabotaged the Hailstorm Brotherhood's foodstuffs? Excellent!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527561" id2="17" version="1065353216">That ought to limit the pirates' numbers on the front lines, at least for a time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527563" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll make the most of the breathing room you've given us. Thank you for your assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527565" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find and destroy the Hailstorm Brotherhood's food stores. If that doesn't force them back, I don't know what will.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let your guard down out there, Jedi. These wastes are crawling with pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527570" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch your back out there, sir. This sector is crawling with pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your eyes peeled, Captain. This area isn't safe, not by a long shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay sharp. You may not see them, but there's pirates out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527576" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blasted Hailstorm scum have been attacking us nonstop. Haven't had a decent night's sleep in weeks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527578" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're wearing us down, making us tired, vulnerable. Won't be long before they storm the outpost and finish us off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="527579" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take the battle to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527580" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've got us outmanned and outgunned. No chance we'll beat them with brute force. But maybe we won't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="527582" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's your plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Either we start preparing our tragic last stand... or we find a way to force them back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="527585" id2="17" version="1065353216">So basically, you're doomed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527586" id2="17" version="1065353216">The situation's not completely hopeless... at least, not yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Food out here is as scarce as it is dangerous. On Hoth, the wildlife eats you, not the other way around.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527590" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you sabotaged the Hailstorm's food supplies, they'd be forced to pull back and hunt--or starve. Either way, we win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="527591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave it to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="527592" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got a blaster--use it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three weeks of pulling double guard duty has made me sloppy. I'd just get myself killed out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527595" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got a lead on where the Hailstorm is storing their foodstuffs. Security there is tight, but I'm sure you've faced worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just find the food stores, destroy them and get out. We'll let hunger handle the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="527599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count me out. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="527602" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hailstorm Brotherhood will overrun us any day now. Best get out while you can.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
