<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>418</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/rishi/hub_1/multi/shared/lana_beniko.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132466" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would have made that shot with my eyes and the droid's eyes shut! Stupid Sith!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132468" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand your frustration, Jakarro, but there's only so much of your bluster I'm prepared to take.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132469" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's going on?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron's been captured by the Revanites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Data from the Nova Blades hinted at the location of a Revanite safehouse in Raider's Cove. We looked into it and were ambushed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan knew we were here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132473" id2="17" version="1065353216">A trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132474" id2="17" version="1065353216">It looks that way. It's possible he may have sensed our presence; I couldn't say for sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132476" id2="17" version="1065353216">They wouldn't bother taking Theron prisoner unless they needed something from him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron wasn't killed....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132477" id2="17" version="1065353216">Were I in their position, I'd do everything I could to learn how much Theron knows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132479" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should have waited for me to finish with the Mandalorian clan. Absolutely stupid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132479" id2="17" version="1065353216">You idiots went without me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132480" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll concede we acted in haste. In retrospect, maybe the lead was simply too tempting for us to have trusted it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever the case, I stand by my decision to not impede in Theron's abduction--and I know Theron would, too. Now he's in a position to do what he does.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where I come from, we value our allies! We do not let them become imprisoned!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132485" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're talking about a seasoned SIS operative. If the Revanites took him to their base, he could learn a lot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana has a point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, if we're to make any use of that knowledge, we'll have to exfiltrate him all the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron should never have fallen into enemy hands. We can't let it stand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132487" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm with you, Jakarro.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132488" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't dream of leaving him with the Revanites. After all, we need to know what he's learned whilst in captivity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where do you stand on this, Deefour?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132489" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does the droid say?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me? No one ever asks my opinion--not even the hairy lug here! You honor me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jakarro does make an excellent point--but, then, so does Miss Beniko....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ultimately, I think we should go after Agent Shan, as it will allow us to plow through as many Revanites as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good suggestion, droid! I will keep you plugged in for that!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan has a fleet of warships on standby.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. From examining the Nova Blades' data, it looks as though they've been routing Imperial and Republic fleets here to Rishi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132499" id2="17" version="1065353216">So the Empire and Republic are drawn into a full-scale battle, and whoever's left standing, the Revanites pick off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132500" id2="17" version="1065353216">And we still don't know who we can trust. We need to interfere with the Revanites' plans, if not stop them outright.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132502" id2="17" version="1065353216">The droid knows where they are!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, it's true. I was able to pinpoint several communications originating from another island.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132506" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm told there's a Rishii village on the outskirts. I can't imagine they would resent our presence there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132507" id2="17" version="1065353216">To the island--and Revan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132509" id2="17" version="1065353216">The village will be our staging area. After the Revanites fall, I will confront Revan myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we will go there immediately and establish a base of operations for my campaign. In the end, Revan will answer to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132512" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132515" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, let's not waste any more time. We'll set up shop there and I'll see if Revan prefers carbonite or cinders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well, hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their village will be remote, high up. Perfect. I'll turn this conspiracy on its ear, then see to Revan himself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132522" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not telling them I'm some pirate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132522" id2="17" version="1065353216">No more pirate subterfuge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132523" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't imagine you'll have to. The Rishii do seem to be very hands-off, from my understanding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you think it matters to me if they mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132525" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't have a choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132526" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was only pointing out that they're not terribly concerned with the affairs of others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132530" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to assume Revan's expecting a resistance force now; you should expect to find patrols along the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tear into those Revanites, but try to save some for me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132539" id2="17" version="1065353216">What have we learned from the Aggressor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very little, I'm afraid. It would appear someone took it upon themselves to corrupt much of the data as a last resort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132542" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a real mess. Getting fragments, but nothing incredibly coherent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132544" id2="17" version="1065353216">The one thing that does keep turning up is the Mandalorian Margok brought up earlier--the one they call Torch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132545" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about her?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, it looks like Torch and Margok were thick as thieves for a while, then something happened. Had to do with the Revanites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't really know the details, but it looks like Torch moved her whole clan to another island here on Rishi. I've got the coordinates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jakarro, ready your ship. I'll go see what this &quot;Torch&quot; has to say for herself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132549" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's where I'm going.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1132550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Beniko has other plans for me and the droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132552" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the matter, Theron--is my being around so distracting you need to hurry me off to some other island?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132552" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Sending me away, Theron?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132553" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not entirely wrong....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132555" id2="17" version="1065353216">There has to be something better to go on than an island of Mandalorians with vague motives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132555" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need a better lead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132556" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's the best we have for now, so it will have to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132558" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I find anything else, we'll have Jakarro look into it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132560" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sending Jakarro out on a scouting run; I've made local arrangements for your transportation should he not return in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow, you've been busier than I thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get whatever information you can from the Mandalorians. With any luck, they'll lead us to the Revanites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132569" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd say the Nova Blades are properly distracted, wouldn't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132570" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would be an understatement. Theron's been monitoring communications; you've caused quite a stir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Want some gratification? Here, check this out. Just recorded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132574" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're blasting up my supplies, my foot soldiers! Taking my workers! What are you people prepared to do about it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132576" id2="17" version="1065353216">This appears to be your problem, not ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132578" id2="17" version="1065353216">How would you like it if I made it your personal problem? Gimme Revan! I wanna talk to Revan!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132580" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, I don't think so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132582" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't put Revan on, the Nova Blades stop rerouting galactic traffic. That ain't negotiable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commodore Margok, are you threatening to alter the terms of our deal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132586" id2="17" version="1065353216">I paid you to do a job and you've done it well, but that's over now. I no longer have any use for your Nova Blades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, I know Torch and her Mandalorian clan up and left us, but the Blades still got a lot to offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not if you don't have your own house in order. Put an end to the upstart causing you trouble and I'll consider resuming our alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132592" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really did it. You got them running scared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132595" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the only way this was ever gonna go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Naturally. You were expecting some other outcome?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess it was silly of me to question, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mandalorians?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132602" id2="17" version="1065353216">Margok said something about Mandalorians. Sure hope I'm not going to have to face my own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132603" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't know much about that yet. Let's take things one step at a time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Margok mentioned Mandalorians. Do you know anything about that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heard the name Torch before, but not much else. I'm looking into it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132609" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is no time to let up. I'm going to get back out there and finish this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now to end it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, not to sell you short or anything--don't think this'll be a cakewalk all of a sudden.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132612" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Nova Blades still have an impressive roster of hardened criminals at their disposal, and the Aggressor is still heavily fortified.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132614" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Aggressor's their headquarters. You've seen it--a crashed ship Margok turned into a fortress. Can't get in without the proper security codes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132615" id2="17" version="1065353216">That won't be a problem for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132618" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll get Jakarro to lend a hand all the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Am I supposed to know you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132626" id2="17" version="1065353216">My name is Lana Beniko. I am a Sith Lord, though I have no interest in the title.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132628" id2="17" version="1065353216">I used to serve as advisor to Darth Arkous of the Dark Council--until he was revealed as a traitor and consequently executed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132629" id2="17" version="1065353216">First I'm hearing it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132631" id2="17" version="1065353216">How is it I'm just learning of this now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132632" id2="17" version="1065353216">I apologize for that being the case, Wrath. The truth is hardly anyone knows what I'm about to tell you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132635" id2="17" version="1065353216">A member of the Dark Council is executed and I learn of it on some backwater?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132636" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid that's correct, Dark Lord. Understand, though, that hardly anyone knows what I'm telling you now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132639" id2="17" version="1065353216">And here I thought I was plugged in to all the juicy gossip.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, well--everything I'm telling you remains unknown to most, hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132643" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's very little that escapes my notice. You'd think I'd have found out about this by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132644" id2="17" version="1065353216">Certainly, Commander. Once I've explained further, I believe you'll understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132646" id2="17" version="1065353216">You almost sound like you're about to explain all this craziness on your own....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132647" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could advise me instead if you want....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132647" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Need a substitute?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132648" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep that in mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Haven't gotten into all the details yet, have you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132652" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're just in time; I was about to start.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good riddance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Last thing the Empire needs is some two-timer mucking up the works.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132656" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm inclined to agree, hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132659" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoever ended his pathetic life did us a favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132664" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the problem ended with Arkous, that would be great, right? But it doesn't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132676" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor's Wrath. Good to see you again. Any... word from your namesake?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing has changed, if that's what you're asking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not as such.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pretty cagey. Think you'd be more open with Lana after all she's sacrificed for your Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132679" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right now, I'd rather hear what you've been up to. It's been too long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132679" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Let's talk about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132680" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should know it's a dangerous thing to pry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132680" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mind your business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132681" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, no, you're doing it wrong. Howling Tempest Gang pirates are way less uptight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132682" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dark Lord. An honor, as ever. And how fares the Dark Council?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132683" id2="17" version="1065353216">No matter the obstacles we come to face, we endure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132683" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are determined.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132684" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a confident one, I'll give you that....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget about the Dark Council. I'd much rather discuss how you've been since last we met.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132685" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Never mind them....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132686" id2="17" version="1065353216">It would be far better off were it operating under my own agenda.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132686" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should be in charge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132687" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought to myself, &quot;Now that sounds like something a Sith would say,&quot; and sure enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132688" id2="17" version="1065353216">The hunter arrives--just as I'd hoped you would. I trust Rishi has been to your liking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sandy beaches, shimmering waters, whole bunch of clowns think they're tougher than me--I could get used to it here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Definitely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132690" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then maybe you haven't smelled a Skarkla's breath yet. Or maybe you have, I don't know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that I know you're here, what's not to like?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132691" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] I like you being here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132692" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you were going to find some backwater to hide out in, but this is a bit much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132692" id2="17" version="1065353216">This dump?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132693" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd be hurting our feelings--if we actually had anything to do with picking this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander. Pleased to see you again. I hope you'll forgive the cloak-and-dagger routine. You must grow tired of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132695" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's actually been a refreshing change of pace to impersonate a legendary outlaw.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132695" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've found it amusing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132696" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to hear; you'll be doing more of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132697" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make an exception this time--for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132697" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] It's okay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132698" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see you haven't changed. Good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132700" id2="17" version="1065353216">It must be true, what they say about absence and the heart....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not interrupting anything, am I? Just kidding; I don't really care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132703" id2="17" version="1065353216">This pirate cover of yours has been pretty tedious, frankly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132703" id2="17" version="1065353216">In fact, I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132704" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can thank me for the cover--or blame me, if that's what does it for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132709" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you are...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132710" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Theron Shan. He's been invaluable in my efforts to investigate a most serious threat, and in bringing you here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132711" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why exactly am I here? And why are you here, for that matter?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132712" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have discovered that Darth Arkous was secretly working for a dangerous cult known as the Order of Revan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132713" id2="17" version="1065353216">I discovered that Darth Arkous had us raid the Jedi Temple to acquire technology he could use to harm the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132715" id2="17" version="1065353216">Along with a high-ranking Republic officer who led the assault on Korriban, Darth Arkous was working for a dangerous cult known as the Order of Revan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132716" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Order of Revan's no secret to me--I had a run-in with them on Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132717" id2="17" version="1065353216">An earlier incarnation, perhaps--but this is a new breed of Revanite.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132719" id2="17" version="1065353216">I feel I should have heard of this order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132720" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Revanites follow the teachings of Revan--a former Sith Lord who later became a Jedi Knight, in case you didn't know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Between what I've dug up through the SIS and what Lana's found on your end, the Republic and Empire are both riddled with undercover Revanites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132723" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're with the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132724" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, that's right. Are we gonna have a problem?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132725" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Lana vouches for you, that will be good enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132725" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trust Lana's judgment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Really. Gotta say I'm surprised, but hey--I won't tempt fate or anything. Glad we can work together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132728" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a feeling we'll get along.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132728" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Not at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132731" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just supposed to trust a Republic spy? I don't think so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132731" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132732" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, I'm in the same boat you are. I've got traitors, you've got traitors, and they're teaming up to tear us apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132734" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're in this together. Believe me, this is our best option by far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that all that's out the way, let's get to the heart of the matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, Theron.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132739" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that a good hello or a bad one? Outside of Lana, I can never tell with you Imperial types.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132740" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's a lucrative client, but they don't own me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132740" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not an Imperial.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, if you say so....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be grateful I'm working with you and leave it at that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't push it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132744" id2="17" version="1065353216">So definitely a good hello. Got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132746" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we're to succeed here, we'll need to cooperate a great deal. I suggest we don't antagonize one another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132748" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, okay. Well, in the spirit of cooperation, I'll get things rolling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132750" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've shown you want the Revanites stopped as much as anyone. That makes you an ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132750" id2="17" version="1065353216">I welcome your assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. Glad we're clear on that front, because here we go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132753" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] I think you know....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132755" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you really asking me that after the last time I saw you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, point taken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132759" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm very glad to see you, Theron.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Really. Okay, good to know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that we're all reunited, perhaps we should get things underway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132764" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right, yeah. Let's get to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132766" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Remain silent]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right. Okay. Moving on....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132769" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Revanites are here--on Rishi. That's why we led you here under false pretenses. They can't know we're on to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Arkous and Colonel Darok have brought their Infinite Army here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132773" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, Arkous and Darok--they're dead. Taken out in a raid on Rakata Prime. We destroyed the Revanites' whole cyborg manufacturing network.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132775" id2="17" version="1065353216">But what we discovered there.... Revan is alive. Alive, and leading the Revanites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132776" id2="17" version="1065353216">I watched him take his last breath and say his last words.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132777" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can he be alive? Wasn't he killed in an Imperial assault?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132778" id2="17" version="1065353216">He claims to have been reborn. He also claims that he only wishes to save the galaxy, but at what terrible price?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132780" id2="17" version="1065353216">The good news--for you--is he'll destroy the Republic in the process. Bad news is he'll destroy the Empire, too. He has to be stopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132783" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need you to go out there and make life hard for the Revanites' allies--the Nova Blades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132784" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the Nova Blades are running things in Raider's Cove, but how are they helping the Revanites?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132784" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are they up to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132785" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Revanites are operating out of Rishi, then it stands to reason their leader is here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is Revan on Rishi?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132786" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's our suspicion, too, but we can't say for sure just yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132788" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll decide what I &quot;need&quot; to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132788" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't give me orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, easy. I'm not making demands, okay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron and I have a plan. Please, hear us out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132793" id2="17" version="1065353216">From what we've been able to gather, the Revanites' agents in the Empire and Republic have been feeding the Nova Blades intel on ship activity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132795" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Blades then use that intel to ambush military patrols and key shipping lanes on both sides. They're essentially remapping hyperroutes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132796" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should be taking the fight to the Order of Revan directly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget the Nova Blades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132797" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we knew where on this planet they were situated, we would do just that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132799" id2="17" version="1065353216">What good does that do them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132799" id2="17" version="1065353216">So?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132800" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what we'd like to find out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132802" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Say nothing]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hate to admit it, but I haven't been able to remotely slice the Blades' computers. I have to have their security shut down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132805" id2="17" version="1065353216">The trouble is, we can't have any suspicion raised that our attack is related to the Revanites' activities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132806" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I assault the Nova Blades as a member of this Howling Tempest Gang, all suspicion is averted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132807" id2="17" version="1065353216">So I am meant to be some base pirate who has a &quot;beef&quot; with the Nova Blades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132808" id2="17" version="1065353216">I light into the Blades like some big-time, greedy pirate and no one's the wiser.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hence the cover. I should appear to be after the Nova Blades, and the Nova Blades alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, you've got it exactly. Bust up their operations, get their attention, make yourself look legitimate--and then go for the throat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132812" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have a trusted source who's determined that the Nova Blades' base, a wrecked ship called the Aggressor, contains their entire security apparatus. That's our final target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where do I start?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get to it, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132814" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the spirit!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132816" id2="17" version="1065353216">It would be nice to know a little more about what I'm getting myself into.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132816" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want more details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132817" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Nova Blades built Raider's Cove, so they get a piece of every kind of action going on here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132819" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're well funded, well staffed and protective as all get-out of the empire they've built here. Empire with a small &quot;e&quot;, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132823" id2="17" version="1065353216">And who might that be?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132823" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Trusted source&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone we trust with our lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone you already know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Two someones, if we're being precise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132836" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll place you in range of the first Nova Blade target; that's where our source is waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132838" id2="17" version="1065353216">It really is good to see you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Been hiding out a long time. It's nice to see someone who isn't a complete stranger. Good luck out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. May the Force serve you well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132850" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Nova Blades have to believe you're a legitimate threat to their supremacy. Show them you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132851" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Nova Blades fear you, as they should. Now take the Aggressor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132852" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Mandalorians ought to assist us--if they know what's good for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132853" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm confident we'll recover Theron. See you at the village.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132858" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force serve you well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133683" id2="17" version="1065353216">If nothing else, the activity will keep him from picking apart Deefour any futher.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133692" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hopefully you fared better with the Mandalorians.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135001" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could have caught up!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135003" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't afford to be so reckless, Jakarro! Losing Theron is bad enough--what if we'd lost you, too?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, now, everyone stay calm... Queen Lina of Onderon once faced a similar predicament, and her solution was quite creative!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut up, droid!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135008" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's going on? Where's Theron?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135009" id2="17" version="1065353216">He was captured. The Nova Blades data listed a Revanite safehouse here in town, and when we tried to investigate....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135011" id2="17" version="1065353216">There were only ten of them! We saw it happen, but she used her Sith wizardry to hold me back!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron is the only one the Revanites saw. They may not know about the rest of us. If so, we need to maintain that advantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135014" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we move quickly, we may be able to catch up before the Revanites disappear again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1135014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's go after him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135015" id2="17" version="1065353216">They already have. Please, this is not the time for reckless heroics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135017" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made a tough call. But I think it was probably the right one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1135017" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made the right call.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135018" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I think it was cowardly! Jakarro does not back down from a fight!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Between the two of you, there was no hope of rescuing him? I don't buy that for a second.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1135020" id2="17" version="1065353216">How could you abandon him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135021" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not the point! Whether we saved him or not, the attempt would have revealed us to the enemy, and then we'd be running now instead of completing our mission!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135023" id2="17" version="1065353216">I really think you're all much too worried. They took him alive! That's a good sign!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135025" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're probably just torturing him a bit, maybe doing some interrogation... where he could tell them about us... oh no!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135027" id2="17" version="1065353216">That won't be an issue. Theron has several discreet implants to help him ignore pain and chemical manipulation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135028" id2="17" version="1065353216">A powerful Force user may still be able to learn what he knows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135029" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if Revan or one of his followers use the Force? Couldn't they read his mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135030" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never been able to--yes, I've tried, I'm sure it's no surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135032" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron's mind is highly ordered, very... resolute. Probably due to his childhood training by the Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135034" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'll keep our secrets, and we will rescue him. But right now, we need to focus and think it all through--just like he would.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135035" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right--we need to stick to the mission. When we find the Revanites, we'll find Theron.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1135035" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Precisely. If we're fortunate, he may even learn a bit about their plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135038" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trusted Theron. I don't trust you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1135038" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't listen to Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trust that I want to defeat the Revanites just as badly as you do.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arguing and killing each other is pointless! We need to be killing Revanites!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135043" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now: what did you learn from the Mandalorians?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan has a hidden fleet here on Rishi. He's preparing for some kind of battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135045" id2="17" version="1065353216">A hidden fleet, pirates altering shipping lanes... that's it! They aren't just affecting the shipping lanes, they're also changing Imperial and Republic patrol paths.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan is trying to draw them into a battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here, over Rishi. With his own ships in the mix, both fleets could be devastated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135048" id2="17" version="1065353216">That must be his goal. Weakening both sides so that he can make his own play.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135049" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to find some way to interfere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135051" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know where to find them!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135053" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? How? Explain, droid!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135055" id2="17" version="1065353216">After they caught Theron, I intercepted their transmissions. After that, triangulating their base was a simple calculation. I completed it almost eighty-seven seconds ago!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135057" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're on a small island, not far from here. The native Rishii have a trading village on the same island. I'm sure they'd give us comfortable lodging.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then let's go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135059" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to clean up any trail we might have left here. You go on--we'll meet you shortly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, I used to love cleaning....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135080" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to have your assistance again. The Nova Blades' information will be in our hands very soon, I can sense it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135081" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Aggressor may look like a junk heap, but the Nova Blades have added quite a bit of security over the years. Be cautious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135082" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope these Mandalorians are in a talkative mood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135083" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll meet you at the Rishi village. Hurry along.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140973" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warning! Adequate encryption has not been verified. Transmission interception is possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please confirm identity. I am authorized only to speak with &quot;the Red Blade.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140976" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the Red Blade. You want to tell me what's going on?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140976" id2="17" version="1065353216">My old cover identity? Okay...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I'm the Red Blade. Maybe I'm not. Who's calling?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140977" id2="17" version="1065353216">First, who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Partial authorization granted. I carry a message from your loyal associate &quot;Jheeg.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hear the message.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140980" id2="17" version="1065353216">No audio available. Your loyal associate requests a meeting at the attached coordinates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140982" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're on the wrong frequency. I don't know any Red Blade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140982" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no idea who you mean.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Verbal identification: Rejected. Facial recognition: Confirmed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140985" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Blade, I am to inform you that your loyal associate Jheeg awaits you at the attached coordinates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please proceed with all appropriate haste. Also: Welcome back to Rishi after your long sojourn on Hutta!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dark Lord. Moff Pyron ready to report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140990" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you have for me, Pyron?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your apprentice Ashara briefed me on the Order of Revan. We are discreetly sweeping for infiltrators in your ranks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140993" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I may, I've also prepared a briefing on current military operations. I'll endeavor to be quick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140995" id2="17" version="1065353216">...as for the Celanon campaign, Darth Marr is coordinating the joint armada with minimal losses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140997" id2="17" version="1065353216">That does raise the issue, however: Our Silencer fleet-killers are underperforming as the Republic adapts tactically and technologically.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140999" id2="17" version="1065353216">We may be able to refine the Silencer cannons further, but their radiation output will begin to kill our own gunners. Shall we proceed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make the refinements, but post a skeleton crew to any ships so equipped. We have only so many troops to spare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Try to minimize our losses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141001" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Silencers served us well, but there's no use clinging to obsolete technology at our people's expense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time we retire the Silencers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141002" id2="17" version="1065353216">If our men are to die, let them die gloriously in my name. Continue the refinements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141002" id2="17" version="1065353216">We proceed, and fear no death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, Dark Lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141005" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is also the question of Alzar. Darth Ravage still believes the natives hold no value and expands rapidly into their territory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your Overseers on Korriban believe the Alzarians might be trained as Sith, but to recruit them now could make an enemy of Ravage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ravage is a useful ally. He may crush the Alzarians with my blessing; we'll find new acolytes elsewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let Ravage do as he wishes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let Ravage whine at the next council meeting. The Empire needs allies, not resentful colonies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recruit the natives anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141010" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you wish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find a slaving ship willing to slip behind Ravage's lines. Anyone taken from Alzar we'll gladly pay for. Ravage need know nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enslave them, but avoid blame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141013" id2="17" version="1065353216">A clever stratagem. It shall be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141015" id2="17" version="1065353216">One last order of business. I understand you're on Rishi; normally I wouldn't bother you with trivialities, but....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speak, Pyron.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141017" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a servant there by the name of Lord Veijel. Like many, he's been seeking an audience since your ascension.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141019" id2="17" version="1065353216">He won't say why, or speak to anyone but you. However, Thanaton clearly prized him--he received significant resources for his &quot;research.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we know anything about what he's doing on Rishi?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about his research.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141021" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of Thanaton's prized dogs wants me in person on Rishi? Surely he wouldn't be so obvious?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141021" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Veijel did serve Thanaton's predecessor, as well--he may truly be loyal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141024" id2="17" version="1065353216">When one of my servants wishes to speak with me, I expect to be informed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why wasn't I told earlier?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141025" id2="17" version="1065353216">Respectfully, you receive dozens of requests daily, most of no import. I sought only to avoid a deluge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Veijel was designated a &quot;seeker into matters exotic and arcane.&quot; Quite a few of your researchers have this designation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whether Veijel's work is productive or--like certain other legacy projects--mere eccentricity is not for me to judge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141030" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where do I find him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141031" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll send coordinates. Perhaps your archaeologist might assess Veijel's work with some insight as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141032" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you are dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141033" id2="17" version="1065353216">My life for yours, Dark Lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141035" id2="17" version="1065353216">My dear friend the Wrath! Always a pleasure to see you intact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Vowrawn. This is unexpected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, what's life without a few surprises?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141039" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are matters I'd like to discuss in person, and I happen to be near the Rishi System.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps we can meet? Enjoy a respite from the bloodshed and destruction?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141042" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's past time we reconnected. I expect we have much to consider together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, Vowrawn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141043" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will await you at these coordinates, but do make haste. My visit to Rishi must be brief.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141044" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are schemes at hand that require my attention. If you are involved, I would know. If you are not, then your moment is poorly chosen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141044" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are plots afoot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141045" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand your position, but I can only say this:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141047" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are neither my friend nor my ally. Baras is gone, and our pact is ended.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our alliance ended with Baras.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141049" id2="17" version="1065353216">What use are you to me now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141050" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wound me, Wrath, but I've endured worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141052" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have much to gain from one another--wisdom to trade that runs deeper than war. And it may be some time before the opportunity comes again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141054" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will await you at these coordinates as long as I can, but I dare not linger. Good day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141056" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello? Hello? Are you the Grand Champion?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141057" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who is this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141058" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Thera Markon. Crysta's daughter. She was your handler, right? On the Great Hunt?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141060" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard you were on Rishi. I want to meet with you. Crysta's dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Crysta never mentioned you, and a lot of people have this frequency. A lot of people don't like me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141063" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do I know this is real?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141064" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't a trap. I know you'd shoot me--that's what you do!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141066" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't the Great Hunt, and I don't work with Crysta anymore. Get off this channel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141066" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not my concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141067" id2="17" version="1065353216">No! Absolutely not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, without Crysta, you'd still be on Dromund Kaas. Without Crysta, you wouldn't have a ship. You may work for Sith now, but you didn't always.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141071" id2="17" version="1065353216">Besides, I'm not asking a favor. I'm offering a job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141072" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. We'll meet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Name a time and place. I'll be there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141075" id2="17" version="1065353216">In that case, we have something to discuss. Been a while since I worked outside the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141075" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those are the magic words.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141076" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got a room at the cantina. I'll be drinking. Bring your slicer if you want to check my story--just come soon as you can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Am I really a person you want to make angry?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1141077" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should watch your tone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141078" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course not. I'm--look, I'm just on edge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141080" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, one meeting, and you can walk away. I'm at the cantina. Bring your slicer if you want to check my story.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
