<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>17</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/bronze/the_defector/lieutenant_treshoda.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="718836" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope this Gryffin Remus proves of value to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="718837" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've already sent someone to arrest your rebel. Perhaps my torture droid will help him remember the names of others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="718839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you the officer who deals with defectors?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="718840" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord. My poor station is honored by your presence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="718842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ye-es... though I prefer not to be quite so open about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="718844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Lieutenant Treshoda. High Command has tasked me to learn how these rebels think. As distasteful as that is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="718846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you found a candidate? Someone of enough value for the Empire to recruit instead of capture?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="718847" id2="17" version="1065353216">A man named Gryffin Remus. He seems to know the rebels well. We should work with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="718847" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recruit him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="718848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. Let me see anything you have on him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="718850" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could use a man on the inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="718852" id2="17" version="1065353216">A man named Gryffin Remus. He gave me this intel already. Why don't you torture him for anything else he's got?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="718852" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's no one. Just capture him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="718853" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll send my men to pick him up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="718855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, my lord. Forgive me the paltry payment for your service. We have a, uh, standard rate....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="718856" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. I'll transfer our standard finder's fee to your accounts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="718858" id2="17" version="1065353216">The sooner these rebels are all caged, the better.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
