<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>37</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tython/bronze/flesh_raider_factfinding/kalisa_gehnso.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92225" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're understanding more about the Flesh Raiders every day. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92227" id2="17" version="1065353216">I examined the Flesh Raiders' idols. Here are my findings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92228" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting. According to these markings... it's like the Flesh Raiders see us as animals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92230" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll inform Master Wix and the Council at once. With more research, we may finally understand the creatures' motivations and restore peace to Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92236" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Padawan. I sense a great future for you in the order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92237" id2="17" version="1065353216">My Padawan would thank you if she could. Instead, you have my gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92239" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find the Flesh Raiders' idols, and be careful.  I cannot lose another to their jaws.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92246" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force is strong with you, but don't think you're invincible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like you, my Padawan showed great talent. She was strong-willed, thoughtful... such potential.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92250" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations, Jedi. It seems like just the other day you came to Tython to study the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92252" id2="17" version="1065353216">My Padawan would be a Jedi, too, by now. She showed great talent, wisdom... such potential.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92254" id2="17" version="1065353216">She would've served the order well, but the Flesh Raiders extinguished her life. I sensed her final moments--terror, agony... then nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92255" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Flesh Raiders will continue to feed on Jedi until we stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="92255" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must end their attacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92256" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's precisely what I'm striving to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something stronger than hunger must be forcing the Flesh Raiders' hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="92258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would they attack?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92259" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish I knew, but I believe we're close to an answer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="92261" id2="17" version="1065353216">A great loss, I'm sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. I'm taking measures to prevent other Jedi from sharing my Padawan's fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92264" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Flesh Raiders mustn't get away with this senseless slaughter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="92264" id2="17" version="1065353216">This won't stand!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't give in to anger. There are other solutions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92267" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we understand the Flesh Raiders' culture, what motivates their violence, we may yet forge peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92269" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately our emissaries are met with aggression. The latest team fled, but not before witnessing strange idols in the Flesh Raiders' camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do these idols fuel the creatures' rage? What do the Flesh Raiders gain from their worship? To know, someone truly brave must examine the idols.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92272" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Flesh Raiders' motivations will soon be known to the Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="92272" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will investigate the idols.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92273" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would shield you from the Flesh Raiders, but this task is too vital.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92275" id2="17" version="1065353216">How will studying their culture help us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="92275" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the use?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92276" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every insight into Flesh Raider society brings us closer to quieting their hunger. But we need aid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Inspect the idols and record your findings. Stare into the face of what they value most, and ignore no detail, however trivial.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92280" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you're done, give the data to myself or Master Wix, my ally in this cause. He's attending to the Pilgrims in Kalikori village.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="92282" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92283" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've tried and failed. For now I can only study the Flesh Raiders from afar and mourn their victims.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92285" id2="17" version="1065353216">What drives the Flesh Raiders? What feeds their hunger?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
