<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>34</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tython/bronze/flesh_raider_factfinding/meeb_wix.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92286" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're analyzing your Flesh Raider findings. In time, balance may be restored to Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92288" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've studied the Flesh Raiders' idols. Here are my notes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92289" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm, these idols appear to record the Flesh Raiders' hunting patterns. Master Gehnso will be ecstatic.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92291" id2="17" version="1065353216">With more research into your findings, we may finally learn what motivates the Flesh Raiders. Through knowledge, we may calm their appetite.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92297" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll spread the word among the Pilgrims, Padawan. May the Force guide you in your training.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92298" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Pilgrims will learn of your bravery. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92300" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Pilgrims grow nervous. Please examine the idols quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92307" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you sense the Pilgrims' suffering, Padawan? If not, just look at them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92309" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good of you to venture outside the Jedi Temple. Our presence calms these Pilgrims, but it isn't enough. Just look at them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92311" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bloodshot eyes, scarred lekku, exhaustion carved into their faces. They're scared for their lives, and for good reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Flesh Raider attacks are up. Three in the past day. Just last night they dragged a dozen Pilgrims into the darkness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92314" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's our duty to protect the weak, and I think these Pilgrims qualify.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="92314" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must stop their attacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92315" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree completely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't we move these Pilgrims away from Flesh Raiders' territory?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="92317" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Pilgrims should relocate.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92318" id2="17" version="1065353216">The creatures hunt far to feed. Believe me, we've tested their hunger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92320" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Pilgrims deserve a better fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="92320" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's awful.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92321" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are those of us who try to prevent their suffering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="92323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a Pilgrim matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92324" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been studying the Flesh Raiders with Master Gehnso. We hope to elucidate the creatures' culture and learn what drives their hunger.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pilgrim stories claim the Flesh Raiders' twisted appetite stems from the idols they worship. We've confirmed the idols' existence, but questions remain.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92328" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do these idols represent? Do they motivate the Flesh Raiders' cravings? We need answers, and that means examining the idols up close--a dangerous task.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92329" id2="17" version="1065353216">If these idols are the key to understanding the Flesh Raiders, I'll study them at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="92329" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92330" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="92332" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92333" id2="17" version="1065353216">We share similar tastes. But our duty to these Pilgrims demands caution.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mark down every detail about the idols; size, temperature, markings--everything. Look on them, and know the Flesh Raider heart.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92337" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you're finished, I'll take your findings, or you may hand them over to Master Gehnso. You'll find her near the Jedi Temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="92339" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't help. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well. Master Gehnso won't be happy. Neither will these Pilgrims.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="92342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will the suffering never end?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
