<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>55</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/world/imperial/information_warfare/sergeant_bator.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552560" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're putting the screws to those researchers you brought in. Their information will give us just the thing to make the Republic squirm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552561" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're wrong, I'm nothing like you! What we did had value. It was for science!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, science--a convenient bastion for the truly amoral. We'll see how detached you can be when you're under the lens, doctor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552565" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most of the scientists are already in their cells. Armed with their knowledge, the Empire will be better prepared for any aliens we encounter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552566" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope those researchers were worth my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552566" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then it is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552567" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely. On behalf of Imperial Intelligence, you have our gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prove what happened on Belsavis. The Republic citizens will want justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Expose the Republic's deeds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. I'm sure the Diplomatic Service has plans of its own for this information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552570" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're lucky I was bored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552571" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand completely. You must be very busy, so I won't detain you further.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552573" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got to bring in the rest of the scientists. The information's no good without corroboration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552574" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is moving on those researchers. Get out there and recover them before it's too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552575" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look out there--hundreds of aliens in a savage fight for supremacy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552577" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clever of the Republic to use a prison planet as the perfect secret laboratory. Test subjects abound, no witnesses who aren't complicit....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552579" id2="17" version="1065353216">...an elegant experiment, forcing imprisoned aliens to fight each other for dominance. Now they're loose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552580" id2="17" version="1065353216">This experiment doesn't sound like the Republic at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552580" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic did that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which is why they did it here. They had their finest scientists on the job, the best chemical cocktails to ramp up aggression.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552583" id2="17" version="1065353216">What was the point of the experiment?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why make aliens fight?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552584" id2="17" version="1065353216">To learn, of course. Here, they did everything to increase aggression among the aliens, then turned them on each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552586" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're boring me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552587" id2="17" version="1065353216">The scientists studied what each alien could take and what they could dish out, learned the breaking point of each species.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think what the Empire could do with that knowledge--to know which species can be soldiers and which are fit only as slaves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552590" id2="17" version="1065353216">It could help the Empire plan its expansion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552590" id2="17" version="1065353216">The study could be valuable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Intelligence agrees--they want to talk to the scientists involved and uncover everything they know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surely the Republic can't get away with this abomination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552593" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's an atrocity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552594" id2="17" version="1065353216">A lot of Republic citizens will agree with you--that's why Intelligence wants to extract confessions from the research scientists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me where I fit in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Intelligence wants to talk to those scientists--that's where you come in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Normally the Republic scientists are well guarded, but aliens overpowered the guards and took the researchers hostage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552601" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic has yet to negotiate their release, so your team could overpower the aliens and bring the scientists back alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552602" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is negotiating their release, but a Sith Lord could overpower the aliens and recover the scientists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552603" id2="17" version="1065353216">We cannot risk losing this opportunity. I'll retrieve the scientists personally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well, I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552604" id2="17" version="1065353216">You honor us, my lord. The aliens have infested a cave on the edge of the jungle--it's a good place to start.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552606" id2="17" version="1065353216">While the Republic figures out how to react, you could recover the scientists for the Empire. Alive, that is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just let me know where to find these scientists, I'll bring them back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552607" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552608" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is negotiating their release, but a Cipher agent could slip in and capture the scientists before they can act.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552609" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is negotiating their release, but someone like you might slip in and capture the scientists before they can act.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552610" id2="17" version="1065353216">The scientists are too valuable to risk losing them. I'll recover them personally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well, I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552611" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll want to start looking in the caves near the jungle--the aliens use them as a base of sorts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic troops, scientists and aliens? This could go badly wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552613" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seems risky, but all right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552614" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire trusts you to see that it doesn't. Look for the aliens near the jungle caves, they seem to camp there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you've dealt with them, you'll be able to gather up the scientists. These neural-override collars will force them to return here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't presume. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, I understand completely. Forgive me for having bothered you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552621" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can see why the Republic kept this place a secret. Everyone would want to live here.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
