<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>105</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_1/failsafe/chief_hurkwill.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry about us. We'll run when the time comes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009970" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've helped you all I can. Rest is up to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009971" id2="17" version="1065353216">Disable those turrets, reprogram the droids and burn yourself a security passcode. You'll breeze right into the Hutt Embassy--guaranteed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009973" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chief Hurkwill? Shalim Avesta sent us. He says you know a way into the Hutt Embassy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009974" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I'd known a Jedi war hero was coming, I'd have cleaned myself up and made some lunch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009976" id2="17" version="1065353216">A real live Jedi Master--now we're talking! Pardon the stink. Haven't been near a shower in days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009978" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's an honor, Major. Forgive the smell, but I haven't seen a working shower since before the takeover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009980" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're one of the Republic's big shots, eh? Forgive the stench. Showers are scarce out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apologies for the stench. Ever since we left the city, showers have been scarce.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009984" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hutt embassy's locked up tight. Used to have a fancy-pants bureaucrat helping us inside--Representative Ecklin--but he's gone quiet. Probably dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good news is, the Cartel hasn't changed anything at their embassy. Got the same turrets, droids, passcodes I set up for them. Lazy Hutts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1009987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Getting in should be easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009989" id2="17" version="1065353216">When this is all over, we'll have to thank the Hutts for making our job simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009990" id2="17" version="1065353216">They may be stupid, but they're still pretty good at killing folks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Storming enemy territory is much simpler with a well-informed guide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009993" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Simple&quot; is a stretch. Let's go with &quot;not instantly lethal.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009995" id2="17" version="1065353216">If your intel's good, this will be a walk in the park.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009996" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Walk&quot; might be generous, but your survival odds just went up to fifty-fifty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009998" id2="17" version="1065353216">The secret to any good break-in is having an inside man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1009999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never figured I'd be on the wrong side of my own defenses. Wish I'd made them less deadly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why does the Hutt Cartel have an embassy on Makeb--much less one that well-guarded?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is there an embassy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010002" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Business Council built it when the Hutts first came to do business here. Thought it would make the slugs feel appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010004" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you know they haven't set up new procedures and kept them secret?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010004" id2="17" version="1065353216">That seems unlikely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010005" id2="17" version="1065353216">The other great thing about Hutts? They're overconfident. Never expected to be facing the likes of you, either.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010007" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want inside the Hutt Embassy, you'll have to finesse three layers of security. First layer is heavy turrets in the courtyard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010009" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only good thing to come out of these groundquakes is that they exposed the turret power generators. Overload those, and turrets lose their punch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Disable the turret power generators so we don't get torched on the way in. And then?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010011" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt the Hutts left those generators unguarded. How hard will it be to reach them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010011" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll try to stop us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010012" id2="17" version="1065353216">City's under curfew. Streets are crawling with Hutt-loyal Regulators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our mission would be a lot simpler if we could take down the entire power grid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we black out the city?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even if I knew how to cause a blackout, the city's computers need energy--and you need computers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Security layer two is the embassy's main door. Three meters of reinforced durasteel. Even a lightsaber would take hours to cut through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010019" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the door will unlock for a diplomatic passcode. You can generate one by accessing the government building's secure terminal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get inside the government building, slice the secure terminal for a passcode and get out. Next?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems easy enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010021" id2="17" version="1065353216">There have to be Regulators on the street carrying passcodes. We'll be fighting them anyway, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010021" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't we just steal one?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only top officers get into the embassy. You won't find them patrolling the streets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010024" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remember when all you needed to bust open a building was detonite and attitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010024" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is so complicated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010025" id2="17" version="1065353216">The good ol' days. I miss them, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Last but not least are the security droids. Top-of-the-line Arkanian models. Nasty disposition. Shoot intruders on sight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good news is they can be reprogrammed. The droid control station in my old security HQ will do the trick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010030" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010032" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could use some allies. Those droids will do nicely. We'll take it from here, chief.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turning the droids against the Hutts will be poetic justice. You've been most helpful, chief--we're going in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010034" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll get the droids working for us. Smart thinking, chief. We're on our way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010035" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've always wanted my own droid army. Thanks for the tip, old-timer. Let's do this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010036" id2="17" version="1065353216">After jumping through those first two hoops, I'll prefer to crush a droid army the old-fashioned way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010036" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather destroy the droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not saying you couldn't, but probably not before everyone in the embassy got hustled to evac shuttles--and the databanks with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you just volunteered for the job. Have fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why don't you go do that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every Regulator in the city knows my face. Wouldn't get ten meters. You'll make it at least twice that far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hit those objectives, and I guarantee you'll get inside the embassy. Whether you'll find your answers is a different matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010044" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Representative Ecklin's still alive, maybe help him escape? He's a fussbudget, but basically alright. I'll keep a comm channel open when I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think twice before you visit the city. Hutt curfew means unauthorized types get shot on sight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010049" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutt Embassy's all yours. Mind your step in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010052" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won't have to worry about those turrets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010055" id2="17" version="1065353216">That should take care of the security droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010058" id2="17" version="1065353216">That passcode will open the embassy's main doors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048708" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're already analyzing the Project Failsafe plans Representative Ecklin transmitted to us. They're sickening.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toborro the Hutt is masterminding the greatest crime in galactic history. With Veedrig's ark, they'll escape Makeb and leave us all to die. We can't let that happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048711" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Devaronian is more salesman than soldier. If we pressure him, he'll turn against the Hutts and give us the ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1048711" id2="17" version="1065353216">Veedrig might help us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048712" id2="17" version="1065353216">No doubt Veedrig's sticking close to his project until he's paid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048714" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Devaronian promises much. We need to know if this ark can accomplish everything he guarantees.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1048714" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time for a chat with Veedrig.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048715" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every other word in his plans is misspelled, and I'm no expert on engineering jargon, but the basics appear sound.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048717" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we want to stop the Hutts from leaving in their fancy ark, Veedrig's the man to see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1048717" id2="17" version="1065353216">Veedrig is the key.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048718" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calling the ark schematics &quot;fuzzy&quot; would be a compliment. We need the source of this data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048720" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know this Devaronian's type. A thousand credits says he'll switch sides if we point a blaster in his face.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1048720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Veedrig will join us, or else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048721" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't condone threats of violence, but in this case... threaten away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048723" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only way that ark's leaving is with us at the helm and Makeb's people safe inside it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1048723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hijack that ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048724" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there's any justice in the galaxy, we'll get to see the look on Toborro's face as we depart in his starship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048726" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't take the ark for ourselves until we hunt down its construction site. Found any clues yet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1048726" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need a place to start.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lemda was just reviewing that data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048729" id2="17" version="1065353216">I matched the ark construction site's map to topographic readings. The ark's being built at a secret facility inside the Giant's Spear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048731" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a big tourist trap--a mesa with a hollow interior. Too dangerous to colonize, but perfect for hiding an ark's construction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1048732" id2="17" version="1065353216">All we need now is a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048734" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the ark is the Hutts' only escape, they'll have it locked down tight. What security measures will we face?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048735" id2="17" version="1065353216">An unplanned assault could result in irreparable damage to the ark. What's the safest way to secure the ship?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure yet, Master Jedi, but we have probe droids gathering intel right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commandeering a ship that size won't be easy. What objectives do we hit to secure the ark?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048739" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't say yet, Major. We're sending probe droids to survey the area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stealing ships is easy. Getting to them is the tough part. Any clue how many guards they have?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048742" id2="17" version="1065353216">No idea, Captain, but our probe droids are scanning the whole mesa.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048744" id2="17" version="1065353216">With all these groundquakes, we'll be lucky if that place doesn't collapse and take the ark with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1048744" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't say &quot;perfect.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048745" id2="17" version="1065353216">All the more reason to move quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048747" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no way the Hutts could've started a major construction project inside a planetary landmark without attracting attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1048747" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one noticed this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048748" id2="17" version="1065353216">We closed all access to the Giant's Spear out of safety concerns months ago--at Toborro's urging. He duped us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1048750" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contact me when you're at the Giant's Spear. I'll help you plan this attack. It won't be an easy fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049125" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're alive--guess my advice worked, huh? Shalim told me to patch you through right away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049127" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't look at me. I've got a city to evacuate. Good luck.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
