<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>76</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_1/failsafe/embassy_door_lower_level.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010466" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, please! I'm an unarmed civilian: Representative Ecklin, with the Makeb Provisional Authority Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010468" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm the official liaison to the Hutt Cartel. Whatever you need, I'll make sure you get it. Just don't hurt me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010469" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't hurt you--I'm a Jedi. I'm here to free Makeb from the Hutt Cartel's occupation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010469" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to bargain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010470" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been talking to Shalim and Chief Hurkwill. We don't need to be free. We need to survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010472" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know who you are, Representative Ecklin. Chief Hurkwill said you were a friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, you're safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then... you're here on Shalim's orders. I'm sorry he brought the Jedi into this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010475" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Republic Special Forces--Havoc Squad. Shalim Avesta sent me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Relax, I'm a friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010476" id2="17" version="1065353216">That madman's gotten the Republic Army involved? Is he trying to start a war?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Relax, I'm not some trigger-happy burglar. I'm with the Republic--and Shalim Avesta.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take it easy, pal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, for the love of.... Please tell me Shalim hasn't dragged the Republic into this nonsense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010481" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm working with Shalim Avesta. He sent me to get information on the Hutt Cartel's plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010481" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want answers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010482" id2="17" version="1065353216">And he thought the best way to do it was to attack their embassy? Typical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010484" id2="17" version="1065353216">I ought to take your head back to Shalim as a present. You sold out to the Hutts, didn't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010484" id2="17" version="1065353216">You spineless traitor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010485" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am working with them. Shalim doesn't understand the situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like it or not, the Hutts control Makeb now. Our only option is to cooperate--make the best of our new situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Instead, Shalim stirs up trouble. He doesn't realize how much worse the Hutts could make things for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your emotions are blinding you to the truth. The Hutts are drilling into Makeb's core. They've destabilized the entire planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm down. Listen to reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now you're the emotional one. A few groundquakes, and suddenly it's the end of the world?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010493" id2="17" version="1065353216">No matter what you offer, the Hutts will always take more. Their deep-core drilling has destabilized the entire planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Appeasement is not an option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, don't be drawn in by Shalim's wild speculation. There's no evidence to support it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010496" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts are bullies. Push them down, and they'll back off. If not, they'll keep drilling into Makeb until the planet cracks in half.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fighting is the only way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010497" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Cracks in half&quot;? Is that a technical term?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010499" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you think the Hutts respect you for rolling over, guess again. While you negotiate, the Cartel's mining right through Makeb's core.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me tell you about Hutts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010500" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only reason we're alive to debate that insane rumor is because of my negotiations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010502" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts aren't here to rule Makeb. They're here to destroy it. Their deep drilling has destabilized the planetary core.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010502" id2="17" version="1065353216">The planet is falling apart!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would they do that? Makeb is an investment for them. If they destroy the planet, they lose their assets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010505" id2="17" version="1065353216">Besides, most of the Hutts are here on the surface. If the planet explodes, they go with it. It's illogical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010506" id2="17" version="1065353216">While you're busy sucking up to the Hutts, they're destabilizing the entire planet with deep-core drilling. Makeb is falling apart, thanks to you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010506" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a complete idiot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010507" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's exactly the kind of ridiculousness I'm talking about. Is that what Shalim tells his recruits?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010509" id2="17" version="1065353216">It doesn't even make sense. The Hutts are here on the planet, too. If Makeb is destroyed, they die with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Geological readings show this planet is coming apart. But we think the Hutts have a &quot;Project Failsafe&quot; to deal with the situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010510" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have proof.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knowing Shalim, he'll risk anything to find it. Well, I'll save some lives and help quash this rumor for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010513" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts have something called &quot;Project Failsafe,&quot; but they'll push this planet to the brink of destruction before using it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010513" id2="17" version="1065353216">You underestimate Hutt greed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say I believed you. Wouldn't I want definite proof before risking my life to stop them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen closely: The planet is breaking apart, but the Hutts have a &quot;Project Failsafe.&quot; You're going to help me find it. Understand?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop wasting my time!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010517" id2="17" version="1065353216">You make a compelling and persuasive argument.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010519" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this &quot;Project Failsafe&quot; exists, there must be some record of it in the embassy's archives. I'll get you access to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010521" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the Hutts are on high alert. They've already summoned reinforcements. You'll have to deal with them. I'll meet you in the archive room.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just do your part, and leave the guards to me. I don't want you getting hurt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay out of sight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010523" id2="17" version="1065353216">The guards won't target me. That's why I prefer to travel separately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010525" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're taking a great risk. You must care deeply about Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for helping.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010526" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do. Enough to know when to fight and when to cooperate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010528" id2="17" version="1065353216">The guards aren't a problem for me. But you won't stand a chance if they catch you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch yourself in here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010529" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've worked at this embassy for years. I know my way around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010531" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was hoping you'd say there's a secret passage that'll take us right where we need to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing's ever easy, is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any passage wide enough for the Hutts wouldn't be very secret.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010534" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a Hutt conspirator. I'm not letting you out of my sight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010534" id2="17" version="1065353216">No way. You stay with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010535" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're marked for death. I'm not. If I die because I'm standing next to you when the shooting starts, you can't access the archives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010537" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if Shalim's right, Makeb will be truly doomed. I don't think you want that on your conscience.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010539" id2="17" version="1065353216">You worry about those reinforcements. I'll make sure we can access the Hutt archives. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1010540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Betray us, and you're dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't even think about running back to the Hutts. There's no place in this galaxy where I can't get you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember who I am. If you warn the Hutts, I will find you. No one can hide from the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010544" id2="17" version="1065353216">You saw what I did to these mercenaries. Warn the Hutts, and I'll do the same to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010545" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got contacts and informants in every corner of the galaxy. Double-cross me, and I'll hunt you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1010546" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not like Shalim. I don't fight losing battles. See you at the archives.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
