<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>9</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_1/failsafe/grevin_holorecording.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Citizens of Makeb: It's my pleasure to share an exciting opportunity offered by the generous Toborro the Hutt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014853" id2="17" version="1065353216">As repayment for any inconveniences brought about during this time of transition, all citizens are offered a percentage of profits from Toborro's mining operations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014855" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be contacted shortly on how to receive your credits. Any non-compliance with Cartel directives will forfeit your share.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Citizens of Makeb: Please disregard any rumors regarding the recent ground tremors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be fooled by lies. These tremors are the result of small, natural changes in Makeb's lunar cycle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone trying to induce panic by suggesting a connection between ground tremors and everyday mining operations should be reported to your closest Cartel representative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Citizens of Makeb, this is Vice Commandant Grevin of the Regulators with an important message from the Hutt Cartel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Compliance with these directives is mandatory, for the safety of everyone. Any non-compliance should be reported to your closest representative. Rewards are offered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049122" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any directives issued by the Hutts or their representatives are only designed to protect you during this time of transition.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
