<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>8</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/heroic_weekly/mission_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175925" id2="17" version="1065353216">B-6NX has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gorinth Canyon sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, B-6NX may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175926" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Larbec has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gorinth Canyon sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Lieutenant Larbec may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Neddis has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gorinth Canyon sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Captain Neddis may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175928" id2="17" version="1065353216">By order of Lysennius Melchiro, Imperial Governor of Balmorra. Offworld sympathizers from crack Republic commando groups have illegally joined the Balmorran resistance in opposition of Imperial domination. 

Rodian, Chagrian and Kel Dor mercenary forces, decorated Republic war heroes, all are well coordinated and have taken up a position near the AA guns outside of the Balmorran Arms Factory. Their snipers have been responsible for 304 Imperial casualties and the destruction of over fifty Imperial aircraft to date. 

Reward offered for anyone who will crush the alien rebels and liberate the AA guns.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Revis has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Farnel Research Facility sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Doctor Revis may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176654" id2="17" version="1065353216">By order of Darth Lachris, revered governor of Imperial Balmorra, champion of the siege of Coruscant. In spite of the Empire's glorious victory at Balmorran Arms, the battle has not been won.

The Republic's top tactician, field commander and gunner have regrouped the scattered resistance forces and are preparing a fresh assault on Imperial Balmorra!

The Jedi Noth Armin, Sergeant Tove Weylan and the mercenary Korin Norrus have been coordinating strikes against Imperial ships and have so far brought down three Imperial squadrons.

Eliminate them and show the resistance the futility of their cause. The wealth and gratitude of your Empire will be at your disposal.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176655" id2="17" version="1065353216">By order of Darth Lachris, revered governor of Imperial Balmorra, champion of the siege of Coruscant. Due to the previous governor's incompetence, the resistance has managed to establish a factory for the production of chemical weapons near the toxic waste pools.

They are using the toxic waste to produce bombs to poison Imperial forces. The bombs are guarded by the resistance's top marksmen. Previous attempts to take back the factory and dismantle the bombs resulted in the annihilation of two crack commando teams.

Dismantle the bombs. Eliminate the resistance. The wealth and gratitude of your Empire will be at your disposal.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Piloc has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Farnel Research Facility sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Lieutenant may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
