<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>110</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tatooine/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Want to hear something hilarious? I'm almost homesick for Korriban.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104910" id2="17" version="1065353216">The heat does not trouble me, but keep cool on this world, little Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like the Imps did a number on this place. Come on--let's get done before your skin starts peeling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104912" id2="17" version="1065353216">People look nervous with all the Imperials here. That's not a good sign. Maybe we should keep a low profile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104915" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is where the scum of the galaxy congregate. Not sure I see the appeal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104916" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have an excellent sabacc face. That was a joke. I hate sabacc.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104917" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sleazy little cantina. If I had to live on a planet like this, I'd be drinking here, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104918" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never been so happy to wander into a scuzzy dive. Anything is better than that heat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104921" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you say we buy a droid to clean up the ship?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104922" id2="17" version="1065353216">More worthless junk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104923" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you figure? Scrap, or is there something decent around here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think someone brought that giant chunk of junk, or the whole market sprung up around a crashed ship?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104927" id2="17" version="1065353216">This reminds me of a cave I found on Corrida. Almost died there. Great, now I'm having flashbacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104928" id2="17" version="1065353216">All the power has passed from this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104929" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sand People are freaks, but I kind of like them. Mean, nasty, tribal... little taste of home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, somebody's living out here. Maybe we should just leave them be, it's not like people are very friendly around here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104933" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I ever tell you I have a fear of dying in the belly of a beast?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104934" id2="17" version="1065353216">These monsters are nothing but dumb prey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah... wait a minute. Let's just take this in for a second.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow, that's gorgeous. Who'd have thought a hole in the ground could be so... majestic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to be out of the sun. But wait for my eyes to adjust, will ya?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104940" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they had this technology on Korriban, perhaps it wouldn't have taken so long to awaken me. Perhaps I wouldn't be your slave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104941" id2="17" version="1065353216">Little piece of Dromund Kaas, smack in the middle of the desert. Just in case you get homesick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quite a setup the Imperial Reclamation Service has got out here. I wonder what they're hoping to dig up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104945" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is either a mirage or a trap set by a nasty underwater monster. Or both.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104946" id2="17" version="1065353216">Water in the desert. A strange sight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104947" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mark it on the map. Next time the speeders break down, we're walking back here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104948" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh! Water! Can we take a break? Please?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104951" id2="17" version="1065353216">As if endless sand wasn't bad enough--here's sand with teeth!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104952" id2="17" version="1065353216">The planet's grinning maw. I wonder how long you'd fall until I could no longer hear your screams.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104953" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a real sarlacc. They say those things take forever to eat you--you can live in its stomach while it scars you up. Kind of poetic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104954" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ack! What is that! It's like a big... mouth, maybe? I can't even tell. Let's give it a wide... let's just stay away from it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104957" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we don't get out of the sun soon, I'm gonna turn purple.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104958" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could destroy this place and no one would notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mess up badly enough, bet your bosses would assign you right here. Wonder what these guys did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104960" id2="17" version="1065353216">That shade looks so good right now. What kind of sadist puts a planet next to two suns?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104963" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen Czerka's work on other worlds. Never pleasant.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104964" id2="17" version="1065353216">What delicious new horrors are they digging up here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104965" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't want to sound like a wuss, but we really don't have to go down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ever considered that Czerka abandoned this place for a reason? Maybe we shouldn't be poking around.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104971" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jawa market = selling controlled droids? // T7 = uncomfortable!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Somebody needs to tell the Jawas that tooling around in a giant vehicle doesn't help them look any bigger. Still, it's a nice ride.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104973" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jawas know desert, repairs, gossip. Good to listen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104974" id2="17" version="1065353216">These little fellas must be professional junk dealers. Considering the size of that crawler, business must be good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pretty impressive for such little guys. I wonder how they keep that old thing running.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gamorrean life-forms detected // Hostiles moving to intercept</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Typical Czerka mentality. Pull out on a day's notice and leave a nice big base for the bad guys to move into.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104980" id2="17" version="1065353216">To whatever world they come, Czerka leave mark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104981" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a nice little underground hideout Czerka left behind. We should keep it for ourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104982" id2="17" version="1065353216">No telling how long ago Czerka dug this place out. Could be anything in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104985" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dreviad Outpost = safe from Sand People attacks</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104986" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll never understand Tatooine settlers. &quot;We live in a giant wasteland. Let's build everything really far apart!&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. Hot sun, beasts to fight... could stay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104988" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm all for wide-open spaces, but why would anybody want to live out in the middle of a desert? A man's gotta have some shade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would anyone live in a place like this? It's a wasteland.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Multiple Geonosian life-forms detected // Location = must be main base</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Geonosians are dug in deep here. Gonna be messy rooting them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soft, Herald. Eyes on us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104995" id2="17" version="1065353216">If these bug-fellas from Geonosis weren't making trouble for everyone, I'd say let them have Tatooine. I mean, seriously.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like the Geonosians' HQ. They must have a huge operation out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="104999" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 external temperature dropping = good for servomotors</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoever built this must hate sunlight. Then again, it is Tatooine....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="105001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is home of soft things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Check out the size of this place. These farmers live better than they let on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not the coziest house I've been in, but it beats standing out in the sun.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="105006" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = relieved to be inside // Tatooine sand = hard on circuits</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have to hand it to the SIS. Nobody does  &quot;nondescript&quot; quite like them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="105008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is too small here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Somehow, I expected a bit more from a spy's house.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105010" id2="17" version="1065353216">So the SIS is taking an interest in this dustball, too? What are the odds.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="105013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Twin Suns gang = running illegal dig site // Jedi + T7 = put them out of business!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105014" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure whatever's happening here is perfectly legal. Let's ask to see their permits.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="105015" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is to mine on Tatooine?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quite an operation these Twin Suns got going. Better than that scum deserves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105017" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't think there was anything worth mining here anymore....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="105020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remains of krayt dragon = extremely large // T7 = relieved creature deactivated</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105021" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, Tatooine. You never run out of ways to let me know I should be dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="105022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Elder krayt dragon. Noble predator, devours all lesser things. Has earned its sleep.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Know what these bones tell me? If you stay here long enough, Tatooine will kill you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoa. That must be a krayt dragon--or what's left of one, at least.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="105027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi + T7 = stop for a rest? // Camp = appears safe</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105028" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know why more people don't live here. Once you get past the endless wastes and blistering heat--oh, and things trying to kill you--it's really nice.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="105029" id2="17" version="1065353216">See tracks? Has been many Sand People here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105030" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place gets hit by Sand People all the time. These locals are blasted stubborn to stay and fight it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105031" id2="17" version="1065353216">These people must be insane to live out here. They're nothing but easy targets.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="105034" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = detecting unusual energy readings + unknown organics</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dear Czerka, please stop discovering horrible ancient things. Love, Kira.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="105036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka places. Always secrets hidden.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems like every Czerka place we visit has a creep factor of ten. Must be in their corporate philosophy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka was definitely up to a lot more than just mining out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Briefing: Records indicate Tatooine's average daily temperature is well above tolerable organic levels. My sympathies, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insight: At least now we know where to find the local undesirables.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023179" id2="17" version="1065353216">Judgment: Buying droid parts here would be like acquiring replacement organs from a butcher.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023182" id2="17" version="1065353216">Presentation: This appears to be a place of spiritual significance to the organic natives... pathetic savages.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rumination: One must admire Tatooine's wildlife. These creatures are master liquidators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023188" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis: It appears your fellow Imperials got homesick, master. This architecture is quite homey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023191" id2="17" version="1065353216">Advice: You may wish to stop and splash a bit of water on yourself, master. You're looking a little peaked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023194" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dismissal: The mighty Sarlacc... possibly the least-efficient predator in galactic history.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023197" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hypothesis: I may require replacement photoreceptors after we leave this world. These ambient light levels are harsh indeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023200" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contemplation: What is it about organics and their need to dig holes in sand?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Announcement: These Jawas are droid scavengers, master. I will refrain from deleting them unless you say otherwise. Please... say otherwise?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023446" id2="17" version="1065353216">Estimation: Scanners indicate multiple troublemakers infesting this facility. There will be many deletions. Hooray!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023449" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observation: This planet's inhabitants appear to require inordinate amounts of personal space.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revelation: Geonosians are especially satisfying to delete, master. Their carapaces make the most interesting sound when broken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023455" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis: So this is how the natives spend their credits. Not exactly Nar Shaddaa, is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023458" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assessment: Apparently the Republic SIS works under severe budgetary restraints.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023461" id2="17" version="1065353216">Encouragement: These troublemakers appear to enjoy digging holes in the sand--let's bury them in one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contemplation: Krayt dragon bones, master--another reminder that no organic lives forever. Droids, however....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Judgment: These natives take stubbornness to unusual extremes. Perhaps the heat has broken them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alert: I am receiving highly unusual and erratic sensor data. Weapons armed.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
