<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>232</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/world/imperial/riot_on_belsavis/lord_medechas.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541326" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear the Dread Masters are on the loose once more. Well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541327" id2="17" version="1065353216">The landing zone site remains secure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541328" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was a rare occasion. We had half their numbers and still handed them their heads!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541330" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ruger must have been furious. I can only imagine the thrill of snuffing out his life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541331" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll only be thrilled when this prison is wiped clean of the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541331" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was just the beginning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you won't have to wait long. With Ruger out of the picture, our landing zone's untouchable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541334" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Thrilling&quot; doesn't begin to describe what it felt like to stick that lawman.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541334" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't know the half of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541335" id2="17" version="1065353216">And as Ruger's screams fade, we know our landing zone won't be threatened again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ruger's dead. I save my excitement for payday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just another job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541338" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've more than earned it. With Ruger gone, no one can threaten our landing zone. Not even the incompetent warden.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ruger was one more casualty of our war with the Republic. Nothing more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Actually, I felt nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541341" id2="17" version="1065353216">I imagine your detachment served you well against Ruger. And with him gone, our landing zone's finally secure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541343" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no thrill in murder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541344" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ruger's history. Now what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541345" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will fortify our landing zone and feed the riot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541347" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear you spared Ruger. At least you managed to squeeze a ransom out of the poor warden. He sent this payment to you, with well wishes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541348" id2="17" version="1065353216">The warden wasn't particularly friendly when we parted ways.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well wishes? I doubt that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541349" id2="17" version="1065353216">You ruined his prize lawman, turned his prison into a circus. I'm surprised he didn't send you a grenade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541351" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trust you didn't skim any off the top.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541351" id2="17" version="1065353216">This better be everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541352" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't dream of denying you your spoils. Not when you kicked Ruger off Belsavis for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ruger didn't need to die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541355" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll never understand that argument. But at least we can agree that with Ruger gone, our landing zone's finally secure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541357" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you'll excuse me, duty calls. I must re-establish contact with Commander Calum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541367" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'll be glad to hear how you handled the riots--and Ellis Ruger. You've served the Empire well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541369" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Medechas. Come in, Lord Medechas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541371" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am here, Commander Calum. What is your will?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ellis Ruger was blocking our signal. Your men re-established contact once he fell, but I've heard nothing from our other operations groups.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541377" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Vandorn must be reached. Our mission is still in jeopardy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541378" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave this mission to me. Lord Medechas will guard the rear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541378" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find Captain Vandorn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541379" id2="17" version="1065353216">I give the orders. But yes--you are best suited to meet the lost operations group.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541381" id2="17" version="1065353216">Secure the landing zone, Lord Medechas. And stay in constant contact. Commander Calum out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541382" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've defeated Ruger, the Republic's dealing with the riot. What's left?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541382" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there a new threat?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541383" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic may be the least of our worries in this prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541385" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Medechas is right. That's why he'll defend the landing zone against further Republic interference. You will perform the rendezvous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541386" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't fret so much, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541387" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters will help us defeat the Republic. I'll stop worrying when they're free of Belsavis's chains.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541389" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Medechas--secure the landing zone. You--rendezvous with our lost operations group. Do not delay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Vandorn was last seen in the high security wing. Find his camp, but be wary. The Republic is conducting strange experiments with the inmates there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541403" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't delay. We can't give Ruger a chance to detect our attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541404" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ruger is finally vulnerable. If you're ready, we can end his campaign and secure this landing zone for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541405" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me where this lawman is, and our problems are over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541405" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ruger and his men are in a guard station. He believes it's more secure than the main intake building.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541408" id2="17" version="1065353216">How much resistance is Ruger packing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541408" id2="17" version="1065353216">What defenses are we facing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541409" id2="17" version="1065353216">He lacks his Crisis Response Unit, but the guard station will be full of veteran soldiers. Expect the worst.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541411" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry before Ruger catches on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541412" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use the security key to drop their shields. My teams will cut off Ruger's backup. No one gets in, no one gets out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541414" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll give you time to work. Just make sure Ruger doesn't escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541415" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been waiting to get my hands on Ellis Ruger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541415" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'll get what's coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541416" id2="17" version="1065353216">His men know what to do in battle. Any shock we cause will wear off quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541418" id2="17" version="1065353216">A solid plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prepare yourself. Just because Ruger hasn't risked himself before doesn't mean he's easy prey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541421" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is his stronghold. Bring everything you have, and every ally you trust. We will get no second chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541422" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happens when Ruger and his men are captured or dead?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541422" id2="17" version="1065353216">And once it's over?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then it's done. The warden will have only stragglers to enforce his will. Our shuttles will be free to fly out anyone we desire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541425" id2="17" version="1065353216">But let's not speculate. Go to the guard station and strike at Ruger. We will be behind you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541428" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's done. I have the key to the security fields.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541429" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must strike quickly, before word of Gholan's death spreads.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541431" id2="17" version="1065353216">Secure Gholan's key, and Ellis Ruger will be exposed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541432" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time someone ends Ruger's career. We've found a way to strike at him directly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541434" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only things keeping us from his throat are the force fields guarding his base. Luckily, a mad Devaronian prisoner--Gholan--has the key.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gholan will surrender the key. He has no choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541435" id2="17" version="1065353216">So we take it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541436" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Devaronian may see things differently.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541438" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Devaronian just got out of prison. There must be a hundred things he'd take in trade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surely he'd take a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541439" id2="17" version="1065353216">We offered him a shuttle off-planet, weapons, aged Corellian brandy, even female companionship. Gholan turned everything down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541441" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't tell me Ruger hid it under a rock outside his base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541441" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did Gholan get the key?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541442" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know Gholan's methods. Only that he stole the key, and Ruger doesn't have a clue it's missing. Sadly, Gholan's less than cooperative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541444" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can get you your key... and the hand holding it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gholan's as good as dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541445" id2="17" version="1065353216">I almost pity the poor Devaronian. But you should know--Gholan is not your average prisoner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541447" id2="17" version="1065353216">He knows the key's valuable. Plus he's trained in the Force, and highly violent. The Republic tried executing him four times.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541449" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's when they shipped him to Belsavis. Now Gholan thinks he can't die. He's refusing to hand over the key to Ruger's guard station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541450" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will study his power in action as I kill him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting, but he will die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541451" id2="17" version="1065353216">What you do or learn is none of my affair. The key is what matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541453" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Gholan may not fear death, but he'll soon beg for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541453" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make him die painfully.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Save your torments for Ruger. This mission simply demands a quick kill and the key in our hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541456" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic may have failed to kill Gholan, but I know tricks they don't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541456" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll quiet him for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541457" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've proved resourceful. Unfortunately, so has he.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541459" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like killing indestructible people. It's worth the wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541459" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can finish him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541460" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it's a challenge you want, you could do worse than this Devaronian.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe Gholan will listen to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541463" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can try talking to him, but he's more the rip-your-arms-off type. Be ready when you approach.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where can I find him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541466" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gholan roams near the resettlement camps, in the open areas where wise inmates leave him alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make your way there. The longer we delay, the more likely Ruger will change the lock frequency on the security fields.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541471" id2="17" version="1065353216">There was only enough power to thaw the best prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541473" id2="17" version="1065353216">We released the psychopaths. They'll show those rioters how to really fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541474" id2="17" version="1065353216">I unleashed the worst murderers I could find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541475" id2="17" version="1065353216">The convicts were violent before. With psychopaths at the helm, there's no telling what crimes they'll commit. Ruger will not be pleased.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541476" id2="17" version="1065353216">We unleashed the agitators. They'll whip this riot into shape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541477" id2="17" version="1065353216">I freed the agitators. They'll give these prisoners a purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541478" id2="17" version="1065353216">What those convicts lack in brutality they make up for in wits. And they've already organized a large-scale riot. Ruger will not be pleased.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541479" id2="17" version="1065353216">He called to threaten me. He seemed unafraid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541479" id2="17" version="1065353216">I spoke with Ruger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ruger's tamed prisons before, even restored order to Coruscant's depths. It's time we end his career.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541482" id2="17" version="1065353216">That lawman doesn't scare me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still, you shouldn't ignore him. Ruger's tamed the most violent, overcrowded prisons in the galaxy. And it's time we end his career.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541485" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can worry about his mood swings. I won't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541485" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care for his feelings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541486" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can use his temper to our advantage. Infuriate Ruger, and he's bound to fall. But first we must remove his defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thaw out the most sadistic monsters you can. Fear is our ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to you, the inmates have turned from whipped dogs into predators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still, we need more convicts on our side. Turn this mob into an army, and the Republic will be permanently occupied.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541493" id2="17" version="1065353216">An army begins with generals. We must provide the prisoners with the leadership they require.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541494" id2="17" version="1065353216">There must be plenty of leadership material locked up here. Break them out, and put them to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recruit prisoners to lead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541495" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541497" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no way I'm commanding this herd of mynocks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't look at me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541498" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would waste our time and your talent. Leaders already exist. We simply must wake them up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541500" id2="17" version="1065353216">Out with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541501" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a carbonite storage facility in the intake yards, full of frozen convicts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some were rebellion leaders. Others simply murdered every guard they found. We need both persuasions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541504" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this is so simple, why isn't it done already?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why does this sound too easy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541505" id2="17" version="1065353216">We face a thinking opponent. I've proceeded as necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541506" id2="17" version="1065353216">Releasing them into the general population should prove entertaining.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541506" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds sadistic. I like it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Splendid. Though the unfreezing process won't be simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541508" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the revolutionary type. I've bagged a few.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541508" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can see where this goes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541509" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose previous experience is a plus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't we train the prisoners ourselves? You've already armed them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do we need these people?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541511" id2="17" version="1065353216">These prisoners are celebrities down here. They command loyalty and respect. Let them lead the riot while we keep this landing zone open.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541512" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds fast and easy. Leave their rescue to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541512" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll thaw them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. I've taken measures to maximize the benefits of this operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make it worth my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541515" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be provided for. However, if my plan works, you may encounter some extra defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prisoner--what of your mission into the carbon gallery?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541519" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Crisis Response Unit ambushed us! I got away. Only me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. Ruger took the bait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now you can free the frozen prisoners and wipe out the Crisis Response Unit, all at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are these guards, exactly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541524" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Crisis Response Unit?</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="541525" id2="17" version="1065353216">They train for everything--hostages, riots, Sith opponents. They slaughtered us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another word, inmate, and I'll throw you back in prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ruger's men are dangerous, but don't let it give you pause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your trap just made my job more dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541531" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've complicated things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541532" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the payoff will be considerable. Without his top men, Ruger must scramble to defend his station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I will go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroy the guards, and defrost the prisoners. They'll turn this riot into an organized army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'll have safe passage to extract the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541540" id2="17" version="1065353216">The warden droids are no more. I hope the rioters took note.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have no fear. Thousands of prisoners already move against the droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541543" id2="17" version="1065353216">More devotees follow your footsteps every minute. Many have died in the process, but that's normal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dismantling those droids wasn't the easiest thing I've ever done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541544" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you appreciate it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541545" id2="17" version="1065353216">I respect the effort involved. Each warden droid has the strength of dozens of prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541547" id2="17" version="1065353216">All in a day's work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I have a powerful ally indeed. The warden droids were meant to be the equal of twenty prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Minimum effort, maximum results, I see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let them kill each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541551" id2="17" version="1065353216">They will occupy the guards' attention with little more energy on our part. A fine move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541553" id2="17" version="1065353216">The warden droids are easy to spot. Look for clouds of tear gas and writhing prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541558" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, my lord. I assumed Commander Calum sent you to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541560" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, agent. I take it Commander Calum sent you to lend us your talents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunter... welcome. I take it Commander Calum conscripted your services.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, welcome. I knew Commander Calum would send assistance once we lost contact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541566" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Lord Medechas, leader of Operations Group Five. We started this riot by arming prisoners and pointing them at their Republic captors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541568" id2="17" version="1065353216">But our primary goal is to extract certain inmates held deep within the prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Calum said they were Sith Lords.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dread Masters, if I recall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541570" id2="17" version="1065353216">Correct. The Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541572" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the status of this riot?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541572" id2="17" version="1065353216">How has the fighting been?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541573" id2="17" version="1065353216">The violence is coming to a boil. But our primary orders are to free several Sith Lords known as the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541575" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we free them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541576" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's complicated. The Sith we're after are known as the Dread Masters. They're held somewhere in Belsavis's most secure wing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541578" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can reach out through the Force and pierce their enemies with terror. Whole armadas surrender to them without firing a shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541580" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic claimed the Dread Masters were killed in the last war. Returning them to the field would be a crowning achievement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why haven't you broken them out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541581" id2="17" version="1065353216">So go get them already.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541582" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic evaded our forces and took the Dread Masters into the Deep Prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have a fix on the Dread Masters' location?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where are they now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541585" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic moved them into the Deep Prison. We've heard nothing since.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds worthy of my efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Free the Dread Masters and you'll find much to your advantage. Unfortunately, the Republic's moved them to the Deep Prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meanwhile, the warden brought in a hardheaded offworld enforcer, Ellis Ruger. He's here to close our exit corridor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541592" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Republic isn't stopped, they'll retake this landing zone. Without an exit, our prison break will fail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't give an inch of ground to the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we hold the landing zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541594" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're trying, but the prison guards aren't helping matters. They're hiding behind force fields, and they've just deployed mechanical peacekeepers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541596" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've held off army units. Prison guards will be like wading through dung.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541596" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fear no soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just the attitude we need to break them. They're cowering behind force fields, sending droids to do their dirty work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541599" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have prisoners rioting all over. Can the Republic truly retake this area?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541599" id2="17" version="1065353216">But aren't you winning?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541600" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have more than lawmen to contend with. The Republic have built new machines to cower behind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541602" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Warden droids have enough firepower to incapacitate a small army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541604" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rioters are losing hope, but we can reignite their rage. Destroy enough droids and the convicts will smell blood. They'll practically defend our landing zone for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541605" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the convicts witness my strength, they'll throw themselves before every droid left standing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541605" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will set an example.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Crush the warden droids beneath the might of the Force. Inspire the rioters' confidence, and they'll gladly fight our enemy for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541607" id2="17" version="1065353216">If a few broken droids will spark the convicts' fury, I'll set this riot ablaze.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541607" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will fuel their anger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impress the rioters with your power, and the droids' weakness. Then they'll fight our enemy for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stirring up a riot is dangerous business--and risk demands hazard pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541609" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it, but not for free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope the convicts learn from your strength and not your mercenary attitude. I could hardly afford to pay them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Defeat enough warden droids to inspire the prisoners' confidence. Then they'll fight our enemy for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Crowds are so easily manipulated. Once I dispatch the droids, the prisoners will run to follow suit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541613" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can incite their movement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like nerf to the slaughter. Simply defeat enough warden droids to inspire the rioters' confidence. Then they'll fight our enemy for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541615" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm obligated to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541616" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's more to this fight than duty. Wreck the warden droids, make it look easy and the rioters will follow your lead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541618" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place is anarchy as it is. You'll do fine without me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="541618" id2="17" version="1065353216">You handle it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541619" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we must.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="541621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing to do? I suppose you could hunt down a few guards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="763682" id2="17" version="1065353216">It won't be my top priority.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
