<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>53</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tatooine/bronze/republic/reap_the_whirlwind/jundo_martik.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615479" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Using his brilliant eye for talent, Mayor Martik enlisted the aid of the Republic to keep Tatooine's jobs on Tatooine!&quot; Let me get that down....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615480" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Skillfully taming the fringe of the underworld, Mayor Martik enlisted the aid of a famous space captain to secure your jobs!&quot; I'll jot that down....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615483" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've already told the townsfolk that the mine is back in our hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615485" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you've made sure that's true?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="615486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those scum you hired tried to steal your ore and frame me for it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615486" id2="17" version="1065353216">No thanks to those mercs.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615487" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm... I... I don't know what to say. I'm really not used to dealing with such people....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615489" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assure you I will tell every other town on Tatooine not to work with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615491" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if I have any further problems, I'll go straight to the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615493" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if I have any further problems, I'll be sure to look for help from, ah, good citizens like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615495" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your mine is safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, thank goodness! I don't know what I would have done if this had gone public.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615498" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're gonna pay me....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. With the mine back in our hands, we should have no trouble making back anything we've lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615501" id2="17" version="1065353216">The good citizens of Tatooine thank you for your service.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooh. That sounds nice. I should remember that one....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615506" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd appreciate if you hurry. I want that mine cleared out before anyone starts blaming me for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, you just figure out a way that this won't all fall back on me! This is an election year!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615511" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry. Things have been a little tense, but nothing that should stop our friends in the Republic from enjoying their stay.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615513" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, Master Jedi. I didn't mean for you to see that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615515" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, sir. I should have taken that call in my office.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry. That wasn't exactly meant for public ears.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615519" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Twin Suns pirates have been harassing us since the day I became mayor. And now they want to take our mine--ninety percent of this town works that mine!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="615520" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't stand by while criminals drive your people from their jobs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I help?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything they say about your order is true!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="615523" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Twin Suns shouldn't profit at the expense of people's dignity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615523" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's terrible.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you'll help us, Master Jedi? Thank you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="615526" id2="17" version="1065353216">These criminals need to learn we're bringing law and order to Tatooine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615526" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need help?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, if you can do that, we'll welcome the Republic, let me tell you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="615529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah? Does it bring in enough to be worth the Twin Suns' attention?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it valuable?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615530" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're an intergalactic syndicate. This is pocket change for them. But it's our whole livelihood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615532" id2="17" version="1065353216">How are you dealing with it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615533" id2="17" version="1065353216">It happens.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, it may not seem like much, but we've made something of this wasteland! And now those gangsters want to steal it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615536" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hired a group of mercenaries to drive off the Twin Suns, but they've had no luck so far. Stopped reporting back a few days ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615538" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can finish what those mercs couldn't, this town would be in your debt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="615539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are these guys? Are they going to need rescuing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about these mercs.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615540" id2="17" version="1065353216">They failed to deliver, we don't owe them anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615542" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have my word.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615543" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll let our citizens know you're on it!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615545" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll let our citizens know that the Jedi are personally involving themselves in our problems!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615547" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll let our citizens know the Republic has taken a personal interest in our problems.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615549" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll let our citizens know that the Twin Suns have met their match.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just go to the mine and drive off the gangsters there. Put the scare on them, so they never come back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615553" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if there's any ore they haven't already sold off, I'd appreciate it if you could bring it back here for distribution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615555" id2="17" version="1065353216">Learn to fight. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615556" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hadn't thought of it that way.... Oh, this is not going to be good for my poll numbers.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615558" id2="17" version="1065353216">A higher standard of life on Tatooine! That's what my administration stands for....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
