<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>58</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/bronze/hit_em_where_they_live/scout.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296762" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you can't bring my brother back, but I appreciate what you did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those snipers won't be a problem anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296766" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're dead? I... I can't believe it. I've been dreaming of this moment ever since they killed my brother.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Couldn't think about anything else. Barely ate. Barely slept. Thought I'd feel better after they were dead. But I just feel... numb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296769" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killing those snipers won't bring your brother back. You know that now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296769" id2="17" version="1065353216">You still miss your brother.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296770" id2="17" version="1065353216">The snipers had to be stopped. But you will not find comfort in their deaths.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296770" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revenge rarely brings peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296771" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not easy being a soldier. Sometimes all the bloodshed just leaves you empty inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296771" id2="17" version="1065353216">War will do that to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, maybe. My brother was always there for me. It's going to be strange carrying on without him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296774" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're just looking for some closure. Kick a few credits my way, and it'll buy you some peace of mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296774" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pay me and you'll feel better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296775" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm worried about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296776" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just need some time. I'll be okay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296778" id2="17" version="1065353216">They didn't go out peacefully. I made sure they paid in full for what they did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296778" id2="17" version="1065353216">They suffered, if that helps.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure that makes me feel any better. Doesn't make me feel worse, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296781" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here, a token of my appreciation. It's not much, but my brother would want you to have it. I want you to have it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296783" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe tonight I'll finally be able to sleep without seeing his face every time I close my eyes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those snipers killed my brother. Somebody has to make them pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey! You gotta help me. Seriously. No one believes me. They think I'm crazy. But I know what I saw!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296793" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gotta act fast, though. Won't be there for long. Poof. Gone. Vanished. Just like last time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296794" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't help you if you freak out. Get a grip on yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296794" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey! Hold it together!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296795" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're rambling. Take a moment to collect your thoughts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm yourself and start over.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay. Right. Sorry. Need to get some sleep. I've been out scouting for three straight days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296798" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think the stress of combat got to be a little too much for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like shell shock.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296799" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not stress. I just need sleep. I've been out scouting the area for three days straight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lay off the spice, kid. That stuff will kill you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. You're hallucinating.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296802" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not on the spice! I just need some sleep. I've been out scouting the area for three straight days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296804" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoa. Slow down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quit bothering me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296806" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're working for the Republic, right? Trying to drive the Imps off of Balmorra? I can help you!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Name's Chedd. I'm with the resistance. Spotted a couple Imperial snipers a few days ago. Followed them back to their base.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ran back here to report the location. We gotta hit them before they move. Only nobody believes me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296811" id2="17" version="1065353216">They don't believe a scout?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296812" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have a great track record lately. The snipers killed my brother last month. Been tracking them ever since... even if it means staying out all night.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296814" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not getting a lot of sleep. The others think it's affecting my judgment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296816" id2="17" version="1065353216">This whole planet is overrun with Imperials. What makes these snipers so important?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who cares about a few snipers?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296817" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've been picking off our people for months. Over a hundred kills. Last month, they got my brother.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296819" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the feeling you're telling the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296819" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296820" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't lie about this. Those snipers killed my brother.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone thinks I'm obsessed with avenging him. They think I'm cracking up. Claim I'm seeing things that aren't there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296824" id2="17" version="1065353216">They tried to pull me off patrol. But I wouldn't quit. I knew I could find these guys. But I can't take them out myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296825" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296826" id2="17" version="1065353216">I might be persuaded to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296827" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't put a price on my brother's life. But if it means getting the scum that killed him, I can come up with something.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296829" id2="17" version="1065353216">The snipers set up camp inside an Imperial-controlled settlement nearby. Probably figured nobody would go after them there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296831" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know I'm asking a lot. But I'm counting on you. Make them pay for what they did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296833" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. I'll find someone else to help me. I don't need you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not in the mood for talk. Out on patrol all night. Gotta get some rest.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
