<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>28</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/world/breakthrough/barrager_tech.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709142" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad Doctor Carsiri's dead. He wouldn't have wanted this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709148" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. We owe you our lives. Balmorra owes you her future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry! The lab can't take this kind of impact!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709151" id2="17" version="1065353216">An open comm call is a blessing and a curse. I heard everything. Is Doctor Carsiri...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709153" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's dead, sir. The Sith's blade struck true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709155" id2="17" version="1065353216">It won't be in vain. Use the Barrager spike to take control. The Empire will never set foot on a Republic-protected world again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709157" id2="17" version="1065353216">But... didn't you hear what Doctor Carsiri said? The Barrager will suck Balmorra dry!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Carsiri made some serious claims, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709158" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a good point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709159" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709160" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Barrager draws power from every resource the host planet has. You'll stop an Imperial fleet, but you'll destroy what you're trying to protect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709162" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one asked you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709163" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one asked you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709164" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you'll listen to your Republic commander. You came to free Balmorra. What good is freedom if we have nothing left?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709166" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to make sacrifices for the greater good. Balmorra's could prevent another Telos, Taris or Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709168" id2="17" version="1065353216">We pay a heavy price for the Barrager's protection, but we have to use it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709170" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was Doctor Carsiri's dying wish. He wouldn't have helped you otherwise. Please, the Barrager must be destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709171" id2="17" version="1065353216">We came here to protect Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709171" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroy the Barrager.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709172" id2="17" version="1065353216">To come all this way for nothing.... Do what you have to. As always, the Republic will clean up the mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709174" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Barrager might be the difference between victory and defeat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709174" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need weapons. Grab it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709175" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the time comes, we'll have a choice. Install the Barrager spike. I'll send a squad to secure the lab.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709177" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've all known we were working toward our own destruction. Only Doctor Carsiri did something about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709179" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Barrager's yours now. I'm just glad Doctor Carsiri isn't here to see it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709181" id2="17" version="1065353216">We work night and day on the Barrager. It was a mistake to build it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709183" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to get out of here. Evacuate, now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709185" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Barrager's self-destruct sequence latched onto a bunch of subsystems. This whole lab is going to blow.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
