<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>195</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/world/breakthrough/commander_madine.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709404" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever brought you to Balmorra, the Republic's glad it did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back. I wanted to be the first to congratulate you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709418" id2="17" version="1065353216">My team's working on the Barrager now. They're already looking into duplicating the weapon on other worlds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709420" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials are fleeing in droves, afraid we'll finish before their ships clear the planet. Balmorra's free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Defeating the Empire is worth any sacrifice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709421" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like the Barrager's worth all the power it needs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709422" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709423" id2="17" version="1065353216">To save a galaxy, you've got to break a few planets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709423" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709424" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll try to minimize the Barrager's damage as much as possible. But it's a small price to pay for protection from an Imperial fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just as I hoped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709427" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Doctor Carsiri was right, the Republic gave Balmorra a stiff bill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709427" id2="17" version="1065353216">But at what cost?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709428" id2="17" version="1065353216">When he sees how many worlds Balmorra's sacrifice will protect, he'll think differently.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709430" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll use the Barrager to make sure the Empire never returns to Balmorra. That's the doctor's legacy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709432" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the Empire on the way out, all that's left is cleaning up the mess. I'll be out of a job soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709434" id2="17" version="1065353216">You secured the Barrager, stormed the Gorinth Brig, freed Sobrik--the Republic is completely in your debt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709435" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire has to learn that independent worlds aren't theirs to take.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709435" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is why we fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Balmorra's been an effective lesson. If war breaks out, the Republic will be ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709440" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even after the Empire's gone, refugees will need escorts, infrastructure's got to get going again....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709442" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's settle up now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709443" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been compensated--quite well, I might add. The Republic knows gratitude's hard to spend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709445" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a lot of work ahead. But Balmorra's free--that's what's important. Good luck to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709449" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials still have stockpiles here. We need two squads up on the Gorinth Plateau--you're back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709451" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're in the middle of final troop deployment. The Empire's lost, but they're attacking on their way out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709453" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think you realize what you've done. If we had the Barrager, the Imperials wouldn't have fired another shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709454" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's on Balmorra to win. We're here to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victory isn't the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709457" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never lied about my intentions, Commander. You did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709458" id2="17" version="1065353216">I signed on to protect the Republic--including allies like Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709458" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just did my duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709461" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wanted to destroy Balmorra for a weapon. You might as well join them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709462" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wanted to give the Republic the best shot I could at defeating the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709464" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's been forced off Balmorra. That's what we wanted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709464" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the big deal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709465" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the Barrager destroyed, the Empire will just move on to another world. And we have no defense against them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Were you there when the Empire attacked Coruscant? They came out of nowhere, and we couldn't do anything about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709470" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Empire invaded Balmorra, I promised myself that it would end here. Can you blame me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Carsiri risked his life for Balmorra, not the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Carsiri would.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709472" id2="17" version="1065353216">For a scientist, he's got guts. Maybe he can help, if he ever forgives me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709474" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, but he believed in it. Right up until it got him killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709477" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... I know. Fast and easy never won a war. I fooled myself into thinking this could be different.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuses, excuses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709480" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got your own way of saying things, that's for sure. But it doesn't make you any less right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709482" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad it was you making the call and not me. When you spend your life fighting, it's easy to forget why.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our next major offensive is Imperial headquarters in the city of Sobrik. There's a sizable Balmorran resistance set up nearby.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Beke Talrott, the resistance leader, requested our aid, but the satellite system kept us from answering. I'd like to send you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone fighting the Empire can consider me an ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709487" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have the same goals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Beke's a bit of a patriot--he'll like your attitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709490" id2="17" version="1065353216">The more allies we have, the better our chances.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709490" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll need their aid too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly. Balmorra's not a member of the Republic, but we're hoping to change that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709493" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's got everything. The resistance can't be well equipped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709493" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll need a soldier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be so sure. Balmorra's covered in factories, workshops, warehouses....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to know someone else is fighting back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709496" id2="17" version="1065353216">I love a rebellion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Up until now, they were the only ones.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709499" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the resistance planning?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709499" id2="17" version="1065353216">To do what, exactly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709500" id2="17" version="1065353216">They claim they can bring down Sobrik's defenses, but they need someone skilled to lead the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709502" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see what I can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709503" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll let Beke know you're heading in that direction. He'll be waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709505" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got to get back to troop deployment. I'm certain we'll cross paths again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709507" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're gaining more ground every day, thanks to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back. The satellite system's down, and the battle's over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709511" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been in some intense ops before, but that... let's just say Bugtown never looked so good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709513" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're holding the Empire back by the skin of our teeth. Freeing captive civilians wouldn't have been my choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709514" id2="17" version="1065353216">There was no alternative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709515" id2="17" version="1065353216">But what's right isn't always what's best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709517" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's made up of allies, not buildings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709517" id2="17" version="1065353216">We gain more this way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709518" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do as I please, got it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709519" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least we've gained some new allies. Sarkus and the rest of the Hawkeyes volunteered to stay and help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709521" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hawkeyes know Balmorra's infrastructure better than anyone. Perhaps they'll make future victories more certain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Either way, we'd likely be standing in a bombed-out mess if it wasn't for you. You've got my thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709524" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a lot of Balmorra left. What's your next move?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709524" id2="17" version="1065353216">This fight's not over yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get into more populated areas, start contacting the locals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709527" id2="17" version="1065353216">No thanks necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709528" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to need more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Serving the Republic has its rewards. Mountains of credits aren't one of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709531" id2="17" version="1065353216">With command down, the Imperials didn't know which way was up. We reclaimed countless Republic and Balmorran defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leaving those Hawkeyes behind was a difficult choice, but I think it was the right one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sarkus took my choice pretty hard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709534" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hawkeyes don't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709535" id2="17" version="1065353216">I noticed. He took the first transport out of here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709537" id2="17" version="1065353216">The admiral threatened Balmorra before I killed him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Riserre had this planned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admiral Riserre always had a vibroblade behind his back in case you dodged the superlaser in front.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Casualties happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709541" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's just unfortunate that civilians had to pay the price of our victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709543" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did what was best for the Republic. There's no shame in that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Entering Imperial-occupied territory is no easy task. I hope you're up to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709549" id2="17" version="1065353216">I ask for one specialist, and I get a crack team. Lieutenant Hollis deserves a promotion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Hollis told me he'd found the best help in the galaxy, but I wasn't expecting a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad. I won't ask what you're doing on Balmorra--I'm just glad you're able to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709555" id2="17" version="1065353216">So the hero of the Esseles is my backup. I couldn't ask for much better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709557" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Commander Madine. We both know why you're here, so I'll lay out the details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709559" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's taken control of Balmorra's satellite defense system. It's only a matter of time before they find Bugtown and blast us out of this swamp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709560" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you know Bugtown's in danger, you should evacuate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709560" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we stay here, yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709561" id2="17" version="1065353216">And lose the only part of Balmorra we've got? Leaving won't solve our problems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709563" id2="17" version="1065353216">A better position could turn this whole thing around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we should move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our ships can't launch without getting shot down, and our troops can't move without ships.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709566" id2="17" version="1065353216">Being quick on the trigger solves a lot of my problems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709566" id2="17" version="1065353216">So blast them first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709567" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our first offensive was shot down. Another would be a huge risk, not to mention give away our position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709569" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's one powerful satellite.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709569" id2="17" version="1065353216">How does it work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709570" id2="17" version="1065353216">The satellites detect enemies, and orbiting turbolasers blast them apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709572" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's news to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Need-to-know basis. I don't want morale any lower than it already is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709575" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's got us cornered. As long as they have that satellite system, they're going to keep Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709577" id2="17" version="1065353216">But if we could get control of the satellite system, we could turn it on the Empire and even the score.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709578" id2="17" version="1065353216">The satellite system must have a weakness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709578" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a good plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709579" id2="17" version="1065353216">All we know is that it's well protected. My scouts and SIS agents can't even get close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that possible?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything of the Empire's is better left in ruins.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709582" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather destroy it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709583" id2="17" version="1065353216">When we can use it to defeat them? Sorry, Master Jedi, but I think that's a little wasteful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709585" id2="17" version="1065353216">But then you leave the system as a potential threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds too risky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709586" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I'm worth even half my rank, the Empire will never have the chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just destroy it. Short, sweet, simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too complicated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709589" id2="17" version="1065353216">In order to destroy it, we need to gain control of it--so then what's the point?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709591" id2="17" version="1065353216">My best agent managed to gather some intel, but he never made it back. His ship was shot down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709593" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need someone to enter Imperial territory, find Agent Jago's downed ship and recover the intel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709594" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you know the Empire doesn't already have it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709594" id2="17" version="1065353216">That intel might be gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709595" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Empire has cracked Agent Jago's encryption, we'd be hearing about it elsewhere. Trust me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't I get shot down too?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709598" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been using a small Balmorran-controlled shuttle pad to transport our scouts. You'll get there in one piece.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your troops can't handle a simple recovery mission?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709600" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't need me for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709601" id2="17" version="1065353216">My troops wouldn't make it through the Imperial army and back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use this decrypter to verify the intel's contents. Then contact me through the comm station at the shuttle pad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709604" id2="17" version="1065353216">If your agent's alive, I'll find him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709604" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll look for survivors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709605" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen the satellite system at work. Nothing gets past it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709607" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force will tell us more than any intelligence can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709607" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll learn what I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709608" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can make some advance strikes if you think it'll help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should I do some damage?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709609" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep my eyes open. Doesn't take SIS training to know the score.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709609" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll check out the situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Try to keep quiet. The longer it takes the Empire to catch on, the better our chances.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ship, intel, shuttle pad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709613" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will be a breeze.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709614" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're right, Master Jedi. I'd need some serious reinforcements to rescue you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709616" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're as quick with your weapon as you are with your mouth, you ought to do fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709618" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll wait for your comm call. Good luck up there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you authorized to be here? This is a war zone. Move along.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, Commander. I made a good living along the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709624" id2="17" version="1065353216">No matter your intentions, the Barrager would have destroyed Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure, dropping your cargo will keep it safe. But then you've got no cargo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good intentions, bad idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709627" id2="17" version="1065353216">The need was the Republic's, and the honor was mine. Safe journey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709628" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right. A soldier shouldn't consider his allies expendable. Maybe an early retirement's in order....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I can see now just how much damage the Empire did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="755855" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is why we fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764313" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the new plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764314" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least I was honest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764316" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a hypocrite.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764318" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too late for that now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764319" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't our way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003288" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to need more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003293" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003304" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to need more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003308" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003309" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is why we fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003310" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is why we fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003311" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is why we fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003312" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is why we fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's settle up now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003314" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's settle up now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003324" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victory isn't the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003325" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victory isn't the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003326" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least I was honest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003330" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a hypocrite.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003331" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just did my duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003332" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just did my duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Carsiri would.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Carsiri would.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003338" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't our way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003339" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't our way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003404" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have the same goals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1003405" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have the same goals.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
