<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>41</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/world/breakthrough/doctor_meln.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Meln? Doctor Ortis?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor... Doctor Ortis. Just give me a minute to catch my breath. I thought that fight would never end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709916" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive him--this whole experience has been traumatic. Doctor Meln, at your service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709920" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe you went to these lengths to rescue us. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709921" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was told you designed the Barrager. I hope I'm not wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709921" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709922" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't go that far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709923" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire imprisoned us because of the Barrager, and now the Republic's set us free. I think I know why you're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709925" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're only free because the Republic needs you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709925" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's nothing personal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709926" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know how these things work. You want us to get you the Barrager.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709928" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Barrager is an incredibly complicated and well-protected weapon, as designed. Luckily, our design notes are in contraband.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709930" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can use Lieutenant Vekarr's credentials to override the security system and get those files. It'll lock down afterwards, of course, but we'll have what we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709933" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can the override do anything else?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709933" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me all our options.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709934" id2="17" version="1065353216">Change prison operations, security settings, nothing that's going to help us now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709936" id2="17" version="1065353216">These files must be as important as you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709936" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised they survived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709937" id2="17" version="1065353216">When we were arrested, the Empire confiscated our research notes, our tools, our datapads--anything related to the Barrager.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709939" id2="17" version="1065353216">For a prisoner, you know a lot about being a warden.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709939" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been paying attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Miserable worm was my boss for months. I got a firsthand view of how this place operates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709942" id2="17" version="1065353216">What good are the files?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709943" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we have no reference, we can't guarantee this spike will work. The Barrager could behave erratically. It might not work at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709945" id2="17" version="1065353216">You designed the Barrager, but you need a how-to book?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709945" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you were experts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709946" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Barrager took years to design, and even longer to build. You can't expect us to have the whole thing memorized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709948" id2="17" version="1065353216">With our files, we can create a foolproof spike for the Republic, guaranteed to get control of the Barrager.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait just a minute. What about all those prisoners? You might have forgotten everything we've seen here, doctor, but I haven't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709952" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is our chance to destroy this terrible place. We have to use that override to let these people go. As for the Barrager... we'll figure out something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709953" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gorinth Brig's caused enough suffering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709953" id2="17" version="1065353216">Free the prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709954" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may have just single-handedly condemned the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709956" id2="17" version="1065353216">The thanks of a thousand prisoners should make up for it. The override worked. Every security field in the Gorinth Brig has failed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709958" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should get to a shuttle. Doctor Meln and I will do our best to get something together for the Barrager spike. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709960" id2="17" version="1065353216">There can't be any question marks on this mission, no matter what the cost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get the Barrager files.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me just input the override... there! Years of research and data, back in our hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709963" id2="17" version="1065353216">You shameless opportunist. I'll help, but only to get rid of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709965" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll get to the nearest Republic shuttle pad and have this ready within the hour. It's been a pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for rescuing us. I'm going to try my best to forget this place.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
