<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>46</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/world/breakthrough/doctor_carsiri.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enjoy your Republic victory. Balmorra was better off fighting the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709850" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Barrager's destroyed... I didn't think I would live to see it. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709852" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Barrager's taking this lab with her, but she won't take us. Move!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come in, Doctor Carsiri. Is anyone there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709858" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're here, Commander. Darth Minax and the other Imperials are dead. The Barrager's ready to accept your spike.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. Use the Barrager spike to get control. I'm sending a recovery crew to take over operations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709862" id2="17" version="1065353216">To take over? But the Barrager is a threat to Balmorra--it must be destroyed! You know that!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709863" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire will never have control of the Barrager again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709863" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not a threat anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709864" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire was never the problem. The Barrager itself caused this mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I miss something?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709867" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's wrong is that your commander is willing to sacrifice Balmorra for a Republic victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709870" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroying a fleet takes every bit of power a planet can give. Solar, geothermal, hydro... if it's part of Balmorra, it's powering the Barrager.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709872" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will leave the planet an empty shell--with nothing left to defend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709874" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire wanted the Barrager so they could hold Balmorra forever. Now I see the Republic does, too. Commander Madine lied to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709875" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure the commander wants to keep Balmorra safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709875" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're trying to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Neither of us knows the commander's true intentions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't assume things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709877" id2="17" version="1065353216">The commander wouldn't have authorized this if he'd known.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709877" id2="17" version="1065353216">That can't be true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709878" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure the commander had a good reason. Don't ask me what.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just take it easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709879" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this true, Commander?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709879" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hear his story.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever your assumptions, doctor, I made it clear that we needed to get control of the Barrager.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709882" id2="17" version="1065353216">You never said the Republic planned to use it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709885" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Madine has died in every Republic war--how dare you accuse me of treason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709887" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really think we'd destroy something that could prevent another Telos, Taris or Coruscant? Save millions of lives and guarantee a Republic victory?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709889" id2="17" version="1065353216">This war's not over. I can feel it. I know the cost is high, but the Barrager could make sure the Republic wins that war. We have to claim it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709890" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't sacrifice one planet to save another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709890" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's too costly. Destroy it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast it, do you realize what you're doing? You've given the Empire a second chance--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709893" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire must be defeated. The Barrager belongs to the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709893" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need weapons. Take it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Almost. Use the Barrager spike to take control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709896" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Barrager's yours. Now the Empire won't destroy Balmorra. I never thought it would be the Republic instead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709898" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, doctor, but we had no choice. Get back to Bugtown and meet me in Republic headquarters. Madine out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709900" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Barrager's made slaves of us all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709902" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Barrager's power core is overloading. We have to evacuate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709904" id2="17" version="1065353216">Running for my life. Next time, I'll leave the adventures to a professional. If we don't meet again--thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many traitors met their ends on my lightsaber.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="709906" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate liars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="709908" id2="17" version="1065353216">I disconnected him. Give me the Barrager spike so we can destroy this accursed thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="755858" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm in no mood for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764340" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like liars.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
