<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>56</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/world/republic/search_and_rescue/jax_dumont.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647814" id2="17" version="1065353216">Phalanx says thanks for keeping his head bomb-free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a bad escape. Now act normal. You never know if an Imperial's watching.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647817" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll question Phalanx, then change his look to help smuggle him offworld.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647819" id2="17" version="1065353216">He should be safe until then. The Imperials rely on those cortexers so heavily their manhunting skills are a little rusty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647820" id2="17" version="1065353216">So is his intel useful?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="647820" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did our work pay off?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. Turns out the Hutt Cartel has internal disagreements about transporting the Empire's starfighter parts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="647823" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just here to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647824" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done a service. It turns out the Hutts have internal disagreements about Imperial starfighter shipments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647826" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we can drive a wedge between them, we can cut off starfighter air support on half a dozen planets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647828" id2="17" version="1065353216">We push here, and the blocks fall down somewhere else. That's how the game is played.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="647829" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thinking. I was about to tell you what this could mean to us, but you don't really need to know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just understand that the intel Phalanx found will help the war on many planets, that's for certain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quickly, get in there before he's prepped for surgery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold your fire. Jax Dumont here, with the Stardogs. I was told you were in the area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647837" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on your side. The less said about how I got this uniform, the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647839" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're getting a friend out of the Empire's prize prison, and I thought it would come in handy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647840" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never heard of your organization.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="647840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you again?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647841" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're mostly former Republic soldiers--free to fight the Empire in our own way. Right now, we could use some help in an extraction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Slow down. You're the one with an Imperial cover, not me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="647843" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean &quot;we&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need your help. This outfit gets me into Shadow Town, but it won't work in the secured labs where our man is held.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647846" id2="17" version="1065353216">His code name is Phalanx. He has vital information on Hutt dealings with the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="647848" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. Brief me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647849" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of our guys, Phalanx, got himself captured to gather intel on the Imperial-Hutt connection.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647851" id2="17" version="1065353216">He succeeded, but we weren't expecting him to be transferred here to Shadow Town. We need him out, fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647853" id2="17" version="1065353216">In a few hours, Imperial surgeons will fit a cortex charge in his skull.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647854" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could help more if I knew what a cortex charge was.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="647854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fit a what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647855" id2="17" version="1065353216">A bomb in his head that detonates if he leaves prison grounds. Once it's implanted, our rescue window closes for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647857" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not sure of his number or what cell he's in. So we need you to get inside and access the main computer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647859" id2="17" version="1065353216">From there, find the cell and lead Phalanx out so we can hide him here. Can you do this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does he stand any chance of escape after one is installed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="647860" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happens then?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only if you know a very brave brain surgeon with experience disarming explosives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="647863" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647864" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not. We're not sure where he is in the prison. That's why I've been gathering passcodes--you or whoever breaks in will need them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, you can get his location from the prison databank. I have a code that'll get you access.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, you'll need to be inside the prison to use it. Guards will be everywhere. Can you do this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your friend is safe with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="647869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647870" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Havoc Squad. The question is, what can't I do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="647870" id2="17" version="1065353216">In my sleep.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, I know prisons. I'm an escapee's best friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="647871" id2="17" version="1065353216">No sweat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, here's today's passcode. Get inside and use it on their main databank.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="647874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, if I were paid....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647875" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, I see... well, it happens that this uniform's former owner wasn't exactly poor. You'll be taken care of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, here's the passcode. Use it before it changes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647879" id2="17" version="1065353216">Open the computer, find Phalanx's cell, and bring Phalanx here to hide him. Search and rescue, am I right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647881" id2="17" version="1065353216">You guys got into this mess. You're getting yourselves out of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="647881" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. [Refuse quest.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647882" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're condemning Phalanx to die in there. I hope you realize that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="647884" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing unusual here. Move along.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
