<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/bronze/imperial/terminal_injuries/captain_heedley.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170632" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made quite an example out of Vomba. I think the other prisoners got the message.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170634" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's done. Vomba's dead, and control has been returned to the terminal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I can finally cross his name off the prisoner registration. Thank you, and good riddance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170637" id2="17" version="1065353216">And here--Vomba's bounty. Sods who caught him didn't survive the firefight, so they won't need it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vomba isn't going anywhere. Get to that terminal and finish him off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170642" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord. Captain Heedley, Imperial Corrections. Sorry to impose, but I've got a mess on my hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170644" id2="17" version="1065353216">You there, hunter. Got a job for you. Right up your alley.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170646" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir. Captain Heedley, Imperial Corrections. Got a fugitive on the lam, needs catching.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170648" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mind helping me? Need a hand catching a fugitive on the run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was overseeing a prisoner transfer. Weequay pirate, name of Vomba. Couple bounty hunters caught him, wanted the reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170652" id2="17" version="1065353216">Somehow Vomba's mates found out. Shut down our security droids, turned the entire spaceport into a war zone before they made off with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170653" id2="17" version="1065353216">A dangerous criminal escaped on your watch? This doesn't bode well for you, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170653" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have failed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170654" id2="17" version="1065353216">He hasn't gotten away yet, my lord. He's still holed up in the spaceport, making his final stand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even a child would have anticipated some ill-conceived rescue attempt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170656" id2="17" version="1065353216">You weren't prepared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170657" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's why I added the extra droid detail. Didn't expect he'd slice them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170659" id2="17" version="1065353216">How much are you willing to pay to get this Vomba back?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170659" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mentioned a reward?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vomba's gang polished off the bounty hunters, so I've still got a fat pile of credits waiting to be claimed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170662" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no shortage of places to hide on Nar Shaddaa. He could be anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170662" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll never find him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vomba? He's still holed up in the spaceport. Making his final stand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170665" id2="17" version="1065353216">How will you get him back?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170666" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Vomba--what's his story?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the prisoner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Career criminal, been in and out of a dozen prisons. Likes to hijack Imperial cruisers, take them on interstellar joyrides.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Between the droid shutdown and his cronies, that swaggering git has the run of the terminal. But we've got him cornered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170671" id2="17" version="1065353216">Negotiations ended with a dead diplomat, I'm not having any more of that. Rather someone just went in there and made an example of him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170672" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Much obliged.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe he'll surrender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170676" id2="17" version="1065353216">He had his chance. Only way he's coming out of there now is in a box.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vomba's gang has sliced control stations throughout the terminal. You reset them, the droids should power back on and do their part.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170680" id2="17" version="1065353216">From there, it's just a matter of cleaning up. Go wild.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170682" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't be me. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170683" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't keep him boxed in forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170685" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the last time I trust a droid.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
