<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>57</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/world/gree_ugnaught_saboteurs/gotrut.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683429" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll hide in the workshop until all the shooting ends. Guess we might be a while, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683432" id2="17" version="1065353216">No blasters! We got no blasters! It's just a workshop. We're not with those Justicar crazies you been fightin' out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cooperate and you won't be harmed. Where's the Gree device?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surrender, please.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683434" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want the Gree device.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, great. I told you guys we should've left that alien thing where it belonged!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683437" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want the Gree device, and I will kill you if I don't get it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talk or you're dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take it easy! The last thing we want is to get killed over some useless tech.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683440" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take it, all right? We thought we could make it work, but we can't. We'll have to find some other way to save everyone on this level.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683441" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are the people on this level in some kind of danger?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683441" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683442" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. We're not thieves, we're engineers. We work to keep this area clean and safe, but it's gettin' harder every day to do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683444" id2="17" version="1065353216">You, save everyone? Don't make me laugh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683444" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got to be joking.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Laugh all you want. People here count on us for essential services. We give them power and light.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still waiting for my device.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683448" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gree stuff is all yours, don't worry. We never woulda taken it if we weren't in such a hopeless situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683450" id2="17" version="1065353216">This level's got a big problem we can't fix. The air filters stopped working.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683452" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senate won't send anybody to make repairs, and things are gettin' bad. We got too many people living in the same area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683453" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Coruscant. Why wouldn't the Senate help with repairs?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683453" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senate won't help?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683454" id2="17" version="1065353216">They don't bother keepin' any of our major systems running. Why should they, when the Justicars won't let 'em in?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683456" id2="17" version="1065353216">It sounds like it's time to find a new home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Couldn't you move away?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coruscant's always been our home. We're all here because we believe in the Republic. Can't you understand that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683459" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd say it's time for some aggressive depopulation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683459" id2="17" version="1065353216">So thin the herds.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you saying we should go out and kill every third refugee just to make room? Are you space-happy?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without our air filters, the smog seeps in fast, which is even harder on the non-humanoids. Pretty soon we're gonna have an epidemic on our hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683463" id2="17" version="1065353216">There must be some way to avoid that outcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683463" id2="17" version="1065353216">What can be done?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683464" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what we keep tellin' ourselves, but so far we've come up empty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683466" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fear unbalances you and makes a bad situation worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683466" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm yourself. Focus.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683467" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's hard to imagine things gettin' much worse than they already are, but that's exactly where things are headed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry about the odds so much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe, maybe not.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, it's not a question of &quot;if,&quot; it's a question of &quot;when&quot;!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regardless of your reasons, you stole Republic property.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683472" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't excuse you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683473" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not makin' any excuses. We got carried away and we're sorry. But we gotta do somethin'!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't look at me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683476" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know. You're workin' with those Gree, right? Maybe you can put in a word?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get over it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, the people down here have families. We have to do something.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683481" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we get our air filters workin', you'll never hear from us again.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683483" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know I'm askin' a lot, but will you tell the Gree about us? Maybe ask them to show us how to fix things up? Please?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683484" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll tell the Gree representatives about your situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I'll help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683485" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't know what this means to us. You're savin' innocent lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here, this datapad's got stuff about us the Gree will wanna know. Schematics of what we're workin' on, our repair manuals, all that stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just show it to them. It'll explain everything about our situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just give me the device before I kill you all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683490" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not your buddy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683491" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, all right! Take the Gree tech. Take it! We'll just start suffocating down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="683493" id2="17" version="1065353216">My friends and I are just workin' hard, all right? We don't want any trouble, especially not with you.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
