<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>69</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/world/gree_ugnaught_saboteurs/gree_console.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213505" id2="17" version="1065353216">Internal transmitters reveal you convey the optimization solution to me. I also scan a crude Ugnaught porcine-biped proposal of collaboration. Curious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213506" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you'll find that datapad worth reading.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213506" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Ugnaughts need your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213507" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Ugnaught porcine-bipeds submit esteem for my efforts and honor my faculties. This is unforeseen pleasantness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213509" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a great opportunity to show your skills as an Administrator unit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213509" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should like collaboration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213510" id2="17" version="1065353216">This unlikely collaboration acknowledges my true aptitude. What a purple tangent, to achieve astounding me this way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213512" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're all a bunch of weirdos. I'm sure you'll get along great.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213512" id2="17" version="1065353216">Freaks should work together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213513" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Ugnaught porcine-bipeds express similar disgruntlement with your species. This describes a foundation for collaboration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Internal tracking transmitters reveal you convey the optimization solution. Were the Ugnaught porcine-bipeds made to regret their plunder?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213516" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Ugnaughts won't bother you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our problem is solved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, superior. This red tangent generates appreciativeness, black bisector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213520" id2="17" version="1065353216">You submit unexpected vagueness of description. I suspect the plunderers evaded full reparations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213522" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think you'll have to worry about those little piggies anytime soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213522" id2="17" version="1065353216">I gave them a real scare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213523" id2="17" version="1065353216">You manufactured fear in the plunderers? I anticipated more determined sanctions than that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213525" id2="17" version="1065353216">I submit that Ugnaught porcine-bipeds are an infestation. I recommend your leaders take precautionary steps to prevent their propagation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213527" id2="17" version="1065353216">With this optimization solution repossessed, Coruscant's waste processors revive. Filth-disease-poison levels recede, plague outbreaks averted. All resolves to purple parallel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213735" id2="17" version="1065353216">The black bisector comes! Pleasing, as it is needed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213737" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am In-iK, science unit. Please &quot;talk up&quot; if your comprehension white-shifts. I will use simple-happy language-words to help you understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213738" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do... appreciate anything you can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213739" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indubitably!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213741" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's with your language, anyway? I can barely understand you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about yourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213742" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gree language-form is dissimilar to Basic language-form. Because Gree senses are unique red bisectors!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Five Gree senses analyze forms. Three Gree senses soak color. So goes language. Other species miscommunicate our language-words.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting. That's not why you wanted to talk to me, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213745" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. A blue vertex has been achieved, and we must embed ourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213748" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ultimately, diversity is what makes the Republic strong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213748" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yet we learn a lot this way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. The Republic is point-of-intersection for many, and Coruscant for most. But Coruscant is now our difficulty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you calling me stupid?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213751" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds like an insult.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213753" id2="17" version="1065353216">All apologies. We should obliterate &quot;small talk&quot; now and move forward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213755" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pat-aK has planted information inside you. But I am the most powerful power-overseer, and responsibility for darkness is mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213757" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coruscant power comes from the Works. Darkness comes from the Works. Coruscant-Senators, traders are blind. The power-darkness must stop.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213758" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're talking about blackouts?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213758" id2="17" version="1065353216">Power-darkness?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes? Perhaps we understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Repeat that. The Works are where Coruscant's power is generated?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213761" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the Works?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Politicians and merchants are always complaining. I wouldn't worry about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lousy whining Senators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Complainants in the enclave meld into the ochre tetrasphere. Not so on Coruscant, alas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213765" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Works is very low on Coruscant. There, Gree spawning generators breed electrons for machine-consumption.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213767" id2="17" version="1065353216">But enemy droid-machines intersect the power conduits and yellow-shift their functionality. Enemy droid-machines must stop, and conduits must be fixed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are the enemy droid-machines disrupting the power conduits?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213768" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's wrong with the droids?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213769" id2="17" version="1065353216">All droids in the Works were damaged when the Empire attacked. Now they are corrupt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213772" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're asking me to repair alien power conduits? I can barely get through this conversation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213772" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must be kidding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213773" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do not need to implement a white bisection! We have a solution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213775" id2="17" version="1065353216">I monitor the power conduits, and know where to implement purple-shifting. As black bisector, you can &quot;take out&quot; many, many droid-machines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213777" id2="17" version="1065353216">With information planted inside you, and our tool-sphere repair-mother in your many fingers, you can perform the fixing function! It is efficacious?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds efficacious to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh, sure. Why not?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent-red tangents envelop us! You will do well, black bisector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213780" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, but I won't do it for you--I'll do it because it's an excuse to kill droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="213780" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe it'll be a decent fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213781" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes? That is... acceptable, I think, for the black bisector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="213784" id2="17" version="1065353216">White bisector, not black! At the end of days, you will intersect with the tricolor tetrasphere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683501" id2="17" version="1065353216">No time for chat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683512" id2="17" version="1065353216">No deal. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683520" id2="17" version="1065353216">The details don't matter.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
