<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>63</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/world/gree_ugnaught_saboteurs/hibarakk.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coruscant's waste processing system revives. Purple parallel, black bisector. The Enclave-Republic bargain evolves fulfilled.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Operator units always inherit fouled labors. I administrate as well as Pat-aK, but I am marooned to waste processing! What have I done to incur white acute?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683534" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a Jedi Knight. I'd like to lend a hand with the repairs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683534" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm here to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi? Ah. I must adjust my estimation of Pat-aK's aptitude for administration, but only slightly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unhappiness is a sign one has lost one's balance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be displeased.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683538" id2="17" version="1065353216">My gyros respond positively. Balance remains stable. Your statement advances nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does that mean what I think it means?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Waste processing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Removal of toxic-rubble-scraping-flushes is fundamental to planetary infrastructure upgrading.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683543" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't always pull the easy ops--sometimes you have to get your hands dirty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doing a lot of grunt work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please restrict unneeded slang terms. Comprehending your sonics is white perpendicular enough as it is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that what you are? An Operator unit?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Operator units?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683547" id2="17" version="1065353216">You submit curiosity? Bewildering. Foreign species customarily embody flawless self-centeredness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gree units fulfill four caste-assignments: Crafter, Operator, Researcher and Administrator. I am Operator. I ensure proper function of Gree ingenuity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pat-aK is Administrator unit. His sole aptitude is communication-command-governance-argument. I can serve Pat-aK's function. Can he serve mine? No!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683552" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you dislike your assignment so much, why not change to a different one?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683552" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sound bitter about this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683553" id2="17" version="1065353216">My aptitudes are gray sphere, but the enclave permits only Operator unit assignment. This is inequitable distribution of my aptitudes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683555" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you know you can do Pat-aK's job?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683555" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you so sure?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683556" id2="17" version="1065353216">I share aptitude for communication-command-governance-argument. Operator caste was compelled to me, not programmed at origin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683558" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is petty politics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Naturally not. Gree assignment structure nuances are beyond your species. Nothing will alter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683561" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not here to listen to you whine in gibberish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683561" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't you try to make sense?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683562" id2="17" version="1065353216">My fault-finding is inconsequential, regardless. Nothing will alter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pat-aK commanded me: Optimize Coruscant's waste processing system. Preserve your organs from filth-disease-poisons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683566" id2="17" version="1065353216">But Ugnaught porcine-bipeds plunder Gree ingenuity from waste processors. With Gree optimization solution stolen, filth-disease-poisons spread uncontrolled. Plagues imminent!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683567" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to act now, before it's too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683567" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't let that happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683568" id2="17" version="1065353216">You comprehend the volatility of this predicament. You exhibit enhanced insight for your species.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683570" id2="17" version="1065353216">What would Ugnaughts gain from possessing your technology?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683570" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why steal your device?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many species attempt access of Gree ingenuity. This is no white convex--ah, mystery-puzzle-labor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683573" id2="17" version="1065353216">I might be here a while--should I be worried about this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh... how imminent, exactly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why interrogate me? Gree Operator units do not possess aptitude for biological predictors. Plague outbreak arrives at appropriate period.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683576" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guns aren't much good for stopping plagues.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683576" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no doctor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683577" id2="17" version="1065353216">Weapons enhance black bisector's success. Plague-state is averted when you repossess the Gree optimization solution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683579" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's an &quot;Ugnaught&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683579" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugnaughts?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683580" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic species databanks express Ugnaughts as porcine-bipeds. Relevant descriptors are &quot;small&quot;, &quot;tusks&quot; and &quot;unfriendly.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Replace whatever was stolen and stop wasting my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683582" id2="17" version="1065353216">So fix it, idiot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Replacing Gree ingenuity forbidden under enclave code-law. Optimization solution must be repossessed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683585" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Ugnaught porcine-bipeds plundered Gree optimization solution unaware of internal transmitters. I detect the plundered device's coordinates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pat-aK authorizes compensation of Republic credits to the black bisector who repossesses the optimization solution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683588" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can find your device.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683589" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683591" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is the expected response, black bisector. Why exhaust respiratory functions on it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pat-aK is a yellow octagon to achieve you for a black bisector. Incompetent Administrator unit!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683596" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Hib-R-ak, Operator unit. If you seek orange vertex, schedule with Pat-aK, Administrator unit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's talk compensation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683599" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683600" id2="17" version="1065353216">The optimization solution exists inside Migrant Merchants' Guild headquarters. You must repossess this device from Ugnaughts and return it to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683602" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic lacks optimization solution to avert plague outbreak. Ugnaught porcine-bipeds took it to coordinates within Migrant Merchants' Guild headquarters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Species inhabiting Migrant Merchants' Guild are green perpendicular, unavailable to negotiation. Be alerted and hazardous in your pursuit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="760998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those thieves are dead.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
