<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>144</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/world/supply_chain/kahrin_wek.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for your work. Now our outposts can survive another month.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find Commander Yajak when you reach Outpost Four. He'll want to know that food is coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Normally, our fourth outpost comes here to pick up its supplies, but their convoy never arrived this month.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621915" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid something happened--they need to be found.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621916" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me where to look.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621916" id2="17" version="1065353216">Want me to find out what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621917" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got to be the best friend these soldiers ever had.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621919" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks. I guess you do care, even if you didn't want to risk the dust-up over turning Gardit in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621921" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's dangerous territory out there. Was the convoy armed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621921" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think they're dead?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621922" id2="17" version="1065353216">The route between the outposts runs along Lake Brell--not the best planning. There's rakghouls there and a nexu spawning ground, and worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Usually the convoys manage by only traveling when the sun is highest. Plus lots and lots of firepower.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621926" id2="17" version="1065353216">But if they're out there too long... well, you need to find them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every moment we delay risks their lives. I'll leave right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then time is of the essence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621928" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a lot of risk to take out of the goodness of my heart....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got any incentive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621929" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll scrounge up some credits if that's what motivates you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure, if credits are all you want, I can find you some.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621931" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621931" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621932" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me some details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621933" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever happened to the convoy, we need to make sure Morne Outpost gets their supplies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sonic emitters along the route usually keep off the worst of the critters. But if they're on the fritz, that convoy would have walked into a feeding frenzy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fix the emitters and see what you can find about the convoy. When you're done, report to Commander Yajak at Morne Outpost. And thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621939" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are better ways to earn money, even on Taris.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nevermind. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not my concern. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621941" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll pass. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621942" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and Gardit are exactly the same. All you care about are yourselves!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621943" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand. Maybe now that they're fed, our soldiers will be able to man a search party....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621945" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have antibiotics. They come on the same ship as everything else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621947" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're supposed to keep better tabs on that sort of thing. These men have the Csillian flu. They could die if--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, you've returned. And with all of you unhurt. Dare I ask if you've managed to recover our supplies?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi! Dare I hope you've made it to our ship?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621951" id2="17" version="1065353216">No number of beasts could have kept me from aiding these men.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621951" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your men are saved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621952" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your order is known for its mercy. Thank you for coming to our aid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621954" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant! Do I read from your face that you've brought welcome news?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell your men they're off rationing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621955" id2="17" version="1065353216">The supplies are here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a moment too soon, Lieutenant. Let me tell you, you really saved my stripes on this one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, our great hope has returned. Dare I ask if you've been able to recover our supplies?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621959" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I didn't even take a gratuity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621959" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's all right here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha. You freelancers. Always taking a poke at us soldiers, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything's here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621963" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just in the nick of time, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621965" id2="17" version="1065353216">The men came close to mutiny when I cut rations again. Hmph. They knew this wasn't going to be a luxury cruise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your outpost won't starve now, no thanks to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621967" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you care?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621968" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now you just watch yourself. I did everything in my power to--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621970" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you expect? You ask your men to starve while you eat bantha steaks from offworld?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621971" id2="17" version="1065353216">These pictures prove you knew the ship was damaged, and you sent it anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621971" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see him court-martialed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621972" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're going to Republic Command. Along with my documentation of every personal purchase you've made.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621974" id2="17" version="1065353216">These men left their families and risked their lives to come here. If they die, it should be for someone better than you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621976" id2="17" version="1065353216">I--I didn't know the ship was so bad. I thought, if it was serious, they'd catch it on Ord Mantell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621977" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should be ashamed of what you've done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621977" id2="17" version="1065353216">You abused your authority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621978" id2="17" version="1065353216">How dare you talk to me like that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621980" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate your help, but maybe you'd better move on now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621982" id2="17" version="1065353216">All due respect, Master Jedi, but this is my command, and you're a guest here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621984" id2="17" version="1065353216">I outrank you, soldier, whatever your heroics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621986" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many crimes would you be wanted for in Republic space if I were to start looking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621988" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621990" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've sent every report ever made about the ship's condition to Republic Command. If they discover the cause of the crash, you're in serious trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621991" id2="17" version="1065353216">The men on Taris deserve a better leader.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621991" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should lose your command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621992" id2="17" version="1065353216">A good commander lives under the same conditions as his troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make it up to the men.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621993" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never realized how quickly we go through our supplies. If I'd thought we couldn't last the month, I--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621995" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have some, uh, personal stores. I'll distribute them while you finish here. As a gesture of good faith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="621997" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never thought I'd see anyone put the righteous fear into him like that. Good job, and thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="621999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Work it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622000" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is ridiculous. I did nothing wrong. Republic Command will never listen to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622002" id2="17" version="1065353216">I--I need to call them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for all your help. But there may be something else, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't talk that way to your commander, quartermaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Respect the chain of command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me, sir. What I meant to say, sir, is that maybe fixing the ship before it crashed would have cost us fewer lives. Respectfully.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just distribute the food, Private. We'll talk later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622011" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you--the men of this outpost owe you a debt of gratitude. We all do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622012" id2="17" version="1065353216">These men have given up a lot to serve the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622012" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was glad to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622013" id2="17" version="1065353216">No thanks needed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622014" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's got to be somewhere more interesting than this--even on Taris.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are we done?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622015" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a pleasure to work with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Actually, if you're still interested in serving our soldiers, there may be something else....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get me those pictures, and I promise we'll bring Commander Gardit to justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622022" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you're just going to make this all better, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Usually people are happy if I come to make things better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622023" id2="17" version="1065353216">What?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622025" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Kahrin Wek, quartermaster. Commander Gardit just called to say you're retrieving our supplies. For which, by the way, I and the rest of the troops here humbly thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Want to calm down and point me to where your supply ship crashed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622027" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just here about the ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course! You think I want to see everyone here starve?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622030" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I don't want Commander Fat-Pants to think it means he gets away with this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622032" id2="17" version="1065353216">Steal from your troops, spend the Republic's money on vintage wine from Alderaan, but it's fine, because there's a gang of big-hearted heroes around to save you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Steal from your troops, waste Republic money bringing in silks and wine from Alderaan, and it's fine, because some wandering Jedi will happen in to save you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Embezzle the Republic's money to bring in dress blues from Alderaan, but don't worry, one of our top Special Forces guys will bail you out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Embezzle the Republic's money to build your office out of Alderaanian timber, but that's fine, because someone like you will waltz in to save the day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622036" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a serious accusation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622036" id2="17" version="1065353216">The commander's embezzling?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622037" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you talking about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622038" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ship didn't have to crash.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622040" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't come here to get yelled at.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Directions? Map? Something?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then let me be straight. Getting our supplies would be a great help, but pulling Commander Gardit from his position would be the best help of all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622043" id2="17" version="1065353216">I said over and over that that ship needed repairs. The left stasis generator was loose, and the hyperdrive motivator was seeping fluid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622045" id2="17" version="1065353216">But Gardit had already spent our allotted maintenance budget. On himself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Putting his men at risk for his own indulgences is a grievous misuse of authority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622046" id2="17" version="1065353216">He should be punished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622047" id2="17" version="1065353216">And then some! But he simply slashed the rations budget in half and figures it's over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622049" id2="17" version="1065353216">The men are starving. And starving men don't hold up well against creatures where one tiny scratch could lead to a base-wide epidemic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622051" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is only with calm purpose that you can bring him to justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622051" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must control your anger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, if that's what it takes, I can be calm as a cloudless day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622054" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this is true, he's a blot on the Republic, and I'll bring him down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622054" id2="17" version="1065353216">He won't get away with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622055" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are good soldiers, here. They deserve a better man to lead them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622057" id2="17" version="1065353216">I noticed he had a pretty posh setup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622057" id2="17" version="1065353216">That explains the gold drapes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every shipment has some personal item he's bringing in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you prove this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622061" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have proof?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622061" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't believe you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622062" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm telling the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Somehow he's juggling the numbers he sends to HQ. No commander needs a personal vehicle in an outpost this size.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622066" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can take this holocamera out to the crash site, you could get the evidence I need to get him court-martialed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622067" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of evidence do you think I'll find?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622067" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you asking me to do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here. Take the camera.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me the camera.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622071" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622073" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you take holopics of the engines, I can show that the documented lack of repairs is what caused the crash.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622075" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want no part of your personal crusade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622075" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just take the camera. You'll see the damaged parts for yourself. Take holopics of the engines, it'll take no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622078" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're not convinced, just bring the supplies. But if you happen to be overcome by a patriotic rage against Commander Gardit's greed, at least you'll be prepared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622080" id2="17" version="1065353216">The most important thing is the supplies, though. The crash site isn't far. When you get everything, bring it back here so I can distribute it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622082" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're under strict rationing right now. No food or fresh water until tomorrow.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
