<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>96</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/class/bounty_hunter/the_ferryman/imperial_intelligence_officer.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484542" id2="17" version="1065353216">You here to take Barrows off my hands?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484543" id2="17" version="1065353216">I noted your return. I figured it was safe to assume you were successful, given your reputation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484545" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've prepared a report of your success for Darth Tormen. I have your compensation right here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484546" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been a pleasure working with you, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Likewise. I admit that I assumed your reputation exaggerated. I see I was mistaken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484549" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could use a friend in Imperial Intelligence. Keep in touch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484549" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484550" id2="17" version="1065353216">So long as you're sure to put in a good word for me, I'll do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484552" id2="17" version="1065353216">I handled more than just Zale.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484553" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid Darth Tormen has absolute authority on the matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484555" id2="17" version="1065353216">However, I could probably procure something with a little time. Is there anything in particular?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484556" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd like to know a little more about my employer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about Darth Tormen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484557" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a dangerous request. Unofficially, I can tell you that any concerns you may have are largely unfounded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Tormen has little tolerance for duplicity. If he bore you any ill will, he'd simply crush you like a bug and move on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484561" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deal honestly with him and you'll live longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484562" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be sure to keep that in mind, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Noted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484563" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll rest a little easier knowing I'm not getting hung out to dry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484563" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's good to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't fault me if I keep my cards close to my vest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484564" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll never trust a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484565" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't fault someone for being smart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484567" id2="17" version="1065353216">New toys are nice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484568" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm certain I can dig up something you'll like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484570" id2="17" version="1065353216">Money, plain and simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484571" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure there are some funds I can reallocate without much fuss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just be sure to mention me favorably to my superiors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484575" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must return to my duties. Again, a pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Horn, I'm in position. What have you got for me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis of data from the custodians is coming slowly, but I believe we've found a solid lead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484586" id2="17" version="1065353216">The bulk of the samples taken recently appear to have been interred in a vault we are designating &quot;block 44.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484588" id2="17" version="1065353216">The majority of the Imperial prisoners have likely been taken there, making it the probable destination for your target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where can I find block 44?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me the location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484590" id2="17" version="1065353216">These coordinates are based on our analysis of the tomb's schematics, but that's as much as I know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484592" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Barrows came to stop the Imperial rescue op, shouldn't he be after the highest profile targets?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484592" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the Dread Masters?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484593" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's possible, but with the majority of our forces concentrating on liberating the Dread Masters, it's unlikely he'd go unnoticed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484595" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the remaining samples?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484595" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happened to the rest?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Operations Groups One and Two identified a separate vault as the location of the Dread Masters. Other samples were separated as well, though the reasons are unclear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any of them could be a potential target, but our primary objective is the Dread Masters. It's unlikely Barrows would go unnoticed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484600" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like working with &quot;most likely,&quot; Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484600" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't sound real certain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484601" id2="17" version="1065353216">My apologies. Deciphering the data is proving difficult. It's the best we have to work with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484603" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's your call. These are block 44's coordinates if you decide to pursue it as a lead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484605" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Barrows is sighted elsewhere, you'll be the first to know. Horn out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our landers can insert you into the Republic fortifications relatively near the last known location of Barrows's vessel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get me on the ground, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good, I'm ready to head out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484609" id2="17" version="1065353216">What am I walking into?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484610" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be heading for a starship hangar in the administrative wing. Expect resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484612" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't know what hit them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484613" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have already disrupted the Republic's ability to maintain control of their captives; the biggest threat to you will likely be the prisoners themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484615" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be absolute pandemonium planetside. This is my direct holofrequency. I am on call should you need me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="484617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Um, Blizz like it if boss tell Blizz what Empire-man's funny words mean on flight down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not often I find myself breaking into prisons. Shall we?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't be dull.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Secret prison fortress, absolute pandemonium, how bad could it be?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Horn, Imperial Intelligence. I have orders to act as your liaison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484625" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've prepared a briefing should you require it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Start from the beginning; I haven't been given a lot of details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go ahead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484627" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take all the help I can get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great, thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then allow me to introduce you to your target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484632" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Zale Barrows. After helping break the Mandalorian blockade during the war, the Republic offered him considerable latitude to plague the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Feh, only suckers took them up on that &quot;Privateer&quot; racket. There's no profit in chasing Sith warships.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Owe him a bloody lip.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484638" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then, after the Treaty of Coruscant, the Republic retained him as their unofficial ferryman to Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484639" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a location for Barrows's ship?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where is he now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484640" id2="17" version="1065353216">We observed his freighter land on Belsavis before our forces invaded; no vessels larger than a shuttle have been spotted leaving the surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would the Republic hire a war hero to run errands?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems like a waste of talent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484643" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their operations here are strictly off the books. Using Barrows ensures nothing here can be traced back to the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a glorified shuttle pilot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484645" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484646" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nearly half the ship captains involved in breaking the blockade became Republic-sponsored pirates. Under Barrows's leadership, they harried the Imperial fleet mercilessly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484648" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis is a remote ice ball with minimal natural resources--the perfect place to keep things you'd rather forget.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which is why the Republic has constructed a substantial prison fortress here to hide away their undesirables.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484651" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not looking to lay siege. What are our options?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484651" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have a plan to break in?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484653" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it's just a prison, why all the Imperial interest?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484653" id2="17" version="1065353216">There has to be more to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484654" id2="17" version="1065353216">We think there may be more to this prison, but our primary objective is to extract persons of interest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484656" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume we're talking about more than swoop gang scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484656" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of &quot;undesirables&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484657" id2="17" version="1065353216">Top organized crime figures, mass murderers, hostile species, political prisoners. Anyone the Republic would like to disappear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484659" id2="17" version="1065353216">That includes a large number of Imperial prisoners of war the Republic did not wish to release after the Treaty of Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hit the high points. Quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="484660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just give the bare essentials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your target is Zale Barrows, ace pilot and daring as they come. His vessel was observed landing on Belsavis before our forces invaded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="484665" id2="17" version="1065353216">We believe he is still inside the Republic prison facility on the surface.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
