<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>37</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/bronze/republic/restraining_the_darkness/jedi_master_korman_reyes.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288958" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288961" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you wouldn't fail. You have the strength of the young. Now let's have a look at what you found.... Hmm....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288963" id2="17" version="1065353216">This appears to be a targeting device. Part of a larger weapon. Thank the stars you kept this away from the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288965" id2="17" version="1065353216">From what I'm hearing on the comm channels, you're needed elsewhere. Go--may the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop the Sith looting the vault first, then disable their starship. Once that's done, return with any technology you find.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288972" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew if I was patient, the Force would send help--but your team is more than I hoped for.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288974" id2="17" version="1065353216">The hero of Tython? The Force must surely have guided you here--and not a moment too soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank the Force you're here, young one. I'm getting too old to face these situations alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288978" id2="17" version="1065353216">You aren't Jedi--but if you've made it this far, the Force is clearly with you. I need your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288980" id2="17" version="1065353216">I came to Belsavis to aid the Republic, but I fear my strengths lie in the Jedi Archives, not on the battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288982" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith are stealing destructive ancient devices from the alien vaults. You must stop those fools from leaving the planet with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="288983" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor seeks to destroy this world. Can your mission wait?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288983" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm busy saving Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288984" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Sith escape with these devices, they could become too powerful for us to defeat. We can't allow that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="288986" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wasn't aware Belsavis stored anything besides criminals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ancient technology? Here?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many things were left on this world in the belief they'd be secured forever. Such was the hubris of the prison's builders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="288989" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've handled containment scenarios like this before. Give me the mission briefing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad is on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="288990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do these devices have a credit value attached? Just curious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288990" id2="17" version="1065353216">I smell opportunity.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288991" id2="17" version="1065353216">These ancient devices could lay waste to planets. They are not to be bought or sold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me? But you're a Jedi Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288994" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi must admit his limits. I'm not a young man. You're young and strong--you'll succeed where I can't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like my kind of fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teams of Sith are looting a nearby vault. You'll need to drive them back and recover any devices they've taken. But that's not all....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288999" id2="17" version="1065353216">You also need to disable the enemy's starship so it cannot leave Belsavis. This charge will destroy the vessel's engines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289001" id2="17" version="1065353216">My objectives are clear.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289002" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Sith vessel tries to leave, the turret here is our last hope. I'll fire it if I must, though artillery isn't exactly my specialty.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Besides, the last thing we want is ancient, deadly technology scattered across this valley.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bring anything you find to me. We need to know what our enemy has toyed with. May the Force be with you....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289008" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm too busy. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289009" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are not merely machines--they're weapons. In Sith hands, they'll create horrific suffering.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps this turret can destroy the Sith vessel when it tries to leave--though my aim isn't what it used to be....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis needs all the defenders we can muster. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="765384" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, Master.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
