<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>24</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x3/pvp/warzone_prototype_ship.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039850" id2="17" version="1065353216">Defending team, welcome to the Voidstar combat simulation. Your enemies are after the ship's datacore, and you must stop them. Let the simulation begin!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039853" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voidstar wargame has begun! Defending team: the attackers have arrived. Treat them as you would the Republic, and block their recovery of the ship's datacore!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039856" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to the Reactor Core pit. Find a path across, and plant explosives on one of the doors. Ensure they detonate, and you're nearly there!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039857" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent progress. Bridge the gap across the Reactor Core pit and place explosives on one of the doors. See that the defending team doesn't disarm them!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039858" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is it! Access the terminal, download the Voidstar's datacore, and win the simulation!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Success is nearly yours! Access the terminal and download the Voidstar's datacore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isn't this fun? As the attacking team, you must retake the Voidstar's datacore. Override a security terminal to breach the first door.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commencing stage two Voidstar wargame. Defending team: stop the attackers from seizing the datacore!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039862" id2="17" version="1065353216">The tables have turned. Defenders: stop the attackers from retaking the Voidstar's datacore. Go team!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commencing stage two Voidstar wargame. Attacking team: override the security terminal, open the door and retake the ship's datacore!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your team prevails! Execution: perfect. Team work: exemplary. Voidstar scenario complete!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039869" id2="17" version="1065353216">So close! Your defeat has been recorded, but everyone's a winner at heart. Voidstar scenario complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039874" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have triumphed. May the opposing team learn from your example. Wargame complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039876" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voidstar falls to the enemy. Your defeat is noted. Wargame complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck claiming the datacore. Let the simulation begin!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commencing wargame. Seize that datacore!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039900" id2="17" version="1065353216">The attackers have advanced to the Reactor Core pit! Stop them before they blow open the doors with explosives. If they plant a bomb, disarm it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attackers have breached the Reactor Core pit. They plan to blow open the doors with explosives. Halt their advance and disarm any bombs before they explode!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039917" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy has nearly won, but you can still triumph! Shield the datacore access terminal from the attackers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1039918" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are on the verge of defeat! Guard the datacore access terminal with your life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1040118" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alert! Attackers have breached the cargo bay. Neutralize their assault and disarm any explosives they rig on the doors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1040151" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've stormed the cargo bay! Bypass the force field, rig a door with explosives, and guard the bomb until it detonates!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1045380" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look out--attackers in the cargo bay! Block their attack, and disarm any explosives they plant on the doors. You can do it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1045381" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wonderful, you've reached the cargo bay! Bypass the force field, and blast open a door with explosives. Don't let the defending team disarm your handiwork.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
