<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>74</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/world/comrades_in_arms/b_6nx.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714777" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for your assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714780" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe you got the data spike instead of the parts for my friend. Now you leave me no choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714781" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will do as I say, droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714781" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's correct.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714782" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time you returned to your duties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714782" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is for the best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714783" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry it up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Repairing personality protocol. Functions resetting to standard. Please stand by.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me now. My current assignment is to prevent enemy incursion into this zone, so I must stay alert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714788" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your... your assistance is... is appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714790" id2="17" version="1065353216">You retrieved the motivator! 5TM, you're going to make it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714792" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will begin repairs. Hopefully, once I return to full functionality, I can get you to resume our duties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714794" id2="17" version="1065353216">I cannot thank you enough, brave organic! Here--these are the coordinates for the supply cache I promised.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714795" id2="17" version="1065353216">No problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we're done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714797" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least there's a reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not be so modest about your heroic efforts!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell, brave organic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714802" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe you're worrying about my programming while my comrade lies damaged on the battlefield!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714803" id2="17" version="1065353216">As soon as we have that new motivator, you'll be as good as new, brother!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714804" id2="17" version="1065353216">Help me! You there! Yes, you! Please!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714806" id2="17" version="1065353216">My comrade took severe damage while engaging the enemy--please, we have to repair him!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not waste these organics' time. I am damaged beyond reasonable field repair. Proceed with assigned contingency 57-8B.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not waste the time of an organic. The damage to my motivator exceeds reasonable repair. Continue our assigned task alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714812" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't just leave you out here! I will return you to headquarters fully operational, brother. I have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714813" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't realize that droids could have such strong emotions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714813" id2="17" version="1065353216">You care a lot for a droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714814" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is my counterpart! My comrade! I can't just leave him in this war zone to face destruction alone. I have to save him!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stand in my way and I'll destroy you both, droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Move aside--now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714817" id2="17" version="1065353216">The droid is worried about his little friend. Adorable!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aw, how sweet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your buddy is scrap, pal. Get back to your job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get over it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714819" id2="17" version="1065353216">No! He can make it, we just have to help him!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714821" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is your assigned task, droid? Why are you here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you malfunctioning?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714822" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were guarding the area perimeter when my comrade was damaged by enemy fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714824" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're boring me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unit B-6NX carries experimental emotional programming, which may be the cause of his current malfunction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Camaraderie and compassion increase unit cohesion, thereby increasing combat effectiveness by a factor of five!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714829" id2="17" version="1065353216">The observed result is that your programming prevents you from ignoring my damage and carrying out mission priorities--a clear flaw.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714831" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't listen to him. This single-use passcard will open a hidden supply locker in the nearby junkyard. You can retrieve a new motivator, and we can repair my comrade!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Using our assigned passcard in order to repair me is a waste, 6NX.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714835" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the organics wish to help, they should use the card to retrieve a data spike to counteract your flawed emotional programming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714836" id2="17" version="1065353216">The card, and the organic's time, would be better used retrieving a data spike to erase your flawed emotional programming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714837" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could spare some time to get you back to your duties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something should be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714838" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll gladly forego a few moments of carnage to get the two of you sorted out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714838" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714839" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got some time between jobs, if you need help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess I should lend a hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714840" id2="17" version="1065353216">If neither of you can complete your assignments, then action must be taken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something needs to be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Couldn't I find a new motivator and a data spike, and fix you both?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why not do both?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Data spikes and motivators are stored separately, and the card will only open one secured case.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am incapable of engaging enemy soldiers, whereas unit B-6NX only chooses not to. Repairing his faulty programming is the most expedient solution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Engaging those resistance fighters would have subjected you to further risk of damage! I couldn't take that chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please--take this card and retrieve the motivator to repair my friend. Please. I can even reward your help!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714850" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the location of another supply cache--one that isn't locked. Its contents will surely be useful to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bribery, refusal to carry out programmed directives... my counterpart's malfunctions are obvious. Please retrieve a data spike to correct him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your counterpart definitely needs to be reprogrammed. Where can I find what we need?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's remove those emotions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714854" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should be able to find the necessary data spike in the nearby junkyard. Use the passcard that 6NX gave you to retrieve it from its locked case.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714856" id2="17" version="1065353216">But my comrade! He needs help! He needs a motivator....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Two battle droids are better than one. I'm going to find that motivator you need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714858" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should repair your damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent--as I said before, you should find one in a locked case, hidden in the junkyard. You're going to make it, buddy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such a waste of time and resources....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not my problem. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, comrade. We'll find someone else. We'll get you out of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714866" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're just wasting your time....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714868" id2="17" version="1065353216">I apologize, but my mission parameters do not permit conversation at this time.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
