<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>62</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/the_colicoid_war_game/imperial/darth_malgus.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="499967" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499968" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Darth Malgus. We've received the results of the competition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499970" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoids were impressed by the damage you inflicted. The Republic challengers did not survive. The outcome is clear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499971" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then the Colicoid leaders will sell weapons to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499971" id2="17" version="1065353216">So we'll get Colicoid tech?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499972" id2="17" version="1065353216">The contract is already signed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499974" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sort of team did the Republic field?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who was my competition?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499975" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic sent Jedi, with military and mercenary support. The mercenary escaped, and the others died.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Winning was simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499978" id2="17" version="1065353216">There were those in the Ministry of War who felt this challenge would demean us--that merely participating would be a sign of weakness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499980" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you have seen the weapons the Colicoids produce. Envision our armies supplied with such devices, and tell me we have not done well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499981" id2="17" version="1065353216">In war, every weapon must be seized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499981" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must take every advantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better equipment ends wars quickly, cleanly. That's worth any price.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499982" id2="17" version="1065353216">New tech will save lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your assistance in this matter will not be forgotten.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499984" id2="17" version="1065353216">The challenge was demeaning, and if Colicoid technology was as good as the insects claimed, I'd be dead. Tell that to the military.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499984" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't need their weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499985" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe our business is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="499987" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499988" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Darth Malgus to Vaiken Spacedock. An unusual opportunity has arisen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499990" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoids are an insectoid species from the Inner Rim, specializing in technological sales and development; you met their lesser cousins on Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499992" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoids' latest weapons and battle droids could change the course of the war. I desire those weapons for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499993" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sort of wartime technologies are the Colicoids offering?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about their weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Portable shielding, ion cannons, hunter drones and more. Ground wars could be won in months instead of years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499996" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Balmorran Colicoids were animals. You're saying these are merchants?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499996" id2="17" version="1065353216">But Colicoids are mindless....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499997" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Balmorran Colicoids were biological experiments, as I understand; these are their creators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499999" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have the Diplomatic Service for making trade agreements. Why am I here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499999" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not your negotiator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic representatives are also eager to obtain Colicoid weapons, so the insects have made a proposal:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Both Republic and Empire strike teams will compete in a war game. The Colicoids will sell technology exclusively to whichever side proves superior.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500003" id2="17" version="1065353216">What will this competition involve?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the war games.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500004" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoids could demand any number of things. Why make us fight for their business?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why arrange a competition?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500005" id2="17" version="1065353216">They wish to assess our forces before committing--there's no point in making allies who'll soon be defeated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500007" id2="17" version="1065353216">That &quot;proposal&quot; is demeaning. If the Colicoids won't trade, those weapons can be taken by force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's just conquer them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500008" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoid homeworld is far beyond Imperial space, and future developments would be lost to us; cooperation costs us nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500010" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoids have designated an asteroid hive as the battleground, containing traps and challenges designed to murder competitors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500012" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will represent the Empire and be tested by Colicoid machines, as well as their warriors--the insects place little value on individual Colicoid life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever force the Colicoids bring to bear pales before the power of a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500013" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will endure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500014" id2="17" version="1065353216">After what I did with their genetic material on Balmorra, those insects are practically family. I'll gladly pay a visit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500014" id2="17" version="1065353216">I always enjoy Colicoids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500015" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe I can help. But in return, you need to ensure the Colicoids and the Republic can't identify me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just keep my part quiet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500016" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll arrange it; I have no desire to compromise your undercover operations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500018" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I wanted to fight for an audience, I'd be a gladiator. Why should I bother?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500018" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't do tricks for cheap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500019" id2="17" version="1065353216">The payment is substantial. Consider it a chance to demonstrate that elaborate machines are no match for your ingenuity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500021" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want me to kill Colicoid soldiers so their leaders can decide whether you're a worthy client? It's despicable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500021" id2="17" version="1065353216">This whole thing is monstrous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wars are not won without bloodshed; do not hesitate because you fight insects instead of Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500024" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a coincidence--I don't value Colicoid life either.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="500024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time for a bug hunt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500025" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoids have been observing our forces for some time; do not assume standard tactics will win this competition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="500027" id2="17" version="1065353216">And do not fail. If the Republic wins because of our weakness, they will gain a technological advantage that could cost us a hundred worlds.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="500029" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
