<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>44</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/bronze/imperial/disgusting_native_life/alan_foreman.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197059" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're something else, the way you handled those Skel. Thanks again.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, you made it out of there alive? And you got the parts?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course you did. You're Sith. What was I thinking? Nothing stands a chance against a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not that I didn't think you could do it, but I wasn't going to bet against those creatures after seeing what they did to my crew.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197066" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. I'll get the shuttle running and get these parts to the outpost as quick as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bring back the engine parts, and kill a few Skel for me and my crew.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197071" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, hunter. Can you lend a fellow freelancer a hand?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ack. Sith! I mean, my lord! Please don't kill me! Please don't kill me! I need your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197075" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, don't kill me! I work for the Empire! Don't kill me!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me and my crew were running engine parts for the Imperials when these things attacked. Hairy, long-nosed monsters. Skel, I think they're called.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197079" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm the only one who survived. Everyone else got torn to pieces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197080" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd better have a good reason for stopping a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197080" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's this got to do with me?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197081" id2="17" version="1065353216">No disrespect, but I need a favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry. The Empire will not make the mistake of hiring you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Worthless weaklings.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197084" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't mind at all if it keeps me out of situations like this. We threw everything we had at those things!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry to hear about your people. Want to pay me to go bust up some Skel?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197086" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd be mad if I lost my crew.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Crew's dead. Nothing's bringing them back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197089" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dangers were part of the job. If you weren't ready for them, you shouldn't have accepted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197089" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should prepare better.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197090" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one's ever ready to die. But my crew was pouring blaster fire into those things, and they just wouldn't go down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197092" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why should I care?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197093" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's awful.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197094" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Skel ran off with the engine parts my crew and I were taking to the Imperial outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197096" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was paid to deliver those parts, and I don't like taking pay if I don't do the job. Course, I'm in no shape to attack the Skel.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197098" id2="17" version="1065353216">You look like you might actually be able to handle those things. Bring back the engine parts. I'll give you my pay, minus expenses, if that matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197099" id2="17" version="1065353216">I love risking my life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197100" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds good.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197101" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks. The Skel are hiding out in those caves. You get me those engine parts, and I'll see that they get to the outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197103" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll pass. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, thanks for your time. I hate to inconvenience anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197106" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be happy if I never have to see this planet again.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="673385" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heard you made the delivery. Hope you made those Talz bleed for me and my crew.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="673386" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire needs those power converters; there's good money in seeing them delivered.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="673387" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me and my crew were running power converters for the Imperials when these things attacked. Hairy, four-eyed monsters. Talz, I think they're called.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="673388" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why not cut your losses?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="673389" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was paid to deliver those parts, and I don't like taking pay if I don't do the job. Bad for future business.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="673390" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not just my problem anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="673392" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire needs power converters to keep its outposts running, but anybody who comes close to my shipment gets picked off by the Talz.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="673394" id2="17" version="1065353216">You look like you might actually be able to handle those things. Finish that delivery for me, and my partner'll give you my pay--minus expenses, if that matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="673395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's where those monsters got the drop on us. Recover the power converters, and Dar will have your credits waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="673397" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're feeling charitable, well, just make those freaks pay for me and my crew, all right?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
