<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>28</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/class/spy/pyther.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715929" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want something?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing more I can say to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715931" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, Chemish brought you in, eh? Too bad we didn't get to train together--I like teaching the new recruits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715933" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Pyther. I'm one of the old hands, from before the Eagle started his whole galaxy-wide campaign. Back when we just had Gray Star.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715934" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are the duties of an &quot;old hand&quot; around here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="715934" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715935" id2="17" version="1065353216">I show the new guys how to put together a bomb without getting killed. You can learn a lot about a person that way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, a lot of times what you learn is that they're pretty much doomed. Not their fault, but... these new guys are fodder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715939" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the story with Gray Star and the Eagle?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="715939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about your leaders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715940" id2="17" version="1065353216">The story? Look, the Eagle trained here. They say he was one of Gray Star's lieutenants before he took off and started finding allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me? I appreciate what the Eagle's done. Killing Darth Jadus, blowing up the Dominator--that took guts. But Gray Star's the guy I follow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715944" id2="17" version="1065353216">What made you get involved with the resistance?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="715944" id2="17" version="1065353216">How'd you join up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715945" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Republic fled Balmorra and let the Imperials take over, mom and dad got killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715947" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll never forgive the Empire for what they did to this planet--or the Republic, either, for leaving us to rot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without Gray Star, I wouldn't have much hope for Balmorra. But he knows what he's doing. He can make a weapon out of a farm boy. He'll get us out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gray Star could be the one to save us all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="715950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715951" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715953" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me what Gray Star's like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="715953" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hear more about him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715954" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never met him, but I've seen his messages. He's not as charismatic as the Eagle, but he's smart. That's all I need in a leader.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715956" id2="17" version="1065353216">You take care of yourself now--I need to get back to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715957" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really believe violence will save you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="715957" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we're hurting people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715958" id2="17" version="1065353216">We won't get our freedom back unless we fight for it. You know that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="715960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, I've got to get back to work. Trying to clean the gunk out of some droid parts we salvaged. I'll see you around.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
