<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>137</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x3/hk_51/republic/hk_51/bren.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667581" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm staying put. There's a lot more I need to see if we're going to get these HK units out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's your cargo manifest. The Fatality was carrying HK droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667584" id2="17" version="1065353216">HK droids haven't been seen in the galaxy for decades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667587" id2="17" version="1065353216">What exactly is an HK droid? What are they used for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain these HKs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better head for the Fatality now. It isn't getting any warmer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally! I've been comming the Republic for days. Starting to get frostbite out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667640" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can kill each other for all I care. I want to know what's in that wreck that's worth fighting for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trust me-- whatever's down there, it's big.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always nice to see a warm, friendly face. Well, a friendly one, anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027989" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have everything we need to reactivate the HK droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything except the best droid engineer in the sector. Luckily, he owes me a favor. He'll meet you inside the Fatality when it's clear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027992" id2="17" version="1065353216">And yes, that means enemy forces have retaken the ship. This time, a Sith calling himself the Lord of Agony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027993" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fought more than a few Sith getting these parts. One more shouldn't make much difference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027993" id2="17" version="1065353216">He won't be a problem for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027994" id2="17" version="1065353216">This one's not your average Sith. He tore through a platoon of our soldiers like they were flimsiplast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whom does this lord serve? The Dread Masters, the Empire, or himself?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me who he works for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does it matter? He's between us and an army of assassin droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027999" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess it's too much to hope that he attacks people with boring conversation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027999" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't sound good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028000" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, that's the Lord of Annoyance. Different guy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say what you want about Sith, but I appreciate their openness. You always know what their hobbies and interests are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028002" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least he's honest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Personally, I'd prefer they keep more to themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028005" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic couldn't spare a platoon to secure the Fatality while I was gone?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028005" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did this happen?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028006" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic assigned a whole company to guard the crash site. It didn't make any difference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028008" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'll have to change his nickname to the Lord of Corpses when I'm done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, I'll kill him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028009" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think that name's taken. Wicked little guy on Nar Shaddaa. You don't want to know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028011" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're in for a nightmare of a fight, but it's the only way to keep those HK droids out of enemy hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once the Fatality is safe to enter, my engineer friend will head inside. Not much of a talker, but he gets the job done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028015" id2="17" version="1065353216">...and that ship is filled with them. Some kind of secret Imperial project. No wonder our friends are fighting over that wreck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028016" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't explain why the Fatality came to Belsavis years ago. Was the Empire planning to use those droids here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028016" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's more to this story.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not the Empire--an apprentice of the Dread Masters. According to this, he stole the Fatality and its HKs at their command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Skipped history class? The HK model was the deadliest assassin droid ever produced. The most famous one was made to order for Darth Revan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's demolish that ship and be rid of this threat once and for all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028020" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should destroy the droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028021" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hang on, we're talking about serious hardware--the kind that wins wars for whoever controls it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028023" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's all starting to make sense. The Dread Masters used their powers to guide the Fatality and its HKs here to stage a breakout.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028025" id2="17" version="1065353216">That plan failed, but now our enemies can use the droids for something much worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028026" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the damage potential of these droids? How much could they do to us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028026" id2="17" version="1065353216">The droids are that powerful?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028027" id2="17" version="1065353216">A single HK droid operating alone can easily eliminate military, political and economic leaders. The Fatality holds dozens of HKs. An army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028029" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Houk and his minions are all dead. The Dread Masters aren't a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028029" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we defeated their forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028030" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're not our only enemies. What if the Empire gets these things--or the Hutt Cartel?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028032" id2="17" version="1065353216">There wasn't a single HK droid on the ship that wasn't damaged and frozen in ice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028032" id2="17" version="1065353216">The HKs I saw were broken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028033" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can bet our enemies have a plan to fix them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028035" id2="17" version="1065353216">HK droids are a bigger advantage than our enemies deserve. We've got to get those things out of the Fatality and working for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028036" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can we use something designed for evil to do anything good?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028036" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure I agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assassination isn't the Republic's style--but if we take out enough Sith to end this war we'll be saving billions of lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028038" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could do a lot of good with an assassin droid on my team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028038" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about working for me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Considering how many defeats you've personally handed the Empire, I'd say you're exactly who needs an HK unit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028041" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard assassin droids have a tendency to kill their own masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028041" id2="17" version="1065353216">HKs shouldn't be trusted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only the ones with poor programming. Remember, they're just machines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Problem is, the Fatality's droids were all damaged in the crash. They've spent years on ice, but we need them working yesterday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Schematics and spare parts are the key ingredients. I know for a fact Czerka Corporation maintains HK designs in their laboratory databases.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028047" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it's the only way to ensure the HKs don't wind up in enemy hands, I'll do whatever it takes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then let's get them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028048" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got a track record for achieving the impossible, master Jedi. I like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028050" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt Czerka's leaders will just hand over the schematics. That doesn't leave us too many legal options.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028050" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028051" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't need Czerka's permission. They desert their operations without wiping the databanks all the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028053" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll start by asking Czerka nicely. If that doesn't work, I know lots of other ways to ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028053" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can get whatever we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028054" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think we can do this without going to war with an entire corporation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028056" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good old Czerka... you can always count on those guys to have things they shouldn't. Time for a little breaking and entering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028056" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028057" id2="17" version="1065353216">Probably more of the former than the latter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028059" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic has no business reactivating murderous droids designed by the Empire. This will end badly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028059" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want no part of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unlike people, droids can be reprogrammed. If anything goes wrong, we'll pull the plug.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028062" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the spy. Go fetch those things yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. Go and get them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028063" id2="17" version="1065353216">In case it's not obvious, I'm the kind of spy who's good at watching and not much else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028065" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a lead on one private Czerka complex. Raiding it won't be easy, but what is? The rest will be up to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get the schematics and whatever parts we'll need. I'll maintain position and watch the Fatality until you get back. Be seeing you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Name's Bren. I'm SIS. Been tracking intel reports of Imperial activity in Belsavis's frigid zone. Nothing's supposed to be here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turns out there's something: the &quot;Fatality.&quot; Imperial destroyer downed years ago. The Dread Masters' forces are holding it like she's still spaceworthy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028071" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire didn't know Belsavis existed until recently. Are you saying one of their warships came here that long ago?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028071" id2="17" version="1065353216">That ship shouldn't be here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028072" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic brass locked down the incident tighter than a Sith Lord's helmet, but yeah--that recent invasion wasn't the first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028074" id2="17" version="1065353216">So the Imperials aren't the only ones after this wreck. That ship must really be something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dread Master forces, too?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028075" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get me wrong, the Fatality's a write-off--which makes this all the more interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once the Imperials and the Dread Masters have softened each other up, we can carpet bomb the lot of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. Let them fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028078" id2="17" version="1065353216">Been piecing together old intel reports. Long time back, shortly after the Dread Masters' capture, the Fatality paid Belsavis a surprise visit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028080" id2="17" version="1065353216">We shot it down before it could do much damage. Looked like the vessel disintegrated on impact. No more Imp ships came, so we figured it was a fluke.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028081" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hard to believe an Imperial destroyer accidentally stumbled onto the Republic's top-secret prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028081" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was no coincidence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028082" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's how it looked then... but the Dread Masters knew to look for the Fatality's wreckage. I'm thinking it came here to rescue them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028084" id2="17" version="1065353216">No escape pods launched before the Fatality went down? It must have been a short fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028084" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did anyone survive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028085" id2="17" version="1065353216">We got lucky--cracked the enemy's reactor with our first hit. Crew died from radiation exposure. Better than freezing under the ice, I guess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028087" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there's more to that wreck than scrap metal, whoever shot down the Fatality didn't do his job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our people failed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028088" id2="17" version="1065353216">We scanned the Fatality's crash site and found nothing. Now I know why--the Imp vessel went deep under the ice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028090" id2="17" version="1065353216">I got close to the fighting out there. The Dread Masters' forces are a nasty bunch, led by a mean mountain of a Houk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028092" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imps are terrified of this guy. Heard the commander telling his men the Houk's hunting them for sport. Can't argue with that assessment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028093" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial soldiers don't scare easily. The leader of the Dread Masters' forces must be especially dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028093" id2="17" version="1065353216">Neither can I.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028094" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen this Houk, master Jedi. &quot;Dangerous&quot; is an understatement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028096" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sense great evil at work here. The Dread Masters have sent something malignant to protect their objective.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028096" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a very bad feeling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028097" id2="17" version="1065353216">My guess? The Imperials bought us very little time to sort this out in our favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028099" id2="17" version="1065353216">If your intel's right, the Dread Masters have the upper hand here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028099" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems like the Houk's winning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028100" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've definitely got position. The Houk and his men are down in the wreck, and the Imps are outside licking their wounds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028101" id2="17" version="1065353216">What I'm hearing is, challenging the Houk to a game of sabacc probably isn't an option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028101" id2="17" version="1065353216">There goes my sly approach.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028102" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think he plays cards. Might eat them, I suppose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028103" id2="17" version="1065353216">If either enemy force had caught you watching them, this conversation wouldn't be happening.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028103" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're lucky to be alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028104" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the spy lifestyle. Glamorous as it sounds, I decided to fall back when I saw that Houk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028105" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've faced all kinds of predators, animal and otherwise. The Imperials may be easily frightened, but I'm not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028105" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that supposed to scare me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028106" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fear's not the issue. This Dread Master legion is vicious and dug in deep.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever's inside the Fatality, we don't want the Imps or Dread Masters getting it. People like you could make sure they don't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028108" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't listen to all this just to say &quot;no.&quot; Of course I'll help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028108" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count me in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028109" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they aren't fighting over some ancient secret weapon that could crack the galaxy in half, I'll be very disappointed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028109" id2="17" version="1065353216">This better be worth my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028110" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make sure the Fatality earns it name. Dread Master forces... Imperial troops... they all die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028110" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll kill them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028111" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate thoroughness, but don't lose sight of what these people are chasing. That's the prize.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028113" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm giving you coordinates to the Fatality's excavation site. Send the competition packing and hunt down the ship's cargo manifest. Then we'll know what we're dealing with. Be seeing you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to you, maybe now we can get the rest of those HK droids working for the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028344" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a Czerka complex you can raid for the schematics. At least give it a look before making up your mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regardless, I'm stuck here until the Republic sends reinforcements. Be seeing you--I hope.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
