<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>37</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x3/hk_51/republic/hk_51/hk_51.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701404" id2="17" version="1065353216">Declaration: Self-diagnostics complete. Personality matrix updated. All systems go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Salutation: Greetings, master. I am HK-51. I am armed, operational and... at your command?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701408" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observation: I previously served the Sith Empire. Now I serve you. That is unexpected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701409" id2="17" version="1065353216">What did the Empire program you for, HK?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701409" id2="17" version="1065353216">List your functions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Summation: My primary function is enemy elimination with extreme prejudice. Secondary functions include threat analysis, bodyguard duties and pleasant conversation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clarification: I will obey your commands regardless. I am, first and foremost, a professional.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't even think about running off or making trouble. I fought a lot of people to reactivate you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Obey me or you're scrap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reassurance: I have neither the desire nor ability to disobey you. My functions are entirely at your disposal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701418" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will serve you and whatever political body you represent. I am a stable, reliable and efficient assassin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Query: Your lightsaber indicates you are a Jedi, master. We are duty-bound to hunt down and destroy Sith, correct?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Usually it's the Sith hunting down and destroying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701421" id2="17" version="1065353216">More like defend ourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701422" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi uses the Force for knowledge and defense, never for attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701422" id2="17" version="1065353216">More like defend ourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Acknowledgment: Of course, master. I will defend you. I will defend you until your enemies lie dead around us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any chance we get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Query: You wear the insignia of the Republic military, master. Will we be involved in heavy combat against the Empire?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701427" id2="17" version="1065353216">We do whatever's necessary to protect the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701427" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we're ordered to, yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Satisfaction: I am certain your enemies will provide many opportunities for me to make myself useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Query: Your appearance fairly screams, &quot;shoot me.&quot; Will we be eliminating your enemies on a regular basis, master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701431" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a people person. I try not to kill anyone I don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701431" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701432" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reassurance: Enemies are not people, master. They are targets and deserve what is coming to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701434" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the feeling you want me to say &quot;yes.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does that please you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreement: I am a Hunter-Killer unit, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any chance we get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Affirmation: Our objectives are in perfect alignment. I foresee no difficulties serving your needs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701440" id2="17" version="1065353216">Information: I will locate your starship and familiarize myself with your crew. I promise not to eliminate anyone without your authorization.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="701446" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This HK unit has been deactivated for quite some time. It will not respond to commands.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028343" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is serving someone who isn't Imperial a problem for you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028343" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sound disappointed.</text>
		<text bitflag="7489" id1="1030931" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's active. I recommend not turning your back on it. Good luck!</text>
		<text bitflag="7489" id1="1030932" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Tarnahok. Bren sent me. I can't believe I'm actually doing this, but a favor's a favor. Give me the parts--I'll get to work on that droid.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
