<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>9</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/heroic_weekly/imperial/mission_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173166" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corporal Xeleste has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Highmount Ridge sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Corporal Xeleste may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173167" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Doresh has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Icefall Plains sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Lieutenant Doresh may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Vujaar has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Starship Graveyard sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Captain Vujaar may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Kavsun has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Glacial Fissure sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Sergeant Kavsun may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177352" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Switts has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Captain Switts may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177353" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Zeleron has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Lieutenant Zeleron may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Viatar has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Captain Viatar may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177355" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Varos has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Lord Varos may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Jerrod has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Captain Jerrod may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
