<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>65</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/world/republic/art_of_interrogation/uli_zhensi.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="648979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm. Calm now. Who would have thought?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="648980" id2="17" version="1065353216">They made it out! Bola and Uthril and Nug, they escaped in the confusion!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="648982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry. Too loud? The torture machines, they're irreparable without someone who knows them. They're complete slag.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="648984" id2="17" version="1065353216">And my cohorts, my co-workers, my family, they're free of the machines. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="648985" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire will no doubt sweep the area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="648985" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="648986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure. But without machines or repair staff, they'll be forced to scrap their little project.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="648988" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the meantime, we'll get the victims somewhere off-planet to heal and disappear. They've been through a lot.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="648990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for all you've done. For once, desperation on this moon turned into something good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="648991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Credits say &quot;thank you&quot; too.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="648992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, I promised, didn't I? Everything... well, I don't have much, but here it is.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="648994" id2="17" version="1065353216">You saved my adopted family. It means something to them, and more, to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="648996" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you hadn't saved them, I'd probably be on a bridge somewhere on the wrong side of the railing. So... see you around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="648997" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't realize your family was in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="648997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your family?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="648998" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, not blood relatives, I lost those long ago. These workers are my adopted family.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649000" id2="17" version="1065353216">To most people on Nar Shaddaa, family's just another angle, but not to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649002" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is as close as we come to having honor on this moon. Thank you for making that possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649004" id2="17" version="1065353216">The machines. Smash the torture machines!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649005" id2="17" version="1065353216">You! Do you have a blaster? I need a blaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Damn Imperials think I'll do nothing. You can't figure everything out with torture!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well? How about it? Can I have a blaster?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649010" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure that decision can wait until you relax a little.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm down.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Relax? Every minute here is fine for you and me, but it's agony for....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Medication not working today?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649013" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see you're completely nuts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, call me crazy. That's fair. When they take your friends, your job, they put you in the machine....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain yourself, first.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Huh? Oh, yeah, I might be coming at this wrong. A day in the device will do that to your mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hi. I'm Uli. I maintained machines in the Empire's Project Threshold, an experimental, uh, training program in the art of interrogation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why should I help an Imperial torturer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649020" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're an interrogator?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649021" id2="17" version="1065353216">We just maintained the machines! And after a while, we couldn't even stand that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649023" id2="17" version="1065353216">You... you see things in a place like that. So we broke in one night to, uh... sabotage the machines. And they caught us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649025" id2="17" version="1065353216">You gotta help me here. The other guys... they're on the machines now, all they know is pain. I gotta break the machines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649026" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose that's one way of paying the bills.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did what you had to, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't judge me. We needed the jobs, but after a few months of... seeing things, we couldn't stand it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649029" id2="17" version="1065353216">We tried to sabotage the torture machines, but they got us. I barely escaped, and the others....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649031" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're still babbling.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649032" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm saying, my men and I maintained experimental Imperial torture machinery. Then we had an attack of conscience.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649034" id2="17" version="1065353216">But when we tried to sabotage the machines, we got caught. Only a few of us escaped.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649036" id2="17" version="1065353216">The others are in the machines. I need--someone needs to save them. They're hurt, dying in there. I gotta break these machines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649037" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire won't do this on my watch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649037" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Brave. You haven't seen what happens to those who fail. But nevermind that. Destroy the machines and their guards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649040" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is good you came to me. I will ease their pain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649040" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will free them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649041" id2="17" version="1065353216">The devices are the target. They'll be guarded, but guards will be replaced. These machines can't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649043" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get your men out of these devices. Point me at them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649043" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds clear-cut. I'm in.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649044" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll be guarded, but I don't think they'll be prepared for someone like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649046" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I touch it, consider it broken. This'll be easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649046" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm good at that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful in there. Since our attempt, they've doubled the number of soldiers around the machines.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649049" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if there's an officer or archon in there, end him. I won't list his crimes, just know they are unspeakable.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649051" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for doing this. In return... in return, everything I have is yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there a reward for helping?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649053" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you free them, you can have whatever I've got.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649055" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just destroy the machines, and watch out for the archon overseeing the project. He is merciless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649057" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I believed even half this stuff, I'd be a fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649057" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're lying. [Refuse quest.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649058" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know how I sound. Why do you think no one listens?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="649060" id2="17" version="1065353216">A blaster. I need a blaster.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
