<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>37</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/bronze/imperial/corsec_crackdown/raddus_venn.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235223" id2="17" version="1065353216">Streets are already starting to feel safer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235225" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've dealt with your friends in CorSec.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235226" id2="17" version="1065353216">They weren't my friends. They were reckless, put innocent lives in danger. Had to be put down.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235228" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't mean I'm doing cartwheels, though. They were Corellians, former comrades. Still... thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235230" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, try to keep the fighting off the streets if you can. Don't want any civilians getting caught in the cross fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235231" id2="17" version="1065353216">This fighting's got to stop! There's good folk dying out there, all because those CorSec boneheads don't know when to quit.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235233" id2="17" version="1065353216">Used to wear the uniform myself once, back when it still meant something.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235235" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now CorSec's just a bunch of trigger-happy hooligans with more ammo than common sense. Always looking for a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235236" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least you had the good sense to submit to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235236" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were wise to give in.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235237" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those other so-called &quot;officers&quot; would've done the same if they actually cared about the public's safety.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235239" id2="17" version="1065353216">The sooner they accept Imperial control, the sooner we can put this bloodshed behind us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235239" id2="17" version="1065353216">They should surrender.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235240" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I told 'em. But they only care about winning. Don't give a hoot about protecting the citizens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235242" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some people just refuse to admit when they're beat. Hard to bring those types in alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235242" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sound pretty stubborn.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235243" id2="17" version="1065353216">Afraid that may be true here, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235245" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you have any information on these insurgents, I suggest you share it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235245" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know their operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235246" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like ratting anyone out, but they've crossed the line, endangering the populace like they have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't expect to see a CorSec officer supporting the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Strange loyalties you have.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235249" id2="17" version="1065353216">Former officer. I joined CorSec to uphold the law. The Empire's the law here now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235251" id2="17" version="1065353216">You hope I'll handle them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235252" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone needs to bring a little peace and order to this city.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235254" id2="17" version="1065353216">These streets would be a lot safer without those hotheads blasting everything in sight.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235256" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen, ah... my lord? If you wanted to give some of those CorSec boys a stomping, I might be able to help out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235257" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're looking to give some of those CorSec boys a good kicking, I can point you in the right direction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235258" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235259" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't say &quot;no&quot; to a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235260" id2="17" version="1065353216">As long as I get my credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235261" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got some funds available. They're yours if you can get this done quiet-like.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shouldn't be hard to draw them out. Just swipe a comm array off a CorSec probe droid and activate its distress signal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't be long before they come a-running. These things tend to escalate fast, so try to activate that signal someplace secluded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235267" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not now. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope you change your mind. These people have seen enough violence.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia's in Imperial hands now. Best everyone just accept it and move on.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
