<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>36</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/voss/bronze/republic/findsman/findsman.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85142" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your signs speak well of you. But this Findsman must continue his work.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85143" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Findsman has read your success in the dust and footprints of this place. Let him see you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. Your signs are changed, and speak to him clearly. Ellrak gone, and enlightenment gained.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85147" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Findsman will see your gathered knowledge reaches Master Halykus. The signs speak of time, water, age, darkness.... The truth must be known.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85149" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Findsman will continue his meditations, until you have the signs he needs.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85150" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Findsman would speak with you. Your face, your walk... they speak signs to him.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85152" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Findsman has come to aid those who suffer here, by following these Gormak that harry them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85154" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic scouts seek in one way, but this Findsman uses another. He finds truth in footsteps, in echoes, in patterns of light. Perhaps his seeking is strange to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85155" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand. Not everything we know comes from mundane sources.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85155" id2="17" version="1065353216">No stranger than the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85156" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't scorn wisdom, no matter where it comes from.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knowledge is found everywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85157" id2="17" version="1065353216">To read the movement of clouds, count falling leaves and see data--this is a Findsman's task.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85159" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can respect your skills. I serve alongside another Findsman, Yuun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85159" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, I have a Findsman.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85160" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Findsman with a name? Then this Findsman would value your help even more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85162" id2="17" version="1065353216">This galaxy would be a boring gray ball if we were all the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85162" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone's different.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85163" id2="17" version="1065353216">You speak a great truth. But this Findsman is concerned with smaller ones.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85165" id2="17" version="1065353216">You look like an ordinary Gand to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85165" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is a &quot;Findsman&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85166" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Findsmen read the world to find what--or whom--must be found. This Findsman has been bounty hunter, scout and investigator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85168" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Truth is built of emotion, events, context and memory. Science answers only a few. This Findsman needs all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85171" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak scouts are led by Ellrak, a being full of anger and cunning. He has done great harm, and no Republic scout can find him.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85173" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Findsman would show you Findsman ways. To find Ellrak, and learn the Gormak signs. It will help in your search for what they seek.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85174" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you need these signs to finish your investigation, I'll do what I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85174" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85175" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the first step?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85176" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Findsman uses a scanner to record signs, for meditation. Use it to see what must be seen, and follow what it shows you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bird flights suggest beginning at the nearby survey station, the last place raided by Ellrak's men. Let the signs guide you from there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85180" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Findsman offers his thanks. He will meditate until you return.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85182" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a chance. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85183" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Findsman read you wrongly? He must meditate on this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85185" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Findsman cannot read you. Not now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572865" id2="17" version="1065353216">That could be useful.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
