<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>66</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/world/the_mandalorian_terror/alya_selray.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467500" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sej has been spreading the word about what you did. Even Republic Command got wind of it. You're a hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467501" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see you were successful. We're going to leak word that the Empire tried to sell Balmorrans as slaves and how the Republic rescued them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because of what you did, we may actually gain support. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467504" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was an honor to assist you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467505" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could do with more of that kind of help around here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467507" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have to admit--it was touch and go for a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Mandalorians were tough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467508" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you came through in the end. That's all that matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467510" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467511" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think the Imperials will bother hiring mercenaries anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467513" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have been... doubting the Republic. It seemed you were using us to satisfy grudges against the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467515" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you have restored my faith in the Republic's motives. You didn't have to go in to the mercenary camp, but you did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467517" id2="17" version="1065353216">You saved my people, and for that, I thank you. Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time is our enemy here. The longer you wait, the more chance the Balmorrans will be shipped offworld.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467522" id2="17" version="1065353216">You lied to me, Alya. You promised to keep us safe! Where was your &quot;protection&quot; when we needed it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467524" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, Sej. We lost some good people, too, but we'll fix this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right on time. I told you Command would come through--these people are responsible for disabling the Imperial satellite network. Your people are as good as rescued.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right on time. I told you Command would come through--this group has done more to damage the Empire than anyone else. Your people are as good as rescued.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi. You see? Command is taking this seriously. With a Jedi's help, your people will be rescued in no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect timing, Captain. You see? Command is taking this seriously. They've sent Special Forces to rescue your people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467530" id2="17" version="1065353216">I told you Command would come through. This person has done more damage to the Empire than an entire army. Your people are as good as rescued.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right on cue. You see? Command is taking this seriously. They've sent the person responsible for taking out the Imperial satellites to rescue your people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Back up a second. Has someone been kidnapped?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who needs rescuing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Balmorran villagers. You didn't know? Then... you aren't from Republic Command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Command didn't send me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Really? Then fate must be smiling at us, because you're just who we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467538" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have neither the time nor desire to hear your problems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467539" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no idea what you're talking about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave me alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, pal, it's my day off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't bother me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please. You have to help--at least listen. Please.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="467543" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Alya Selray, Republic ambassador to the Balmorran people. It's my job to make sure civilians are kept safe during the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="467545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Safe? Republic Command doesn't supply enough soldiers to keep a child safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sej is one of the local leaders. He stepped up after the others were wiped out--but what he says is true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic soldiers were supposed to escort us to a safe zone. But Mandalorian mercenaries attacked--wiped your people out, killed half of my village and kidnapped the rest!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467550" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to get out there and bring your people back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467550" id2="17" version="1065353216">The villagers must be rescued.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467551" id2="17" version="1065353216">That monster has probably sold them off by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467553" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the point in kidnapping villagers?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why kidnap them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467554" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those mercenaries need to see what happens when you attack civilians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467554" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Mandalorians must pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467555" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Mandalorians need to see the business end of a blaster rifle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467555" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mercs need a lesson.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467556" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mercenaries need to be shown what happens when you ally yourself with the dark side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time for punishment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467557" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree; their boss thinks nothing can touch him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467559" id2="17" version="1065353216">The leader of the Mandalorians is Monta Drai. They work for the Empire, but Monta has a slave trade operating on the side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467561" id2="17" version="1065353216">He has gotten away with his crimes for too long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467563" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree, but our main priority is getting those villagers back before they're shipped offworld. Taking Monta down would be a bonus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467565" id2="17" version="1065353216">Besides... if we fail in this, the Balmorrans may withdraw their support for the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467566" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get the safe zone ready. I'll have those Balmorrans out in no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467566" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get the villagers back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch your back out there. The Mandalorians are better trained than the Empire's soldiers. They have snipers, shock troops, everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467570" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've set up camp outside the city. That's where they'll be holding the prisoners. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, but rescuing villagers isn't really my thing. I'm sure Command will send someone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not my job. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467575" id2="17" version="1065353216">I really hope so. We don't have much time left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467579" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't talk now. I've got a blaster wound to take care of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467581" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll rescue the villagers and take care of Monta Drai. He'll see the consequences of accepting the Empire's money.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="467581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rescue, check; kill, check.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="467582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. But make sure you focus on the villagers, first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764184" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there's no one else.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
