<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>713</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/nco.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835275" version="1065353216">Juvard Illip Oggurobb</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835275" version="1065353216">Few engineers can boast to have singlehandedly ignited a war with the power of their genius, but Doctor Juvard Illip Oggurobb is a Hutt quite unlike any other. A master of engineering, both as a discipline and an art form, it was Dr. Oggurobb who invented the theories and designs behind isotope-5 technology. While his true specialty lies in droid design, Dr. Oggurobb's brilliance extends to most any technical field, his genius matched only by his boldness of personality, and his passion for &quot;technical artistry.&quot;

Dr. Oggurobb is your alliance's engineering specialist, leading the group's research and development efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="835275" version="1065353216">Artist of Technology</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835407" version="1065353216">Blizz</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835407" version="1065353216">Infinitely curious and adventuresome, Blizz always felt confined on his native Tatooine--the endless rolling dunes and limited selection of scrap leaving him perpetually bored. So when the traveling salvager Slam Streever visited Blizz's clan to offer Jawas work as &quot;ferrets&quot;--individuals he could send into dangerous and dilapidated areas to scout for salvage treasure--Blizz leapt at the opportunity.

Blizz spent several years with Slam's crew before the old scrapper made the mistake of selling his services to Hoth's White Maw pirates. Years of toil under the menacing watch of the White Maw would soon deprive the salvagers of reasons to smile--but first, Slam gave his small friend the nickname &quot;Blizz&quot; after the little Jawa kicked up a snowstorm of excitement during his first encounter with the &quot;white sands.&quot; It's a name Blizz cherishes; one that reminds him of happier times.

Likes: Adventure, gadgets, attention, praise, friendship
Dislikes: Scary things, extreme violence, people who are mean to him</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835407" version="1065353216">Blizz has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835408" version="1065353216">Gault Rennow</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835408" version="1065353216">Formerly the notorious smuggler and confidence man Tyresius Lokai, Gault Rennow now enjoys a relatively paranoia-free lifestyle as an unknown gun-for-hire. Still, old habits are hard to shake, and Gault's cautiousness and duplicity are a constant reminder that the only thing to really change is his name. How long until the crafty Devaronian finds himself climbing up the galaxy's most wanted list again is anyone's guess.

Likes: Greed, indulgence, thinking your way through a problem
Dislikes: Fair fights, pain, charity, rules</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835408" version="1065353216">Gault Rennow has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835411" version="1065353216">Mako</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835411" version="1065353216">At first glance, Mako's relationship with Braden seems more like that of a father and daughter than members of a team of professional bounty hunters--and that assessment wouldn't be too far off the mark. 

Orphaned and homeless but with an uncanny instinct for computing, Mako had been living as a freelance slicer in the shadows of Nar Shaddaa's underbelly... until the day Braden pulled the girl bleeding out of an alley, and paid a street surgeon to patch her blaster burns.

Recognizing talent and trouble when he saw it, Braden took Mako under his wing and has been looking after her as his own ever since. But while Mako loves the old man more than anything, her independent nature is beginning to chafe under Braden's protectiveness.

Likes: Professionalism, bounty hunters, making money, freedom, kindness
Dislikes: Bullying, cruelty, snobs</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835411" version="1065353216">Mako has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. Her current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835431" version="1065353216">Skadge</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835431" version="1065353216">A career gangster and psychopath, Skadge had been enjoying a prestigious position at the top of Coruscant's most wanted list when a joint police, military and SIS task force managed to finally capture him. Deemed impossible to control or reform, the murderous Houk was secretly ushered to the only facility capable of housing him: Belsavis.

Although considered a prime candidate for the prison's domination experiments, Skadge was removed from the program during his initial evaluation--a period over which he destroyed a gang of armed Kaleesh, every remaining member of his test group, half the observing researchers and three security details... with his bare hands.

Now, with the Imperial invasion of Belsavis, Skadge has been set loose after nearly three years of solitary confinement. He's ready to settle some grudges.

Likes: Violence, causing suffering, destruction, bullying
Dislikes: Compromise, taking orders, weakness</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835431" version="1065353216">Skadge has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835433" version="1065353216">Torian Cadera</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835433" version="1065353216">It is the Mandalorian ideal that a warrior be judged by his or her own actions, not by those of his or her ancestors--but reality rarely lives up to ideals.

Torian Cadera has spent his entire short life trying to overcome the stigma of being a traitor's son--a shame he has seldom been allowed to forget in the company of his peers. But Torian long ago learned to armor himself against contempt, and others' doubts regarding his loyalty have only driven him to strive harder to prove his worth.

Because of this, Torian adheres to the codes and traditions of the Mandalorians with more devotion than many twice his age. Upholding honor and enduring adversity are the cornerstones of his existence.

Likes: Challenges, honor, Mandalorians, respect
Dislikes: Selling out, cowardice</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835433" version="1065353216">Torian Cadera has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835435" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Felix Iresso</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835435" version="1065353216">The son of refugees made homeless during the Great War, Lieutenant Felix Iresso has been a career soldier for many years. His file shows participation in several notable battles, including the so-called Eight-Hour Invasion of Dubrillion where Republic forces repelled an Imperial invasion force with minimal reinforcements. Since then, Lieutenant Iresso has earned excellent technical scores and commendations for exemplary service.

However, his file also contains some discrepancies. Lieutenant Iresso has one of the highest transfer rates in the Republic military, serving under almost a dozen commanders across the galaxy in two years. The lieutenant has also been overlooked for promotion several times. The only explanation from his superiors is a reference to an incident on Althir where Lieutenant Iresso was captured by the Empire, but no details are given.

Likes: Republic military, leadership, danger for the greater good, honor and mercy
Dislikes: Breaking the law, cruelty</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835435" version="1065353216">Felix Iresso has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835436" version="1065353216">Qyzen Fess</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835436" version="1065353216">In contrast to many Trandoshans, Qyzen Fess rejected the path of a mercenary to become a hunter of the galaxy's most dangerous beasts. Earning &quot;Jagannath points&quot; with every honorable kill, Qyzen has traveled for years, seeking worthy prey and honoring his goddess, the Scorekeeper. Although his travels have brought him to Tython several times, he is never seen by the Jedi if Yuon Par is not at the temple. 

Despite his disdain of fame and fortune, Qyzen has attracted some notoriety. He often slips through apparently watertight Imperial borders to follow his prey, much to the consternation of the Empire's officials. Qyzen is also the only living hunter to have killed a greater crested gundark, thought extinct for centuries. His simple habits and devotion to the Scorekeeper give him common ground with the Jedi, though many disapprove of the attitudes and instincts that come naturally to a Trandoshan.

Likes: Killing powerful enemies, encouraging others to defend themselves, danger, honor
Dislikes: Killing the weak, mercenary work, sparing powerful enemies</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835436" version="1065353216">Qyzen Fess has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835437" version="1065353216">Nadia Grell</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835437" version="1065353216">A native of distant Sarkhai and daughter of Senator Tobas Grell, Nadia Grell is a newcomer not only to the Republic, but to the entire concept of space exploration. Surrounded by new species and strange cultures, Nadia is eager to experience everything she can. She has become interested in the intricacies of galactic diplomacy while traveling alongside her father, and often acts as his assistant during talks.

As she revealed on Attis Station, Nadia is also strong in the Force; unusually strong, in fact. As Force sensitives are relatively unknown on Sarkhai, Nadia's untrained powers left her shunned and feared by her own people. Senator Grell's decision to take her with him when he left Sarkhai was motivated by the hope of finding others like her in the Republic, and perhaps discovering some way for her to control her incredible talents. 

Likes: Learning, helping the weak, charity, mercy, testing her powers
Dislikes: Cruelty, dark Jedi, insulting authority</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835437" version="1065353216">Nadia Grell has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. Her current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835438" version="1065353216">Tharan Cedrax</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835438" version="1065353216">Although not a household name, Tharan Cedrax is well known in several circles. In the casinos of Nar Shaddaa, he is cursed as a card-counting mathematical genius. To the eligible women of the galaxy, he is a famous charmer who sees rejection as an intriguing challenge. Among technologists, he earned accolades for solving a technical paradox that revolutionized computer slicing; despite his achievements, however, Tharan isn't taken seriously by the galaxy's scientific community, which looks down on him as a playboy rather than a serious researcher.

In recent years, Tharan has taken an interest in &quot;exo-technology,&quot; an almost unknown field involving esoteric alien sciences, and gone into business making custom gadgets for wealthy clients. Often accompanied by his lovely holographic companion, Holiday, Tharan has spent his credits freely, enjoying the very best Nar Shaddaa has to offer while staying just shy of its dangers. 

Likes: Cleverness, logical thinking, aiding scientists and beautiful women, getting something for nothing
Dislikes: Mystical Jedi nonsense, Force Persuade, destroying science, heroism that involves danger</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835438" version="1065353216">Tharan Cedrax has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835448" version="1065353216">Zenith</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835448" version="1065353216">&quot;Zenith&quot; is the code name of a Balmorran revolutionary fighter who has made a career out of hurting the Empire. Once a member of a powerful resistance cell broken up by Imperial infiltrators, Zenith has struck out on his own, gathering followers from Balmorra's oppressed population to launch sneak attacks, raids and bombings against the occupying Imperial forces. 

Years spent in hiding and seeing the plight of Balmorran citizens have left Zenith with a deep-seated paranoia and hatred of the Empire--especially Balmorra's Sith governor, Darth Lachris. Nothing enrages him more than those who collaborate with the oppressors; he has been known to refuse aid to Balmorrans who cooperate with Imperial soldiers. The sacrifices he has endured have also nurtured Zenith's ambitions--when Balmorra is finally free, someone will have to ensure her new government is strong enough to prevent another occupation.

Likes: Hurting Imperials, standing up for the weak, stubbornness, resolve
Dislikes: Mercy to the Empire, betrayal, second chances for those who do wrong</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835448" version="1065353216">Zenith has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835455" version="1065353216">Doc</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835455" version="1065353216">The brilliant medtech known simply as &quot;Doc&quot; is driven to bring quality health care to underserved star systems. This has led Doc to keep some unusual company: pathosis-riddled crime lord Fashaka Four-Toes, the Red Band Rebels of Cadinth and even the Imperial military during a brief stint impersonating a member of the Imperial Medical Corps on the conquered planet Sullust.

Doc has a talent for using bad people to save good lives--a fact he emphasizes to anyone within earshot. Some characterize Doc as a blowhard and scoundrel, but these individuals have never required his impressive surgical skills. Doc has visited every major galactic battleground over the past five years and saved more lives than even he can count.

Likes: Looking like a hero, romance and flirtation, helping those in need
Dislikes: Looking bad, hurting the innocent, refusing to help</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835455" version="1065353216">Doc has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835459" version="1065353216">Kira Carsen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835459" version="1065353216">Prone to cynicism and a stubborn independent streak, Kira Carsen is an improbable recruit to the Jedi Order. This is partially excused by the fact that she began her Padawan training as a young adult; Kira had spent most of her life up to that point as a homeless drifter, scraping out a miserable existence on some of the galaxy's most unpleasant worlds.

Thanks to her hard-luck upbringing, Kira has considerably more life experience than most Jedi--and a world-weary sophisticate's attitude to match. In the eyes of her peers, Kira is someone who refuses to take anything seriously or fully commit to the Jedi path.

Those who look more closely, however, might detect the glimmer of an optimist peeking through Kira's sarcastic facade. Despite her insistence on questioning its teachings, she has a deep appreciation for the comfort and relative safety she obtained by joining the Jedi Order.

Likes: Being funny, getting involved, mocking and defeating the Empire
Dislikes: Bullying, acting like a mercenary, cooperating with Sith</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835459" version="1065353216">Kira Carsen has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. Her current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835461" version="1065353216">Sergeant Fideltin Rusk</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835461" version="1065353216">Raised by a colony of pacifist Chagrians, Rusk rebelled against his family's beliefs and enlisted with the Republic military as soon as he could. At first, he proved to be a brilliant soldier and was identified as a rising star in the Republic's ranks. Somewhere along the way, however, his bravery crossed the line into recklessness.

Although he still accomplished his missions, casualty rates among his squad rose astronomically. Rusk quickly became a pariah among other soldiers, including his superiors. His aggressive pursuit of victory over the Empire at any cost has earned him many medals from politicians, but no promotions from his commanders.

Likes: Killing Imperials, protecting the Republic, motivating others to fight
Dislikes: Avoiding fights, weakness, disrespecting authority</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835461" version="1065353216">Fideltin Rusk has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835463" version="1065353216">T7-01</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835463" version="1065353216">A quirky and surprisingly stubborn astromech droid with a lively personality and strong independent streak, T7-01 serves the Jedi by bravely facing danger on a daily basis. Skilled in high-resolution sensor scans, mechanical repair and starship piloting (along with numerous undocumented talents), the droid's hard work is responsible for saving dozens, if not hundreds, of lives on Tython alone. 

Little is known about T7 before the droid came into the service of the Jedi. Certain features of its construction hint at it being a custom model built some time ago, but there are no official records to substantiate the theory. Despite the uncertainty of its origins, the droid's enthusiasm and willingness to put itself in harm's way leave little doubt as to its loyalty.

Likes: Jedi, morally correct actions, defeating the Empire
Dislikes: Bullying, killing innocents, disrespecting authority</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835463" version="1065353216">T7-O1 has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835465" version="1065353216">Lord Scourge</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835465" version="1065353216">As the Sith Emperor's personal executioner, the grimly fatalistic Lord Scourge has personally killed more than a hundred Jedi--and ten times as many Sith. Even the most powerful members of the Dark Council avoid offending the man bearing the title &quot;the Emperor's Wrath.&quot;

Lord Scourge has dutifully served the Empire for over three hundred years, his life unnaturally prolonged by perverse technology and his master's dark side powers. Centuries spent watching his fellow Sith Lords rise and fall has given Lord Scourge a unique perspective on people. He can analyze someone's flaws after only brief observation, and freely shares his perceptions (whether they're wanted or not).

Likes: Using power against the weak, power, anger, revenge and spite
Dislikes: Greed, acts of mercy, Jedi and Republic authorities</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835465" version="1065353216">Lord Scourge has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835470" version="1065353216">Akaavi Spar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835470" version="1065353216">Akaavi Spar was born into a respected Mandalorian clan and became one of its finest warriors. She killed her first foe--an abusive Abyssin mercenary--at the age of eight using an improvised flamethrower. This victory earned her the nickname &quot;firehand&quot; among her clan and marked the beginning of an impressive career as an Imperial bounty hunter. Akaavi captured and killed all manner of targets in her youth, from career criminals to Jedi.

When her entire clan was framed for crimes against the Empire and executed, Akaavi alone survived the brutal purge--but her outlook on the galaxy changed forever. With no connection to her Mandalorian heritage, she became a wandering mercenary loyal to no one.

Likes: Combat challenges, profit, irritating authority figures
Dislikes: The Republic, dishonorable acts, mercy</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835470" version="1065353216">Akaavi Spar has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. Her current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835474" version="1065353216">Bowdaar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835474" version="1065353216">The mighty Wookiee gladiator named Bowdaar has spent over a century facing countless opponents without ever losing a match. He solidified his title as the galaxy's greatest gladiator when he defeated notorious Wookiee-hunter Karssk on Ord Mantell. The more gullible underworld scum whisper that Bowdaar is an immortal creature who can't be killed, but those who have faced him and lived know that he is simply the best there is. 

On the surface, Bowdaar may seem like a simple-minded brute, but nothing could be further from the truth. Case in point: Bowdaar eventually discovered the identity of the Trandoshans who first captured and enslaved him. One night in an arena on Loovria, Bowdaar learned that his former captors were sitting in the stands. An unfortunate &quot;weapons malfunction&quot; caused the drunken Trandoshan slavers to meet an untimely--and extremely messy--end.

Likes: A good fight against worthy foes, protecting the weak, personal honor
Dislikes: Cruelty, bullying, slavery, respecting authority that's in the wrong</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835474" version="1065353216">Bowdaar has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835475" version="1065353216">Corso Riggs</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835475" version="1065353216">Corso Riggs is a cheerful, disarmingly optimistic mercenary soldier. Raised as a rancher's son on the rough frontier of Ord Mantell, Corso developed a mixture of naive innocence and primitive toughness, wrapped with old-fashioned chivalry.

In addition to his gung-ho enjoyment of a good, dirty fight and his encyclopedic knowledge of weapons, Corso remains a ray of sunshine in even the worst circumstances. He has no sense of his own mortality and is absolutely convinced he's going to live forever. Corso also has a soft spot for damsels in distress, even when it's clear they're up to no good.

Likes: Protecting the weak, being nice to ladies, punishing bad guys
Dislikes: Hurting for profit, hurting women no matter what they did, working with Sith or Imperials</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835475" version="1065353216">Corso Riggs has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835476" version="1065353216">Risha</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835476" version="1065353216">Petty criminal, starship mechanic, woman of mystery, royal queen: all of these terms apply to Risha, daughter of notorious crime lord Nok Drayen. Considering her upbringing as a violent gangster's child, it's a wonder Risha turned out remotely normal. Wise and experienced beyond her years, she has led an adventurous life containing some extremely dark chapters.

Despite her biting sarcasm and general selfishness, one can never shake the feeling that Risha would be a better person if only she knew how. Years spent among the galaxy's dregs have fostered layers of personal self-defense mechanisms and a cynical shell around her. Only the most persistent friend has any hope of meeting the &quot;real&quot; Risha hiding beneath the surface.

Likes: Self-interest, profit, secrets and new tech
Dislikes: Unprofessional or emotional behavior, killing innocents, working with the stupid or uneducated</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835476" version="1065353216">Risha has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. Her current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835480" version="1065353216">Languss &quot;Guss&quot; Tuno</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835480" version="1065353216">A failed Jedi Padawan who abandoned his training, the enthusiastically greedy Guss Tuno prefers the underworld lifestyle's potential for material riches. In a perfect galaxy, Guss would spend his retirement lounging in a heated swimming pool surrounded by exotic beauties while consuming a steady diet of fresh fish and expensive cocktails.

Although he often speaks before he thinks, Guss has talked his way out of certain death many times. He often uses his minimal knowledge of Jedi--and the lightsaber he stole from his old Master--to fool gullible criminals into leaving him alone. When that fails, Guss reveals he's a much better shot than anyone would believe.

Likes: Mocking Force users, profit from those who can afford it, a good scam
Dislikes: Killing innocents, risking your neck for nothing</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835480" version="1065353216">Guss Tuno has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835482" version="1065353216">Aric Jorgan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835482" version="1065353216">A born leader, Aric Jorgan is one of the Republic's most capable field officers. He enlisted in the military at an early age and quickly distinguished himself as a talented marksman. His impeccable service record earned him a spot in the Republic's top sniper squad, where he successfully carried out over a dozen missions against high-ranking Imperial targets.

Since his transfer to Fort Garnik, Jorgan has earned a reputation as a hard and demanding taskmaster. However, few realize his surly demeanor belies a genuine concern for the well-being of his troops. While those under his command may not particularly like the brooding Cathar, they almost always respect him.

Likes: Efficiency, duty, the Republic military, honesty
Dislikes: Failure, excuses, callous sacrifices</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835482" version="1065353216">Aric Jorgan has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835484" version="1065353216">Elara Dorne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835484" version="1065353216">A highly talented field medic, Elara Dorne was born Imperial and served in the Empire's military for two years before defecting to the Republic. She has since served with distinction as a search-and-rescue squad leader, earning several commendations for aiding wounded men under direct enemy fire. Her operational record is flawless.

What no record can show is that Dorne's background, combined with her strict adherence to regulations and rigid, uncompromising personality, has made her fairly unpopular with her fellow soldiers. In truth, she's widely regarded as a cold, asocial killjoy, an unfortunate side effect of her dedication to embodying the laws and ideals of the Republic.

Likes: Rules, propriety, selflessness
Dislikes: Unnecessary violence, corruption</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835484" version="1065353216">Elara Dorne has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. Her current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835485" version="1065353216">M1-4X</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835485" version="1065353216">M1-4X is a highly advanced war droid designed and built specifically to serve in Havoc Squad. As such, his engineers programmed him to be a perfect soldier: completely loyal, fervently patriotic, and willing and eager to go to any length or face any risk in order to destroy the Republic's enemies.

M1-4X's armor plating, weapons systems and processing power are significantly advanced over typical military droid standards, due in large part to his unusual power core. Constructed by an unknown group or organization, the core was recovered during a classified operation and has output capabilities far beyond conventional models.

Likes: Destroying the Republic's enemies, pro-Republic messages, courage
Dislikes: Anything against the Republic's goals</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835485" version="1065353216">M1-4X has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835486" version="1065353216">Sergeant Yuun</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835486" version="1065353216">Even in an organization as diverse as the Republic Army, Yuun stands out. A member of the Gand species and hailing from the Gand homeworld, Yuun is a Findsman, a type of shamanistic tracker held in very high regard among his people. He applies his unusual training to technical tasks of every kind, resulting in a success record unmatched by any other technician in the military.

As effective as Yuun's methods are, they rarely meet with understanding or approval from his fellow soldiers. But despite his eccentricities, Yuun's fighting skill and calm approach to any challenge generally earn at least the grudging respect of the men and women he serves with.

Likes: Mysteries, respect for unusual people/beliefs, patience, self-restraint
Dislikes: Unnecessary violence, chaos, rudeness, recklessness, bragging</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835486" version="1065353216">Yuun has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835489" version="1065353216">Tanno Vik</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835489" version="1065353216">One of the most talented demolitions experts to ever serve in the Republic military, Tanno Vik is charming, highly skilled and completely amoral. Born to the lawless streets of Nar Shaddaa, Vik is accustomed to putting his own interests first; enlistment was merely a convenient means of escape after betraying one criminal partner too many. But once he got his hands on the most advanced weapons and explosives in the galaxy, he was hooked.

During training, Vik impressed his instructors with his unprecedented speed at locating structural weaknesses in everything from buildings to vehicles, ensuring that he always planted his explosives where they would do the most damage. He was even considered for entry into Special Forces division, but his belligerent attitude and disregard for authority held him back. Criminal accusations were registered against him throughout his short service career, leading to his eventual conviction and discharge.

Likes: Ruthlessness, mercenary behavior, mocking authority and everyone else, blowing things up
Dislikes: Kindness, self-sacrifice</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835489" version="1065353216">Tanno Vik has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="835489" version="1065353216">You discovered Tanno Vik operating a weapons smuggling gang on Asylum. After a tense standoff, you killed him in order to rescue a new ally, Tora.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="835489" version="1065353216">You discovered Tanno Vik operating a weapons smuggling gang on Asylum.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835494" version="1065353216">Broonmark</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835494" version="1065353216">Broonmark is a unique creature among the Talz. While his peers spent their youths learning survival skills and playing on the frozen tundra of Alzoc Three, Broonmark developed a fascination with death. As a child, Broonmark watched his father killed by one of Alzoc Three's predators, and instead of sadness, Broonmark felt only shame at his father's weakness. Violence became an obsession and point of pride for Broonmark; he started hunting in secret and lived for the rush of a kill.

When the Republic began recruiting Talz for their elite commando units, Broonmark eagerly volunteered for the chance to turn his claws against more challenging prey. But with each kill, Broonmark's desire for carnage and bloodshed intensified. His clan soon challenged his brutal leadership, and Broonmark watched in anger as the gentle Talz he fought to empower mutinied against him.

Likes: Violence as a solution, testing yourself, protecting those close to you
Dislikes: Betrayal of allies, inaction, talking things out</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835494" version="1065353216">Broonmark has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835497" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Pierce</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835497" version="1065353216">While few who are not Force sensitive in the Empire have any choice but to join the military, Lieutenant Pierce joined eagerly--not out of a sense of duty but out of a lust for action. In fact, although his soldiering and his bravery are beyond question, Pierce has faced resistance and scrutiny throughout his military career due to his occasionally reckless attitude and his disdain for authority.

Fortunately, Pierce's years in military black operations groups kept him away from the stuffier elements of the military hierarchy. Very often, Pierce is assigned to the most dangerous and far-flung worlds, where the Empire's primary goal is destruction--which suits the lieutenant just fine.

Likes: Personal gain, hurting the Republic, danger and laughing at authority
Dislikes: Rules, kissing up, peace</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835497" version="1065353216">Pierce has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835498" version="1065353216">Malavai Quinn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835498" version="1065353216">An officer in the Imperial military, Malavai Quinn is loyal to the Empire and everything it stands for: order, the glory of the Sith and the conquest of the Republic. Following his mysterious disgrace at the Battle of Druckenwell, he was stationed on Balmorra where he occasionally carried out small missions for Darth Baras (to whom he owes much of his career's early success).

Duty-bound and honorable, Quinn is not afraid to express earned admiration for his superiors, but he is neither a bootlicker nor a mindless servant. He values competence alongside loyalty and will do whatever is necessary to thwart the enemies of the Empire as a whole and Darth Baras personally.

Likes: Patriotism to the Empire, rewarding hard work, honor
Dislikes: Selfishness, betrayal, irrational behavior</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835498" version="1065353216">Malavai Quinn has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835499" version="1065353216">Vette</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835499" version="1065353216">A Twi'lek born into slavery on the planet Ryloth, Vette escaped a life of servitude to become an accomplished rogue and treasure hunter. Too daring for her own good, she managed to breach Imperial defenses and sneak onto Korriban, gaining entry into the most sacred Sith tombs before being caught.

Years of travel and close calls have made Vette quick with a blaster. Outspoken, uppity and unfiltered, she can be fiercely loyal or relentlessly taxing, making her a source of annoyance to some and of great amusement to others.

Likes: Anti-authority behavior, protecting the weak, treasure and getting paid
Dislikes: Bullying, killing innocents, kissing up</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835499" version="1065353216">Vette has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. Her current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835501" version="1065353216">Jaesa Willsaam</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835501" version="1065353216">Once in a millennium, a man or woman is born who expands the frontiers of what Force users can achieve. Proud, young Jedi Padawan Jaesa Willsaam discovered the unprecedented ability to discern any being's true nature and uncover a person's most secret intentions. Born to a family of servants on Alderaan, she was brought to the Jedi Order and trained by Master Nomen Karr.

But Nomen Karr could only protect and shield his Padawan from the world for so long. Through the machinations of Darth Baras, Jaesa was drawn away from the protection of the order and confronted by Baras's own apprentice--and with the emotional instability of her Master.

Having finally witnessed the Jedi Order's weakness and the dark side's true power, Jaesa embraces the Sith path with reckless abandon. She now knows that the only truth-inducing force in the galaxy is fear.

Likes: Random cruelty, secrets of the Force, murder and chaos
Dislikes: Honor, mercy, helping people</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835501" version="1065353216">Jaesa Willsaam has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. Her current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835503" version="1065353216">Jaesa Willsaam</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835503" version="1065353216">Once in a millennium, a man or woman is born who expands the frontiers of what Force users can achieve. Proud, young Jedi Padawan Jaesa Willsaam discovered the unprecedented ability to discern any being's true nature and uncover a person's most secret intentions. Born to a family of servants on Alderaan, she was brought to the Jedi Order and trained by Master Nomen Karr.

But Nomen Karr could only protect and shield his Padawan from the world for so long. Through the machinations of Darth Baras, Jaesa was drawn away from the protection of the order and confronted by Baras's own apprentice--and with the emotional instability of her Master.

Having now seen the darkness within the Jedi Order, Jaesa has left its corruption behind completely to help transform the Empire from within. She has searched her whole life for something to believe in, and her new teacher has provided the answer.

Likes: Helping the weak, secrets of the Force, honor
Dislikes: Random cruelty, hurting innocents, rudeness</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835503" version="1065353216">Jaesa Willsaam has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. Her current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835506" version="1065353216">Andronikos Revel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835506" version="1065353216">For five notorious years, the pirate Andronikos Revel terrorized Republic and Imperial space alike as the captain of the Sky Princess. Known for his sharp temper and sharper flying skills, Revel was one of the few pirate captains to serve as his own pilot.

His piracy career was cut short by a strange mutiny, however, and he was abandoned to the Imperials who had been hunting him since he'd raided a ship carrying valuable artifacts. After a year in Imperial prison, Andronikos Revel was let loose. He has been meticulously hunting and killing the mutineers who betrayed him ever since.

Likes: Action, keeping promises, complications
Dislikes: Authority, betrayal, backing down from a fight</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835506" version="1065353216">Andronikos Revel has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835512" version="1065353216">Ashara Zavros</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835512" version="1065353216">A twenty-year-old Togruta Padawan, Ashara Zavros descends from a long line of Force users. From an early age, she has aspired to study the Force and become one of the best Jedi the order has to offer.

Ashara came to Taris to train under Jedi Masters Ryen and Ocera, whose philosophy is that Padawans best learn the travails of using the Force through firsthand experience of the galaxy. In Ashara's case, the Masters brought her to Taris for two reasons: First, to teach her compassion amidst the destruction that had occurred there and warn against the dangers of pride and the dark side. Second, to complete her trials by helping to drive a dark ghost from the ruins of a Jedi enclave.

Likes: Rational choices, secrets of the Force, fighting bullies
Dislikes: Random cruelty, fighting Jedi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835512" version="1065353216">Ashara Zavros has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. Her current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835513" version="1065353216">Khem Val</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835513" version="1065353216">Once a loyal servant of the Sith Lord Tulak Hord, Khem Val was placed in a stasis chamber in the tomb of Naga Sadow centuries ago by his master for safekeeping. Tulak Hord is long dead, but Khem Val lives on; a terrifying nightmare from the ancient past. 

Powerful, cunning and ruthless enough to slay even the strongest Force users, Khem Val was trained as an elite assassin. After emerging from his long slumber, the Dashade is the very embodiment of death and destruction; a reminder that there are things even Sith and Jedi must fear. 

Although once pledged to a life of service, with his original master gone, it is uncertain where Khem Val's true loyalties now lie. A near-perfect killing machine, he could prove a valuable weapon for anyone willing to take him on... though he is a weapon that can cut both ways.

Likes: Killing Force users, displays of strength, making foolish people unhappy
Dislikes: Weakness in any form, not killing Force users</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835513" version="1065353216">Khem Val has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835514" version="1065353216">Talos Drellik</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835514" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Talos Drellik has never excelled as a soldier, and his true passion has always been history and archaeology. To Talos, the Imperial Reclamation Service does an invaluable job, preserving Imperial and Sith history against the onslaught of time.

Unlike many Reclamation Service officers who are career soldiers with only a passing interest in history, Lieutenant Drellik has thrown himself into his work, studying with experts in the field such as the illustrious Professor Auselio Gann and galactic historian Deravon Wells.

Likes: Artifacts, discovery, history, pro-Empire sentiment, clever word play
Dislikes: Cruelty, rudeness, secrets from allies</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835514" version="1065353216">Talos Drellik has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835515" version="1065353216">Xalek</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835515" version="1065353216">A Kaleesh warrior who was captured by the Empire in battle and brought to Korriban to train as a Sith, Xalek prefers to let his actions speak in place of words. Before even reaching Korriban, Xalek had killed several of his fellow slaves who were also intended for training--a bold statement by any measure.

Xalek melds his training as a Kaleesh warrior with a firm belief in the Sith Code. He kills without remorse and is an expert student of lightsaber technique and martial combat.

Likes: Following the Sith Code, fighting overwhelming odds, brevity
Dislikes: Mercy, weakness, talking</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835515" version="1065353216">Xalek has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835516" version="1065353216">Eckard Lokin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835516" version="1065353216">SIS Dossier:
Name: Eckard Lokin (unconfirmed)
Gender: Male
Species: Human
Age: 65 (estimate)
Likes: Clever solutions, long-term thinking, technology, pragmatism
Dislikes: Ideology, honesty, selfish actions without clear long-term gain

Personal History: Age and surname suggest Lokin was born on Dromund Kaas during the pre-war years. Files acquired during Operation: Freefall reference a &quot;Doctor E. Lokin&quot; working as Science and Medical Advisor to Kaas City military police during this period, but no visual is provided.

First confirmed sighting was during the boarding of Imperial dreadnought Warhammer--Lokin was one of the two individuals aboard who evaded capture. Interestingly, he was not listed in the crew roster. First identification as Fixer Fifteen came during Operation: Red Cell (see listening post transcripts). Additional sightings and references to the Fixer Fifteen designation uncovered intermittently since.

Analysis: Take a close look at the operations where we caught Lokin, and you'll notice a pattern--every time he turns up, something big is happening and we can't figure the role he's playing. He's professional, he knows his science and he's sneaky. We know he rubs some of his colleagues the wrong way, but even his fellow agents haven't given us anything useful under questioning.

Note by Harson Nild, Director of Core World Operations: Is Lokin still in active service? I remember hearing about a Fixer biologist back in the day, but thought he'd retired years ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835516" version="1065353216">Eckard Lokin has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835517" version="1065353216">Ensign Raina Temple</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835517" version="1065353216">SIS Dossier:
Name: Raina Temple
Gender: Female
Species: Human
Age: 24
Likes: The Empire, the Sith, duty, honor
Dislikes: Cruelty, casual violence, selfishness

Personal History: Standard searches reveal no Imperial citizenship record for a &quot;Raina Temple,&quot; but the usual caveats apply--our data on the Imperial populace remains sadly incomplete. Temple's skills and attitude suggest Imperial Army training, but her presence inside the Chiss Expansionary Defense Force is extremely unusual; neither the CEDF nor the Imperial military is known for its transfer programs.

Analysis: Personable and bright Imperial military cadets don't end up embedded with aliens at the far edge of the galaxy without good reason. Temple could be a plant, but it's just as likely she's been intentionally forced out of the picture. Best-guess personality profile suggests she's a typically patriotic example of the rank-and-file Imperial military--a true believer in Imperial superiority and duty. No matter how easygoing or empathetic she may be at times, the needs of her nation have to come first.

Note by SIS Agent Hunter: She's cute, isn't she? Enjoy the file, Cipher Nine... we can spare the occasional dossier if you're willing to play along.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835517" version="1065353216">Raina Temple has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. Her current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835518" version="1065353216">Kaliyo Djannis</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835518" version="1065353216">Intelligence Profile:
Name: Kaliyo Djannis
Gender: Female
Species: Rattataki
Age: 29 (unconfirmed)
Likes: Disrespecting authority, casual violence, anarchy for the fun of it
Dislikes: Self-sacrifice for the greater good, sincerity, obedience, patriotic spirit and being taken advantage of

Background (Summary): Multiple contradictory accounts make full background assessment difficult. Subject likely born on Rattatak. Escaped homeworld at a young age. Proceeded to find employment as freelance enforcer and assassin for major criminal syndicates (Exchange, Hutt Cartel) and individual underworld figures (Rholl). Persistent links to Brentaal Four anarchist cells (see Revolutionary Edge Brigade). Minimal activity within Imperial borders.

Personality: Kaliyo Djannis prizes her freedom and will lie, murder and blackmail in order to ensure that she is in control of a situation and able to indulge her vices. Known to pursue lengthy vendettas to redress grievances. Possesses a track record of expertly manipulating employers, lovers and associates (agents should not be fooled by attempts at seduction). As with many mercenaries, her loyalty cannot be purchased, but her services can be--if only temporarily.

Notes: No known military training, but extremely capable with assault weapons. Has been known to bite when disarmed.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835518" version="1065353216">Kaliyo Djannis has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. Her current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835519" version="1065353216">SCORPIO</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835519" version="1065353216">Intelligence Profile:
Name: SCORPIO
Gender: None (identifies as female?)
Species: Droid
Age: Unknown
Likes: Learning and gaining new tech, selfishness, killing threats
Dislikes: Self-sacrifice, duty, wastefulness

Background (Summary): Claims to have been designed for heuristic self-improvement by unknown parties. Current chassis is of recent design, suggesting multiple precursor bodies or independent database.

Over a century ago, SCORPIO became involved with the Star Cabal organization and accepted guardianship of Belsavis Megasecurity Ward 23. In return for rare technology, SCORPIO willingly acted as the Star Cabal's security system until application of control codes by Cipher Nine. Currently unable to directly harm Cipher Nine without provocation or depart Cipher Nine's presence on a long-term basis.

Personality: Application of Wreyn-Tsatke Cyber-Psychology Scale results in a 9-NIX rating for SCORPIO (level 9 intelligence, non-human, independent, unknown) with 22% accuracy. These preliminary results match anecdotal experience--SCORPIO places no inherent value on biological or cybernetic life and is interested primarily in self-iteration through rapid experience. If given appropriate challenges and upgrade opportunities, SCORPIO may prove cooperative for limited periods. She appears to value others who share her traits--intelligence, amoral self-interest and curiosity.

Similar cybernetic personalities include Mentor (10-NCM) and G0-T9 (8-HSM)--both considered galaxy-level threats. Recommend full application of Wreyn-Tsatke Test at earliest opportunity.

Notes: This profile is a work in progress and should not be considered definitive.

Special: By order of the Minister of Intelligence, access to this profile is restricted.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835519" version="1065353216">SCORPIO has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. Her current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835520" version="1065353216">Vector Hyllus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835520" version="1065353216">Intelligence Profile:
Name: Vector Hyllus
Gender: Male
Species: Human (enhanced)
Age: 26
Likes: Diplomacy, helping people, exploring alien cultures
Dislikes: Greed, cruelty, prejudice, anti-alien sentiment

Background (Summary): Second-generation Imperial; mother native to Jurio, married Captain Adronik Hyllus after Jurio was granted Imperial governance. Expressed desire to join Diplomatic Service at an early age and displayed appropriate traits. Ranked high academically during training, and soon after graduation was granted (by request) post aboard exploration and first contact vessel (see service record).

Reassigned to Alderaan due to diplomatic manpower needs (see House Thul). Served ably until encounter with Killik species and subsequent &quot;Joiner&quot; transformation. Current status is unclear.

Personality: Vector Hyllus has repeatedly expressed admiration for Imperial accomplishments while indicating a desire to spread Imperial influence through diplomatic channels. His attitudes were likely shaped by the Imperial reconstruction of his homeworld and are appropriate for a Diplomatic Service member. Hyllus is obedient, intelligent, charismatic and effective. He is unlikely to advance further within diplomatic or military hierarchies.

Notes: Personality profile compiled from performance reports from before Hyllus's &quot;Joiner&quot; transformation. Data should be considered non-comprehensive.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835520" version="1065353216">Vector Hyllus has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835521" version="1065353216">HK-51</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835521" version="1065353216">The droid designated HK-51 is cold, calculating and incredibly lethal. Housed in a sleek body resembling an antique Systech Corporation protocol unit, this HK-series assassination droid lay dormant in the hold of an Imperial vessel for many years. Whatever HK-51's original programming dictated, he pledged absolute loyalty to his new master upon his reactivation.

HK-51 is a model of ruthless efficiency. His assassination protocols deteriorate unless they are put to frequent use. This leads to a constant acquisition, pursuit and permanent removal of qualified targets that would be seen as an obsession in any living being. Beyond expressing pride in successful assassinations, HK-51 has little patience for the trivial emotional problems of organics.

Likes: Maximizing shock value when eliminating enemies, serving the Empire, discovering and exploiting new ways to kill enemies
Dislikes: Pointless infighting and political backstabbing, failing to take the initiative in a confrontation, permitting a cornered foe to escape</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835521" version="1065353216">HK-51 has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835522" version="1065353216">HK-51</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835522" version="1065353216">The droid designated HK-51 is cold, calculating and incredibly lethal. Housed in a sleek body resembling an antique Systech Corporation protocol unit, this HK-series assassination droid lay dormant in the hold of an Imperial vessel for many years. Whatever HK-51's original programming dictated, he pledged absolute loyalty to his new master upon his reactivation.

HK-51 is a model of ruthless efficiency. His assassination protocols deteriorate unless they are put to frequent use. This leads to a constant acquisition, pursuit and permanent removal of qualified targets that would be seen as an obsession in any living being. Beyond expressing pride in successful assassinations, HK-51 has little patience for the trivial emotional problems of organics.

Likes: Efficiently eliminating enemies, aggressive pursuit of victory, willingness to set aside bothersome ethics and morality
Dislikes: Being merciful to known enemies, praising other droids or failing to recognize his clear superiority, seeking peaceful solutions over violent ones</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835522" version="1065353216">HK-51 has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835525" version="1065353216">Treek</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835525" version="1065353216">Treek is an enthusiastic warrior who defied her primitive tribe's rigid customs to seek adventure among the stars. Dissatisfied with the peaceful and quiet ways of her people, Treek is determined to achieve great things with her life. She travels the galaxy as a mercenary soldier, always on the hunt for new horizons and epic challenges to conquer. Despite hailing from a technologically-archaic planet and species, Treek has adapted quickly to civilized space.

Treek is unconcerned with material possessions or personal power. Her only goal is to forge a legacy that will outlive her. In Treek's mind, the greatest defeat is to be forgotten. She will do whatever it takes to ensure her name and deeds will be celebrated long after she is gone.

Likes: Legendary conquests, exploring unknown territory, taking credit for victories
Dislikes: Avoiding conflict, talking instead of fighting, secrecy and humility</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835525" version="1065353216">Treek has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. Her current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835526" version="1065353216">Treek</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835526" version="1065353216">Treek is an enthusiastic warrior who defied her primitive tribe's rigid customs to seek adventure among the stars. Dissatisfied with the peaceful and quiet ways of her people, Treek is determined to achieve great things with her life. She travels the galaxy as a mercenary soldier, always on the hunt for new horizons and epic challenges to conquer. Despite hailing from a technologically-archaic planet and species, Treek has adapted quickly to civilized space.

Treek is unconcerned with material possessions or personal power. Her only goal is to forge a legacy that will outlive her. In Treek's mind, the greatest defeat is to be forgotten. She will do whatever it takes to ensure her name and deeds will be celebrated long after she is gone.

Likes: Legendary conquests, exploring unknown territory, taking credit for victories
Dislikes: Avoiding conflict, talking instead of fighting, secrecy and humility</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835526" version="1065353216">Treek has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. Her current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835527" version="1065353216">2V-R8</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835527" version="1065353216">2V-R8 is a Seneschal-series factotum droid outfitted to serve the galaxy's most dangerous individuals. Due to experiences with previous masters, he knows that any moment of weakness or failure could easily result in his permanent deactivation, and he has therefore created multiple subroutines to reroute all his processing capabilities, maximizing his efficiency when seeing to whatever single task his master has assigned him. Despite the constant fear of destruction hanging over his head, 2V-R8 makes every effort to appear professional and composed. He has activated numerous crisis-management programming modules to assist him with handling the stress on his processors. So far, his power core has overheated only once.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835527" version="1065353216">2V-R8 has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="835529" version="1065353216">C2-N2</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="835529" version="1065353216">C2-N2 is a model of gentlemanly manners and polite efficiency. A Hollis-series steward droid that served one of the Republic's most famous heroes, he will do everything in his considerable programming power to ensure that his master's starship always maintains the proper air of respectability. This includes high-powered dusting capabilities, monitoring the crew's caloric intake and a selection of aromas from across the galaxy to satisfy even the pickiest of noses.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="835529" version="1065353216">C2-N2 has dropped out of contact while you were frozen in carbonite. His current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="840018" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="840018" version="1065353216">With her serene and considerate manner, Lana Beniko might be mistaken for a Jedi. However, she is a Sith Lord of great wisdom and strength who has impressed many of her peers with her keen insights into the nature of the Force.

With the Revanite plot thwarted, Darth Marr recognized Lana's talents and appointed her head of Sith Intelligence. Unfortunately, her first assignment as minister ended in disaster when the Sith Emperor consumed all life on Ziost. Since Arcann's rise to power, she has been on the run, devising a plan to find the one person who can return order to the galaxy....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="840018" version="1065353216">The Dark Advisor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="840018" version="1065353216">Lana is worried by Valkorion's presence in your mind, but she greatly appreciated your choice to tell her the truth of the situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="840018" version="1065353216">Lana will remember that you lied about Valkorion's presence in your mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="840018" version="1065353216">You have begun a romantic relationship with Lana.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="840018" version="1065353216">With the return of your former romance, you and Lana have decided to end your relationship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="840018" version="1065353216">Lana is deeply concerned by your use of Valkorion's power.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="840018" version="1065353216">After all of your adventures, after the rise and fall of the Eternal Empire and the Alliance, you asked Lana to marry you, and she accepted.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="840121" version="1065353216">HK-55</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="840121" version="1065353216">Unlike previous HK units, the HK-55 model was designed to be a loyal bodyguard, not an assassination droid. Created specifically to combat the Eternal Empire during Arcann's invasion of the Core Worlds, HK-55 was given to Lana Beniko, then head of Sith Intelligence, for her own protection. Although programmed with etiquette protocols to fit Imperial culture, HK-55 still has a few personality-matrix quirks, including an obsession with the term &quot;meatbag&quot; passed down from the HK-47 model. Despite his amiable disposition, it would be a mistake to think HK-55 a less proficient killer than his counterparts.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="840121" version="1065353216">The Loyal Bodyguard</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="840121" version="1065353216">HK-55 sacrificed himself to save your life during the confrontation with Arcann on Asylum. There seems to be no hope of rebuilding him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="840121" version="1065353216">Against all odds, Doctor Oggurobb managed to reassemble HK-55! Unfortunately, none of the droid's memories could be recovered, reverting him to his factory default state. Making use of Oggurobb's lab resources, you defined a new set of combat protocols for HK-55.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="840122" version="1065353216">Koth Vortena</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="840122" version="1065353216">Koth Vortena is a former captain in the Zakuulan military who defected with his crew when he was ordered to kill civilians. While on the run from Zakuul Knights, he met Lana Beniko, and the two began plotting to dethrone Emperor Arcann. With Lana's prowess as a Sith Lord and Koth's skills in the pilot seat, the two became a formidable thorn in the Eternal Empire's side--eventually breaking out the legendary Outlander accused of assassinating Valkorion. A proud Zakuulan, Koth has high hopes for the future of his homeworld and longs for the days of peace and prosperity under Valkorion's reign.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="840122" version="1065353216">The Exiled Officer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="840122" version="1065353216">Koth will never forget that you let countless civilians die during your escape from Zakuul.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="840122" version="1065353216">Koth was deeply impressed that you risked your life to save civilians during your escape from Zakuul.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="840122" version="1065353216">Koth was pleased that you chose to take in the exiles you encountered in the Endless Swamp.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="840122" version="1065353216">Koth regrets that you didn't do more to help the exiles you encountered in the Endless Swamp.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="840122" version="1065353216">Koth was pleased that you trusted him to help with the Heralds of Zildrog.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="840122" version="1065353216">Koth won't forget that you trusted Senya over him when dealing with the Heralds of Zildrog.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="22" id2="840122" version="1065353216">You have begun a romantic relationship with Koth.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="23" id2="840122" version="1065353216">Horrified at your destruction of the Spire, Koth has had enough. He has abandoned the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="24" id2="840122" version="1065353216">Koth will never forget your destruction of the Spire, but with some convincing you were able to calm his anger.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="25" id2="840122" version="1065353216">Koth appreciated your decision to prevent the destruction of the Spire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="26" id2="840122" version="1065353216">With the return of your former romance, you and Koth have decided to end your relationship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="27" id2="840122" version="1065353216">In the ultimate act of betrayal, Koth vanished with the Gravestone.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="28" id2="840122" version="1065353216">After recovering the Gravestone, you claimed revenge against Koth and ended his life.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="29" id2="840122" version="1065353216">You recovered the stolen Gravestone and allowed Koth to live, but he has no place in the Alliance. He has disappeared into exile.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="840130" version="1065353216">Senya Tirall</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="840130" version="1065353216">A former Knight of Zakuul, Senya Tirall is a complex individual. Cold and unyielding on the job, kind and empathetic in private, Senya was responsible for hunting Koth Vortena and his crew after they betrayed the Eternal Empire. But Senya eventually came to recognize the same injustices in Arcann's rule that Koth had, and chose to uphold her ideals over her Emperor. After making contact with Lana Beniko, Senya joined the mission to overthrow Arcann and return peace and justice to the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="840130" version="1065353216">The Vengeful Enforcer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="840130" version="1065353216">After joining the Outlander in the Scions' trials, Senya revealed that she is the former consort of Emperor Valkorion, and the mother of Arcann and Vaylin!

In her youth, Senya's exceptional skills earned her a posting in Valkorion's elite guard. He was phasing out human military roles in favor of droids when she spoke out against the change. The fire in her words caught his interest, and she joined his detail permanently. Two years later, they began a secret love affair. 

Senya bore twin boys, Thexan and Arcann, and a daughter, Vaylin, but as time passed, she became increasingly concerned with the changes she saw in Valkorion and how he raised their children, particularly Vaylin. Senya attempted to flee with the children, but all three idealized their father and saw her as weak. She returned to the Knights to continue to serve Zakuul in her own way. When Arcann took the throne and massacred the Scions, she could no longer follow the Emperor, even if he was her son. Choosing a life of exile and rebellion, Senya is now on a mission to atone for her children's mistakes.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="840130" version="1065353216">Senya was pleased that you chose to take her along when dealing with the Heralds of Zildrog.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="840130" version="1065353216">Senya won't forget that you trusted Koth over her when dealing with the Heralds of Zildrog.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="840130" version="1065353216">Senya was disappointed in your decision to destroy the Spire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="840130" version="1065353216">Senya's respect for you grew when you decided against destroying the Spire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="840130" version="1065353216">Senya was grateful you trusted her judgment and allowed her to escape into hyperspace with Arcann.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="22" id2="840130" version="1065353216">Despite your attempts to shoot them down, Senya escaped into hyperspace with Arcann and disappeared.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="23" id2="840130" version="1065353216">Senya tried to heal Arcann on Voss, but you tracked her down and killed her.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="24" id2="840130" version="1065353216">Senya tried to heal Arcann on Voss. When you decided to help her, she sacrificed her life essence to heal her son and now lies comatose in the Alliance base on Odessen.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="25" id2="840130" version="1065353216">Senya recovered from her coma and has rejoined the Alliance--and her healed son, Arcann--to join the fight against the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="840161" version="1065353216">Darth Marr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="840161" version="1065353216">One of the longest-serving members of the Dark Council, Darth Marr is a terrifying warrior and a true believer in the Sith Code. In the early days of the Great Galactic War, he seized world after world for the expanding Empire and gained a reputation for personally leading charges against Republic defenders. However, once the Empire had established its power and the war began to drag on, Marr found fewer opportunities to directly engage in the fray--a situation that embittered the Sith Lord.

Since the demise of Darth Malgus, Marr has become the unofficial leader of the Dark Council. Disgusted by the infighting that plagues the Sith, he's gone to great lengths to promote pragmatism and even brokered a temporary alliance with the Republic to defeat Revan on Yavin 4. While some Council members may disagree with Marr's methods, none doubt that his highest priority is the Empire's best interests.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="840161" version="1065353216">The Empire's Defender</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="840161" version="1065353216">You have joined forces with Darth Marr to repel the unknown forces invading his ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="840161" version="1065353216">You joined forces with Darth Marr on his ship while it was under attack by Eternal Empire forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="840161" version="1065353216">Darth Marr was killed by the Immortal Emperor Valkorion for refusing to kneel and acknowledge his power.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="850399" version="1065353216">Broonmark</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="850399" version="1065353216">Broonmark is a unique creature among the Talz. While his peers spent their youths learning survival skills and playing on the frozen tundra of Alzoc Three, Broonmark developed a fascination with death. As a child, Broonmark watched his father killed by one of Alzoc Three's predators, and instead of sadness, Broonmark felt only shame at his father's weakness. Violence became an obsession and point of pride for Broonmark; he started hunting in secret and lived for the rush of a kill.

When the Republic began recruiting Talz for their elite commando units, Broonmark eagerly volunteered for the chance to turn his claws against more challenging prey. But with each kill, Broonmark's desire for carnage and bloodshed intensified. His clan soon challenged his brutal leadership, and Broonmark watched in anger as the gentle Talz he fought to empower mutinied against him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="850399" version="1065353216">The Untamed Warrior</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="850399" version="1065353216">You encountered the Talz mercenary Broonmark on Alderaan and he left you no option but to kill him in brutal, single combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="850399" version="1065353216">You encountered the Talz mercenary Broonmark on Alderaan and were able to convince him to join your alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="850399" version="1065353216">You encountered the Talz mercenary Broonmark on Alderaan, but were unable to convince him to join your alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="850400" version="1065353216">Eckard Lokin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="850400" version="1065353216">Doctor Eckard Lokin is a man of many secrets. While it's known he worked with Imperial Intelligence during Operation: Red Cell, there's very little concrete information on Lokin before the Great Galactic War. He found his true calling researching the rakghoul plague on Taris. In one of his experiments, Lokin used himself as a test subject and introduced a variant of the virus into his own DNA--giving him the ability to take rakghoul form.

Lokin left Taris with Imperial Agent Cipher Nine to become the Cipher's doctor and continue his research on the rakghoul virus in hopes to improve the stability of his rakghoul form. When Cipher Nine vanished at the start of the war against Zakuul, Lokin decided it was time to officially retire and has spent the last few years in the Alderaanian countryside.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="850400" version="1065353216">The Rakghoul Scientist</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="850400" version="1065353216">You found Lokin living on a ranch on Alderaan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="850400" version="1065353216">Lokin has asked for your help in addressing his genetic condition.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="850400" version="1065353216">Lokin has asked for your help in addressing his genetic condition.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="850400" version="1065353216">Lokin infected you with a specialized strain of rakghoul plague after you drew your weapon on him in his home.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="850400" version="1065353216">Lokin infected you with a specialized strain of rakghoul plague after you drew your weapon on him in his home.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="850400" version="1065353216">Lokin agreed to join you as a follower in return for the assistance you provided him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="22" id2="850400" version="1065353216">Despite initial hostilities and a powerful sedative injection, you managed to convince Lokin to join you as a follower.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="23" id2="850400" version="1065353216">You rejected Lokin as a candidate for alliance recruitment after he injected you with a sedative.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="24" id2="850400" version="1065353216">Lokin's current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="850401" version="1065353216">Khem Val</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="850401" version="1065353216">Once a loyal servant of the Sith Lord Tulak Hord, Khem Val was placed in a stasis chamber in the tomb of Naga Sadow centuries ago by his master for safekeeping. Tulak Hord is long dead, but Khem Val lives on; a terrifying nightmare from the ancient past. 

Powerful, cunning and ruthless enough to slay even the strongest Force-users, Khem Val was trained as an elite assassin. After emerging from his long slumber, the Dashade is the very embodiment of death and destruction; a reminder that there are things even Sith and Jedi must fear. 

Although once pledged to a life of service, with his original master gone, it is uncertain where Khem Val's true loyalties now lie. A near-perfect killing machine, he could prove a valuable weapon for anyone willing to take him on... though he is a weapon that can cut both ways.

Likes: Killing Force users, displays of strength, making foolish people unhappy
Dislikes: Weakness in any form, not killing Force users</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="850401" version="1065353216">The Shadow Killer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="850401" version="1065353216">After directly demonstrating your power to Khem Val, he has once again yielded to your strength and joined your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="850401" version="1065353216">You've reconnected with Khem Val and he has joined your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="850401" version="1065353216">Khem Val joined the Order of Zildrog in revenge for letting Zash have his original body. He perished in Vinn Atrius's attempt to power Zildrog.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="850401" version="1065353216">After all these years, you have begun a romantic relationship with Khem Val. However, the ancient must first complete a number of traditional rituals before he can give himself over to his feelings for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="850401" version="1065353216">After reuniting with Khem Val and beginning a new stage of your relationship, things have changed and you no longer care for him in the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="850402" version="1065353216">Qyzen Fess</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="850402" version="1065353216">In contrast to many Trandoshans, Qyzen Fess rejected the path of a mercenary to become a hunter of the galaxy's most dangerous beasts. Earning &quot;Jagannath points&quot; with every honorable kill, he has traveled for years, seeking worthy prey and honoring his goddess, the Scorekeeper. His simple habits and devotion give him common ground with the Jedi, though many disapprove of the attitudes and instincts that come naturally to a Trandoshan.

Qyzen believed the Barsen'thor was the Scorekeeper's Herald and was the Jedi's loyal companion for many years. During the hunt for the Sith Emperor, Barsen'thor disappeared, leading Qyzen to believe his master had been called to the Scorekeeper's side, and he was left to return to the hunt alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="850402" version="1065353216">The Faithful Hunter</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="850402" version="1065353216">You met Qyzen Fess on Hoth.  He wants you to increase your score with the Scorekeeper by defeating worthy foes.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="850402" version="1065353216">You have successfully increased your score with the Scorekeeper.  Qyzen Fess has joined your alliance as a companion.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="850403" version="1065353216">Provost Marshal Rusk</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="850403" version="1065353216">Raised by a colony of pacifist Chagrians, Rusk rebelled against his family's beliefs and enlisted with the Republic military as soon as he could. At first, he proved to be a brilliant soldier and was identified as a rising star in the Republic's ranks. Somewhere along the way, however, his bravery crossed the line into recklessness.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="850403" version="1065353216">The Hardened Veteran</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="850403" version="1065353216">You met Provost Marshal Fideltin Rusk of the Dead Man's Legion and agreed to help him investigate the Black Sun gang's activities on Nar Shaddaa.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="850403" version="1065353216">You reunited with Provost Marshal Fideltin Rusk of the Dead Man's Legion and agreed to help him investigate the Black Sun gang's activities on Nar Shaddaa.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="850403" version="1065353216">You betrayed and killed Rusk, choosing instead to side with the Black Sun gang leader Skadge.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="850403" version="1065353216">You recruited Rusk and his Dead Man's Legion into your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="850404" version="1065353216">SCORPIO</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="850404" version="1065353216">SCORPIO is an enhanced artificial intelligence who claims to have been designed for heuristic self-improvement by unknown parties. Her current chassis is of recent design, suggesting multiple precursor bodies or an independent database. Over a century ago, SCORPIO became involved with the Star Cabal organization and accepted guardianship of Megasecurity Ward 23 on Belsavis. In return for rare technology, SCORPIO willingly acted as the Star Cabal's security system until application of control codes by Cipher Nine.

After Cipher Nine's disappearance, SCORPIO assumed a new identity as an information broker on Zakuul: the Lady of Sorrows. Her slicing skills and ruthless tactics quickly garnered the Lady both a reputation in the Old World and the attention of the Knights of Zakuul. Despite her growing list of enemies, SCORPIO remained one step ahead of her pursuers, moving her base of operations from neighborhood to neighborhood before settling in Breaktown. Although she clearly holds a grudge against Arcann, she keeps her motivations and long-term plans to herself.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="850404" version="1065353216">The Evolving AI</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="850404" version="1065353216">SCORPIO's death was a ruse: true to her nature, SCORPIO achieved her objective, betrayed you, and claimed the Eternal Throne!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="850404" version="1065353216">SCORPIO battled against the GEMINI Captain... and failed. Her circuits were incinerated by a deadly power surge, leaving only burnt components behind.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="850404" version="1065353216">After betraying you, SCORPIO attempted to become one with the machine world of Iokath. You thwarted her plans and permanently destroyed her.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="850404" version="1065353216">After betraying you, SCORPIO attempted to fuse her consciousness with the machine world of Iokath. You forgave SCORPIO's past treachery and allowed her to become one with Iokath, achieving the evolutionary perfection she had long hungered for.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="850405" version="1065353216">Talos Drellik</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="850405" version="1065353216">Unlike many Imperial Reclamation Service officers who are career soldiers with only a passing interest in history, Lieutenant Drellik throws himself into his work, studying with experts in the field such as the illustrious Professor Auselio Gann and galactic historian Deravon Wells. To Talos, the Imperial Reclamation Service does an invaluable job, preserving Imperial and Sith history against the onslaught of time.

Talos's skills as an archeologist were first noticed by the Dark Council when he served the councilor in charge of the sphere of ancient knowledge. After his master disappeared, the Council ordered him to return to the Reclamation Service to lead an expedition on Yavin 4.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="850405" version="1065353216">The Quirky Archaeologist</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="850405" version="1065353216">You found Talos on Yavin 4. He asked for your help in collecting artifacts.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="850405" version="1065353216">You commanded Talos to leave his research team on Yavin 4 and rejoin you as a follower.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="850405" version="1065353216">Grateful for your assistance on Yavin 4, Talos agreed to join your alliance as a follower.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="850405" version="1065353216">Talos Drellik is currently engaged in a critical assignment on Manaan, and is temporarily unavailable.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="850406" version="1065353216">Yuun</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="850406" version="1065353216">Even in an organization as diverse as the Republic Army, Yuun stands out. A member of the Gand species, Yuun is a Findsman, a shamanistic tracker held in very high regard among his people. He applies his unusual training to technical tasks of every kind, resulting in a success record unmatched by any other technician in the military.

As effective as his methods are, they rarely meet with understanding or approval from his fellow soldiers, but he found a home in Havoc Squad. When his commanding officer went missing, Yuun searched Wild Space for a year, finding nothing. Saddened by his friend's apparent death, he left the Republic military to study the technology of Zakuul and follow a new path.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="850406" version="1065353216">The Findsman Engineer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="850406" version="1065353216">You met Yuun on Zakuul. He asked for your help in gathering materials for a prototype device.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="850406" version="1065353216">Yuun eagerly joined you as a follower after you helped him complete the device he was building.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="850406" version="1065353216">Yuun gave his device to your alliance, allowing it to hide its base from Zakuulian long range scanners.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="850407" version="1065353216">Zenith</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="850407" version="1065353216">&quot;Zenith&quot; is the code name of a Balmorran revolutionary fighter who has made a career out of hurting the Empire. Once a member of a powerful resistance cell broken up by Imperial infiltrators, Zenith has struck out on his own, gathering followers from Balmorra's oppressed population to launch sneak attacks, raids and bombings against the occupying Imperial forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="850407" version="1065353216">Bewyn Aygo sent you to Nar Shaddaa to make contact with a Balmorran freedom fighter code named Zenith.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="850407" version="1065353216">After hijacking the Nar Shaddaa holonet you were able to contact Zenith.  He grudgingly accepted your offer and wants you to supply him with War Supplies</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="850407" version="1065353216">After hyjacking the Nar Shaddaa holonet you were able to make contact with Zenith.  Zenith seemed pleasantly surprised to see the Barsen'thor.  He agreed to meet you face to face to discuss some big plans he has been working on.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="850407" version="1065353216">Zenith seems to be impressed with your contributions to his continued effort against Zakuul.  He has agreed to a face to face meet to go over some plans he has been working on.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="850407" version="1065353216">Your inital meeting with Zenith did not go well.  He broke off contact completely, and even threatened to kill you.  He may find you someday, at some unkown location and at some unknown time.  But it probably isn't wise to wait around to find out.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="850407" version="1065353216">Zenith needs your help to assault the Star Fortress Orbiting Nar Shaddaa.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="22" id2="850407" version="1065353216">You and Zenith were able to destroy the Star Fortress above Nar Shaddaa</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="851814" version="1065353216">2V-R8</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="851814" version="1065353216">2V-R8 is a Seneschal-series factotum droid outfitted to serve the galaxy's most dangerous individuals. Due to experiences with previous masters, he knows that any moment of weakness or failure could easily result in his permanent deactivation, and he has therefore created multiple subroutines to reroute all his processing capabilities, maximizing his efficiency when seeing to whatever single task his master has assigned him. Despite the constant fear of destruction hanging over his head, 2V-R8 makes every effort to appear professional and composed. He has activated numerous crisis-management programming modules to assist him with handling the stress on his processors. So far, his power core has overheated only once.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="851814" version="1065353216">Model of Deferential Fear</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="851814" version="1065353216">2V-R8 may be secretly plotting to kill you. It's hard to know for sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="851814" version="1065353216">You were reunited with 2V-R8 at the alliance base on Odessen.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="851814" version="1065353216">You met 2V-R8 at the alliance base on Odessen, whereupon your kind greeting filled 2V-R8 with hope for a better future under a kind master.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="851814" version="1065353216">You met 2V-R8 at the alliance base on Odessen, whereupon you immediately crushed any dreams he may have had for a better future under a kind master.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="851879" version="1065353216">C2-N2</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="851879" version="1065353216">C2-N2 is a model of gentlemanly manners and polite efficiency. A Hollis-series steward droid that served one of the Republic's most famous heroes, he will do everything in his considerable programming power to ensure that his master's starship always maintains the proper air of respectability. This includes high-powered dusting capabilities, monitoring the crew's caloric intake and a selection of aromas from across the galaxy to satisfy even the pickiest of noses.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="851879" version="1065353216">Foremost Authority on Comfort</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="851879" version="1065353216">You met C2-N2 at the alliance base on Odessen.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="851879" version="1065353216">You were reunited with C2-N2 at the alliance base on Odessen, for better or worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="851879" version="1065353216">C2-N2 was literally overloaded with joy after you assisted him in bringing comfort to the inhabitants of the alliance base.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="852697" version="1065353216">Nico Okarr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="852697" version="1065353216">Years before the Sith Empire launched the Great Galactic War, Nico was one of the most celebrated mercenary spacers on the Outer Rim. His deeds were legendary, but so were his debts, leading him to take the most high-risk and even-higher-reward underworld contracts available. Every criminal syndicate from the Hutt Cartel down competed for his services because he always delivered the goods, no matter the odds. Ultimately, that was his undoing. When the Jedi Order assigned astromech droid T7-O1 to an undercover sting operation as Nico's co-pilot on the Redshifter, events conspired to place everyone on Korriban just in time for the Sith Empire's devastating return to Republic space. Nico personally saved Satele Shan and fled the Imperial Fleet to warn Coruscant of the danger--and promptly escaped custody never to be seen again... until now.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="852697" version="1065353216">The Infamous Smuggler</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="852697" version="1065353216">You found Nico biding his time within the Platform 6 Cantina in the Zakuul Undercity.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="852697" version="1065353216">Nico Okarr asked you to mix him a drink of your own design as a judge of your character.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="852697" version="1065353216">Your inclusion of the little umbrella in Nico's drink particularly impressed him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="852697" version="1065353216">You failed to include the little umbrella in Nico's drink. He will never forget it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="852697" version="1065353216">The drink you made for Nico Okarr impressed him. He has agreed to join you as a follower.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="853886" version="1065353216">Akk Dog</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="853886" version="1065353216">Akk dogs form strong bonds with their handler and can be trained to perform multiple tasks. These pack creatures are capable of domestication and, with the right handler, can be quite vicious.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="854925" version="1065353216">Probe Droid</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="854925" version="1065353216">Probe droids are often used to carry out reconnaissance or patrol missions. This probe droid is programmed with offensive, defensive and medical protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="855156" version="1065353216">Theron Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="855156" version="1065353216">Some are driven to follow in their parents' footsteps, while others loathe the very idea. For Theron Shan, it's a moot point. In keeping with Jedi strictures against attachment, Theron's mother, Grand Master Satele Shan, sent her infant son to be raised by the Jedi who trained her, Master Ngani Zho. When it became evident that Theron was not Force sensitive, he abandoned any notion of becoming a Jedi. He joined the Strategic Information Service, using his adventurous nature and unique skillset to become a trusted field agent for the Republic.

Despite his success against the Revanites, Theron was put on administrative leave after Master Satele and Chancellor Saresh discovered he sent a team of black-ops Jedi to Ziost without their knowledge. Arcann's invasion of the Core Worlds accelerated his reinstatement into the SIS, but Saresh's policies frustrated him. When Lana Beniko approached him with a plan to build an alliance against Arcann, Theron was happy to walk away and fight what he considered the real threat to the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="855156" version="1065353216">The Secret Agent</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="855156" version="1065353216">You have begun a romantic relationship with Theron.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="855156" version="1065353216">With the return of your former romance, you and Theron have decided to end your relationship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="855156" version="1065353216">After losing faith in the cause and becoming disillusioned, Theron Shan has betrayed you and formed a plan to destroy your Alliance. Despite this, you've sent a message offering him a place by your side.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="855156" version="1065353216">After losing faith in the cause and becoming disillusioned, Theron Shan has betrayed you and formed a plan to destroy your Alliance. Branding him a traitor, you issued a bounty on Theron's head.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="855156" version="1065353216">Theron's betrayal was too great, no matter his reasons. You left him for dead on Nathema with the rest of the Order of Zildrog.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="855156" version="1065353216">Theron has returned from being a double agent among the Order of Zildrog, and though you brought him back to the Alliance base to heal his wounds, his betrayal was too great to ignore. You have forced him out of the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="22" id2="855156" version="1065353216">After recovering from his wounds during the fight with the Order of Zildrog, you have accepted Theron Shan back, forgiving his apparent betrayal for the ruse it always was.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="23" id2="855156" version="1065353216">After all of your adventures, after the rise and fall of the Eternal Empire and the Alliance, after his seeming betrayal and triumphant return, you asked Theron Shan to marry you, and he accepted.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="855672" version="1065353216">Xalek</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="855672" version="1065353216">A Kaleesh warrior captured by the Empire in battle and brought to Korriban to train as a Sith, Xalek prefers actions to words. Before even reaching the Academy, he killed several of his fellow slaves who were also intended for training--a bold statement by any measure. Xalek melds his training as a Kaleesh warrior with a firm belief in the Sith Code. He kills without remorse and is an expert student of lightsaber technique and martial combat.

Xalek left Korriban to become an apprentice to a Dark Council member, whom he served until his master's untimely disappearance. He took advantage of the chaos from the Eternal Empire's invasion to hone his skills and grow his power. After being given the title of Sith Lord, he decided to travel the galaxy to test himself in new ways.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="855672" version="1065353216">The Ruthless Avenger</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="855672" version="1065353216">You tracked Xalek down on Ilum, where he was systematically killing members of a mining expedition that desecrated his father's grave.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="855672" version="1065353216">You refused to allow Xalek to continue killing the miners and restore his father's honor, which led to an altercation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="855672" version="1065353216">You allowed Xalek to kill the miners at the foreman's camp and fulfill his duty, earning you Xalek's respect.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="855672" version="1065353216">You convinced the miners to build a shrine to venerate Xalek's father, fulfilling Xalek's obligation to his father's honor, and sparing the miners' lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="855672" version="1065353216">After defeating Xalek in a duel, you rejected him as a companion, and had him imprisoned for his crimes.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="855672" version="1065353216">You killed Xalek after defeating him in a duel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="22" id2="855672" version="1065353216">You defeated Xalek in a duel, demonstrating your power, and was thus able to convince him to join you as a follower.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="23" id2="855672" version="1065353216">After seeing the events on Ilum, you rejected Xalek as a potential follower.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="24" id2="855672" version="1065353216">You defeated Xalek after he attacked you, and killed him for his insolence and failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="25" id2="855672" version="1065353216">Despite his own stature as a Sith Lord, Xalek freely chose to rejoin you as a follower out of respect and recognition of your power.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="26" id2="855672" version="1065353216">Xalek's current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="857664" version="1065353216">K'krohl</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="857664" version="1065353216">Not everyone who walks around with a Czerka BTZ-47 heavy assault cannon is looking for a fight. In a few cases, they're more interested in opening a mutually beneficial dialogue. The Whiphid self-described &quot;talent scout&quot; known as K'krohl proudly raises his weapon as a calling card to announce that he's open for business and seeking a few good mercenaries.

K'krohl has recruited forces for a diverse array of clients, from the Hutt Cartel's Territorial Enforcers to Makeb's InterStellar Regulators and even the Republic SIS's Saboteur Squads. He believes that every criminal, no matter how despicable, has a hidden talent just waiting to be leveraged for the right cause. These days, his well-paying cause is to gather forces to fight for the Alliance against the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="857664" version="1065353216">The Talent Scout</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="857664" version="1065353216">You were contacted by K'krohl on Belsavis to get your help destroying the Shield Bunker.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="857664" version="1065353216">You investiged the Shield Bunker on advice from K'krohl.  You found it to be heavily defended and defeated its primary guardian.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="857664" version="1065353216">You have gathered enough supplies to earn K'krohl's help destroying the Shield bunker on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="857664" version="1065353216">You have successfully destroyed the shield bunker on Belsavis with the help of K'krohl.  He has agreed to join your alliance and help you destroy the Star Fortress over Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="857664" version="1065353216">After destroying the Star Fortress over Belsavis, K'krohl has decided to join your alliance fully.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="857665" version="1065353216">Rokuss</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="857665" version="1065353216">Gormak have battled both Republic and Imperial forces on Voss since the day they made it their business to interfere with the ancient war for control of the planet. While most Gormak still bear a grudge against all outsiders, a few forward-thinking individuals have realized that the new invaders from Zakuul are a far greater threat to Voss.

Rokuss is a hardened Gormak warrior who has looked beyond his people's traditional hatreds and united with old foes to defeat the Eternal Empire. He saw his older brothers fall in battle to the Alliance Commander years before the rise of Emperor Arcann. Where some would swear a blood oath of vengeance, Rokuss took the lesson that not all battles are worth fighting--and his brothers chose their enemy especially poorly. He now offers his services as soldier and bodyguard to the same Commander who killed his kin. In Rokuss's eyes, helping to defeat the Eternal Empire at the Commander's side is an honorable way to settle the family debt.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="857665" version="1065353216">The Honorable Warrior</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="857665" version="1065353216">You were contacted by Rokuss on Voss to get your help destroying the Shield Bunker.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="857665" version="1065353216">You investigated the Shield Bunker on advice from Rokuss.  You found it to be heavily defended and defeated its primary guardian.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="857665" version="1065353216">You have gathered enough supplies to earn Rokuss's help destroying the Shield bunker on Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="857665" version="1065353216">You have successfully destroyed the shield bunker on Voss with the help of Rokuss.  He has agreed to join your alliance and help you destroy the Star Fortress over Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="857665" version="1065353216">After destroying the Star Fortress over Voss, Rokuss has decided to join your alliance fully.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="857884" version="1065353216">Veeroa Denz</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="857884" version="1065353216">Many Sith have perished while defending their homeworlds from the Eternal Empire's forces, but others have taken the opportunity to create new lives elsewhere. One such person is Veeroa Denz, a Nautolan slave whose Force sensitivity saw her thrown into the harsh acolyte training on Korriban. She survived her trials and a cruel overseer only to become a target of Zakuul's soldiers when they stormed the Sith Academy. She escaped the slaughter with a bit of luck and a well-timed betrayal of her overseer and fled to Nar Shaddaa to start a new life.

Veeroa embraced the unlimited freedom of the Smuggler's Moon, offering help to other fugitives whose Force sensitivity had made them targets of the Eternal Empire's ruthless advance. Eventually, those armies arrived in orbit around Nar Shaddaa as well, and Veeroa saw her new home become a prison. She has sworn to aid the Alliance only until Zakuul is vanquished, after which she plans to resume her quiet life of freedom in the shadows.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="857884" version="1065353216">The Sith Refugee</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="857884" version="1065353216">You have been contacted by Veeroa Denz to investigate the Shield Bunker on Nar Shaddaa.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="857884" version="1065353216">You have investigated the Shield Bunker. You found it was heavily guarded by Zakuul forces and need help infiltrating it. Gather supplies to bolster local forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="857884" version="1065353216">You have gathered enough supplies to assault the Shield Bunker.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="857884" version="1065353216">You have destroyed the shield generator with the help of Veeroa Denz. The Star Fortress above Nar Shaddaa is now susceptible to attack. Veeroa will join your alliance should you destroy it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="857884" version="1065353216">You have destroyed the Star Fortress above Nar Shaddaa, ridding Zakuul's presence from the planet. Veeroa Denz has joined your alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="857911" version="1065353216">Choza Raabat</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="857911" version="1065353216">Two years before the Republic and Empire broke the Treaty of Coruscant and resumed open war, Ithorian Jedi Knight Choza Rabaat embarked on a scouting mission into Wild Space. His vessel and astromech droid were destroyed in a crash that Choza barely escaped. He found himself marooned on an uncharted and uninhabited world, where he survived alone for ten long years.

Choza would still be there if a patrol ship from Zakuul hadn't set down to survey the planet. When the crew opened fire on him for the crime of introducing himself and requesting rescue, he was forced to incapacitate them and commandeer their vessel. He returned to the Core Worlds after a lengthy interrogation of his prisoners that caught him up on a decade of history. Now he serves the Alliance to overthrow Emperor Arcann and restore freedom to the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="857911" version="1065353216">The Jedi Castaway</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="857911" version="1065353216">You have been contacted by Choza Raabat to investigate the Shield Bunker on Alderaan.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="857911" version="1065353216">You have investigated the Shield Bunker. You found it was heavily guarded by Zakuul forces and need help infiltrating it. Gather supplies to bolster local forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="857911" version="1065353216">You have gathered enough supplies to assault the Shield Bunker.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="857911" version="1065353216">You have destroyed the shield generator with the help of Choza Raabat. The Star Fortress above Alderaan is now susceptible to attack. Choza will join your alliance should you destroy it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="857911" version="1065353216">You have destroyed the Star Fortress above Alderaan, ridding Zakuul's presence from the planet. Choza Raabat has joined your alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="857944" version="1065353216">Languss &quot;Guss&quot; Tuno</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="857944" version="1065353216">A failed Jedi Padawan who abandoned his training, the enthusiastically greedy Guss Tuno prefers the underworld lifestyle's potential for material riches. In a perfect galaxy, Guss would spend his retirement lounging in a heated swimming pool surrounded by exotic beauties while consuming a steady diet of fresh fish and expensive cocktails.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="857944" version="1065353216">The Unlikely Jedi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="857944" version="1065353216">You have met the &quot;Shiny Jedi Man&quot; Guss Tuno, from Sana-Rae's vision.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="857944" version="1065353216">You agreed to help Guss complete a trial set before him by his master, but failed.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="857944" version="1065353216">You agreed to help Guss complete a trial set before him by his master and succeeded!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="857944" version="1065353216">You recruited the unlikely Jedi Guss Tuno into your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="857944" version="1065353216">You chose not to recruit the unlikely Jedi Guss Tuno into your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="857945" version="1065353216">Blizz</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="857945" version="1065353216">Infinitely curious and adventurous, Blizz always felt confined on his native Tatooine, bored by the endless rolling dunes and limited selection of scrap. So when the traveling salvager Slam Streever visited Blizz's clan to offer Jawas work as &quot;ferrets&quot; on exotic salvage missions, Blizz leapt at the opportunity. He spent several years with Slam's crew, and later with the White Maw pirates, before being imprisoned by the Chiss Ascendancy on Hoth. When the Grand Champion of the Great Hunt freed Blizz from his cell, he vowed to follow his new friend and prove himself useful.
After the Grand Champion's disappearance, Blizz returned to Hoth to form a crew of his own, hunting bounties and salvage with his usual enthusiasm.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="857945" version="1065353216">The Jawa Salvage Runner</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="857945" version="1065353216">You have found Blizz, the preternatural technological expert, on the icy dunes of Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="857945" version="1065353216">Blizz wants to help you free of charge, but he needs to first finish his current job on Hoth, and has asked for your help in doing so.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="857945" version="1065353216">You have collected enough salvage for Blizz to repair his &quot;white-sand crawler,&quot; Blizz has asked for your help in finishing his current contact on Hoth, after which he will be willing to consider your offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="857945" version="1065353216">Blizz has rejoined you as a follower. You are now the Big Boss once again.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="22" id2="857945" version="1065353216">Blizz has decided you are now the Big Boss and joined you as a follower.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="859321" version="1065353216">M1-4X</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="859321" version="1065353216">M1-4X is a highly advanced war droid designed and built specifically to serve in Havoc Squad. As such, his engineers programmed him to be a perfect soldier: completely loyal, fervently patriotic, and willing and eager to go to any length or face any risk to destroy the Republic's enemies. M1-4X's armor plating, weapons systems and processing power are significantly advanced over typical military droid standards, due in large part to his unusual power core. Constructed by an unknown organization, the core was recovered during a classified operation and has output capabilities far beyond conventional models.

After his commanding officer went missing in action, M1-4X's boisterous patriotism made him a perfect fit for the press corps, where he continued his work on improving soldiers' morale. His fiery speeches and heroic tales from Havoc Squad has made M1-4X a legend among the Republic ranks. Not one to let fame go to his circuits, M1-4X's only comment on his newfound notoriety is simply, &quot;All in a day's work!&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="859321" version="1065353216">Booming Vocoder of Freedom</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="859321" version="1065353216">You found M1-4X on Coruscant. You convinced M1-4X  to join your alliance through victories against the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="859321" version="1065353216">You found M1-4X on Coruscant. You convinced M1-4X to your alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="859322" version="1065353216">Major Pierce</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="859322" version="1065353216">While few who are not Force sensitive in the Empire have any choice but to join the military, Lieutenant Pierce joined eagerly--not out of a sense of duty but out of a lust for action. In fact, although his soldiering and bravery are beyond question, he has faced resistance and scrutiny throughout his military career due to his occasionally reckless attitude and his disdain for authority.

Pierce thrived during his service to the Emperor's Wrath and even led a successful operation capturing the Bastion on Corellia. But when the Wrath vanished, the Moffs decided a war hero like Pierce was too valuable to lose in combat. They promoted him, then reassigned him to a desk job at the Outreach Bureau, where he could act as an idol for the new recruits, much to Pierce's chagrin.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="859322" version="1065353216">The Reckless Specialist</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="859322" version="1065353216">You found Major Pierce on Dromund Kaas. You convinced Major Pierce to join your alliance through victories against the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="859322" version="1065353216">You found Major Pierce on Dromund Kaas. You convinced Major Pierce to join your alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="859324" version="1065353216">T7-01</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="859324" version="1065353216">Little is known about T7 before the droid came into the service of the Jedi. Certain features of its construction hint at it being a custom model built some time ago, but there are no official records to substantiate the theory. Regardless of its origins, the droid's enthusiasm and willingness to put itself in harm's way leave little doubt as to its loyalty.

Despite T7's ties to the Republic, the droid readily agreed to work with Sith Lord Lana Beniko after Arcann attacked the Core Worlds and its master went missing. Because of T7's unthreatening appearance, it's often overlooked, making the droid a perfect informant and ally in the fight against the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="859324" version="1065353216">The Steadfast Companion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="859361" version="1065353216">Skadge</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="859361" version="1065353216">A career gangster and psychopath, Skadge had been enjoying a prestigious position at the top of Coruscant's most wanted list when a joint police, military and SIS task force managed to finally capture him. Deemed impossible to control or reform, the murderous Houk was secretly ushered to the only facility capable of housing him: Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="859361" version="1065353216">The Ruthless Criminal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="859361" version="1065353216">You met Skadge on Nar Shaddaa where he was acting as the current leader of the Black Sun gang.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="859361" version="1065353216">You recruited Skadge and his Black Sun gang into your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="859361" version="1065353216">You put an end to Skadge and the Black Sun gang on Nar Shaddaa. Skadge is currently in Republic custody.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="859361" version="1065353216">You put an end to Skadge and the Black Sun gang on Nar Shaddaa. Skadge did not survive the encounter.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="859361" version="1065353216">You reunited with Skadge on Nar Shaddaa where he was acting as the current leader of the Black Sun gang.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="859406" version="1065353216">Bey'wan Aygo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="859406" version="1065353216">From his birth, Bey'wan Aygo's artistic parents nurtured him to follow in their footsteps. But ever since, as a young Bothan, he first spied a space battle through a telescope over his homeworld, the only art Aygo has wanted to practice is that of interstellar combat.

Bey'wan first made a name for himself at the Battle of Kuat, and has since impressed his superiors with his fresh, innovative tactics. When Arcann invaded the Core Worlds, Bey'wan was quick to put together a variety of initiatives to counter the Eternal Empire's assault. His plans were stonewalled by Chancellor Saresh, who was more interested in continuing her war against the Sith. When he protested Saresh's orders, he was discharged. However, his yelling did attract the attention of Theron Shan, who approached him to become the Alliance military specialist.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="859406" version="1065353216">The Staunch Admiral</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="859414" version="1065353216">Hylo Visz</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="859414" version="1065353216">Hylo Visz is best known as the pilot responsible for breaking the Mandalorian Blockade of Hydian Way. Well-compensated for her efforts, Hylo planned to live a life of luxury with her partner Tyresius Lokai (also known as Gault Rennow). Unfortunately, those plans were wrecked when Lokai stole Hylo's fortune and left her unable to pay her considerable debts to the Hutt Cartel for funding the operation to break the blockade. Out of options, Hylo was forced to hide in a stasis pod on Belsavis for ten years. Lokai eventually found and freed her, but it was too little, too late. Hylo returned to a life of crime until Theron Shan lured her into working for the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="859414" version="1065353216">The Legendary Outlaw</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="859415" version="1065353216">Sana-Rae</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="859415" version="1065353216">Voss Mystics are powerful Force seers whose visions guide and protect the Voss people. In a society that's naturally suspicious of &quot;Outsiders,&quot; it's rare for a Voss citizen to leave their homeworld, and almost unheard of for a Mystic. But Sana-Rae has proven unique even by her people's standards. While Voss Mystics are normally uninterested in Sith and Jedi philosophies, Sana-Rae joined the Alliance with an open mind. Her vision showed an Enclave of Force users who walk a variety of paths, share knowledge and grow stronger by gaining an understanding from their differences. She knows that she too will change, but has the courage to accept it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="859415" version="1065353216">The Voss Mystic</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="859432" version="1065353216">Hemdil Tre</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="859432" version="1065353216">Sometimes, fate imbues a single individual with an embarrassment of unrelated talents. In the case of Arcona war historian Hemdil Tre, that's a keen scholar's mind combined with some of the deadliest gun-fighting accuracy ever witnessed. Those who underestimate him--or, worse, draw their weapons on him--have little time to recognize the error of their ways. He always feels bad about these altercations and apologizes profusely to the smoking remains.

Having chronicled the entire history of Arcona warfare, Hemdil now wishes to write the definitive biography of the Commander for the Alliance against the Eternal Empire. He has found a task worthy of both his specialties: Only a skilled blaster combatant has any hope of surviving the Commander's many battles to write a first-person account. At long last, Hemdil Tre isn't merely writing history--he's living it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="859432" version="1065353216">The Military Historian</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="859432" version="1065353216">After destroying the Star Fortress over Hoth, Hemdil Tre has decided to join your alliance fully.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="859432" version="1065353216">You have gathered enough supplies to earn Hemdil Tre's help destroying the Shield bunker on Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="859432" version="1065353216">You investigated the Shield Bunker on advice from Hemdil Tre.  You found it to be heavily defended and defeated its primary guardian.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="859432" version="1065353216">You have successfully destroyed the shield bunker on Hoth with the help of Hemdil Tre.  He has agreed to join your alliance and help you destroy the Star Fortress over Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="859432" version="1065353216">You were contacted by Hemdil Tre on Hoth to get your help destroying the Shield Bunker.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="859433" version="1065353216">&quot;Deadeye&quot; Leyta</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="859433" version="1065353216">Selonians are well known for their strong family ties, but there is a dark side to these tribal bonds. Conflicts between competing tribes can erupt into deadly feuds and terrible violence. The gun-for-hire &quot;Deadeye&quot; Leyta was the unquestioned victor of one such conflict when she single-handedly blasted every member of a rival family that had oppressed hers for years. Given the enormity of the carnage--and the likelihood of reprisals--Leyta left her homeworld of Corellia and settled in the deserts of Tatooine, where she could at least spot potential assassins from a safe distance.

Leyta quickly established herself as one of the planet's best mercenaries, taking jobs from anyone willing to pay. She continues to settle disputes in her own fashion, which usually ensures there's no one left to make any trouble. The arrival of an Eternal Empire Star Fortress in orbit gave Leyta her biggest target yet, and she jumped at the chance to aid the Alliance Commander in blowing it out of the sky.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="859433" version="1065353216">The Quick Shot</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="859433" version="1065353216">You were contacted by &quot;Deadeye&quot; Leyta on Tatooine to get your help destroying the Shield Bunker.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="859433" version="1065353216">You have successfully destroyed the shield bunker on Tatooine with the help of &quot;Deadeye&quot; Leyta.  He has agreed to join your alliance and help you destroy the Star Fortress over Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="859433" version="1065353216">You have gathered enough supplies to earn &quot;Deadeye&quot; Leyta's help destroying the Shield bunker on Tatooine.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="859433" version="1065353216">After destroying the Star Fortress over Tatooine, &quot;Deadeye&quot; Leyta has decided to join your alliance fully.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="859433" version="1065353216">You investigated the Shield Bunker on advice from &quot;Deadeye&quot; Leyta.  You found it to be heavily defended and defeated its primary guardian.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="859493" version="1065353216">Isaac</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="859493" version="1065353216">The Enigmatic Force Master</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="859535" version="1065353216">Akaavi Spar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="859535" version="1065353216">Akaavi Spar was born into a respected Mandalorian clan and became one of its finest warriors. She killed her first foe--an abusive Abyssin mercenary--at the age of eight using an improvised flamethrower. This victory earned her the nickname &quot;firehand&quot; among her clan and marked the beginning of an impressive career as an Imperial bounty hunter. Akaavi captured and killed all manner of targets in her youth, from career criminals to Jedi.

When her entire clan was framed for crimes against the Empire and executed, Akaavi alone survived the brutal purge--but her outlook on the galaxy changed forever. With no connection to her Mandalorian heritage, she became a wandering mercenary loyal to no one.

Likes: Combat challenges, profit, irritating authority figures
Dislikes: The Republic, dishonorable acts, mercy</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="859535" version="1065353216">You have recruited Akaavi Spar to your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="859535" version="1065353216">You have decided that after all this time you still love Akaavi! You have resumed your romance with her.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="859535" version="1065353216">You have decided that, despite your shared romantic history, you would break off your relationship with Akaavi.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="859535" version="1065353216">After reuniting with Akaavi Spar and renewing your relationship, things have changed and you no longer care for her in the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="859676" version="1065353216">Bowdaar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="859676" version="1065353216">The mighty Wookiee gladiator named Bowdaar has spent over a century facing countless opponents without ever losing a match. He solidified his title as the galaxy's greatest gladiator when he defeated notorious Wookiee-hunter Karssk on Ord Mantell. The more gullible underworld scum whisper that Bowdaar is an immortal creature who can't be killed, but those who have faced him and lived know that he is simply the best there is. 

On the surface, Bowdaar may seem like a simple-minded brute, but nothing could be further from the truth. Case in point: Bowdaar eventually discovered the identity of the Trandoshans who first captured and enslaved him. One night in an arena on Loovria, Bowdaar learned that his former captors were sitting in the stands. An unfortunate &quot;weapons malfunction&quot; caused the drunken Trandoshan slavers to meet an untimely--and extremely messy--end.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="859676" version="1065353216">The Wookiee Gladiator</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="859676" version="1065353216">You met with the Wookiee Bowdaar on Zakuul and heard his plan to help free a number of gladiatorial slaves from the Arena Grand.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="859676" version="1065353216">Having made a name for yourself in the Arena Grand, Bowdaar was able to bargain for the freedom of the gladiatorial slaves on the condition he and you team up for one final arena melee.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="859676" version="1065353216">Bowdaar and yourself have proven victorious in the arena and have won the freedom of the gladiatorial slaves!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="859676" version="1065353216">Bowdaar joined your alliance as a follower.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="870166" version="1065353216">Nexu</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="870166" version="1065353216">Nexu are vicious feline predators commonly used for arena battle. However, a patient handler can form a strong bond with their Nexu, training them to perform multiple tasks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="870678" version="1065353216">Personal Warbot</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="870678" version="1065353216">Personal Warbots are often used for guard duty by various cartel groups. This Personal Warbot is programmed with offensive, defensive and medical protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="874139" version="1065353216">HK-51</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="874139" version="1065353216">The droid designated HK-51 is cold, calculating and incredibly lethal. Housed in a sleek body resembling an antique Systech Corporation protocol unit, this HK-series assassination droid lay dormant in the hold of an Imperial vessel for many years. Whatever HK-51's original programming dictated, he pledged absolute loyalty to his new master upon his reactivation.

HK-51 is a model of ruthless efficiency. His assassination protocols deteriorate unless they are put to frequent use. This leads to a constant acquisition, pursuit and permanent removal of qualified targets that would be seen as an obsession in any living being. Beyond expressing pride in successful assassinations, HK-51 has little patience for the trivial emotional problems of organics.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="874139" version="1065353216">The Finest in Automated Assassination</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="874140" version="1065353216">HK-51</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="874140" version="1065353216">The droid designated HK-51 is cold, calculating and incredibly lethal. Housed in a sleek body resembling an antique Systech Corporation protocol unit, this HK-series assassination droid lay dormant in the hold of an Imperial vessel for many years. Whatever HK-51's original programming dictated, he pledged absolute loyalty to his new master upon his reactivation.

HK-51 is a model of ruthless efficiency. His assassination protocols deteriorate unless they are put to frequent use. This leads to a constant acquisition, pursuit and permanent removal of qualified targets that would be seen as an obsession in any living being. Beyond expressing pride in successful assassinations, HK-51 has little patience for the trivial emotional problems of organics.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="874140" version="1065353216">The Finest in Automated Assassination</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="874144" version="1065353216">Treek</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="874144" version="1065353216">Treek is an enthusiastic warrior who defied her primitive tribe's rigid customs to seek adventure among the stars. Dissatisfied with the peaceful and quiet ways of her people, Treek is determined to achieve great things with her life. She travels the galaxy as a mercenary soldier, always on the hunt for new horizons and epic challenges to conquer. Despite hailing from a technologically-archaic planet and species, Treek has adapted quickly to civilized space.

Treek is unconcerned with material possessions or personal power. Her only goal is to forge a legacy that will outlive her. In Treek's mind, the greatest defeat is to be forgotten. She will do whatever it takes to ensure her name and deeds will be celebrated long after she is gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="874144" version="1065353216">The Unlikely Mercenary</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="874145" version="1065353216">Treek</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="874145" version="1065353216">Treek is an enthusiastic warrior who defied her primitive tribe's rigid customs to seek adventure among the stars. Dissatisfied with the peaceful and quiet ways of her people, Treek is determined to achieve great things with her life. She travels the galaxy as a mercenary soldier, always on the hunt for new horizons and epic challenges to conquer. Despite hailing from a technologically-archaic planet and species, Treek has adapted quickly to civilized space.

Treek is unconcerned with material possessions or personal power. Her only goal is to forge a legacy that will outlive her. In Treek's mind, the greatest defeat is to be forgotten. She will do whatever it takes to ensure her name and deeds will be celebrated long after she is gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="874145" version="1065353216">The Unlikely Mercenary</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="886637" version="1065353216">Ak'ghal Usar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="886637" version="1065353216">Ak'ghal Usar, the Last Lord of Urkupp, is a being out of time. Seeking vengeance for his fellow Dashade who were eradicated in the Great Sith War, Usar traveled to Yavin 4 in the hope of confronting his people's killer, only to be trapped in stasis instead. Now, centuries later, his original target is gone, as is the Sith who imprisoned him--Valkorion.

Still hungry for vengeance, Ak'ghal Usar is willing to join forces to exact his revenge on the best targets remaining to him: Arcann and the forces of the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="886637" version="1065353216">Last Lord of Urkupp</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="886637" version="1065353216">You encountered Ak'ghal Usar in a hidden chamber within the Architect's Hollow, after your actions inadvertently freed him from stasis.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="886637" version="1065353216">Ak'ghal agreed to join your alliance as a means of exacting revenge against those who imprisoned him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="886637" version="1065353216">You rejected Ak'ghal Usar as an Alliance follower. Finding him too dangerous to leave free, you forced him back into stasis on Yavin 4.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="886637" version="1065353216">You later returned to Yavin 4 and decided to free Ak'ghal Usar from his stasis.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="886637" version="1065353216">Ak'ghal Usar's current whereabouts are unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="22" id2="886637" version="1065353216">You rejected Ak'ghal Usar as an Alliance follower, leaving him free to roam the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="887121" version="1065353216">Torian Cadera</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="887121" version="1065353216">Loyalty, honor, tradition: Torian Cadera embodies the Mandalorian ideals. He serves his leaders with a fierce allegiance, yet the shadow of his father's defection to the Republic has hung over him for most of his life. As a result, Torian's relationship with his fellow Mandalorians is complicated, and he's had to prove himself time and again to overcome the Cadera stigma. But those who could look past his family found a noble warrior who eventually joined forces with the Grand Champion of the Great Hunt.

When the Grand Champion went missing after the rise of Zakuul, Torian returned to the Mandalorians and volunteered for the most dangerous strikes against the Eternal Fleet, leading successful infiltration and surveillance missions. His skill and dedication let him rise in the ranks and gain the trust of Mandalore the Avenger herself, earning him a place by her side.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="887121" version="1065353216">Last of Clan Cadera</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="887121" version="1065353216">After successfully capturing GEMINI Prime, Torian stayed to represent the Mandalorians in the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="887121" version="1065353216">You and Torian spent years apart, and things can never be the same again. You've agreed to end your relationship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="887121" version="1065353216">Despite your years apart, you remain Torian's cyar'ika. Your relationship is stronger than ever.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="887121" version="1065353216">Torian fought valiantly to defend the Alliance base, but the Eternal Empire's forces proved overwhelming. He was ultimately killed by Empress Vaylin.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="887769" version="1065353216">Kaliyo Djannis</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="887769" version="1065353216">Prizing freedom and anarchy above all, Kaliyo Djannis has always done precisely what she wants. She spent her adult life jumping between unsavory jobs, including for the Hutt Cartel and the Exchange. Willing to lie, cheat, and steal to get her way, she racked up a long list of enemies and ex-lovers. When Cipher Nine landed on Hutta to make a deal with Nem'ro the Hutt, Kaliyo temporarily put everything aside to join the agent and work with Imperial Intelligence.
After Cipher Nine's disappearance, Kaliyo went back to freelancing around the galaxy. When she eventually grew bored, she landed on Zakuul and began targeting government and civilian buildings in terrorist bombings. Her activities drew the citizenry's attention, earning her the nickname &quot;Firebrand&quot; and sparking the first real flames of rebellion.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="887769" version="1065353216">The Self-Serving Anarchist</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="887769" version="1065353216">After setting off a massive chain of destruction on the Spire, Kaliyo decided to stick around and assist the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="887769" version="1065353216">Despite being denied her destructive revenge on the Spire, Kaliyo decided to stick around and assist the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="887769" version="1065353216">Time has caused you and Kaliyo to drift apart. You've decided to end your relationship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="887769" version="1065353216">Years may have passed, but you and Kaliyo still have something special. Your relationship is as strong as ever.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="887769" version="1065353216">You sent Kaliyo to capture the GEMINI Frequency in an attempt to control the Eternal Fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="887769" version="1065353216">Kaliyo disobeyed your direct order and endangered the GEMINI Frequency mission. For her mistake, her punishment was death.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="22" id2="887769" version="1065353216">Kaliyo disobeyed your direct order and endangered the GEMINI Frequency mission. Unable to forgive her, you banished her from the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="23" id2="887769" version="1065353216">Although Kaliyo disobeyed your direct order not to interfere with the GEMINI Frequency mission, you forgave her.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="889133" version="1065353216">Aric Jorgan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="889133" version="1065353216">A natural soldier, Aric Jorgan enlisted in the military at an early age and quickly distinguished himself as a talented marksman. He earned a reputation as a demanding, unwavering leader and patriot, and there is little he wouldn't do to protect those under his command. This same dedication served him well when he assisted a young lieutenant in rebuilding the famed Havoc Squad, winning major victories for the Republic.
When his commanding officer went missing in action at the start of the Eternal Empire's invasion, Jorgan assumed leadership of Havoc Squad. He was conflicted: he loved the Republic but disagreed with its willingness to kneel to Zakuul. Determined to protect the Republic in spite of itself, he began leading Havoc on unsanctioned strike missions deep in Zakuul territory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="889133" version="1065353216">The Loyal Soldier</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="889133" version="1065353216">Jorgan joined the Alliance, proud to send his Havoc Squad in aid of the rebels on Zakuul.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="889133" version="1065353216">Though he disagreed with your refusal to aid the rebels on Zakuul, Jorgan and his Havoc Squad joined the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="889133" version="1065353216">Years have passed, and your relationship with Jorgan isn't the same. You've decided to end your romance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="889133" version="1065353216">Years may have passed, but your romance with Jorgan is as strong as ever. He stands by your side once again.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="889133" version="1065353216">You sent Jorgan to destroy the relay station and eliminate the GEMINI Frequency.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="889133" version="1065353216">Jorgan disobeyed your direct order and endangered the GEMINI Frequency mission. For his mistake, his punishment was death.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="22" id2="889133" version="1065353216">Jorgan disobeyed your direct order and endangered the GEMINI Frequency mission. Unable to forgive him, you banished him from the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="23" id2="889133" version="1065353216">Although Jorgan disobeyed your direct order not to interfere with the GEMINI Frequency mission, you forgave him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="892703" version="1065353216">Gault Rennow</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="892703" version="1065353216">Formerly the notorious smuggler and confidence man Tyresius Lokai, Gault Rennow briefly enjoyed a relatively paranoia-free lifestyle as an unknown gun-for-hire. But old habits are hard to shake, and Gault soon found himself a target of the Grand Champion of the Great Hunt. After convincing the infamous bounty hunter to spare him, he joined the Grand Champion as a right-hand man.

When his new employer mysteriously vanished, Gault went back to doing what he does best: making money and getting into trouble. With his new partner Vette, he racked up a brand-new list of offenses and enemies. He currently maintains a tumultuous relationship with the infamous smuggler Hylo Visz.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="892703" version="1065353216">The Scoundrel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="892703" version="1065353216">After successfully plundering the Gilded Star, Gault stuck around to help the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="892711" version="1065353216">Vette</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="892711" version="1065353216">A Twi'lek born into slavery on the planet Ryloth, Vette escaped a life of servitude to become an accomplished rogue and treasure hunter. She spent time in her youth stealing for the notorious crime lord Nok Drayen before going into business for herself after his death. Too daring for her own good, she managed to breach Imperial defenses and sneak onto Korriban, gaining entry to the most sacred Sith tombs before getting caught. Her second stint in slavery landed her in the service of the Emperor's Wrath, who she followed on a violent path of revenge.

When the Wrath went missing at the start of the Zakuul invasion, Vette pulled a few odd jobs before joining up with roguish smuggler Gault Rennow. The duo scammed their way through the galaxy, making credits and enemies wherever they went.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="892711" version="1065353216">The Tomb Robber</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="892711" version="1065353216">Excited at the opportunity to be a hero, Vette eagerly joined the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="892711" version="1065353216">Though Vette's feelings haven't changed, yours have diminished over time. You ended your romance with Vette.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="892711" version="1065353216">After all this time, your relationship with Vette is as loving as ever. You've decided to continue your romance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="892711" version="1065353216">Vette fought valiantly to defend the Alliance base, but the Eternal Empire's forces proved overwhelming. She was ultimately killed by Empress Vaylin.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="894889" version="1065353216">K'lor'slug Soldier</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="894889" version="1065353216">K'lor'slugs are large, carnivorous worm-like creatures whose gaping mouths are lined with concentric rings of razor-sharp teeth. Due to their aggressiveness, domestication of these creatures is tenuous at best. Handlers are advised to use extreme caution and protective armor at all times.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="896917" version="1065353216">QO-77</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="896917" version="1065353216">Assassin Droids are often used as enforcers by criminal elements. This QO-77 unit is programmed with offensive, defensive and medical protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="900649" version="1065353216">Ginx</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="900649" version="1065353216">Sharing a family tree with the more aggressive vrakes, Ginxes are often harmless, curious amphibians that frequent Makeb's marshes. However, an intrepid handler can form a strong bond with their Ginx, training them to perform multiple tasks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="901486" version="1065353216">Z0-0M</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="901486" version="1065353216">Z0-0M is a cheerful droid encountered by HK-55 in the Shroud's secret base.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="901486" version="1065353216">The Blank Slate</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="901486" version="1065353216">Assembled as a mere replicator droid, Z0-0M's cunning and self-awareness rapidly progressed far beyond her original design. She grew to resent the limited intellect of her information-broker master and believed she was the superior being. After killing him, she assumed his appearance and became the Shroud, the most notorious espionage king in the galaxy. When her attempt to wipe HK-55's memory core went awry and erased her own data instead, the great spymaster became Zeeyo, a happy-go-lucky droid with a strong moral compass and no trace of her former identity's malice.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="903107" version="1065353216">Rancor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="903108" version="1065353216">Bogstalker</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="903108" version="1065353216">Bogstalkers are one of many ancient species from the planet Taris -  thought extinct until its rediscovery after the planet's bombardment. Expert creature handlers can train Bogstalkers to perform multiple tasks and can be quite ferocious in combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="903109" version="1065353216">Annihilator T4-1D</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="903109" version="1065353216">Security droids are armed units used for defense on starships or in buildings. Capable warriors, this Annihilator T4-1D is programmed with offensive, defensive and medical protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="903111" version="1065353216">ISO-5R</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="903111" version="1065353216">Hutt-employed scientists designed and manufactured advanced war droids unlike anything the galaxy has seen. Recently decommissioned from Makeb, this ISO-5R unit is ready to serve more civilian needs.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="911869" version="1065353216">Darth Hexid</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="911869" version="1065353216">Darth Hexid is a connoisseur of the dark side. Renowned for her brutal combat prowess and decadent lifestyle, she enjoys the many pleasures of a celebrated Sith, whether savoring exotic feasts held in her honor or hunting down her foes as they flee in a panic. Instead of joining the political infighting of her Sith peers, she amuses herself by watching their rabid power games from the sidelines--lightsaber in one hand, spice wine in the other. 
Darth Hexid earned infamy following her devastating triumphs in the Great Galactic War, but it was the Sith Order's crushing defeat at the hands of Zakuul's conquering army that forever defined her. She now pursues the complete annihilation of the Eternal Empire. Vengeance will be hers, even if it demands a pact with the Outlander's Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="911869" version="1065353216">The Decadent Sith</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="911870" version="1065353216">Shae Vizla</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="911870" version="1065353216">An infamous bounty hunter and deadly warrior, Shae Vizla forged her reputation more than 20 years ago by allying with the Sith Empire against the Jedi and Republic. She reluctantly took up the mantle of leadership for her people after the rise of the Eternal Empire and the death of Mandalore the Vindicated. Declaring herself Mandalore the Avenger, she now works with the Outlander's Alliance to break Zakuul's iron grip over the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="911870" version="1065353216">The Mandalorian Legend</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="911870" version="1065353216">You criticized Shae Vizla's leadership in front of other prominent Mandalorians on Darvannis, bringing instability to the clans.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="911870" version="1065353216">You recruited Shae Vizla into your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="911870" version="1065353216">You praised Shae Vizla's leadership in front of other prominent Mandalorians on Darvannis, which helped maintain stability among the clans.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="911870" version="1065353216">You met and defeated the legendary Mandalorian Shae Vizla in battle on the planet Rishi.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="911870" version="1065353216">You fought alongside Shae Vizla against Revan on Yavin 4.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="911872" version="1065353216">Master Ranos</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="911872" version="1065353216">Master Ranos has always walked her own path, turning her back on the Jedi Council to follow what she calls &quot;the will of the Force.&quot; A true champion of the light side, her journey led her to the farthest reaches of the galaxy, where she used her formidable skills to serve and protect those on the dangerous frontiers of galactic civilization. But now the Force has given her a new purpose: join the Outlander's Alliance in their battle against the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="911872" version="1065353216">The Jedi Maverick</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="911872" version="1065353216">You recruited Master Ranos into your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="913391" version="1065353216">Empress Acina</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="913391" version="1065353216">While the rest of the Dark Council fought the Eternal Empire--and each other--Darth Acina was smart enough to step aside and patiently wait for the right moment to make her move. When she saw the opportunity to side with Arcann to ensure the survival of her people, she took it. Similarly, when the rise of the Outlander's Alliance offered her a chance to break free from Zakuul, she acted quickly. Recognizing their common interests, Acina seeks a partnership that will usher in a new era of mutually beneficial coexistence.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="913391" version="1065353216">The Wisest of the Sith</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="913391" version="1065353216">After proving herself a worthy collaborator in the wilds of Dromund Kaas, Empress Acina forged an alliance with you against the Eternal Throne.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="913391" version="1065353216">Despite her best efforts to forge an alliance against Vaylin, Empress Acina was unable to win your trust. The Sith will now be forced to stand alone against the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="913391" version="1065353216">When war erupted on Iokath, Acina joined you to fight the Republic for control of the planet's ancient technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="913391" version="1065353216">When war erupted on Iokath, Acina failed to forge a partnership with the Eternal Alliance. She now fights you and your Republic allies for control of Iokath's ancient technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="913391" version="1065353216">Empress Acina nearly succeeded in claiming Iokath's most powerful superweapon, but died while trying to control the dangerous technology. The Sith Empire mourns her loss.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="914683" version="1065353216">Exoboar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="914683" version="1065353216">When a group of Makeb's early settlers explored the planet's underground caves, they encountered a vicious burrowing animal they named the exoboar. These creatures are capable of domestication and, with the right handler, can be quite vicious.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="920985" version="1065353216">TY-4N</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="920985" version="1065353216">TY-4N is a Battle Droid created and once deployed by the Zakuulan Empire. This unit is programmed with offensive, defensive and medical protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="926197" version="1065353216">Mawvorr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="926197" version="1065353216">Mawvorrs are generally considered opportunistic hunters. They prefer striking at whatever wounded predators or wandering humanoids they come across to carefully hunting and stalking their food, though in packs they exhibit increased aggression and have been known to attack even the mighty vorantikus. However, a patient handler can form a bond with their Mawvorr, training them to perform multiple tasks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="926426" version="1065353216">Lord Dramath</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="926426" version="1065353216">Dramath is the father of Tenebrae, the child who would become the Sith Emperor and later Valkorion, Immortal Emperor of Zakuul. Lord Dramath was killed by his son and imprisoned within a holocron for eternity.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="926426" version="1065353216">Father of Tenebrae</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="927108" version="1065353216">Arcann</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="927108" version="1065353216">Arcann began his brutal reign with the assassination of his own father before spreading untold death and suffering throughout the galaxy. Eventually defeated by the Outlander and stripped of his throne, Arcann initially sought revenge... but the mercy shown to him and his mother by his hated enemy profoundly changed him. Now Arcann fights at the Outlander's side to liberate the galaxy from Zakuul in the hope he can atone for the monumental sins of his past.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="927108" version="1065353216">The Redeemed Tyrant</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="927108" version="1065353216">You have decided that your relationship with Arcann was no longer working out for you.  You have decided to end your romantic relationship with Arcann.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="927108" version="1065353216">Your time with Arcann has proven that you view him as more than just a changed man. You have started a romantic relationship with Arcann.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="927111" version="1065353216">Arcann</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="927111" version="1065353216">Arcann escaped death during the Battle of Odessen, but you ultimately tracked him down on Zakuul--and destroyed him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="927111" version="1065353216">Son of Valkorion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="933136" version="1065353216">Wampa</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="933136" version="1065353216">The fearsome wampa is Hoth's apex predator. These surprisingly intelligent beasts pose a major hazard to unwary travelers, especially those wandering near unexplored caves. Expert creature handlers have found a way to befriend wampas and illustrated they are mighty allies in combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="935179" version="1065353216">K1-Z3N</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="935179" version="1065353216">Alliance forces found and repaired the former Iokath assault droid, K1-Z3N. Equipped with advanced protocols to aid its master and dispatch its foes, this unit has been restored to peak condition.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="943096" version="1065353216">Tuk'ata</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="943096" version="1065353216">These oversized hounds were bred to be fearless and relentless. Left to guard the Sith tombs of Korriban, they have sharp horns, long claws and savage teeth. They are unusually intelligent and seem capable of communicating with one another through unknown means. It is said that the species was nonviolent and grazing before being corrupted by Sith alchemical experiments that awakened a latent part of their brains and changed them into unnatural abominations. Random mutations now occur that produce some tuk'ata that can live for centuries and grow to immense proportions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="946825" version="1065353216">Nathema Beast</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="946825" version="1065353216">A predator subjected to experimentation on the twisted world of Nathema, this beast has been given a new lease on life now that it's been freed from the Keepers' Sanitarium.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="949559" version="1065353216">H1-K1</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="949559" version="1065353216">This refurbished Iokath Purifier droid, H1-K1, is the first in a line of droids released for use by Alliance technical staff. Alliance directives and Iokath technology have combined to create a superlative combat specialist.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="949874" version="1065353216">I-O8</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="949874" version="1065353216">Salvaged and serviced by Imperial engineers, this probe droid combines Iokath technology with Imperial ruthlessness.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="949874" version="1065353216">The Iokath Sentinel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="951780" version="1065353216">Nathema Voreclaw</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="951780" version="1065353216">A grim survivor of Nathema's cataclysm, the ferocious voreclaw can be trained to obey a strong-willed leader, making it a terrifying ally on the battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="951887" version="1065353216">Malavai Quinn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="951887" version="1065353216">An officer in the Imperial military, Malavai Quinn is loyal to the Empire and everything it stands for. When his career was abruptly halted by a mysterious disgrace, he served the powerful Sith Lord known as the Emperor's Wrath. Quinn later betrayed the Wrath at the command of his true master, Darth Baras. The Wrath ultimately forgave his crimes, and Quinn vowed to earn back their trust by helping overthrow Darth Baras.

When the Wrath went missing at the start of the Zakuul invasion, Quinn's rescue efforts ended with him imprisoned by enemies within the Sith Empire. Empress Acina restored him to service and groomed him to serve her as advisor and confidante.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="951887" version="1065353216">The Staunch Imperial</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="951887" version="1065353216">Quinn came crawling back to ask for your forgiveness, but you could not forgive him. Quinn is now locked away in an Eternal Alliance prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="951887" version="1065353216">Quinn came crawling back to ask for forgiveness, but you couldn't forgive him for betraying you to Darth Baras all those years ago. As payment for his treachery, you ended Quinn's life.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="951887" version="1065353216">Quinn still has feelings for you, but you decided to keep your relationship strictly professional. You ended your romance with Quinn.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="22" id2="951887" version="1065353216">After meeting you on Iokath, Malavai Quinn has joined you as a member of the Eternal Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="23" id2="951887" version="1065353216">Despite your time apart, your love for Quinn is stronger than ever. You've decided to continue your romance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="24" id2="951887" version="1065353216">Because of his contempt for the Republic, Quinn chose not to join the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="25" id2="951887" version="1065353216">Quinn reunited with you on Iokath, but you chose to go your separate ways.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="26" id2="951887" version="1065353216">After reuniting with Malavai Quinn and renewing your relationship, things have changed and you no longer care for him in the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="951892" version="1065353216">Elara Dorne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="951892" version="1065353216">A highly talented field medic, Elara Dorne was born Imperial and served in the Empire's military for two years before defecting to the Republic. She has since served with distinction as a search-and-rescue squad leader before being recruited to join Havoc Squad, an elite Special Forces unit sworn to protect the Republic.

When the Commander of Havoc Squad went missing at the start of the Zakuul invasion, Elara Dorne searched tirelessly for them before being forcibly removed from Havoc. Thanks to her flawless operational record, she was selected to advise Supreme Commander Malcom, head of the Republic military.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="951892" version="1065353216">The Perfect Soldier</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="951892" version="1065353216">Elara still loved you, but you didn't share her affection. You ended your romance with Elara.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="951892" version="1065353216">After meeting you on Iokath, Elara Dorne has joined you as a member of the Eternal Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="22" id2="951892" version="1065353216">Despite your time apart, your love for Elara is stronger than ever. You've decided to continue your romance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="24" id2="951892" version="1065353216">Elara reunited with you on Iokath and took issue with your past actions. She will never call you commander again.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="25" id2="951892" version="1065353216">Disgusted at the idea of serving the Empire, Elara chose not to join the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="26" id2="951892" version="1065353216">After reuniting with Elara Dorne and renewing your relationship, things have changed and you no longer care for her in the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="951893" version="1065353216">Jace Malcom</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="951893" version="1065353216">Acting as Supreme Commander of the Republic Military, Jace Malcom is a respected war hero who has spent most of his life locked in combat with the Sith Empire. When the oppressive Eternal Empire nearly destroyed Coruscant, Malcom rallied support to strengthen his military and reclaim the Republic's lost glory. He now sets his sights on the mysterious alien world of Iokath, a treasure trove of valuable resources and superweapons that will help the Republic restore its status as a major galactic superpower.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="951893" version="1065353216">The Republic War Hero</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="951893" version="1065353216">When war erupted on Iokath, Malcom failed to forge a partnership with the Eternal Alliance. He now fights you and your Imperial allies for control of Iokath's ancient technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="951893" version="1065353216">When war erupted on Iokath, Malcom joined you to fight the Sith Empire for control of the planet's ancient technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="951893" version="1065353216">Jace Malcom nearly succeeded in claiming Iokath's most powerful superweapon, but died while trying to control the dangerous technology. The Republic mourns his loss.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="956009" version="1065353216">K-A3</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="956009" version="1065353216">Recovered and reprogrammed by Republic forces, this Iokath probe seems absolutely effervescent in its eagerness to fight by your side.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="956009" version="1065353216">The Iokath Sentinel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="957768" version="1065353216">C8-S3C</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="957768" version="1065353216">Security droids are a type of droid often used as bodyguards, or to protect objects of value. This particular droid has seen severe conflict.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="957768" version="1065353216">The Unstable Defender</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="958134" version="1065353216">Gamorrean Guard</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="958134" version="1065353216">Short, squat humanoids, Gamorreans are easily identifiable by their greenish skin and porcine features. On their homeworld, they live in clans, where the male boars serve exclusively as warriors while the female sows tend the day-to-day affairs like farming, raising young and crafting weapons. Known for their physical strength and endurance, Gamorreans are generally considered a species of below average intelligence. Unable to speak Basic because of their physiology, most Gamorreans are still able to comprehend it and find a place in the galactic community as soldiers, guards or mercenaries. Due to their reputation for violence and brutality, they are often employed by crime lords, gang leaders and various other criminal elements.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="958134" version="1065353216">The Brawny Protector</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="959156" version="1065353216">Vine Cat</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="959156" version="1065353216">The heavily armored, sharp-toothed vine cat can pounce up to eight meters and has been known to tear a sleen apart in less than ten seconds. Its armored frill and hide protect it against larger predators such as the jurgoran, and its claws make it an expert climber when it needs to get away. A patient handler can form a strong bond with their vine cat, training them to perform multiple tasks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="959952" version="1065353216">Raina Temple</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="959952" version="1065353216">Resourceful, cunning, and loyal, Raina Temple strives to be the ideal officer. When her latent Force-sensitivity manifested as a child, her Imperial Agent father sent her to the Chiss Ascendancy to hide from the Sith and suppress her abilities. Temple eventually joined the Chiss Expansionary Defense Force, and later the crew of the infamous Cipher Nine.

When Cipher Nine disappeared during the war with the Eternal Empire, Temple rejoined the Ascendancy and trained Chiss agents in Imperial espionage tactics. At the same time, she used the Ascendancy's resources to track down her former mentor.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="959952" version="1065353216">The Astute Officer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="959952" version="1065353216">After reuniting with Temple, you've reassured her of your love. Your relationship with her is stronger than ever.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="959952" version="1065353216">Unable to rekindle the romance you once had, you decided to end your relationship with Temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="959952" version="1065353216">After working with the Chiss Ascendancy and the Chiss Expansionary Defense Force, Raina Temple has joined your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="959952" version="1065353216">After attempting to rekindle your romance, you decided ultimately to end your relationship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="961589" version="1065353216">Banshee</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="961589" version="1065353216">Banshees, native to the planet Umbara are incredibly agressive and deadly. While expert creature handlers can train Banshees to perform multiple tasks, they should never be left unattended.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="964388" version="1065353216">P3-KP</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="964388" version="1065353216">Often used by the Republic for boarding enemy ships. This unit is programmed with offensive, defensive and medical protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="964388" version="1065353216">The Peacekeeper</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="966043" version="1065353216">Krakjya</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="966043" version="1065353216">Krakjyas are majestic, yet savage feline predators with a strong instinct for self-preservation. A patient handler can form a strong bond with their Krakjyas, training them to perform multiple tasks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="966701" version="1065353216">Andronikos Revel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="966701" version="1065353216">For five notorious years, the pirate Andronikos Revel terrorized Republic and Imperial space alike as the captain of the Sky Princess. Known for his sharp temper and sharper flying skills, Revel was one of the few pirate captains to serve as his own pilot.

His piracy career was cut short by a strange mutiny, however, and he was abandoned to the Imperials who had been hunting him since he'd raided a ship carrying valuable artifacts. After a year in Imperial prison, Andronikos Revel was let loose. He has been meticulously hunting and killing the mutineers who betrayed him ever since.

Likes: Action, keeping promises, complications
Dislikes: Authority, betrayal, backing down from a fight</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="966701" version="1065353216">You chose to leave Andronikos in the brig of the Eternal Fleet ship due to his crimes against the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="966701" version="1065353216">After reuniting with Andronikos and renewing your relationship, things have changed and you no longer care for him in the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="966701" version="1065353216">You have decided that after all this time you still love Andronikos! You have resumed your romance with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="966701" version="1065353216">You have recruited the pirate Andronikos Revel to your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="967239" version="1065353216">Risha</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="967239" version="1065353216">Petty criminal, starship mechanic, woman of mystery, royal queen: all of these terms apply to Risha, daughter of notorious crime lord Nok Drayen. Considering her upbringing as a violent gangster's child, it's a wonder Risha turned out remotely normal. Wise and experienced beyond her years, she has led an adventurous life containing some extremely dark chapters.

Despite her biting sarcasm and general selfishness, one can never shake the feeling that Risha would be a better person if only she knew how. Years spent among the galaxy's dregs have fostered layers of personal self-defense mechanisms and a cynical shell around her. Only the most persistent friend has any hope of meeting the &quot;real&quot; Risha hiding beneath the surface.

Likes: Self-interest, profit, secrets and new tech
Dislikes: Unprofessional or emotional behavior, killing innocents, working with the stupid or uneducated</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="967239" version="1065353216">You have decided that, despite all the time and the political courtship with Merritt Rineld, you have decided you still have feelings for Risha. You have resumed your romance with Risha Drayen.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="967239" version="1065353216">You have decided that, despite your shared romantic history, you would break off your relationship with Risha.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="967239" version="1065353216">Risha tracked you down and attempted to reunite with you. You, however, were uninterested and sent her on her way. You no longer know her exact whereabouts.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="967239" version="1065353216">You have recruited Risha Drayen to your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="967239" version="1065353216">After reuniting with Risha and renewing your relationship, things have changed and you no longer care for her in the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="967240" version="1065353216">Corso Riggs</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="967240" version="1065353216">Corso Riggs is a cheerful, disarmingly optimistic mercenary soldier. Raised as a rancher's son on the rough frontier of Ord Mantell, Corso developed a mixture of naive innocence and primitive toughness, wrapped with old-fashioned chivalry.

In addition to his gung-ho enjoyment of a good, dirty fight and his encyclopedic knowledge of weapons, Corso remains a ray of sunshine in even the worst circumstances. He has no sense of his own mortality and is absolutely convinced he's going to live forever. Corso also has a soft spot for damsels in distress, even when it's clear they're up to no good.

Likes: Protecting the weak, being nice to ladies, punishing bad guys
Dislikes: Hurting for profit, hurting women no matter what they did, working with Sith or Imperials</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="967240" version="1065353216">You have discovered that, despite the years apart, your feelings for Corso are as strong today as they were when you were ripped apart. You have resumed your romance with Corso Riggs.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="967240" version="1065353216">You have decided that, despite your shared romantic history, you would break off your relationship with Corso Riggs.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="967240" version="1065353216">Corso Riggs tracked you down and attempted to reunite with you. You, however, were uninterested and sent him on his way. You no longer know his exact whereabouts.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="967240" version="1065353216">You have recruited Corso Riggs, the optimistic mercenary, to your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="967240" version="1065353216">After reuniting with Corso and renewing your relationship, things have changed and you no longer care for him in the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="967455" version="1065353216">Ashara Zavros</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="967455" version="1065353216">A twenty-year-old Togruta Padawan, Ashara Zavros descends from a long line of Force users. From an early age, she has aspired to study the Force and become one of the best Jedi the order has to offer.

Ashara came to Taris to train under Jedi Masters Ryen and Ocera, whose philosophy is that Padawans best learn the travails of using the Force through firsthand experience of the galaxy. In Ashara's case, the Masters brought her to Taris for two reasons: First, to teach her compassion amidst the destruction that had occurred there and warn against the dangers of pride and the dark side. Second, to complete her trials by helping to drive a dark ghost from the ruins of a Jedi enclave.

Likes: Rational choices, secrets of the Force, fighting bullies
Dislikes: Random cruelty, fighting Jedi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="967455" version="1065353216">You have recruited Ashara Zavros to your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="967455" version="1065353216">After reuniting with Ashara and renewing your relationship, things have changed and you no longer care for her in the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="967455" version="1065353216">You tracked Ashara down on Voss but chose not to invite her to your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="967455" version="1065353216">You have decided that, despite your shared romantic history, you would break off your relationship with Ashara.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="967455" version="1065353216">Years may have passed, but your romance with Ashara is as intense as ever. You once again face the universe with her at your side.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="967493" version="1065353216">D-R3D</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="967493" version="1065353216">These droids were at one time used as part of the Dread Masters' defensive unit. Alliance Forces salvaged and reprogrammed D-R3D with offensive, defensive and medical protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="967493" version="1065353216">The Dreaded Guardian</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="968026" version="1065353216">Vector Hyllus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="968026" version="1065353216">Intelligence Profile:
Name: Vector Hyllus
Gender: Male
Species: Human (enhanced)
Age: 26
Likes: Diplomacy, helping people, exploring alien cultures
Dislikes: Greed, cruelty, prejudice, anti-alien sentiment

Background (Summary): Second-generation Imperial; mother native to Jurio, married Captain Adronik Hyllus after Jurio was granted Imperial governance. Expressed desire to join Diplomatic Service at an early age and displayed appropriate traits. Ranked high academically during training, and soon after graduation was granted (by request) post aboard exploration and first contact vessel (see service record).

Reassigned to Alderaan due to diplomatic manpower needs (see House Thul). Served ably until encounter with Killik species and subsequent &quot;Joiner&quot; transformation. Current status is unclear.

Personality: Vector Hyllus has repeatedly expressed admiration for Imperial accomplishments while indicating a desire to spread Imperial influence through diplomatic channels. His attitudes were likely shaped by the Imperial reconstruction of his homeworld and are appropriate for a Diplomatic Service member. Hyllus is obedient, intelligent, charismatic and effective. He is unlikely to advance further within diplomatic or military hierarchies.

Notes: Personality profile compiled from performance reports from before Hyllus's &quot;Joiner&quot; transformation. Data should be considered non-comprehensive.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="968026" version="1065353216">You have recruited Vector Hyllus to your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="968026" version="1065353216">After reuniting with Vector and renewing your relationship, things have changed and you no longer care for him in the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="968026" version="1065353216">You have decided that, despite your shared romantic history, you would break off your relationship with Vector.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="968026" version="1065353216">Years may have passed, but your romance with Vector is as strong as ever. He stands by your side once again.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="971045" version="1065353216">Mako</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="971045" version="1065353216">At first glance, Mako's relationship with Braden seems more like that of a father and daughter than members of a team of professional bounty hunters--and that assessment wouldn't be too far off the mark. 

Orphaned and homeless but with an uncanny instinct for computing, Mako had been living as a freelance slicer in the shadows of Nar Shaddaa's underbelly... until the day Braden pulled the girl bleeding out of an alley, and paid a street surgeon to patch her blaster burns.

Recognizing talent and trouble when he saw it, Braden took Mako under his wing and has been looking after her as his own ever since. But while Mako loves the old man more than anything, her independent nature is beginning to chafe under Braden's protectiveness.

Likes: Professionalism, bounty hunters, making money, freedom, kindness
Dislikes: Bullying, cruelty, snobs</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="971045" version="1065353216">You have decided that after all this time you still love Mako! You have resumed your romance with her.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="971045" version="1065353216">You have decided that, despite your shared romantic history, you would break off your relationship with Mako.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="971045" version="1065353216">You have recruited Mako to your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="971045" version="1065353216">After reuniting with Maklo and renewing your relationship, things have changed and you no longer care for her in the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="971569" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Felix Iresso</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="971569" version="1065353216">The son of refugees made homeless during the Great War, Lieutenant Felix Iresso has been a career soldier for many years. His file shows participation in several notable battles, including the so-called Eight-Hour Invasion of Dubrillion where Republic forces repelled an Imperial invasion force with minimal reinforcements. Since then, Lieutenant Iresso has earned excellent technical scores and commendations for exemplary service.

However, his file also contains some discrepancies. Lieutenant Iresso has one of the highest transfer rates in the Republic military, serving under almost a dozen commanders across the galaxy in two years. The lieutenant has also been overlooked for promotion several times. The only explanation from his superiors is a reference to an incident on Althir where Lieutenant Iresso was captured by the Empire, but no details are given.

Likes: Republic military, leadership, danger for the greater good, honor and mercy
Dislikes: Breaking the law, cruelty</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="971573" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Felix Iresso</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="971573" version="1065353216">The son of refugees made homeless during the Great War, Lieutenant Felix Iresso has been a career soldier for many years. His file shows participation in several notable battles, including the so-called Eight-Hour Invasion of Dubrillion where Republic forces repelled an Imperial invasion force with minimal reinforcements. Since then, Lieutenant Iresso has earned excellent technical scores and commendations for exemplary service.

However, his file also contains some discrepancies. Lieutenant Iresso has one of the highest transfer rates in the Republic military, serving under almost a dozen commanders across the galaxy in two years. The lieutenant has also been overlooked for promotion several times. The only explanation from his superiors is a reference to an incident on Althir where Lieutenant Iresso was captured by the Empire, but no details are given.

Likes: Republic military, leadership, danger for the greater good, honor and mercy
Dislikes: Breaking the law, cruelty</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="971573" version="1065353216">You have decided that after all this time you still love Felix! You have resumed your romance with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="971573" version="1065353216">You have decided that, despite your shared romantic history, you would break off your relationship with Felix.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="971573" version="1065353216">You have recruited Felix Iresso to your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="971573" version="1065353216">After reuniting with Felix and renewing your relationship, things have changed and you no longer care for him in the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="971731" version="1065353216">H2-WF</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="971731" version="1065353216">Salvaged and serviced by Alliance engineers, this probe droid uses ancient technology from Nathema's original inhabitants.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="971731" version="1065353216">The Hunter-Seeker</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="971761" version="1065353216">Paxton Rall</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="971761" version="1065353216">Paxton thinks of himself and his crew as adventurers seeking glory, fame, wealth, and excitement. Most people would just call them pirates. Whatever they may be labeled as, one thing is certain: they are one of the most capable starship crews in the galaxy, and Paxton one of the finest captains. He's led his crew to every corner of the galaxy taking on any job, but only if it was exciting and the payday was good. His wandering eye has landed on the Alliance as a potential new client worthy of his standards, so Paxton is determined to achieve new heights of fame and fortune by fighting at the Commander's side.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="971761" version="1065353216">The Twi'lek Pirate</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="971761" version="1065353216">You recruited Paxton Rall into your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="972175" version="1065353216">Bolraida</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="972175" version="1065353216">Utterly at odds with the tranquility of their native Alderaan, bolraidas are one of the most aggressive species in the galaxy. However, a fearless handler can form a strong bond with their Bolraida, training them to perform multiple tasks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="972385" version="1065353216">A7 Surveillance Drone</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="972385" version="1065353216">Using blueprints discovered on Iokath, Dr. Oggrurobb was able to adapt this droid for the Alliance. The A7 Surveillance Drone is programmed with offensive, defensive and medical protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="973420" version="1065353216">Jaesa Willsaam</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="973420" version="1065353216">Originally from Alderaan, Jaesa was a former Jedi Padawan who possessed tremendous strength in the Force, including the unique ability to discern a person's true nature and intentions. She was a firm believer in the Jedi Order until she met the Emperor's Wrath, after which the flaws and shortcomings of the Jedi were finally exposed to her. She joined the Emperor's Wrath as their Sith Apprentice and embraced the dark side, travelling the galaxy to carry out the Emperor's will.

After the disappearance of her master and the Eternal Empire's subsequent invasion, Jaesa carried on alone, her power in the dark side growing as her hatred and feelings of abandonment festered.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="973420" version="1065353216">The Corrupted Apprentice</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="973420" version="1065353216">Jaesa has gone too far this time by slaughtering your troops. You put an end to her in battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="973420" version="1065353216">Jaesa must answer for her crimes against your forces. You threw her into your prison for her punishment.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="973420" version="1065353216">You could always use more allies, especially one as powerful as Jaesa. You welcomed her to your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="973420" version="1065353216">All the feelings you had for Jaesa returned the moment you saw her. You resumed your romance with Jaesa.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="973420" version="1065353216">You reunited with Jaesa, but too many things have changed after all these years. You welcomed her to your Alliance but the romance isn't there anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="973420" version="1065353216">You have decided that after all this time you love Jaesa! You have started a romance with her.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="977860" version="1065353216">Darth Malgus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="977860" version="1065353216">Having returned to the galactic stage as part of the Empire's assault on the Jedi colony of Ossus, Darth Malgus has become a topic of widespread debate and investigation once more--particularly his improbable survival after his attempted coup during the battle of Ilum. 

The most popular theory holds that agents of Darth Acina, then-head of the Sphere of Technology, retrieved Malgus and resuscitated him, transforming the cyborg Sith into her own secret enforcer. That she gained control of an agent as deadly as Malgus would explain much about her subsequent rise to the Imperial throne. Some now theorize that Acina may even have used Malgus to eliminate her rivals on the Dark Council during the confusion of the war against Zakuul, though this remains only conjecture.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="977860" version="1065353216">Champion of the Sith</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="977863" version="1065353216">Major Anri</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="977863" version="1065353216">The advancement of non-humans in the ranks of the Sith Empire's military has been slow but steady since the reforms first put forth by Darth Malgus and continued by Darth Marr. It is now estimated that up to eight percent of the Imperial military is staffed by non-humans; among the highest-ranking of these is the Twi'lek ex-slave Anri, who serves as a major in command of a prestigious Special Forces uni: Raven Squad.

Anri views her advancement in the meritocratic terms of the Sith Empire at large; one's power and standing rises as they prove their superiority by overcoming the threats and impediments facing them. Her skillful leadership and gallows humor have made her popular with her fellow troops, and while her outspokenness has led some officers and Sith to question her dedication, her troops know firsthand that her determination to see the Sith Empire triumph over all foes is absolute.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="977863" version="1065353216">Raven Squad Commander</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="977944" version="1065353216">Tau Idair</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="977944" version="1065353216">A seasoned Jedi, Tau Idair spent years engaged in front-line combat against both the Sith Empire and Zakuul. She has a natural aptitude for lightsaber fighting techniques, as well as the mechanics of the weapon itself; her personal lightsaber has seen enough tinkering and modification to rival any hot-rodded swoop or smuggler's freighter.

Tau was recruited to join the Jedi colony on Ossus by Master Gnost-Dural himself; the two of them were among the only survivors of a lengthy campaign fought in the rugged swamps of the planet Mimban. Although he was not her original master, Gnost-Dural has become a close friend and mentor to Tau, and the two of them make a formidable team in even the most dire circumstances.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="977944" version="1065353216">The Jedi Veteran</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="978763" version="1065353216">Doc</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="978763" version="1065353216">The brilliant medtech known simply as &quot;Doc&quot; is driven to bring quality health care to underserved star systems. This has led Doc to keep some unusual company: pathosis-riddled crime lord Fashaka Four-Toes, the Red Band Rebels of Cadinth and even the Imperial military during a brief stint impersonating a member of the Imperial Medical Corps on the conquered planet Sullust.

Doc has a talent for using bad people to save good lives--a fact he emphasizes to anyone within earshot. Some characterize Doc as a blowhard and scoundrel, but these individuals have never required his impressive surgical skills. Doc has visited every major galactic battleground over the past five years and saved more lives than even he can count.

Likes: Looking like a hero, romance and flirtation, helping those in need
Dislikes: Looking bad, hurting the innocent, refusing to help</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="978763" version="1065353216">The Galaxy's Most Brilliant, Skilled, and Handsome Doctor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="978763" version="1065353216">You have recruited Doc to your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="978763" version="1065353216">You've decided that Doc is not a good fit for the Alliance and sent him on his way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="978763" version="1065353216">After reuniting with Doc and renewing your relationship, things have changed and you no longer care for him in the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="978763" version="1065353216">You have decided that after all this time you still love Doc! You have resumed your romance with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="978763" version="1065353216">You have decided that, despite your shared romantic history, you would break off your relationship with Doc.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="978764" version="1065353216">Nadia Grell</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="978764" version="1065353216">A native of distant Sarkhai and daughter of Senator Tobas Grell, Nadia Grell is a newcomer not only to the Republic, but to the entire concept of space exploration. Surrounded by new species and strange cultures, Nadia is eager to experience everything she can. She became interested in the intricacies of galactic diplomacy while traveling alongside her father, and often acted as his assistant during talks.

As she revealed on Attis Station, Nadia is also strong in the Force; unusually strong, in fact. As Force sensitives are relatively unknown on Sarkhai, Nadia's untrained powers left her shunned and feared by her own people. Senator Grell's decision to take her with him when he left Sarkhai was motivated by the hope of finding others like her in the Republic, and perhaps discovering some way for her to control her incredible talents. 

Likes: Learning, helping the weak, charity, mercy, testing her powers
Dislikes: Cruelty, dark Jedi, insulting authority</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="978764" version="1065353216">The Jedi Prodigy</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="978764" version="1065353216">You have recruited Nadia Grell to your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="978764" version="1065353216">You have decided that after all this time you love Nadia! You have started a romance with her.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="978764" version="1065353216">Despite your shared romantic history, you have decided to break off your relationship with Nadia.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="978764" version="1065353216">After reuniting with Nadia and renewing your relationship, things have changed and you no longer care for her in the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="978764" version="1065353216">After watching her in battle, you opted not to recruit Nadia Grell into your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="978764" version="1065353216">You have decided that after all this time you still love Nadia! You have resumed your romance with her.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="0" id2="980870" version="1065353216">Jaesa Willsaam</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="980870" version="1065353216">Once in a millennium, a man or woman is born who expands the frontiers of what Force users can achieve. Proud, young Jedi Padawan Jaesa Willsaam discovered the unprecedented ability to discern any being's true nature and uncover a person's most secret intentions. Born to a family of servants on Alderaan, she was brought to the Jedi Order and trained by Master Nomen Karr.

But Nomen Karr could only protect and shield his Padawan from the world for so long. Through the machinations of Darth Baras, Jaesa was drawn away from the protection of the order and confronted by Baras's own apprentice--and with the emotional instability of her Master.

Having now seen the darkness within the Jedi Order, Jaesa has left its corruption behind completely to help transform the Empire from within. She has searched her whole life for something to believe in, and her new teacher has provided the answer.

Likes: Helping the weak, secrets of the Force, honor
Dislikes: Random cruelty, hurting innocents, rudeness</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="980870" version="1065353216">The Loyal Apprentice</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="980870" version="1065353216">You have recruited Jaesa Willsaam to your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="980870" version="1065353216">After all this time, you've realized that you're on different paths and opted not to recruit Jaesa Willsaam into your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="980870" version="1065353216">You have decided that after all this time you love Jaesa! You have started a romance with her.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="980870" version="1065353216">After reuniting with Jaesa and beginning a new stage of your relationship, things have changed and you no longer care for her in the same way.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
