<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>73</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/lgc/reputation.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Outsider</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Newcomer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Friend</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Hero</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Champion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Legend</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="738432" version="1065353216">You have reached your weekly cap for this Reputation: &lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Reputation</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="738432" version="1065353216">You have gained &lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt; Reputation points with &lt;&lt;2&gt;&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The Gree Enclave</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The Gree are a largely-unknown species of cephalopods whose ancient culture predates the Galactic Republic and the Sith Empire by many centuries. Gree devices and starships are capable of feats that would be impossible with conventional galactic technology, making these unusual beings highly valuable as potential allies.

Increase your standing with the Gree Enclave by completing missions in Ilum's Western Ice Shelf during the &quot;Relics of the Gree&quot; event.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Republic Hyperspace Armada</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The Republic Hyperspace Armada is always on the lookout for deft pilots to play a vital role in their many operations across the galaxy. Established by Admiral Sodoh Reddik, whose sharp tactical abilities won many Republic victories during the Great Hyperspace War, few affiliations bestow a greater honor.

Increase your standing with the Republic Hyperspace Armada by completing daily Heroic Space and Operation New Eclipse Missions from Fleet Command.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Imperial First Mobile Fleet</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="738432" version="1065353216">When enemies can strike at a moment's notice from virtually anywhere in the galaxy, the Imperial First Mobile Fleet must always be prepared to scramble into action. From mercenaries to pirates to Republic forces, there is never a shortage of disturbances to tamp down and adversaries to triumph over in the depths of space.

Increase your standing with the Imperial First Mobile Fleet by completing daily Heroic Space and Operation Ascendant Pride Missions from Fleet Command.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Republic 5th Assault Battalion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The Republic is struggling against the dark forces that are taking over Belsavis' Section X ultra-maximum security prison. What the cultish Dread Guard want from within Section X is unclear, but the 5th Assault Battalion is determined to take back control of the prison while keeping Imperial forces from gaining any ground in the region. 

Increase your standing with the 5th Assault Battalion by completing missions in the &quot;Section X&quot; daily area on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Imperial Guard on Belsavis</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The Empire's most elite non-Force sensitive fighters, the Imperial Guard, have taken position on the prison world Belsavis. Their purpose: to serve the Emperor's will without pause. Their mission: to stop the fanatical Dread Guard from storming the prison compound designated &quot;Section X&quot; while also fending off Republic forces.

Increase your standing with the Imperial Guard on Belsavis by completing missions in &quot;Section X&quot; daily area.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The Voss</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The native people of the recently-discovered planet Voss can be difficult for outsiders to comprehend; their speech can seem reserved and terse, and their use of the Force defies the standards of Jedi and Sith alike. But both the Republic and the Empire have deemed friendship with the Voss a top priority due to a single, inarguable truth: the Mystics of the Voss have visions of the future, and those visions are always correct.

Increase your standing with the Voss by completing heroic missions on the planet Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The Contraband Resale Corporation</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The Hutt Cartel blockade of Makeb exerts formidable control over the importation of goods to the planet's surface. Faced with the vast quantities of embargoed items being confiscated every day, the Cartel formed the Contraband Resale Corporation to catalogue and sell these valuable goods to customers elsewhere in the galaxy, creating a new and highly lucrative revenue stream. 

Increase your standing with the Contraband Resale Corporation by purchasing Contraband Packs from the Cartel Market.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Citizens of Makeb</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The inhabitants of the planet Makeb face overwhelming hardships. Their world has been conquered by outside enemies, their freedom stolen by the very men and women who were supposed to protect them, and their homes and cities ravaged by deadly groundquakes. The Galactic Republic has promised to aid Makeb's citizens in their time of crisis, and your assistance could mean the difference between survival and death for these oppressed people.

Assist the people of Makeb by completing missions in the &quot;Rise of the Hutt Cartel&quot; Digital Expansion.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Makeb Imperial Forces</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The remote planet Makeb holds a secret resource powerful enough to change the course of the entire galactic war: a rare substance known as isotope-5. The Hutt Cartel has initiated a massive operation to seize the planet and harness isotope-5 for themselves, and the Republic is already moving to oppose them. With resources running thin, elite Imperial forces are needed to strike subtly and decisively through the chaos on Makeb and capture isotope-5 for the Empire.

Assist the Empire's forces on Makeb by completing missions in the &quot;Rise of the Hutt Cartel&quot; Digital Expansion.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Galactic Solutions Industries</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="738432" version="1065353216">A fast-rising star in the personal weapons market, Galactic Solutions Industries (GSI) often seeks out high-profile business partners willing to provide resources and research data from the front lines. GSI gladly works with both Republic and Imperial-aligned partners; as their motto glibly states: &quot;We stay neutral, so you don't have to.&quot;

Increase your standing with Galactic Solutions Industries by completing missions provided by GSI terminals across the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Hutt Space Navigators</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="738432" version="1065353216">As the Hutt Cartel has tightened its borders and increased patrols to ensure that all necessary kickbacks and &quot;fees&quot; are being paid by anyone traveling through their space, an elite cadre of starship captains have taken it upon themselves to ensure that passengers and goods can still be carried through Cartel territories without unecessary Hutt entanglements. Known as the Hutt Space Navigators, these  brash smugglers have quickly made a name for themselves in underworld circles--and risen to the top of the Cartel's most wanted list.

Earn reputation with the Hutt Space Navigators by trading in commendations earned from Flashpoints, Warzones, and Daily Missions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="738432" version="1065353216">&quot;&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="738432" version="1065353216">You have reached &lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt; rank with &lt;&lt;2&gt;&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Bounty Brokers Association</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="738432" version="1065353216">For most individuals, the act of placing a bounty can be fraught with legal nightmares and shady contractors. The Bounty Brokers Association was formed to help alleviate such worries. By streamlining and standardizing the bounty contract process, the BBA ensures that prospective clients will receive quality, reliable service without fear of judicial persecution--all for a cut of the action, of course. No other bounty brokerage conglomerate in the galaxy is as trusted as the BBA.

Increase your standing with the Bounty Brokers Association by completing contract missions provided by BBA terminals on the Fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Ordnance Acquisition Corps</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The Adjudicators</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="738432" version="1065353216">In war, having a large military force isn't everything. The soldiers must be armed, and armed well. The Ordnance Acquisition Corps was created under the guidance of Moff Kresk to obtain not simply mass quantities of armaments, but every possible scientific edge against the enemies of the Empire. A large, equipped, technologically advanced military force--that's the difference that could decide the war.

Increase your standing with the Imperial Ordnance Acquisition Corps by completing missions on CZ-198.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="738432" version="1065353216">When crime and corruption threaten to rot the underpinnings of the Republic economy, only the Department of Adjudications has the scope and skill to intervene. Faced with the extraordinary proposition of unraveling Czerka's tangled mess of shady deals, the Republic's Adjudicators hope to legally transfer the corporation's assets before it collapses, taking the galactic economy along with it.

Increase your standing with the Adjudicators by completing missions on CZ-198.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Strike Team Oricon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Ever since the Dread Masters escaped Belsavis prison, Supreme Chancellor Saresh has made locating the powerful rogue Sith lords a top priority. As soon as the Masters' fortress on Oricon was discovered, a special task force designated Strike Team Oricon was formed to handle the threat proactively. An initial orbital bombing failed and resulted in the routing of their fleet. Now Strike Team Oricon has taken to attacking from the ground with what few resources they have left.

Increase your standing with Strike Team Oricon by completing missions on Oricon.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The Dread Executioners</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="738432" version="1065353216">There was a time when the Empire welcomed the Dread Masters' return from imprisonment. Now that the rogue Sith lords intend to turn the entire galaxy to ash, the Empire has no choice but to destroy them. Enter the Dread Executioners. Initiated by Darth Rictus of the Dark Council and led by the dedicated Lord Hargrev, the Executioners are committed to ending the Dread Masters' nihilistic plans once and for all.

Increase your standing with the Dread Executioners by completing missions on Oricon.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="738432" version="1065353216">T.H.O.R.N.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="738432" version="1065353216">While best known as the founder and CEO of Galactic Solutions Industries, Addalar Hyland has also made a name for himself as a philanthropist, using his vast wealth to further the causes he deems most worthy. One such cause is the eradication of the rakghoul plague, for which he has created The Hyland Organization for Rakghoul Neutralization, or THORN. Tasked with searching for a cure to the plague while also stomping out major planetary infestations, THORN regularly accepts talented volunteers, who are affectionately referred to as &quot;Neutralizers&quot;.

Increase your standing with THORN by completing missions provided by Neutralizers and THORN mission terminals located throughout the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="738432" version="1065353216">With the number of fugitives from justice on the rise, the last thing a law enforcement contractor needs is to worry about faulty equipment. The Bounty Supply Company offers quality weaponry, transportation, and adaptive armor for those who want to make some extra credits bounty hunting. The Bounty Supply Company's buyers are always on the hunt for one-of-a-kind deals so they can pass the savings on to you!

Increase your standing with the Bounty Supply Company by purchasing Bounty Packs from the Cartel Market.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Bounty Supply Company</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Imperial Forward Command</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The brainchild of Grand Moff Kilran, Imperial Forward Command concerns itself with focused, high-risk offensive strikes against the Galactic Republic and its allies. With a seldom-seen autonomy, and the bold and decisive leadership of Admiral Zasha Ranken, Imperial Forward Command acts with swiftness and efficiency, making it one of the Empire's deadliest fleets.

Increase your standing with Imperial Forward Command by completing Kuat Drive Yards missions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Republic First Fleet</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The pride of the Republic Navy is its First Fleet. Under the command of Fleet Admiral Bey'wan Aygo, the Republic First Fleet serves as a beacon of hope to civilizations across the galaxy, protecting the Galactic Republic's member worlds and corporate partners from the dark designs of the Sith Empire.

Increase your standing with the Republic First Fleet by completing Kuat Drive Yards missions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Interplanetary Component Exchange</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="738432" version="1065353216">A simple marketplace listing service for starship mechanics and service personnel looking to offer parts for sale, the Interplanetary Component Exchange has become increasingly popular in the criminal underworld, allowing military-grade equipment, weapons, components, and even whole starfighters to be bought and sold without attracting attention from Republic or Imperial enforcement personnel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Binary Star Realty</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="738432" version="1065353216">When the galaxy's most famous and important figures want to buy extravagant new quarters on a prominent world or sell one of their existing luxurious residences, they turn to Binary Star Realty. Binary Star lists only the finest locales, and its team of dedicated agents never stops until they've paired each unique client with that one-of-a-kind living space they can truly call &quot;home.&quot;

Increase your standing with Binary Star Realty by purchasing Stronghold Packs from the Cartel Market.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="328" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Coalition Forces on Yavin 4</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Forces under the command of Sith Lord Darth Marr and Jedi Grand Master Satele Shan have forged a temporary alliance, hoping to finally end the apocalyptic campaign waged by Revan and his fanatical followers, the Revanites.

Foster their cooperation and increase your standing with the Coalition Forces on Yavin 4 by completing daily missions on Yavin 4.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="738432" version="1065353216">People of Rishi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="738432" version="1065353216">From thrill-seeking adventurers and impulsive tourists to its native Rishii and immigrant civilians, Rishi offers a grand experience for many walks of life. But vicious beasts, the tyranny of the Nova Blades, and the machinations of the Order of Revan threaten to squash that experience.

Increase your standing with the People of Rishi by completing repeatable missions on Rishi.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Freebooter's Trade Union</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Those who want the best the galaxy has to offer and aren't concerned about little details like &quot;ownership&quot; and &quot;trade rules&quot; know that the Freebooter's Trade Union can deliver--for the right price. 

Increase your standing with the Freebooter's Trade Union by purchasing Shadow Packs from the Cartel Market.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Esstran Exports</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Specializing in the distribution of fine goods not normally found outside the restrictive Esstran Sector, Esstran Exports leverages its considerable contacts to make its wares available to anybody with the credits to spend.

Increase your standing with Esstran Exports by purchasing Explorer Packs from the Cartel Market.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Republic Forces on Iokath</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Imperial Forces on Iokath</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Imperial forces have arrived on Iokath under the charge of Empress Acina. They have partnered with the Eternal Alliance to battle the Republic for control of advanced Iokath technology.

Increase your standing with the Imperial Forces on Iokath by completing Iokath missions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Republic forces have arrived on Iokath under the charge of Supreme Commander Malcom. They have partnered with the Eternal Alliance to battle the Sith Empire for control of advanced Iokath technology.

Increase your standing with the Republic Forces on Iokath by completing Iokath missions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Underworld Exchange</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="738432" version="1065353216">A simple marketplace listing service for starship mechanics and service personnel looking to offer parts for sale, the Underworld Exchange has become increasingly popular in the criminal underworld, allowing military-grade equipment, weapons, components, and even whole starfighters to be bought and sold without attracting attention from Republic or Imperial enforcement personnel.

Increase your standing with the Underworld Exchange by purchasing Ultimate Cartel Packs from the Cartel Market.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Ossus Colonization Initiative</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="343" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The Jedi and civilians responsible for the colonization of Ossus have been living in seclusion for years--but that peace has been shattered by the arrival of a strike force from the Sith Empire. Without help, their colony is doomed to destruction.

Increase your standing with the members of the Ossus Colonization Initiative by completing repeatable missions on Ossus.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="344" id2="738432" version="1065353216">Ossus Assault Battalion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="345" id2="738432" version="1065353216">The Sith Empire has deployed an elite strike force to the planet Ossus, charged with destroying a Jedi colony hidden on the desolate planet. Success in this mission could mean the difference between victory and defeat in the war to come.

Increase your standing with the Ossus Assault Battalion by completing repeatable missions on Ossus.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
