<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>6</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/support/hoth/shared/bb_group_1_board_1.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111409" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
CRASH SITE READINGS

It's widely known that Hoth's unique combination of electromagnetic fields and gravitational pull are responsible for the tendency of ships to crash into the planet. At GSI, we're looking for ways to replicate the phenomenon.

Our Natural Weapons Division plans to use any readings of the condition of Hoth's wrecked ships and escape pods you provide to reverse engineer the circumstances that cause so many crashes.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111412" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
DATA RECOVERY

A band of White Maw pirates were in possession of sensitive research data belonging to GSI's Superweapons Division when their ship crash-landed on Hoth. As you might expect, we here at GSI are eager to get our data back.

Search the pirates' crash site for any recoverable data. We will be most grateful for your discretion in this matter.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111456" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
IRRADIATED DURASTEEL SAMPLES

Orbital readings suggest that a leak in the Ambria's Fury reactor core has had a unique effect on the wrecked ship, mutating its durasteel into what could be the ideal casing for a new generation of thermonuclear weaponry.

As you will be extracting durasteel samples near the intense radiation of the ship's reactor core, GSI strongly advises the wearing of any protective gear found within. Such gear will not, however, provide protection against any organic cargo still living inside.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111559" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
UNIDENTIFIED SHIP DEBRIS

As they say, you can't swing a vibrosword on Hoth without hitting ship debris... but GSI surveyors believe they have found the mother lode. Lost under ice spires that formed over centuries are the remains of what appear to be ships of unknown origin.

Any remnants of the ships' components could prove quite valuable to our Starfighter Division, thereby making them valuable to your faction as well.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1111705" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
EMBERSTEEL SAMPLES

Volcanic rock is not something the research teams of GSI typically value. However, when metallic ores are melted by lava, subjected to the unique electromagnetic properties of Hoth and then instantly cooled by the planet's frozen surface, the result is anything but typical.

Our researchers are looking to obtain samples of this special &quot;embersteel,&quot; which can only be found near active volcanoes on Hoth, so we may one day supply your faction with state-of-the-art plasma cannons.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112013" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI OPPORTUNITY: VALUED PARTNER INITIATIVE

At Galactic Solutions Industries, we're always looking for ways to grow our partnerships. By accepting and completing multiple GSI assignments, you may qualify for GSI's Valued Partner Initiative. The VPI rewards your hard work with reputation above and beyond what you've earned for each individual commission.

Thank you for your consideration in becoming one of our most valued partners.

Addalar Hyland, founder and CEO
GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
