<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>68</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/dromund_kaas/world/warning_sign/commander_rilan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673797" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always a pleasure to see you, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to see you again, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Things are quiet now--let's keep it that way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello again. Excuse me, but I'm somewhat busy at the moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to see you all survived. The landing beacons appear to be functioning normally again, thanks to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back, my lord. Sensors indicate you rerouted power to all the landing beacons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673807" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did it, sir. According to sensors, all energy fluctuations from the landing beacons have ceased.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems you did your job. We're not reading anymore energy fluctuations from the landing beacons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673811" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis indicates they were deliberately sabotaged to drive the jungle beasts insane. I'm transmitting a full report to Kaas City.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673813" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done the Empire a great service and earned this special recognition. Good day to you all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673814" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please accept this and my deepest gratitude, my lord. I bid you good day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673815" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trust you'll find this payment satisfactory, sir. I apologize if I delayed you. Good day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673816" id2="17" version="1065353216">You earned your wages for this work, but don't think it entitles you to special treatment. Goodbye.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your efforts here are greatly appreciated. Take this reward and my thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673821" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still read energy fluctuations in the jungle, my lord. Some of the landing beacons haven't had their power rerouted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, reports indicate some of the landing beacons have not yet had their power rerouted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sensors indicate the energy fluctuations continue. We need those landing beacons dealt with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, all of you. I'm Commander Rilan. I have an emergency situation here--your timing couldn't be better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673828" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Commander Rilan, my lord. I apologize for my abruptness, but I'm afraid I must request assistance with an emergency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, sir. I'm Commander Rilan. We have an emergency on our hands and could use an extra officer on point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673832" id2="17" version="1065353216">You, there. I'm Commander Rilan. I'm authorized to recruit armed individuals to deal with an emerging threat in this area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673834" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Commander Rilan. I have an emergency situation that requires immediate assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something is stirring up the jungle beasts, which makes the route between here and Kaas City hazardous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Several individuals traveling on foot have disappeared. I've even had reports of jungle beasts attacking speeders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673839" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fail to see how this is my problem, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="673839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deal with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673840" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, the situation is more complex than a few hungry predators. Permit me to explain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dromund Kaas is going to be more exciting than I thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="673842" id2="17" version="1065353216">How delightful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, yes, my lord. As you say. However, this situation cannot be allowed to continue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673845" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send a strike team to put down these predators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="673845" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exterminate the beasts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673846" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've already tried that, sir. The results were... unexpected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bet you Imperials taste pretty good with some gacho sauce.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="673848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe the beasts are hungry?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673849" id2="17" version="1065353216">You alien scum think you're hilarious, don't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch that tone with me, or I'll revoke your authorization to visit this world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="673853" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm trained to handle this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given the circumstances, I believe someone of your abilities is precisely what's needed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="673856" id2="17" version="1065353216">This seems trivial.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673857" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of the speeders that was attacked belonged to an admiral. She escaped serious injury, but the situation demands immediate action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673859" id2="17" version="1065353216">I dispatched two commando teams into the jungle to clear out the beasts, but they never returned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673861" id2="17" version="1065353216">An emergency holomessage came through from one of the team leaders. I'll play it for you....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673863" id2="17" version="1065353216">...Repeat, landing beacons are emitting some kind of energy! Power surges are driving the beasts mad!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't get close enough to reroute power... lost my team... beasts closing in... need reinforce--yaaaah!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sensors confirm unusual energy readings in the jungle. The spaceport's landing beacons appear to be the cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673868" id2="17" version="1065353216">How could landing beacons affect the creatures?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="673868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Landing beacons?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673869" id2="17" version="1065353216">If a beacon's energy signature has been altered, the sonic frequency could be extremely disruptive to a creature's nervous system.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="673871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's deal with this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. A team as skilled as yours is exactly what's needed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673874" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm deeply grateful for your assistance, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, sir. I'm glad you're here to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. Your willingness to serve will be noted in my report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673880" id2="17" version="1065353216">The spaceport's landing beacons are scattered throughout the nearby jungle. You'll need to reroute power on all of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673882" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no mystery here, Commander. Destroy the landing beacons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="673882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get rid of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673883" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't do that. Without proper guidance, approaching starships can easily stray off course and crash into the jungle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673885" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand you're all very busy, but I need people of your skills to reroute power on those landing beacons--and quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673887" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hesitate to ask, my lord, but if you reroute power on those landing beacons, the Empire will be most grateful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673889" id2="17" version="1065353216">I realize I'm asking a great deal of you, sir, but someone needs to reroute power on those landing beacons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673891" id2="17" version="1065353216">You look like someone at home in a jungle, and you're well armed. I need you to reroute power on those landing beacons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673893" id2="17" version="1065353216">I require someone of your particular skills to reroute the power on those landing beacons immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673895" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll track your progress from here. Return when you're done. Good luck--the jungle predators are fierce.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673899" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's an honor to receive you, my lord. Welcome to Dromund Kaas. I am at your service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Dromund Kaas, sir. If there is anything I can do for you, do not hesitate to ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Move along, or I'll have you arrested for loitering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="673902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pardon me, but I'm quite busy at the moment.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
