<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>42</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/bronze/republic/dousing_the_flames/lieutenant_kallum.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234466" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I had a medal, I'd pin it on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234469" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're alive--and you got all the torpedo charges! You saved everyone in the whole sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234471" id2="17" version="1065353216">With people like you on our side, we'll take back Corellia yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234473" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess you hear that sort of thing all the time, huh? Must be nice, being a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234475" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know what to say, sir. Soldiers like you are the reason I signed up.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234477" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you were crazy to even try, but I guess you're some kind of hero and I just didn't see it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to you, we've got a fighting chance in this sector. The Empire's not getting rid of us that easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Put out the fires around the torpedoes, then remove the detonite charges and bring them to me. It's the only way we'll be safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless you're looking to get atomized, you people need to clear out!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Run for it, Master Jedi! If you stay here, you're as good as dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fall back, sir! The whole area's about to be one big crater.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234492" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is no place for civilians! The area could go sky-high any second.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234494" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire torched a munitions factory full of starship torpedoes. When the flames hit them, blam! Everything here says goodbye.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234495" id2="17" version="1065353216">My job is to save every life I can. Someone needs to put out that fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234495" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't let that happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234496" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sent an emergency alert requesting reinforcements, but the Empire is jamming all signals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234498" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic has troops all over this sector. I'd like to keep them alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Including our forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234499" id2="17" version="1065353216">That makes two of us--but the fire's too big.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234501" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy has forces all over this sector. They'd be killing themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234501" id2="17" version="1065353216">That also hurts the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234502" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think the Empire's planning that far ahead anymore--or maybe they just don't care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234504" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got business here, and I hate saying goodbye. Guess I'd better take a personal interest in this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Including me. Hmm....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234505" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want to help, I can't stop you--but this is no campfire you can snuff out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why aren't you running?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234508" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's too late for me. I can barely breathe, much less run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yelling about it won't solve anything. Get a team together and stop the fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go deal with this--now!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234511" id2="17" version="1065353216">My squad went into the munitions plant and tried putting out the fire. We failed. I barely made it out. The others... they're gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234513" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we'd just extinguished the flames and removed the torpedoes' charges, they'd be disarmed. I don't guess you'd want to give that a try....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turning back isn't an option--and I'm not planning to die today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234514" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no other choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Actually, I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234516" id2="17" version="1065353216">But it's practically a suicide mission. You people are either big blasted heroes or crazier than you look. Either way, you're alright by me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even Jedi aren't fireproof. You go in there, you might not come out... but I guess you knew that when you volunteered.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, I can't ask you to... aw, who am I kidding? You're the only hope this place has.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234522" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know who you are, but it doesn't matter. You pull this off, you'll be a hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use my extinguisher to put out the fires, then remove the torpedo detonite charges and bring them here. Good luck!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a chance. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you'd better run while you can--those torpedoes could go any second! I'll stay here and warn everyone else to evacuate....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234531" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's setting fires everywhere! They've lost their blasted minds!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
