<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>52</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/class/jedi_wizard/master_syo_bakarn.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655584" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've landed on Nar Shaddaa? Few on that world will be pleased to see you, I'm afraid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nar Shaddaa is a den of corruption, excess and gang violence. It is ruled by a crime syndicate, the Hutt Cartel, that takes a cut from every black deed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nar Shaddaa must have been a lawful place once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Has it always been like this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655588" id2="17" version="1065353216">At best it was a refugee camp for the Evocii, the original natives, until the Hutts imposed their heavy industry there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surely someone must stand up to this Hutt Cartel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody stops them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655591" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Cartel deals badly with those who say &quot;no.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655593" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should look into this corruption--purely for research, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally, somewhere exciting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many Jedi have thought the same, and either fallen to darkness or run afoul of the Cartel itself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655596" id2="17" version="1065353216">But now, despite its power, the Hutt Cartel is clashing with a new group called the &quot;Guiding Hand.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655598" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Guiding Hand's followers are fanatically loyal to an unknown leader. I believe this leader is Duras Fain, one of the missing Jedi Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there evidence suggesting Master Fain is involved?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do you think so?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655600" id2="17" version="1065353216">What was Master Fain's business on Nar Shaddaa?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why was he here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655601" id2="17" version="1065353216">He went there hoping to quell the worst of the Cartel's activities. Against my advice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blind obedience to a secret leader... if it is Fain, he's got the makings of an army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655603" id2="17" version="1065353216">It sounds like a cult.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655604" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is my fear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fain is an undisciplined maverick, but he has great charisma--incredible skill at influencing others through the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655608" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Guiding Hand has attacked Cartel spice shipments--operations Fain despises--in a way that shouts Fain's tactics. It's him. I know it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655609" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find him, Master. Hopefully he'll be cooperative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655609" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can stop Fain peacefully.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655610" id2="17" version="1065353216">If he is forcing these people to fight the Hutts, he must be stopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655610" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's risking innocent lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fain has flirted with darkness for years--the plague may have finally tipped the balance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ill or not, he is right about opposing the Hutt Cartel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fain's doing the right thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even fighting the Guiding Hand, the Cartel is immensely powerful, second only to the Republic and the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655616" id2="17" version="1065353216">So far the Hutt Cartel has tolerated--even aided---the Republic, but if it discovers a rogue Jedi is hurting business....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655617" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd lose the Cartel's trade routes, information and credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655617" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will turn on the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655618" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts might even strike against the Jedi over this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655618" id2="17" version="1065353216">The order would be blamed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655619" id2="17" version="1065353216">My concern is less for the order than for the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655621" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic can manage without scraps from a gangster's table.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655621" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't need the Hutts!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655622" id2="17" version="1065353216">But what if the Cartel were allied with the Empire instead?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655624" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must find Fain before the Hutt Cartel discovers his involvement. I have a contact on Nar Shaddaa who can help you, named Tharan Cedrax.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tharan is a professor of exo-technology. He was once a friend of mine, and of Fain's.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655627" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not a science I'm familiar with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exo-technology?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tharan specializes in technology thought to originate outside the galaxy itself. Fascinating, and quite over my head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655630" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do I find this &quot;Tharan Cedrax&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655630" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I'll speak to him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655631" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Tharan Cedrax was friends with Fain, he might not be willing to help me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tharan could be loyal to Fain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Being Fain's friend puts him in danger, if the Cartel uncovers the truth about the Guiding Hand. He'll help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tharan has offices on Nar Shaddaa's Promenade. He's usually there... if he's not &quot;nurturing his genius&quot; in a casino.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck. And don't underestimate Duras Fain, Jedi. His gifts of persuasion are unsurpassed.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
