<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>9</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/heroic_weekly/mission_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Feero has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Camp Traken-4 sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Feero may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174847" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent Protarius has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Sobrik sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Agent Protarius may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alay Selray has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gorinth Canyon sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Alay Selray may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Nic'ala has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Sundari Flatlands sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Captain Nic'ala may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176696" id2="17" version="1065353216">Larindaz has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Sundari Flatlands sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Larindaz may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176697" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chedd has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gorinth Canyon sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Chedd may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Galway Bourke has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Gorinth Canyon sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Galway Bourke may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Tenn has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Sundari Flatlands sector of Balmorra. For additional details about the mission, Sergeant Tenn may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Pol Tamso has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Sundari Flatlands sector of Balmorra. The mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
