<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>82</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/trooper/chapter_3/event_2/senator_arnus.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, Major. We appreciate you taking the time to come and respond to our concerns in person. Senator Zian, you may proceed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. As many of you are aware, Havoc Squad is widely considered to be the finest infantry team in the Republic military.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their reputation earns them a great deal of leeway--so much that they have become a danger to the Republic itself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632884" id2="17" version="1065353216">My friends and colleagues--what is it that Havoc Squad actually does, day in and day out? Disturbingly, almost no one knows for sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632885" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Say nothing]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632886" id2="17" version="1065353216">My squad and I put our lives on the line to defend the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632886" id2="17" version="1065353216">We fight the Empire!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632887" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must direct you to reserve any comments until the appropriate time, Major. Please continue, Senator Zian.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632889" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at the previous commander of Havoc Squad. His treason would have been impossible if the squad were more closely supervised.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632891" id2="17" version="1065353216">We all remember the mysterious disappearance of Havoc Squad's previous commander. No doubt a crime was committed and covered up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632893" id2="17" version="1065353216">And that nonsense with the so-called &quot;Gauntlet superweapon.&quot; An astronomically expensive operation to destroy a science project whose danger was never substantially proven!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632895" id2="17" version="1065353216">And it was only after that reckless operation that the Empire attacked us with full force. Why wasn't the Senate consulted beforehand?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632896" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Say nothing]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you really trying to put this entire conflict on our shoulders?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632897" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're blaming the war on us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major, you've already been warned. Do not speak out of turn again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632900" id2="17" version="1065353216">It isn't your turn to speak, Major. Please remain quiet until Senator Zian has completed his statement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632902" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will end with this simple fact: Since the war broke out, Havoc Squad hasn't made a single trip to the front lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632904" id2="17" version="1065353216">If all of the Republic's battles are being won and lost without the help of our best team, then it's time we made changes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Senator Zian. Major, if you'd like to make a response, you may begin now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632907" id2="17" version="1065353216">My team is not a threat to the Republic--but traitors like Zian are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad serves faithfully.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632909" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senator speaks very persuasively, but not truthfully.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zian isn't what he seems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632911" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have evidence here proving that Senator Zian is a paid agent for the Sith Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senator Zian is a lying traitor, and I have proof!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632912" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is all a sham!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here, rock-solid evidence that Zian is taking bribes from Imperial agents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zian is only doing this because the Imps paid him off. I have proof.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ignore this traitor!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632916" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is outrageous! Are we really going to tolerate wild accusations like this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632918" id2="17" version="1065353216">The commander of Havoc Squad deserves more than to be dismissed out of hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632920" id2="17" version="1065353216">Treason is a very serious accusation. I would like to hear more before passing judgment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632922" id2="17" version="1065353216">Preposterous. I called this hearing to present facts, not paranoid delusions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632923" id2="17" version="1065353216">The facts are right here. Give it up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632923" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's over, Zian.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Though it is highly irregular, these are dangerous times. We are in no place to ignore accusations of treason, even among our own body.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632926" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imps paid you to shut us down--that's what this is about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632926" id2="17" version="1065353216">You just want Havoc removed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talk again and you'll regret it, Zian.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough lies!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, let's all remain calm. I see no reason we couldn't delay these proceedings momentarily to evaluate this new evidence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guards--seal the area and allow no one to leave until we are prepared to reconvene.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632932" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senator Zian. In light of this evidence, I must order that you be detained by the Senate Guard pending charges for high treason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632934" id2="17" version="1065353216">But, this is insane! I'm no traitor! Whatever you've seen, it must be a forgery--some kind of military conspiracy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please accept our apologies, Major. I hope you understand that you were called here with the best of intentions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632937" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a duty to ensure that we're acting in the Republic's best interest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632938" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right. And rest assured that your tireless efforts in the Republic's defense are greatly appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632940" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you'll excuse me, then, I need to return to duty immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632940" id2="17" version="1065353216">May I go now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632941" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. I see no further issues for discussion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632943" id2="17" version="1065353216">You didn't take the Imps' money, but you still did what they wanted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632943" id2="17" version="1065353216">Save it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632944" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people of the Republic entrust you with their defense. We have a responsibility to supervise your actions on their behalf.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632946" id2="17" version="1065353216">Further discussion is unnecessary. Let's get on with other business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632948" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given the change in circumstances brought about by new evidence, I hereby adjourn this meeting immediately. Major, you're dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632950" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to know what Havoc Squad does? We kill traitors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me show you. [Kill Zian]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632951" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wh--what are you doing? No, no, you can't. You can't!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632953" id2="17" version="1065353216">He... he's dead. He's dead! You've killed him!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632954" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zian was working for the enemy. Here's the proof.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632954" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've executed a traitor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632955" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't debate the enemy in the field, and I won't do it here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killing is my job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zian was a traitor--this proves it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632958" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you shot him? What's wrong with you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Were you working with him? Did the Imps pay you like they paid Zian?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632960" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a problem with it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632961" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? What are you talking about? Have you lost your mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632963" id2="17" version="1065353216">By what right have you done this, Major? By what right have you killed an unarmed man in the capitol of the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632964" id2="17" version="1065353216">I took an oath to destroy the enemies of the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632964" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was doing my duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632965" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, on the battlefield. This is not a battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killing the enemy somewhere else is fine, but here, it's a problem?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is this different?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632968" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a place of democracy, of lawful procedures--not bloodshed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632970" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave us, Major. Go back to the war where you belong--we have a lot to discuss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632971" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did what needed to be done. I'm leaving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632971" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get in my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632972" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? You can't just leave--you've killed a Republic Senator in cold blood! Guards!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold your posts, men. Enough damage has been done here today.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
