<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>56</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/bronze/imperial/pirated_lock_box/captain_switts.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196693" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've made Hoth more secure for the Empire. May our enemies tremble!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196696" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're back! I'm sure the scum quotient has been drastically reduced. Bet those pathetic pirates never knew what hit them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196697" id2="17" version="1065353216">They died like dogs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196698" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least they can serve entertainment purposes. The important thing is the stolen orders. Thanks to you, we'll know the Republic's plans and movements now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196700" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was tougher than expected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196701" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. Maybe I've been underestimating the opposition here. The important thing is the stolen orders. Thanks to you, they've been secured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just take the Republic orders and be grateful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough bravado.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry if I offended you, my lord. The important thing is the stolen orders. Thanks to you, we'll know the Republic's plans and movements now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, sir. The important thing is the stolen orders. Thanks to you, we'll know the Republic's plans and movements now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196708" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't mean to step on your toes, bounty hunter. The important thing is the stolen orders. Thanks to you, they've been secured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196710" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a great day for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196712" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be here to receive the stolen Republic orders you relieve from those idiotic pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196715" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, now here comes somebody with some real mettle. Nothing but lowlifes and opportunistic scum on this ice cube.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196717" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on the trail of something big. High-level Republic orders up for grabs. Could use some high-powered help to bring them home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196718" id2="17" version="1065353216">My attention is valuable, Imperial. Better be worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196718" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time is money.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196719" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a discretionary fund, if that's what you mean. Shouldn't rely on the enlisted for something this important.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196721" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on the trail of something big. High-level Republic orders up for grabs. Sith involvement would be much appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see if you can capture my ambition and rage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speak, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196723" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've attracted my attention, Captain. I hope for your sake you can keep it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196723" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196724" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, my lord. I hope you'll agree this is too important to rely on my grunts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196726" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on the trail of something big. High-level Republic orders up for grabs. Would appreciate your collaboration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep talking, Captain. You haven't lost my attention yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196727" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm intrigued.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right. Pretty confident you'll agree--this isn't something we should leave to my grunts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196730" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on the trail of something big. High-level Republic orders up for grabs. Could use someone like you to bring them home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196731" id2="17" version="1065353216">By &quot;someone like me,&quot; you better mean a &quot;lethal killing machine.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196731" id2="17" version="1065353216">That better be a compliment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196732" id2="17" version="1065353216">To be sure. This is too big to trust to my grunts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196734" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the big deal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196735" id2="17" version="1065353216">Word from Intel is they lay out the enemy's movements, allocations and plans on Hoth. The advantage we would get is considerable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196737" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it too much for you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, it's a big opportunity--don't want to trust it to my grunts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196740" id2="17" version="1065353216">Idiot Republic flew a shuttle too low, even the yahoo pirates couldn't miss. Shot it down, pilfered a lock box with the military orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Luckily, pirates can't open the box. Republic shuttle crew has pieces of the cylinder key in their belts. Hoping you can salvage the key then secure the box's contents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196743" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get the orders. And I'll decimate any pirates who get in my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing will stop me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like the Republic crew is already dead. Too bad--I'll have to destroy extra pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196744" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll kill many along the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196745" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like how you think, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196747" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it, but I better be paid well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196747" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll pay me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196748" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire is generous when pleased with the results.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196750" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic orders will go a long way toward defeating our enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196750" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knew I could count on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makes sense to hit the crash site and salvage the key, then invade the pirate camp for the box.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196755" id2="17" version="1065353216">No promises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, alright. If the mood strikes, you can hit the crash site to salvage the keys, then invade the pirate camp for the lock box.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196758" id2="17" version="1065353216">Feel free to waste as many pirate scum as you like along the way. I'll be here waiting to relay the Republic orders to High Command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="196760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not interested. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph. Fine. Change your mind, come see me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="196763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our enemies on this planet are pathetic. I predict absolute victory here.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
