<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>43</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_15/scene_06_lana_brig.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182626" id2="17" version="1065353216">There you are. I'd like you to meet the ship's cargo, en route to the Eternal Throne.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admiral Zasha Ranken, one of the few experienced officers to survive Zakuul's conquest. You may recall her from your time on Kuat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182630" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a great pleasure to see you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zasha Ranken, decorated Imperial admiral. One of the few experienced officers to survive Zakuul's conquest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182633" id2="17" version="1065353216">A pleasure to meet you--your reputation precedes you, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tai Cordan, former President of Balmorra. Now with the Galactic Senate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182639" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe you already know Tai Cordan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Barsen'thor. It's been a long time since Balmorra. I'm with the Galactic Senate now. Glad to see you alive and kicking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182650" id2="17" version="1065353216">And finally, Malita Tal. She was a popular holo-performer back home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182652" id2="17" version="1065353216">She became one of the first to loudly question Arcann's rule. It was either go into exile or be killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182654" id2="17" version="1065353216">A pleasure and an honor. You inspire me. You inspire us all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182657" id2="17" version="1065353216">What makes these three so important to Arcann?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1182657" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are they headed for Zakuul?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182658" id2="17" version="1065353216">You, in essence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182660" id2="17" version="1065353216">We knew of your Alliance. For each of us, it made sense to join, but we didn't know how to reach you. In searching, we found each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182664" id2="17" version="1065353216">We all knew influential people whose ears we could bend. Loyalties we could ensure. So we started an alliance of our own, inspired by yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182666" id2="17" version="1065353216">It wasn't long before we were found out and captured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182694" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't see that happening, Commander. But I do want you to try. I want you to try with all your might.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1185865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Having better luck than with the blast doors. Almost like the captain's distracted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1185867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry. We'll have you out of there in no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1185867" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be safe soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1185870" id2="17" version="1065353216">There isn't a doubt in my mind. But we aren't simply helpless prisoners in need of rescue. Everyone here is eager to join your cause!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1185881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arcann assumes we're affiliated with you. He wants to &quot;interview&quot; us--to discover where you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1185882" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could use more allies. You'll all be welcome in the Alliance, assuming you're still interested.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1185882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Join us, all of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1185883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you kidding? Sign me up. Literally--if there's anything I have to sign, let me know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1185885" id2="17" version="1065353216">We aren't as formal as all that, Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1185889" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hear that? Everyone either wants to be like me or kill me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1185889" id2="17" version="1065353216">It really is all about me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1185890" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can certainly attest to that in this particular moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1185892" id2="17" version="1065353216">The GEMINI captain sent out a message. Arcann's on his way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1185892" id2="17" version="1065353216">He already knows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1185893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well. That will make this rescue more difficult.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1185895" id2="17" version="1065353216">And... you're free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1185897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh. That was meant to take you at least four minutes longer. I hope my calibrations haven't been affected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1185902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay here until we secure the bridge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193117" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rest are their bodyguards and associates, captured alongside them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195968" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're in the middle of a mission! I can't be playing nursemaid for a bunch of prisoners!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1195968" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have time for this!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195969" id2="17" version="1065353216">These people have suffered because they dared to stand against Arcann. These are exactly the kind of allies we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1210898" id2="17" version="1065353216">We aren't as formal as all that, Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1210901" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can certainly attest to that in this particular moment.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
