<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>16</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/uprisings/tat/dust/transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216281" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got a problem. The Dust Viper gang ambushed one of our Alliance patrols--and made off with Odessen security data. Now they're selling it to the highest bidder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216282" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dust Vipers' raiding days are over. Good news for us--and for the Outer Rim.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216285" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can shut down those vicious scum bags, but you'll need to hit them hard. And fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216287" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stomp into the Dust Vipers' den, and take down their leader, Bel Nerodia. Then recover our data. Can't forget that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, we can't forget the best news of all: you stopped our data from falling into enemy hands. The Alliance base is safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216291" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that's what I call a victory. The underworld's already buzzing with stories about how you wiped the Dust Vipers off the map.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216293" id2="17" version="1065353216">And with our data secure, the Alliance doesn't have to worry about another attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216297" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did some real good today. Now kick back and celebrate. You've earned it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216300" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're stronger than ever. And if anyone forgets that, we'll break 'em in half--just like the Dust Vipers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216305" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, well, well. The beast master Jai Quallo finally bites the dust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216307" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I were you, I'd use his transponder to get the local wildlife on your side. But that's just me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216311" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a nasty character near your location. Goes by the name Rakesh the Foul.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216316" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's a dangerous criminal, wanted in every sector. The Dust Vipers locked him up after he tried to chew off their leader's hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216318" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take down Rakesh and you'll be doing the galaxy a favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216430" id2="17" version="1065353216">So much for Rakesh. Can't say I'll miss the old scumbag.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1216447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bel Nerodia can't run far. Secure that Alliance data, then you can cut off the Vipers' head.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
