<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>40</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/daily_area/ziost/world_arc/shared/multi/transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149455" id2="17" version="1065353216">It started with just a few soldiers, this whole thing. Quietly acting as one, no hesitation. It's unsettling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149456" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know Agent Shan doesn't like to place his people in harm's way. What's happened to the Sixth Line--it must be eating him up inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149458" id2="17" version="1065353216">Minister Beniko has been a smart boss. Capable. This has to be pushing her to her limits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149481" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd hate to be one of them. No control, helpless. Guess I should thank my implants.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149561" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vitiate's pawns have control of the perimeter defenses. They're shooting anything that moves, bombarding civilian centers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149563" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to cut the defenses' power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Saresh has her forces all over New Adasta. Some of them are possessed now. Made a real mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149814" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you talking about her now, or you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's keep on target. Doesn't matter how bad things get. We have to put an end to Vitiate's plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149816" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Lana. Agent Kovach may have been hurt, possibly worse. I haven't heard from him, and his tracker's off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149817" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should know Theron Shan is here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thought you'd like to know--Theron's alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149819" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I'm aware.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149821" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last I heard from Agent Kovach, he had a plan involving the city's electrical grid. I'll steer you to where he might have gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, I've placed the dampeners on manual. I'll be controlling them while you alter the makeup of the grid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once it's all set, we'll put a shock into every living thing in New Adasta. Then we'll figure out what's next.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149825" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's one down. I've got you covered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally heard from Agent Kovach. He says you're working together on a solution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149828" id2="17" version="1065353216">More and more of our forces have fallen to Vitiate. It's spreading beyond the city now, along with the war. There must be an end to this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me. My attention is needed elsewhere. Everywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149831" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, the other one. The other one!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry. Master Surro took down a squad trying to evac slaves. Then turned on the slaves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Running triage on the survivors. I just wanted to, uh.... Just--good luck, okay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you don't want to hear this. I have to say it, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149838" id2="17" version="1065353216">I respect Lana Beniko--sincerely. But the Empire enslaves and slaughters innocent people every day, and I respect common decency more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron's a good man. It matters that he placed his trust in me. But I work for the Republic. That's the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, that's enough. Any more and it's the dampeners that will take the brunt of the surge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1149863" id2="17" version="1065353216">All that's left is to disable the system failsafe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150175" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before we go ahead with this, you and I should talk--in person. I'll see you shortly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron's alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150285" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey. That was... awkward. Not as bad as my previous chat with her, believe it or not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150287" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, my team--my Jedi--more than anyone here, they're my responsibility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, I know killing Jedi is kind of a thing for you, but the Sixth Line.... It's because of me they're here in the first place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150289" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, I know saving the lives of Jedi isn't high on your priority list. The Sixth Line, though--they're here because of me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150291" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you could find some way--any way at all--just... please, help them. Don't do the other thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150592" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got some unexpected power loss going on here. I know you're a little busy, but there's no way I can get there and back in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150593" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just ended a holocall with Darth Marr. He would like very much to speak with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, managed to get through to Saresh. Couldn't get her to budge on the withdrawal idea, but maybe you can sway her. She wants to talk to you anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150599" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm supposed to tell you Saresh wants to talk to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1150688" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you understand.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
