<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>45</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/bronze/imperial/unintended_consequences/major_charkron.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289480" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Reclamation Service has much more work to do on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289482" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Wraith Box is reassembled, and it activated on its own. Whether it'll work again, I can't say.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289483" id2="17" version="1065353216">I registered the power surge from here. You experienced an alien device of rejuvenation and rebirth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289485" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll take it back to Dromund Kaas to study--but you may have seen it function for the last time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289487" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Wraith Box is yours, if you're able.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289488" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;In the final years of the reign of Ajunta Pall, five Dark Lords explored the machine--the Wraith Box.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289490" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;One burned in purple flame, another vanished from sight. Two brothers slew each other--and only one Sith returned to Korriban.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289492" id2="17" version="1065353216">From the chronicles. Major Gart Charkron, Imperial Reclamation Service--it's an honor, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289493" id2="17" version="1065353216">From the chronicles. Major Gart Charkron, Imperial Reclamation Service. Your arrival is fortunate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289494" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're Reclamation Service archaeologists, you're not here for the Republic. You're on Belsavis to study the Rakata.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289494" id2="17" version="1065353216">We may have similar interests.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289495" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right, my lord--there are strange things locked below this prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289497" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are Reclamation Service archaeologists doing on Belsavis?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me your purpose here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289498" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you don't know this planet's secrets, I'm not authorized to explain; suffice to say, there are antiquities under the prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289500" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't recognize the quotes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289501" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Chronicles of Lord Skaysh, one of the more obscure translations. I've found it inspiring as we explore Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spare me the nonsense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289504" id2="17" version="1065353216">My team excavated a tunnel, and an alien device of unknown purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289506" id2="17" version="1065353216">We call it the &quot;Wraith Box,&quot; after the device from the Ajunta Pall legend. It disintegrated three of my men, but the tunnel carvings suggest it grants great power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your men have done enough. I will seize the Wraith Box.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Its power belongs to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then adjust your mission. You're going to help me claim your Wraith Box.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289508" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want that device, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289509" id2="17" version="1065353216">So your job is to get it working for the military.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Useful for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our job is research and recovery; I'd be glad to work with Intelligence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289512" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mystical alien devices aren't really my thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289512" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like superstition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289513" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing mystical about it. Just technology we haven't mastered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289515" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do we know about it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289516" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not sure--it radiates on a different wavelength every six seconds, and reacts to organic contact. It's at least ten thousand years old.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your men had it coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289519" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe the device is incomplete--when the breakout started, the prisoners went scrounging for salvage. They had no idea what they had.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289521" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the pieces can be recovered and the Wraith Box restored, the Reclamation Service would be proud to see it in the hands of a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289522" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have the firepower to recover the parts, but I'm willing to make a deal: reassemble and reactivate the Wraith Box, and its power is yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289525" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;And so the mighty descended into darkness, to seek the secrets long forgotten.&quot; Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't you want it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289527" id2="17" version="1065353216">The tunnel carvings also suggest only the strongest in body and spirit will be rewarded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even the Sith in the Wraith Box legend didn't all survive. But millennia later, we still remember them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not interested. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289532" id2="17" version="1065353216">I respect your decision. I wish you well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289534" id2="17" version="1065353216">This planet is more than a prison. It is a legend. Be wary.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
