<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>64</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/class/jedi_knight/general_var_suthra.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518645" id2="17" version="1065353216">General, I'm on Alderaan. Have you heard from Master Orgus?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518648" id2="17" version="1065353216">No--and I'm uncomfortable discussing this in the presence of a known enemy operative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518650" id2="17" version="1065353216">I left the Empire when I was ten. The only thing I &quot;operated&quot; was a refresher.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518652" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care what Master Satele says. This mission is too important for someone with Kira's history to be involved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518653" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trust Kira with my life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518653" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's loyal, I guarantee it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518654" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're all here for the same reason, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518656" id2="17" version="1065353216">I answer to the Jedi Council, not you. Kira stays until they say otherwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518656" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't make that call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518657" id2="17" version="1065353216">No matter what you may think, I'm here to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518659" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just watch your back. Alderaan's dangerous enough. Whole planet's a war zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518661" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand, General. That's why she'll be staying here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518661" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's absolutely right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine by me. From what I hear, the spaceport's the safest place to be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518664" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's right. Alderaan's a war zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Negative. Considering the chaos there, it's a wonder any messages get through. Alderaan's a war zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518668" id2="17" version="1065353216">The nobles are fighting to decide who's in charge--and whether this world aligns with the Republic or the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your weapons project is to secure Alderaan for the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518669" id2="17" version="1065353216">That explains our presence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518670" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought Alderaan was already a Republic world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alderaan is neutral?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518671" id2="17" version="1065353216">When we signed the Treaty of Coruscant, hard-liners on Alderaan formally withdrew from the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, some nobles took the opportunity to ally with the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518675" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could crush any Imperial-aligned factions if we committed troops here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518675" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should invade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518676" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senate wants a diplomatic solution. I don't think there is one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518678" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people developed the Death Mark weapon to end this conflict with surgical precision.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518680" id2="17" version="1065353216">Extraordinary device. It marks targets with a microscopic tag. Undetectable. Tracks targets anywhere on the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518682" id2="17" version="1065353216">Feed the target's coordinates to a focused-beam laser, and it can kill them from across a continent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518683" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since when is the Republic in the assassination business?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518683" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's murder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518684" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I can save a billion lives by killing one man, I'll gladly pull the trigger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518686" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've tested this Death Mark weapon on a live target?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does this actually work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518687" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only in a laboratory environment--but the results were astonishing. Flawless accuracy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518689" id2="17" version="1065353216">A weapon like that could take out enemy leaders without risking troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518690" id2="17" version="1065353216">Generals, tacticians, Sith Lords... eliminate them, and the enemy collapses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518692" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Death Mark has one regrettable disadvantage. The targeting device's range is extremely limited. Twenty meters or so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once a target is marked, however, the laser can hit it from any range.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518696" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fear efforts to guard the weapon have failed. Master Orgus's last transmission came from Organa Palace. After that... nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518697" id2="17" version="1065353216">Considering what happened to Master Kiwiiks, it's a sure bet Orgus is in danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518697" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to find him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope he's only been captured. I'm ready to move--what's the plan, General?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518698" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to find him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518699" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could someone in the palace have betrayed Master Orgus?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518699" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you suspect the Organas?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518700" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Organa is the Republic's strongest ally. Something's happened, but not on their end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Elderly people have problems with technology. Maybe he just can't figure out the holo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518702" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's an old, confused man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518703" id2="17" version="1065353216">He does hate using them... but he should've reported in by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518705" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count Alde was the last to see Master Orgus. He co-funds the Death Mark project with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518707" id2="17" version="1065353216">I tried informing the count of your arrival, but communications there have been crippled.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518709" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reports indicate multiple holorelays destroyed. Standard Imperial battle tactic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518711" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Organa can't spare the troops to get their holorelays online. Maybe you can help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518712" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll restore communications and then meet Count Alde.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518712" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me where they are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finding Master Orgus and the Death Mark are my top priorities, but I'll do what I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518713" id2="17" version="1065353216">No promises, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518714" id2="17" version="1065353216">Transmitting holorelay coordinates. If you get them up and running, it'll tighten House Organa's defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518716" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a Jedi, not a repair tech.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="518716" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518717" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood. We'll make do with what we have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="518719" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find Count Alde at the embassy near Organa Palace. Good luck--Var Suthra out.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
