<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>35</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/bronze/imperial/the_brig_stompers/sergeant_kavsun.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="537838" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt we'll be hearing from the Brig Stompers anytime soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="537841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't hold back on the Brig Stompers.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="537842" id2="17" version="1065353216">You armed? If not, I suggest you head to Requisitions immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="537844" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hoth must be a magnet for the galaxy's scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="537847" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our scouts just spotted enemy hostiles massing in a nearby ice field. Head count puts them at a two-to-one advantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742724" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's a Brig Stomper?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742725" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Brig Stompers are alien mercenaries, ex-military. Gained notoriety when they wiped out Gaftikar's entire planetary defense force during a coup.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742727" id2="17" version="1065353216">We knew they were operating out of Hoth. Just didn't realize they were fixing to turn this outpost into their new headquarters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742731" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got to love mercs.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742744" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're organized, disciplined and outfitted with state-of-the-art weaponry.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742747" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it's a fight you're spoiling for, look no further.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742748" id2="17" version="1065353216">However, they're also vulnerable. Doubt they'd expect an attack. We can strike now and stop this invasion before it starts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742758" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll attack the Brig Stompers.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742759" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have nothing but contempt for any soldier who'd discard loyalty and patriotism for a few credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742762" id2="17" version="1065353216">These aren't your typical pirate trash, either. These are Brig Stompers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wipe them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742840" id2="17" version="1065353216">With our forces divided between the Hailstorm Brotherhood and the Republic, the Brig Stompers couldn't have picked a worse time to strike.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742841" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're scared of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Call it caution. The Brig Stompers have a reputation for being the most professional, stone cold mercs in the trade.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742849" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Brig Stompers have a history. Wouldn't be the first military installation they've overrun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742851" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll never take this base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a chance. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742884" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then if you'll excuse me, I need to prepare our defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thing I'm here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742914" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there was another paramilitary group as good as the Brig Stompers, I'd be hiring them right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742916" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't know they're hostile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="742917" id2="17" version="1065353216">What will that involve?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742918" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our scouts have spotted several storage caches where the Brig Stompers keep their weapons, ammunition and medical supplies.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742920" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroying the supply caches and thinning the Brig Stompers' numbers ought to put a dent in their plans. Gives us a fighting chance, at least.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742922" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our scouts witnessed the carnage. Said you did quite a number on those Brig Stompers.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742924" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're still tallying the damage, but it looks like you officially wrecked their operation. They'd be crazy to attack us now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="742926" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think we'll be in the clear. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="743088" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not scared of anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="743092" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope this is worth my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="743093" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assure you, the threat is real.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
