<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>63</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/companion_characters/multi/republic/c2n2/c2n2.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477108" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back, master. Your vessel is in flawless condition, naturally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477109" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am functioning at peak efficiency, master--all the better to serve you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477110" id2="17" version="1065353216">I took the liberty of dusting your quarters, master. Your respiratory health is one of my top priorities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477111" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be pleased to know I remain the most advanced steward droid in the galaxy. If that ever changes, I shall recommend a replacement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477112" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you eat properly while away from the ship, master. Perhaps I should create non-perishable meals to send with you....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477113" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome home, master. I hope you find your vessel a model of efficiency, convenience and comfort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, I have reprogrammed your vessel's food processor to reduce the crew's caloric intake. Some of them were growing a bit thick....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477115" id2="17" version="1065353216">Providing you with the highest level of service is my greatest pleasure, master--and I am not just programmed to say that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every time I see you return from a mission, I thank the Maker I wasn't designed for combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, I've marked the best escape pod for your sole use. I, of course, will go down with the ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477118" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, you'll be pleased to know I added extra padding to all the seat cushions aboard this vessel. I hope you find them comfortable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477119" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back, master. If you detect the aroma of Alderaanian nectar, I programmed the air circulators to simulate it. Enjoy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477120" id2="17" version="1065353216">My new master, at last. I am Seetoo Enntoo, steward of this vessel. It is my extreme good fortune to serve you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always happy to have another droid. My Teeseven unit has been invaluable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477121" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's nice to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477122" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Teesevens are a fine utility model. I am programmed to provide for your &quot;creature comforts.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477124" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see you're programmed for protocol.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477124" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're too kind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477125" id2="17" version="1065353216">Diplomacy is merely my subfunction. As a Jedi, you bear considerable responsibility. I will relieve you of lesser burdens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477127" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would General Garza saddle me with some overblown protocol droid? You're not even armor-plated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477127" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expected a combat unit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477128" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every soldier requires proper logistics to function. I provide the highest support level available.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477130" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were bought by a thieving, gutless son of a kath hound--but this is my ship. You take orders from me, got it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477130" id2="17" version="1065353216">You work for me, not Skavak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477131" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am programmed to serve this vessel's captain, not my purchaser. I will happily accept your every command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477133" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to have you aboard. Tell me your functions, Seetoo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477133" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pleased to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477134" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fetch a vibromop, droid. I want this ship to sparkle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477134" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477135" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, master--custodial duties are only one of many vital functions I possess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477137" id2="17" version="1065353216">C2-series droids represent the latest advances in everything from starship technical maintenance to nutritional advice tailored for your specific organic needs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome aboard this Corellian Defender-class Light Corvette. It was custom-built to offer a Jedi both first-rate combat performance and meditation amenities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477141" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome aboard your Corellian XS Light Freighter: a marvel of customization. I can only speculate why such large engines were mounted to its hull.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477143" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome aboard the Rendili Hyperworks BT-7 Thunderclap: a rapid assault craft designed especially for Republic Special Forces at enormous taxpayer expense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Along with the usual accommodations, you'll find a secure captain's locker for storing valuables.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477147" id2="17" version="1065353216">The equipment enhancement station provides resources to improve the efficiency and comfort of your personal accessories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your bridge contains an ever-updating map of the galaxy. It's quite beautiful to look at.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477151" id2="17" version="1065353216">Long-range communications are available via the holoterminal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477153" id2="17" version="1065353216">Priority alerts from the Republic network are accessible at the HoloNet console.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477155" id2="17" version="1065353216">And finally, the ship's intercom will inform your crew that you wish to meet. Do you have any questions, master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you're good at everything. Does that include combat?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you fight?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477157" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I think of anything, I'll let you know. Thanks for the tour, Seetoo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477157" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477158" id2="17" version="1065353216">My pleasure, master. I do have a few final notes....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477160" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been too long since I was aboard. I'd almost forgotten all that stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477160" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nope--thanks for the review.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477161" id2="17" version="1065353216">My duty is to ensure you need never concern yourself with such matters, master. Which brings up one final point....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prep the ship for flight. We're leaving shortly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prepare for takeoff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477164" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ship is fueled and ready, master. There are just a few final points we should review first....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477166" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you can see, I am not equipped for physical danger. My function is to maintain this starship as your home away from home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477168" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am happy to assist you with any non-hazardous task, of course. I pride myself on the utmost attention to detail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477169" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you consider a &quot;non-hazardous&quot; task?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me an example.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477170" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am programmed to modify other technology. I can also perform long-range surveillance and diplomacy. I'm quite useful, I assure you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477172" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won't be safe here. Leave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477173" id2="17" version="1065353216">On the contrary, master--this ship is quite sturdy. I have also discovered several excellent hiding spots in the event of a hostile boarding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477175" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm... add a little armor, some combat protocols and a blaster, and you just might be worth something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477175" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could equip you for combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, please... Any non-factory modification will void my warranty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whenever you are ready to depart, consult the galaxy map on the bridge. The ship's computers will handle the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477180" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh... and you may wish to investigate the cargo compartment. The items within it arrived before I did.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
