<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>13</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/ilum/xalek/shaft_12_entrance.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182213" id2="17" version="1065353216">[You find the entrance to Shaft 12 collapsed, just like the entrance to Shaft 16]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182215" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Given the other bodies in the area, it seems unlikely that Anna would have survived even if she did make it out of the shaft in time]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182216" id2="17" version="1065353216">(Force Sensitive Background) Through your connection to the Force, you sense powerful emotional traces left behind by the attacker....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182217" id2="17" version="1065353216">(Demolitions Training) It is clear to your trained eye that this shaft's collapse is not natural. However, it is also clear that the shaft was not collapsed by an explosive force.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182219" id2="17" version="1065353216">(Force Sensitive Background) Seething hatred... but also great sadness, regret, and a profound sense of loss.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182221" id2="17" version="1065353216">(Force Sensitive Background) These are not the emotions of random violence. There is a very specific reason for these attacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182223" id2="17" version="1065353216">[You recall finding a datapad at Shaft 16. Perhaps there is another clue around the Shaft 12 camp?]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182224" id2="17" version="1065353216">(Force Sensitive Background) Perhaps a more thorough investigation of the Shaft 12 and Shaft 16 camps could yield some clues as to the motive?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182226" id2="17" version="1065353216">(Demolitions Training) The lack of a debris pattern suggests the shaft was pulled in upon itself with an implosive force, but you cannot spot any of the telltale signs of grav charges.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182227" id2="17" version="1065353216">[You found a datapad here at Shaft 12. Perhaps there was another clue around the Shaft 16 camp that was missed?]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182229" id2="17" version="1065353216">(Demolitions Training) Was this crushed using the power of the Force? If so, the individual you are chasing may be quite powerful.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182232" id2="17" version="1065353216">[You should complete your investigation of the two sites, and then report your findings to the Mining Foreman]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182241" id2="17" version="1065353216">[You should report your findings to the Mining Foreman]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
