<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>41</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/voss/class/jedi_knight/master_satele_shan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602340" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're in orbit around Voss, Master Satele.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602341" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be wary when you reach the surface. Voss is a strange world under the absolute control of a group of powerful Force users called the Mystics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602343" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Mystics reject the idea that the Force has both a light and dark side. They claim to follow a &quot;neutral&quot; path, both in their politics and the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Despite their claims, I fear the Mystics have more in common with the Sith than us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you saying the Voss are servants of the dark side?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602348" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602349" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Mystics use the visions given to them by the Force to control the lives of ordinary citizens. Like the Sith, they use their power to dominate others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602351" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll deal with the Mystics the same way I deal with the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602351" id2="17" version="1065353216">They don't scare me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602352" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Mystics are prophets who shape the direction of Voss society. The Emperor wants to wipe out all life in the galaxy. Hardly the same thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602354" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dark side is subtle and insidious--as you well know. The Emperor did not begin his conquest of the galaxy by declaring his true intentions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602355" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever the Emperor is up to, I'll stop him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602355" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me my mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602356" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be careful while I'm down there, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for the warning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602357" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi must be ever vigilant. But the Mystics are not your primary concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just because the Mystics don't follow the Jedi Code doesn't make them evil.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602359" id2="17" version="1065353216">They don't sound that bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602360" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let the views of your companion corrupt what the order has taught you. A Jedi does not compromise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602362" id2="17" version="1065353216">In any case, the Mystics are not your primary concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602364" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've haven't uncovered the Emperor's plan to destroy Voss yet. But he recently dispatched a Sith Lord named Fulminiss to this system.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602366" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Fulminiss created the Harrowers you faced in the Emperor's fortress--be wary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me his location and I'll take care of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602367" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find a way to stop him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602368" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Harrowers were twisted beings of pure evil.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602368" id2="17" version="1065353216">He made those abominations?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602369" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dark side has the power to corrupt life itself. Fulminiss is a master at manipulating evolution to create unimagined horrors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602371" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care what kind of creatures he surrounds himself with--when I find him, he's dead!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602371" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Harrowers won't save him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your bloodlust is unsettling. You must try to control your emotions, especially when working with the former Emperor's Wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602374" id2="17" version="1065353216">We know Fulminiss is somewhere on Voss. He's communicating with the Emperor through an encrypted communications relay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602376" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've detected several signal scramblers outside the planet's capital city of Voss-Ka. Disable them and we can track the comm signal to his location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602377" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602378" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fulminiss wouldn't just leave those scramblers undefended.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602378" id2="17" version="1065353216">This could be a trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602379" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm too valuable to be sent on a simple sabotage mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602379" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is beneath me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602380" id2="17" version="1065353216">The signal scramblers were hidden deep inside the savage Voss wilderness. Reaching them will be dangerous, even for a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602382" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you act quickly, you should be able to disable all the scramblers before Fulminiss knows what's happening--then we can find him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602384" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
