<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>12</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/yavin_4/world/altars_of_history/lieutenant_sabri.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140746" id2="17" version="1065353216">When this is over, we'll make an accounting of what's here. I promise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140748" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wanted these relics preserved. Consider it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. I'm glad someone in the Republic doesn't need our whole history purged.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. I was the only one of my unit cleared to operate here... I was afraid the Republic would see our history purged.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Believe me, we're not forgetting the Empire any time soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dark Lord! These will be studied and go to your vaults, I swear. The Reclamation Service will not fail you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140757" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is all the Revanites' fault. A thousand years of history treated like a battleground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140760" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Reclamation Service. You don't have anyone I can talk to? Someone who'll protect these ruins?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry. The Republic doesn't have &quot;combat archaeologists.&quot; Maybe because our history doesn't want to kill us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140764" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe because your army values &quot;guts&quot; above &quot;education.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140766" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm begging you--if you won't hold your fire around the temple, at least remove any artifacts for preservation. I can't do this alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140769" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every shot we fire turns the past here to dust.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
