<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>14</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_2/taking_on_toborro/secret_entrance.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your hidden entrance appears to be unguarded, doctor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. Toborro doesn't even know it exists. He has no eye for such exquisite detail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019453" id2="17" version="1065353216">He is also despairingly predictable, and almost certainly ranting away in his throne room while clutching the fuel rods to his bosom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019455" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am transmitting procedures to defeat the security protocols separating you from Toborro. Follow them precisely. I'll be unable to reach you via holo after this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019456" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can take things from here. You've been most helpful. The Republic will remember your cooperation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1019456" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate your aid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps your Supreme Chancellor will reward me with my own private laboratory. The planet Tisheraan would be perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019459" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if we need more information from you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1019459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why can't we keep talking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019460" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you use my instructions, you won't. The palace employs transmission dampers to prevent unauthorized transmissions. You will be on your own, I'm afraid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gosh, that's a real shame. I'll miss our little talks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1019462" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was tired of you anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019463" id2="17" version="1065353216">As will I.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019465" id2="17" version="1065353216">A last word of advice: Toborro asked for some rather unorthodox droid designs. It's possible he actually built a few. If so... good luck with them.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
