<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>110</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/jedi_knight/captain_maddox.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022980" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bothawui needs help. The Protectors are here to deliver.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1023001" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got good timing, Captain. I've just finished securing the Bosnar Dam.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1023006" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and your men chose to fight. These civilians came to us for protection, and I won't force them into harm's way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1023007" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want anyone who can hold a blaster front and center. Have the rest run supplies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1023007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone fights, no exception.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1023008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not only are the civilians staying put, but some of these men are going to guard them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1023008" id2="17" version="1065353216">We keep the civilians safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1023011" id2="17" version="1065353216">You heard the Jedi. Move!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1023752" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold the line! Protect the civilians!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1023758" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi's mine! Kill the rest!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1023761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aim for the Imperials! Stay out of the Jedi's way!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1023770" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did we get the only sociopath in the order? More death is not the answer!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1023774" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get moving. Sounds like that scout doesn't have much time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1025135" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry about us. You just get to that dam.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039781" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we live through this, I'll be the first to shake your hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039783" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got Imperials marching on us from all directions. Not Blight's men. Scouts are reporting a Sith Lord at rear guard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Were you able to get past the dam? Just send me coordinates, and I'll move out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1039784" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be right there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did the scouts get a good look at this Sith Lord? Can they confirm his identity?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1039785" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think it's Legius?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039786" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this is a direct attack from the Imperial military, our troops have to respond.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1039786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we get backup?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039787" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're camped at a village in the flooded plains, on the way to Camp Sovereign. Been taking in refugees, thought we'd be safe out here....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Down, behind the supplies! Garith, get your men out here--</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1039791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Protectors = in trouble // Jedi + T7 = must hurry!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039792" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like the Empire showed up early. They're always doing that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039793" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not going to get a lot of downtime while we're here, am I?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039794" id2="17" version="1065353216">Estimated travel time to Ferla is fifteen minutes. Ready when you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039795" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith Lord's heralds have arrived. We should not delay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040397" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. But I sure hope there aren't two Sith Lords gunning for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just started their final push into Imp territory. If they couldn't spare anyone before, they definitely can't now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reassurance: Many have tried to delete the Protectors, master, but none have succeeded. Yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040408" id2="17" version="1065353216">How rude! Holocall etiquette should really be part of basic training.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044422" id2="17" version="1065353216">She sure knew how to make an entrance. What a mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044424" id2="17" version="1065353216">The civilians fought bravely, for not having a choice about it. Make sure these bodies are gone before the rest come back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044426" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take a pile of rubble over the alternative. Those civilians wouldn't have lasted ten seconds against a Sith Lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044428" id2="17" version="1065353216">From what the Sith said, you've done this countless times. Against your own Masters, even... it must have been difficult.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044429" id2="17" version="1065353216">I made a promise to serve the Republic, the same as you. We face what we have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044429" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a Jedi's duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Served three tours before the treaty. Never thought to thank a Jedi until now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044431" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi's life should be dedicated to peace. Mine's been nothing but war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044431" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sometimes, it gets tiring.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe one of us will live to see the end. At my age, I'd bet it's you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044440" id2="17" version="1065353216">They betrayed me to serve the Emperor. I'm only sorry they went so quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044440" id2="17" version="1065353216">They got what they deserved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044441" id2="17" version="1065353216">In my day, Jedi were pacifists. Guess war does change everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heard from our boys at the Bosnar Dam. They say there's a new river where an Imperial outpost used to be. Nice work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heard from our boys at the Bosnar Dam. That water carved out a whole new river. Too bad we flooded out the Imps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044449" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our injured here will make it. No damage to our supplies or your shuttles. We want to hit Camp Sovereign, now's our chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044451" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the best battering ram we've got. If you carve out room for us to land, we'll have that work camp evacuated in minutes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044452" id2="17" version="1065353216">We just killed a Sith Lord's apprentice. He may try to strike back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch out for Legius.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044453" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll keep both eyes open. But you've got to keep yours forward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044455" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we know anything about Camp Sovereign's defenses?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044455" id2="17" version="1065353216">What can we expect?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044456" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could use a squad of angry resistance fighters at my back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Garith should help me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044457" id2="17" version="1065353216">So could we, while you're gone. They'll be coming in with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044461" id2="17" version="1065353216">Garith sent some scouts to see what you're up against. They were supposed to rendezvous with Doctor Kantos--ah, must be her now....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044463" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir. The scouts are back--one of them, anyway. Says the rest died in the field.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044467" id2="17" version="1065353216">The one who lived... he's badly injured. Doctor Kantos thinks we might lose him, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me your location, and I'll get there as soon as I can. Try to keep him comfortable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044468" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd better hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Comfortable? We passed &quot;comfortable&quot; six blood transfusions ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044471" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't interrogate a dying man. Whatever's waiting in Camp Sovereign, I'll face it alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let him rest, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, no. This man risked his life to bring you information, and you're going to hear it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044474" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll pay for this, Garith. I'll take ten of Blight's men for every Bothan we've lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blasted Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send them the coordinates. Then quit fiddling with the comm and help me keep this man alive!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't wait up for us. When you've got what you need, hit Camp Sovereign. We'll be ready when you call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Report, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044480" id2="17" version="1065353216">All civilians accounted for, but resistance scouts report one more squad on the way. It's not over yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will be when they get here. Half my men are dead or dying. The civs can't stand on the sideline anymore--we need them armed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1044483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Civilians = not combat trained // Jedi + T7 = combat veterans!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044485" id2="17" version="1065353216">First you'd let a village get bombed. Now you want to give guns to small children?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044487" id2="17" version="1065353216">So they can die, too? I think you're missing the point, here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me thirty seconds to teach aiming and ten for reloading. They'll be ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044491" id2="17" version="1065353216">We fight for our own survival. Why shouldn't they?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perplexity: My master and I are already armed. What more is required?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044495" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, it seems highly unlikely the civilians have permits for heavy weaponry....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. They'll get front-row seats to this massacre.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044501" id2="17" version="1065353216">More Imperials are on the way. We need volunteers to fight with Garith's men.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let the people choose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044502" id2="17" version="1065353216">The more people step forward, the more of us survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044509" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is your champion. The one you trust with your lives, and those of every trembling parasite you rescue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044511" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi who murdered Tarnis, Sadic, Nefarid and Angral. Who attacked his own Masters for siding with the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044512" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were threats to the Republic. They had to be stopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044512" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had no choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044513" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you call us barbaric.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044515" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seem to know a lot about me, Sith. I can't say the same of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044518" id2="17" version="1065353216">I also killed the Emperor. But I'm sure no one's mentioned that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044518" id2="17" version="1065353216">And that's not all....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mention it again, and I'll cut out your tongue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044521" id2="17" version="1065353216">My master swore the Republic would burn for lying about the Emperor's fate. You opposed him on Talravin. Did you think he forgot?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044528" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Emperor's alive, where is he? Why hasn't he spoken? It's the Dark Council who's lying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044528" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor truly is dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Angral swore the Republic would burn. I defeated him, and I'll defeat Legius, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your master won't win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056721" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone's in position, but you've got to get these Seekers online!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056722" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was the civilians' choice to fight. No soldier could have done better. Make sure their families know that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056724" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Lord Votari. Apprentice to Darth Legius, the Hammer of Chommell and Praetor to the Army of the Dark Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Silence!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056733" id2="17" version="1065353216">If my master falls, he'll take all of you with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know how many Sith Lords threaten the Republic every day? I lost count back on Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1058882" id2="17" version="1065353216">I forgot him pretty fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058883" id2="17" version="1065353216">My master is no ordinary Sith. He stands for the Empire--and I stand for him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069290" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi who murdered Tarnis, Sadic, Nefarid and Angral. Who attacked her own Masters for siding with the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1098198" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get as many civs inside as you can. The rest, take cover!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
