<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>132</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/jedi_knight/garith.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any enemy of the Empire is a friend of mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like you two made it. And you're Garith, I'm guessing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022960" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've taken everything from us, and we're the ones who have to take something back. Our planet, our fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022961" id2="17" version="1065353216">This village is someone's home. I won't sacrifice it to your bloodlust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1022961" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll sit, and that's final.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe those turrets can do more damage. Tefani, see what you can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1022962" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll support your fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022963" id2="17" version="1065353216">One turret-powered energy shield, coming right up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure, Master Jedi? Most of these houses won't survive a bombardment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Head on out, and you'll run straight into the walkers. We'll hold position as long as we can. Go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022968" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know where the walkers are. Make it slow and painful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022971" id2="17" version="1065353216">Garith and his men fought bravely to protect us. Whatever you've lost, I promise we'll rebuild.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022973" id2="17" version="1065353216">My children grew up in that house. We hid there from the Empire. And now I hear he could have saved it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022975" id2="17" version="1065353216">As long as the Blight holds that dam, Bothawui will never be free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037820" id2="17" version="1065353216">That shield was the only thing keeping our buildings intact. Not enough to kill us, I guess--the Imps have to take our homes, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tefani is the Protectors' chief engineer. He might know how to repair your shield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tefani, any suggestions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Single-story shacks? A few market stalls? I don't see anything here worth saving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037825" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're just crummy buildings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037826" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wouldn't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037828" id2="17" version="1065353216">But your engineer said he could do something about our energy shield. We're all here, so spit it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037830" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? Oh, sorry. Still rattled from that landing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037832" id2="17" version="1065353216">I saw you had some turrets back there. Inside are all the parts I need to get that shield back online.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those turrets are the only weapons we have. You scrap them to build a shield, what are me and my men supposed to do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037835" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can handle the walkers on my own. I won't need backup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me take care of the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037836" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tefani's found a way to save Vel'lik. Shouldn't you be happy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Problem, Garith?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Saving Vel'lik isn't the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroying their weapons? Is this really the best you can do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037839" id2="17" version="1065353216">It does sound like a bad plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best I can do with this headache, yeah.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1037842" id2="17" version="1065353216">If homes destroyed // Then civilians = refugees</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sense a lot of anger in you. You probably shouldn't be armed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037846" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not thinking straight, pal. You shouldn't be operating heavy machinery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037848" id2="17" version="1065353216">I advise against the Protector's plan, Master Jedi. We need every advantage we can get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037850" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Bothan is thick with rage. He will fight to the death, if you allow it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interjection: Already these newcomers show signs of treachery, master. See how the engineer tries to sabotage your assault!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037854" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am not a combat model, master, but surely additional firepower couldn't hurt?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037856" id2="17" version="1065353216">You shouldn't be fighting the walkers anyway. You should take shelter with the civilians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037858" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been under Imperial rule for over a decade. Do you know how many villages they've ruined? How many lives?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037860" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't approve, but I won't stop you. We'll find new homes for these people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037860" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wash my hands of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037863" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what New Uphrades is for, I guess. I'll see where I can help with the civs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounded plenty clear to me. Turrets are that way. Get to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038282" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think they would have stopped at your house? We had to show the Imps what happens when they cross us!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038283" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was my decision to leave your homes unprotected. And I'd do it again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1038283" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blame me, not him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038284" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone want to argue with a Jedi? I didn't think so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038286" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your hatred for the Empire sounds more... personal, than most.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1038286" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why so angry, Garith?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038287" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I'd known it would cause this much damage, I wouldn't have allowed it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1038287" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a disaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could have, would have, should have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038291" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did maintenance on that shield for years. Never would have thought of turrets as spare parts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038293" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, it was nothing. Some jumper cables here, a few stripped bolts there....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038295" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to talk genius, look at this one. Took down a bunch of walkers without breaking a sweat!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038296" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's our duty to protect you from the Empire. And we don't plan to stop here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1038296" id2="17" version="1065353216">No applause necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038297" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd never know this village was under attack. Looks good as new.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1038297" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't sell yourself short.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038298" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, go on. That good, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038300" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we'd left it up to your leader here, the whole village would be rubble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1038300" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your boss almost killed you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038301" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the Imperials would know never to come close to Vel'lik again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038303" id2="17" version="1065353216">They think that's the worst the Empire can do. But this village--Vel'lik--it's been lucky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038305" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic said you Protectors are here to help civilians. Well, most of us are either in Camp Sovereign, or know someone who is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038307" id2="17" version="1065353216">...casualty report, Liah'starn region. Incendiary devices continue to produce outstanding results. Ninety-five percent civilian loss in surrounding villages....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038309" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meet &quot;the Blight.&quot; Imperial &quot;efficiency&quot; expert. Here to kill as many as he can before the Empire jumps ship. Those walkers were his.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038311" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand the fight for victory, but our troops can't ignore this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1038311" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where's the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038312" id2="17" version="1065353216">When it comes to Imperials, I'm a bit of an efficiency expert myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1038312" id2="17" version="1065353216">He doesn't scare me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blight's men control everything from here to Camp Sovereign, including the Bosnar Dam. Huge hydroelectric facility, provides power for half the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hauled off to Camp Sovereign, all the way in Liah'starn. By the time your troops get there, the Imps will have cleaned house.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038319" id2="17" version="1065353216">It doesn't matter where this camp is. I can tear through the Imperials like jelly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1038319" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't need troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038409" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume that's not his real name. Unless he's secretly a Sith Lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1038409" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Blight, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ever since the Imps came, we've been prisoners on our own world. They tell us where to go, what to do, how to think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038426" id2="17" version="1065353216">You disobey, you get punished. Or your family gets punished. Locked up in work camps where no one comes out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1038433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imps opened the dam once years ago. Flooded an entire valley. Now we need to move through the area--and what do you think Blight's men'll do if they see?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better let them get to it. All of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040865" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's because it is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040866" id2="17" version="1065353216">And your family?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040868" id2="17" version="1065353216">The camp wasn't part of our briefing. Is it still in operation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1040868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Camp Sovereign?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since the treaty. Imps will keep it running until the end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then that's our mission. If you can get us behind enemy lines, we can free Camp Sovereign.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040874" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not that easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040875" id2="17" version="1065353216">An Imperial army's marching on your command center. Some nutjob colonel's about to plow a small village. Which one do you pick?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel Berlo Harlight. We all think Blight suits him better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040877" id2="17" version="1065353216">My kind of Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1040880" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 + Jedi = should hurry // T7 = cannot swim</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Capturing a Dam 101, right? Master Kiwiiks made that a tough one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040884" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm gonna get wet, aren't I?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040886" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll need coordinates. And emergency oxygen tanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040888" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Blight is worth half his rank, he'll have anticipated this. We should be cautious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suggestion: Perhaps we could assume the name &quot;Blight&quot; after his men are destroyed. It has a certain resonance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040892" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew waterproofing the crew's footwear would come in handy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040898" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is it? You said you had a Jedi army!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, so you'd stop yelling at us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1040902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I hope you're ready to fight. Civilians are safe underground, but the walkers already took out our energy shield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044910" id2="17" version="1065353216">That much I can see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cleaned house... you mean they'll kill all the prisoners?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1044912" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't sound good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Minute they see Republic flags. It's happened everywhere else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044936" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have to get through the vanguard outside first. Once you're in, head for the dam control room. Whatever happens, don't let it blow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045444" id2="17" version="1065353216">With due respect, sending walkers against this place seems... excessive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1045444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are the Imps even here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045445" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not just Vel'lik. These walkers have been hitting villages all over; they avoid military outposts, so they're no one's priority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056705" id2="17" version="1065353216">The sick prisoners will make it. We'll hold out as long as we have to. Now go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056706" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you doing out here? Find the override so we can fire these things!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056707" id2="17" version="1065353216">A lot of those scouts were veteran fighters. Blight and his men will pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056708" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Sith Lord... these Protectors must be pretty important, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056709" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith's moving too fast! Shoot around her!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still catching my breath. Maddox can fill you in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056711" id2="17" version="1065353216">You heard the captain. Don't give 'em a centimeter!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056713" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll get packing and head out while you've got them busy. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058889" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless we get control of the dam, half of Bothawui will be in the dark and underwater.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1058889" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see the problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we have to pass the dam? Isn't there another way we can reach Camp Sovereign?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1058890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we go around?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing that wouldn't take months. We're lucky if these prisoners have a week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058893" id2="17" version="1065353216">A little water never hurt anybody. And anything destroyed by the dam can be rebuilt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1058893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Big deal, another flood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058894" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not talking &quot;a little water.&quot; We're talking a tidal wave of epic proportions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we need Blight's men out, plain and simple. More your department than ours, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1098199" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're going to blast their way inside. Defensive positions, everyone!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1098200" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're trying the other side now! Regroup over there and keep firing!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1098459" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imps'll never stop coming unless we plug that hole. Do something, Jedi!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
