<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>59</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/jedi_knight/seeker_controls.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1024289" id2="17" version="1065353216">Override engaged. You can fire the Seekers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1024290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever you're gonna do, do it quick. There's an awful lot of movement outside these gates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1024293" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is your choice, Garith. If your men are willing to stand guard here, I won't stop you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1024293" id2="17" version="1065353216">Garith's call, not mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1024298" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll get the prisoners to safety and update the Supreme Chancellor. Meet you back on your ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most are healthy, though they could use a solid meal. It's the prisoners who've been here longest I'm worried about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once we get them out of here, they'll receive the best medical care in the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052048" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to worry now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052049" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't help overhearing--Garith's loved ones were among the first dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Including Garith's family.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052050" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does this disease affect other species? We don't want to start another outbreak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052050" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have we been infected?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052051" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're safe, Master Jedi. The disease only affects Bothans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunker down? We're in the middle of Imperial territory. You've got to get out before they send reinforcements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052056" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a brave gesture, Garith, but are you sure you've thought it through?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052056" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure about this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052057" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have to fight alone. The Protectors can make it back without me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052057" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can stay with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052058" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is suicide. You and your men wouldn't last five minutes on your own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052058" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be slaughtered!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052059" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give us a little credit. We brought down that Imp bomb squadron, didn't we?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056348" id2="17" version="1065353216">But Jastra was so strong. And Irys and Mak... they were just children.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056349" id2="17" version="1065353216">That disease is brutal. They went quick, if it helps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056351" id2="17" version="1065353216">How are we coming, Audra?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056354" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've contracted Torolis fever. The Imperials provided no treatment whatsoever--hundreds died in the first outbreak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056355" id2="17" version="1065353216">Poor man. We're in time to save the rest, I hope?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056357" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've done what I can, but it'll be days before they're well enough to move. We'll have to hunker down here until then.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1056364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Protectors = take sick anyway // Doctor Kantos = help prisoners survive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056366" id2="17" version="1065353216">We couldn't just bring the sick ones and hope for the best?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056368" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are we sure the sick can't be moved? I've kept people alive in worse conditions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056370" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victory is unlikely. We should evacuate everyone now, including the sick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056372" id2="17" version="1065353216">A foolish gesture. Load the sick prisoners onto the shuttles and be done with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056374" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recommendation: I suggest evacuating everyone now, master. If the sick do not survive, nature has run its course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056376" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a dreadful place, master. Surely the sick prisoners would rather leave now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056378" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Empire wants Camp Sovereign back, make them fight for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056378" id2="17" version="1065353216">The resistance can stay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056393" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care if these people are foaming at the mouth. We're taking all of them with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Load the sick prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, let me stay. We'll hide in the command center. I just need a few days....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Skies are clear, Master Jedi. Come out and join the party.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058899" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know it's been a long fight. But we have to protect these people until they're well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1058899" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can handle them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058900" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it was just us, I'd agree. But we've got hundreds of healthy prisoners to worry about, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every Imperial in Camp Sovereign is dead. What makes you think they'll send more?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1058902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reinforcements?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058903" id2="17" version="1065353216">You overwhelmed their forces here, but the Empire will raze this place before they call it lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058905" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't risk everyone's lives for a few sick Bothans who might end up dying anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1058905" id2="17" version="1065353216">Garith's right on this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058906" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you two suggesting? That we just leave the sick ones here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get the rest of the prisoners on your shuttles. My men and I will stay and guard the sick until they can be moved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058909" id2="17" version="1065353216">And what if another Sith Lord shows up? Or there's a crisis somewhere else on Bothawui? We can't waste you here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058910" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it means these people get back to their families... yeah, I'm sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say we evacuated the sick prisoners now. What are their chances?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058913" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's already touch and go for most. Now you want them to stand up, board a shuttle, and get jounced around for hours?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058915" id2="17" version="1065353216">These people will make it. That's a promise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058916" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm staying. Anyone who wants to leave had better go now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058918" id2="17" version="1065353216">Defensive positions, then. We'll hold out here until Doctor Kantos says otherwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1058920" id2="17" version="1065353216">The decision's been made, Audra. Get the sick on board and do what you can for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1069306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shouldn't be more than a day or two. I'll find my own way back to your ship. Good luck.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
