<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>59</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/jedi_knight/ship_holoterminal.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1034291" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose he's not here for his charm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1034301" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got Imperial walkers about to hit this village and no defenses to stop them. Send a lot of men with guns!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1034302" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold out as long as you can. My crew and I will head for the surface immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1034302" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just stay calm....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1034303" id2="17" version="1065353216">They must have run out of targets. Or this village is really a secret Republic base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1034303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Walkers? Seriously?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1034304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like this is my fight. You can stay here and... roll bandages, or something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1034304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thing I'm here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1034305" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't our first op, you know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1034317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Retaking a planet shouldn't mean destroying it. Has the fighting been that bad?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1034317" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1034318" id2="17" version="1065353216">For years, it seemed we were fighting a losing battle. I'm glad that's changed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1034318" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally, a victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1034325" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you should take over. I have a feeling you're better than Doc at a lot of things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1034325" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Is that so?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1034326" id2="17" version="1065353216">We all know basic first aid. I only keep Doc around for entertainment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1034326" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's an idiot, it's true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1034327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doc's been with me since Balmorra. He's a little unorthodox, but I trust his judgment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1034327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doc does fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1034333" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't be serious. Master Jedi, no decent medical facility would let him through the door.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1034335" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're trying to make me jealous, boy, it is not working.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1034339" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I'm surprisingly with Doc.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1034343" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course I am. But so are trained apes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, I'm irresistible. It's only natural you want to be around me. But this is too much!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037343" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's going on?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037344" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm your chief medic. Me. Not her. She's been nosing around the medbay, touching my stuff....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037346" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll remember that the next time you lose a toe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037347" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you think you can do better, Audra, you can examine me whenever you want.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1037347" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Is that so?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037348" id2="17" version="1065353216">I may hold you to that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037350" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, people, listen up. I've got the numbers on Bothawui, and they're... big. Bigger than anything we've done before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037356" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's not leaving quietly. If they can't take it with them, they're getting rid of it--and that includes the Bothan people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037360" id2="17" version="1065353216">...and get those barricades in position! Whoever you are, get off this channel! We've got an emergency down here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Maddox, of the Protectors. We're trained to respond to emergency situations. Tell us how we can help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that a joke? Is the Jedi laughing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037366" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be fast. Hey! Don't waste that kolto--that's all we have....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1037368" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll need you before they need us. We'll get supplies and personnel together and follow you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039547" id2="17" version="1065353216">This world could feed half the Republic. Billions live here, and the Supreme Chancellor's trusting us with their lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039549" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought the Imps got Bothawui in the treaty. We're not here to free the whole planet, are we?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039554" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic soldiers just get in my way. I can handle anything the Empire throws at us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1039554" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't need help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039555" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm counting on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039556" id2="17" version="1065353216">The more time we waste here, the worse things will get. Where do we start?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1039556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then let's get moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039557" id2="17" version="1065353216">Protection of civilians should be the military's top priority, no matter who has the upper hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1039557" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our troops should be helping.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legius is the one who threatened your work. Has there been any sign of him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1039562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any Sith presence?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a flash. We'll just have to keep our eyes open.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039565" id2="17" version="1065353216">And our weapons armed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039567" id2="17" version="1065353216">The resistance will be our guide. They control a village outside Imperial territory where we can set up base. I'll contact them now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Garith, get your civilians under cover and do not engage. We'll be there as soon as we can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why shouldn't I be down there? You clearly need adult supervision.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Burned fields, flooded villages, slavers and death camps... Command sent holo-images, but you're better off without.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039764" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our troops have a war to fight. Local resistance is overwhelmed. It's our job to pick up the slack and keep the Bothans safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victory must come first, or there will be none to protect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1039767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Official strategy is to hit high-priority targets first. Not our decision, anyhow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our military's already got the Imps on the run. We're here to make sure they end up with more than a burned-out husk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1044871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just wish the price wasn't so dear.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
