<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>23</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/jedi_knight/vellik_transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094097" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reactivating the energy shield now. Keep those walkers away, and Vel'lik should come out fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094098" id2="17" version="1065353216">Garith and his men are in position. Powering on the turrets, and then I'm taking cover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094099" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some free advice? That baby's triple-thick durasteel. Gonna take something with a little punch to bring her down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094100" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very creative. Now go for the guts!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094103" id2="17" version="1065353216">The walker is designed to resist melee attacks, master. Please, try something else--for both our sakes!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quick, master! Kill it before it gets up again!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094106" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observation: The walker is hardened against conventional deletion, master. A new technique may be required.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Target compromised. Move in for the kill, master!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094108" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fought these things on Balmorra. Blasters aren't gonna cut it--need something big, loud and explosive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094109" id2="17" version="1065353216">Took fifty of us to do that on Balmorra. Get in close and finish it off!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094110" id2="17" version="1065353216">That armor looks too thick for lightsabers. Any missile launchers lying around out here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094111" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice moves, Master Jedi. Lightsabers ought to work now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094112" id2="17" version="1065353216">Plasma and ion cells ineffective, sir. Recommend heavy ordnance... if we can find any.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094113" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy is vulnerable. Engage and destroy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lightsabers will not pierce this flesh. We must bring the walker down by other means.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094115" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now is your chance, Jedi. Strike while the walker is down!</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1094116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Walker plating = 75% durasteel + 15% cortosis // Conventional weapons = ineffective</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1094117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Walker = disabled // Jedi + T7 = charge!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094364" id2="17" version="1065353216">That'll wake a fella up. Energy shield's holding, but I'd look to those walkers if I were you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094365" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever you're gonna do, Master Jedi, do it faster. Vel'lik's getting hammered!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1096673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another village saved by the fearsome Jedi and his plucky engineer!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1097036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seriously, great job. Captain Maddox and the rest of the gang's landing now. Meet you back in Vel'lik.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1097037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another village saved by the fearsome Jedi and her plucky engineer!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
