<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>110</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally, real civilization. Come on, I'll show you the sights.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful, little Sith. This would be an easy place to let your guard down. I cannot vouch for your safety if you do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171446" id2="17" version="1065353216">You ever been to Nar Shaddaa? I can show you the cantinas, get you into the best fights, tour the organ markets... it'll be fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like they added more lights to hide the grime. Don't be fooled by the glamour; when you come to Nar Shaddaa, you're here to lose something. Money, morals, a past. Anything can fall through the cracks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I ever mention I have a fear of dying before I make a million credits?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171451" id2="17" version="1065353216">So much flesh. Are you sure I can't have a taste?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, ugly! Pay you twenty credits to lick my feet.... He'll go for it. Spot me twenty credits?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171453" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Promenade's as close to legitimate as Nar Shaddaa gets. All the families in the Hutt Cartel contribute a cut of their best enforcers to keep the peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171456" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place always makes me feel dirty.... Let me borrow some credits?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Drink and play, little Sith. I want you sated when I kill you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171458" id2="17" version="1065353216">No weapons allowed, but I bit a guy's ear off here, once. Security bootlegged the footage. Not a big fan of casinos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171459" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know, I've never actually been inside one of these casinos. I was just a kid when Braden pulled me out of here, and I haven't been back since.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your hands on your credits. This is not the most respectable part of town.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171463" id2="17" version="1065353216">The lowest of the low. No one will notice if I consume one or two.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171464" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can smell the desperation on these guys. It's like a Duros pheromone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch it around here. Nar Shaddaa may be Hutt territory, but it's a big place; they can't control every corner. I'm sure someone thinks this is their turf.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anybody need some gadgets? Maybe I can finally get that lekku buffer I've always wanted.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171469" id2="17" version="1065353216">The night is a shadow-killer's ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171470" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to buy me a droid? Guy tried to impress me, got me a serving unit once--took me about twelve hours before I smashed it for parts. Kind of fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171471" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're heading into the Corellian Sector, big tech industry hub. I used to spend a lot of time here checking out all the latest and greatest gadgets, before someone'd chase me off anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171474" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like science. Would have been my favorite subject in school. You know, if someone had let me go to school.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough of labs. We were born for conquest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't grow up with a lot of fancy tech. Don't really trust it. Place can burn for all I care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171477" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's something going on down here. Not sure what exactly, but it's definitely off the grid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now leaving comfort zone--please check your sense of security at the door.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171481" id2="17" version="1065353216">The brain of the mechanical planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rumor is, all this hardware runs straight into the moon's core--Nar Shaddaa's one giant computer. Don't know if it's true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171483" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the feeling this is some kind of boundary. We're on our own outside of here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171486" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't recognize any of these droid parts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only cowards let droids do their fighting for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171488" id2="17" version="1065353216">More droids than people on Nar Shaddaa. Kind of creeps me out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171489" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is some pretty impressive equipment. Bet they're building some serious droids here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Took a ride in one of those Mon Cal ships once--not as fast as they look.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171493" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should seize this place and build a fleet to overrun the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice ships. You help me steal one of those, I'm yours for life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171495" id2="17" version="1065353216">I used to love watching ships get put together. It was nice to pretend when one was finished, it'd take me away from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spent a lot of time here back in the day. But the back alleys change daily. It's all different now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful, little Sith. They are small creatures, but they sting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171500" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bunch of losers. Come on--bet I can shoot more of them than you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171501" id2="17" version="1065353216">See that ugly-looking fixture over there? Rumor has it the Hutts hide bodies that need to vanish in art like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171506" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nar Shaddaa = rich + filthy // Jedi = hold onto credits</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171507" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can translate the signs here. They all say &quot;Welcome to Nar Shaddaa. Give us your credits.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nar Shaddaa. Light and color, covering rot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nar Shaddaa sure is colorful. I can see why Risha likes this place. Not exactly my speed, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171510" id2="17" version="1065353216">From here, you could almost forget just how scummy and dangerous this place really is.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith + Imperials = welcome on Promenade // Nar Shaddaa = lacks good taste</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171514" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is neutral territory for Republic and Empire. No fighting allowed--or so they say.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunt and killing is forbidden on Promenade. Shame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rubbing elbows with the enemy and playing nice doesn't sit right with me. We should be kicking the Empire's tail off the Promenade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171517" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard you can find just about anything on Nar Shaddaa. If it's illegal somewhere else, it's a bargain here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Market goods = illegal + expensive</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171521" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is where all the bargain shoppers come. I wouldn't inspect the merchandise too closely.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can find anything on Nar Shaddaa. Save honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep one hand on your credits and the other on your blaster. This place looks rough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171524" id2="17" version="1065353216">More markets. Everyone on this planet is looking to make some credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Area = extremely hostile</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171528" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the strangest feeling we're not welcome here. Might be all the Kintan Kings gangsters.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soft things here trade strength for safety.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171530" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least we don't have to feel bad about shooting anybody here. The Kintan Kings don't seem interested in playing nice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171531" id2="17" version="1065353216">All of these tall buildings would make perfect sniper nests. Let's hope nobody else has thought of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171534" id2="17" version="1065353216">High amount of electronic interference = jamming T7's sensors</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171535" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least it's a pretty place for a shoot-out. Lots of flashing lights and colors while people get killed....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too much brightness and moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171537" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know what most of those light-up signs are saying, but I bet they're not friendly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171538" id2="17" version="1065353216">The best place to find the newest tech in the galaxy--or at least the most convincing knockoffs.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nar Shaddaa Red Light Sector = bad reputation // Criminals = everywhere</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171542" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear this is where you can buy all the best technology. Some of it's even legal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apologize if others stare at me, Herald.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Folks are having all sorts of tech implanted in them here. Call me crazy, but I like to put my blaster down once in a while....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171545" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place is starting to hurt my eyes. Do they have to have those holo-ads every few meters?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Organics in casino = displaying erratic behavior</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody does casinos quite like Nar Shaddaa. They can't afford to.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soft things stare at bright colors. Ignore stars above.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171551" id2="17" version="1065353216">I once knew a guy who bought two extra sets of eyes here. One for the back of his head, and the other implanted someplace ridiculous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171552" id2="17" version="1065353216">Club Vertica. The fastest place in the galaxy to lose every credit you have.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171555" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial neural agonizer arrays = must be destroyed!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171556" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm in the mood for some property damage. This Imperial interrogation facility might be just the thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171557" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here is the Empire's true face.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171558" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stinking Imperials and their torture centers. Let's bust up this place!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171559" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're going to make sure the Imps can't torture anyone in this place ever again.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shadow Town = Imperial-controlled // Enemies = surrounding Jedi + T7</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171563" id2="17" version="1065353216">For a place called Shadow Town, it's surprisingly well lit. Maybe the name refers to the residents.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171564" id2="17" version="1065353216">No good deaths here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171565" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't figure there's anything about this Shadow Town worth saving. Maybe we should torch the whole place on our way out....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171566" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is Shadow Town. I always thought this place was just a rumor.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sewage facility = highly toxic // Jedi = had all inoculations?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171570" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you think this sewage dump is bad, the real trouble's waiting on the other side.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fagh! Cannot smell this? Sickens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't know why they bother putting sewer pipes down here. Not like the residents care about disposing of their filth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171573" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have definitely never smelled anything worse than this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023113" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speculation: I believe I was originally designed and constructed on Nar Shaddaa, master. This is the Maker's workshop.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calculation: At least thirty percent of the population here consists of undesirables who should be liquidated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023119" id2="17" version="1065353216">Presentation: Observe, master--organics with poor math skills and too many credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023122" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warning: HoloNet records indicate high levels of criminal activity here. Be cautious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023125" id2="17" version="1065353216">Request: When we are finished with liquidations, may we come back and shop for upgrades?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023128" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reverie: There is a high probability I was designed in this very sector, master. What a thrill to come home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023131" id2="17" version="1065353216">Declaration: We are departing Imperial-controlled territory and entering a hostile zone. My processor just skipped a beat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023134" id2="17" version="1065353216">Conjecture: I wonder if I was constructed here. Are you there, Maker? It's your favorite creation, HK-51!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023137" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revelation: I have always wanted my own starship. If I serve you well, please remember that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023140" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prediction: If I were capable of appreciating aesthetics, Nar Shaddaa's undesirables would very likely offend me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trivia: All the best droids are designed and manufactured on Nar Shaddaa--including me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alert: We are surrounded by Imperial troublemakers. However, the Hutts have forbidden deletions here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Advice: Avoid purchasing any goods here, master. My scanners indicate they are inferior quality.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Declaration: Troublemakers ahead. Minor criminals, but worthy of deletion all the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perplexity: The overabundance of electronic signals is jamming my sensors. Targeting restricted to line of sight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explanation: I believe this Red Light Sector is more commonly referred to as a &quot;buyer beware&quot; commercial zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023431" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis: Detecting high levels of hormones, organic sweat and desperation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rejection: The Empire loves its interrogation centers, but I find them inefficient and gaudy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Approval: It appears the Empire has perfected organic retraining bolts. Cranial explosives... what a brilliant idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023440" id2="17" version="1065353216">Announcement: I believe this is what organics refer to as an open sewer. Interesting.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
