<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>6</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/weekly_heroic/mission_board_imperial.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corporal Haddon has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the High Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Corporal Haddon may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187892" id2="17" version="1065353216">TA-350 has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the The Tomb sector of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, TA-350 may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Ferrid has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Minimum Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Lord Ferrid may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Shaar has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the High Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Lord Shaar may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187899" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Arten has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Tomb sector of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Lord Arten may be contacted via a Monitoring Station Console. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ava Seldin has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the High Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Ava Seldin may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
