<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>6</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/weekly_heroic/mission_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1176825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major Valyn has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Maximum Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Major Valyn may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1177065" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Skylast has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in The Tomb sector of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, General Skylast may be contacted via his Tech Station. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1177068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Shohn-Lowt has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the The Tomb sector of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Master Shohn-Lowt may be contacted via a Monitoring Station Console. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1177069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent Hextal has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the High Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Agent Hextal may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1177070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent Firehawk has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Minimum Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Agent Firehawk may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1177071" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Everis has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the High Security Section of Belsavis. For additional details about the mission, Doctor Everis may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
