<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>52</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tython/world/combat_leadership/liam_dentiri.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604266" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really showed your expertise out there. Good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604267" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unbelievable! To tell the truth, I didn't think it was possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604269" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you've more than qualified for the job of leading Republic soldiers in battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's your certification. Congratulations. Amazing!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604273" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last round's ready for you. Let's see what you can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604274" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, this is it. You've been tearing through these droids about as fast as I can repair them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604276" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we just received the latest combat simulation data from the Republic and combined it with the data we've collected from your earlier fights.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604278" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll be tough, but if you can do this, there'll be nothing more we can throw at you. You'll be fully qualified to lead Republic troops in battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604280" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unbelievable! I don't think I've ever seen anything like that. But I've still got a few more tricks. Check back later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604281" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see you handle these new models.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604282" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your last round with the droids was impressive, but we've made modifications to their behavior that should make for a real challenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604284" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another impressive round. Looks like we'll have to make things tougher next time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604285" id2="17" version="1065353216">The droids are ready for you. Let's see what you're made of!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604286" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made it look easy last time, but we've thrown some surprises in there for you this time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work out there. We're going to have to get you a real challenge next time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604289" id2="17" version="1065353216">The droids are set up and waiting. Get to it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604290" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was an impressive go earlier, but we've upped the programming on these droids. Care to give it another shot?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get out there and show them what you're made of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604294" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm impressed. Hopefully we'll have something more challenging for you soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604295" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got your task. Go to it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604302" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi, I wonder if you'd be interested in a little challenge. I don't ask everyone, but I've heard promising things about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Padawan, I heard you've begun your trials. Master Orgus speaks very highly of you. No doubt you're pleased to have come this far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604305" id2="17" version="1065353216">Padawan, I heard you've begun your trials. Master Yuon says you show great promise. No doubt you're pleased to have come this far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604307" id2="17" version="1065353216">But some Jedi have the ability to do more, help more people. Interested?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604308" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me a bit more about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604309" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always looking for a way to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604309" id2="17" version="1065353216">I welcome challenges.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604310" id2="17" version="1065353216">A war is brewing in the greater galaxy. The Sith Empire plots against the Republic, and the Republic looks to the Jedi for aid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604312" id2="17" version="1065353216">But not all who train to become Jedi are skilled combatants and leaders. Many are scholars, diplomats, strategists and scientists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604314" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which is why we've created a simulation to test Jedi and Padawans and certify them to lead Republic troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604315" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want me to participate in this simulation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604315" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I qualify to try?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604316" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I'm asking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604318" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm pretty good with a blade, but this... what does this simulation entail?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604318" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure I'm right for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604319" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fight when I have to, but I do not consider myself a leader. What does this simulation entail?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604319" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure I'm right for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your humility is admirable, but unnecessary. I have already heard tales of your potential.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604322" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're looking for a leader, you've come to the right person. Where do I start?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confidence is good. A leader must have confidence, in herself and others. Just don't get arrogant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604325" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confidence is good. A leader must have confidence, in himself and others. Just don't get arrogant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604327" id2="17" version="1065353216">The droids here in the yard have been programmed to act according to Imperial military protocols and battlefield tactics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Demonstrate your proficiency at defeating these droids, and you will be on your way to qualifying to lead Republic troops into battle. Can you do it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604330" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604331" id2="17" version="1065353216">No sweat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's just get to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. The first set of training droids are ready for you. Get to it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604336" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand that your trials must be your primary focus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604338" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will not use up anymore of your time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, I'm busy. Got to make sure the programming on these droids is just right.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
