<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/bronze/republic/bomb_disposal/sergeant_larus.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks again. Maybe I can get out of here without worrying about where I step.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nerves of durasteel. I could feel those detonations from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, we located the bomber we shot down; they were shipping in supplies. I think you've earned first pick, don't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234539" id2="17" version="1065353216">You look like everything's still attached. The detonations must be going well.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh no. Don't tell me someone set those things off. No, can't be that--you're still in one piece.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry--be careful when you leave, Master Jedi. There's unexploded bombs outside.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, sir. We've got unexploded ordnance outside. Hardly ZR-57s, but nasty hardware all the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take my advice: When you go outside, walk close together. We've got unexploded bombs close by.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take my advice: Watch your step outside. We've got unexploded bombs nearby.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our AA guns winged an Imperial bomber, and it dropped its payload as it crashed. Too low to set the bombs off, but sooner or later, something will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234551" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should have this area cordoned off until the bombs are dealt with. It's not worth risking lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then keep people away.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234552" id2="17" version="1065353216">No good, Master Jedi. This is a major staging zone; we need the streets open.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234554" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to remember this situation could have been a lot worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234554" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least their target is safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234555" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're telling me. That bomber was heading straight for a residential district.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234557" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't leave live ordnance lying around; call in a bomb squad and have them cleared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234557" id2="17" version="1065353216">So get them disarmed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234558" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wish it was that easy, sir, but the Empire's bombed the whole city. We're low on the list.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234560" id2="17" version="1065353216">These bombs can't be that sensitive. Can they?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234560" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like what?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234561" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me put it this way. If you get the urge to sneeze, don't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me a worst-case scenario.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234564" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they all went off right here, those bombs could ignite the underground gas conduits. Half the city would be in flames.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234566" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you haven't evacuated.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234567" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where am I going to go? At least here I know exactly where the danger is.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234569" id2="17" version="1065353216">We set up a safe area for controlled detonations, but getting the bombs there is easier said than done.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just moving the bombs will start their countdown. If they go off while someone's holding them, well, it's not going to be pretty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234572" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll help. I'm not afraid.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234573" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're absolutely, completely sure? I won't turn away help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234575" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the countdown on the bombs?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234575" id2="17" version="1065353216">How long will I have?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234576" id2="17" version="1065353216">Um. That's a good question. But if you do it fast, there's no problems, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just take the bombs to the detonation area--very, very carefully. We've got ground emitters there to contain the blast.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234580" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for this. And don't take any chances with those things. Who knows what the Empire's been cooking up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234582" id2="17" version="1065353216">So handle it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234583" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose I'll try asking among my men for volunteers. Again.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234585" id2="17" version="1065353216">I keep waiting for that &quot;bang&quot; in the distance.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
