<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>91</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/world/industrial_sabotage/derrik_reed.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532959" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really saved our skins. A battalion of walkers would have been the end of us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those overload modules worked like a charm. The walkers are out of commission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="532961" id2="17" version="1065353216">I took care of the walkers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532962" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you'd make it! And I heard you took out that active walker, too. Wish I could've seen it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532963" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you'd make it! I just wish I could've been there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532964" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was your modules that destroyed those walkers. You saved lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="532964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be proud of your contribution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532965" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. It means a lot to know I made a difference. Be safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532966" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt this was the last item in the Empire's bag of tricks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="532966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get too comfortable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532967" id2="17" version="1065353216">For now, it just feels good to buy Balmorra some time. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="532968" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm the best, kid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532969" id2="17" version="1065353216">No argument here. Stay safe. And thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532971" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry! If the Empire gets those walkers mobilized, we could lose all of Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532972" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a walker online already? I thought we had more time!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532974" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, the modules are done, but it doesn't matter if no one can get close... wait, I gotta go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi! You could get past a walker, right? You've got to....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain! You're Havoc Squad! You could get past a walker, right? You've got to....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, you're that privateer! You could get past a walker, right? You've got to....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, I've heard of you! You could get past a walker, right? You've got to....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532980" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still your mind and explain. Is there an attack?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="532980" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must calm yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Brief me like a professional or I can't help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="532981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey! Pull it together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take it easy and tell me what's going on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="532982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Relax. What's wrong?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, it's just... walkers get me a little anxious. The Empire just launched the first of a whole battalion they're building.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Private Reed. I'm building hardware to sabotage the Empire's walker construction program. Unfortunately, the scum just launched their first unit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Walkers are dangerous. I like being alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="532988" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather not....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please hear me out! The Empire's building a battalion of walkers at the Balmorran Arms Factory. They've already got one running.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those machines are serious. I saw one in action at the outpost where I was first stationed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532993" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were ready--troops, battle droids, hardened turrets. But when that walker was done... there was just a crater full of crushed metal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532995" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we don't sabotage the rest of the battalion before it comes online, they could take Balmorra in one sweep.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532996" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume you have a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="532996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sabotage them how?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah. Too bad for the Imperials I'm not some useless kid anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="532999" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've convinced me. I'll find a way to stop the walkers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="532999" id2="17" version="1065353216">No time to waste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here, I built these overload modules. Plant one on each unit in the factory, and it'll fry their systems permanently.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their active walker will probably be patrolling outside. If you can destroy it, great.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533004" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're sure you're not overstating things?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="533004" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you're exaggerating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533005" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the specs on these things. They'll crush us. But we can still stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533007" id2="17" version="1065353216">I built a batch of overload modules. My own design. They'll permanently fry the systems on those walkers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533009" id2="17" version="1065353216">But planting them means getting past that active walker first. Can you do that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those walkers will never leave that factory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="533010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533011" id2="17" version="1065353216">We cannot allow the Empire such power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="533011" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm willing to risk it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533012" id2="17" version="1065353216">No chance they'll get those walkers mobilized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="533012" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take care of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, kid. I'll take care of those walkers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="533013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533014" id2="17" version="1065353216">One day I'll call in a favor, and you'll say yes. Understand?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="533014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, but you'll owe me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh... okay, I guess I understand. Here, these are the overload modules.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh... well, I guess I can scrape some credits together. Don't worry, I'll think of something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533020" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can destroy that active walker patrolling outside the factory, great.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533022" id2="17" version="1065353216">But if it's too tough, just get past it. The ones inside are the real threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="533024" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll pass. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533025" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, there goes Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="533027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't talk. I have to get these overload modules finished.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="755842" id2="17" version="1065353216">With those bombers destroyed, we can go back to fighting men, not machines.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764201" id2="17" version="1065353216">All intel reports the Empire's bombers are history. The entire shipyard is wiped out-- I don't know how you did it!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764203" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got to give you credit, Private. Your solution was a good one, once we found someone crazy enough to try it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764205" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll get your chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764206" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got to take out those bombers, or we might as well pack up now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764207" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's no solution, Reed. Those bombers are heavily guarded. We just don't have the skills to--</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764209" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey! Halt there! Your squad's better equipped than my entire platoon. You've got to help us!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764211" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi! Wait, please-- I don't mean to be rude, but you've got to help us. It's your duty!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764213" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait. I know that logo anywhere. That's Havoc Squad! Captain, over here! We need your help!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764215" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, you! You're that merc, right? The one who's been pulling special ops across Balmorra?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764217" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we don't do something about the Empire's new bombers, every Republic outpost will be a smoldering crater by sundown!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764218" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry. It's just chaos out here-- the minute we take down one Imperial defense, that factory pumps out another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764220" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're kidding.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764221" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you were hoping for shore leave, you landed on the wrong planet. In this sector, the Empire's fighting for keeps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764223" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds about right.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764224" id2="17" version="1065353216">With all due respect, we're doing our best out here. But we can't predict what that factory's going to spit out next!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764226" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Balmorran Arms Factory's got an experimental shipyard. They've developed stealth bombers-- small, fast ships designed to hammer us into oblivion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764228" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what can we do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764229" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then get to it, soldier!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764230" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have the resources for this large an assault. But we do have a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Private Reed here's been studying our recon data. He's developed a way to disable the bombers from the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764234" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't offer any support. You'd be making a solo assault into the factory shipyard, and it's crawling with Imps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764235" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you need my help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764236" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Havoc Squad, aren't I?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764237" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've done stupider things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you offer a reward?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764240" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coordinates to the shipyard, and instructions on how to install the modules. Reed will monitor them from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764242" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can pull this off, you'll save the Republic war effort on Balmorra. Get out there and scrap those bombers!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
