<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>68</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_2/planetary_surgery/d_lz8.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028250" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sold us out to that maniac Toborro. Now that he's turned on you, we're supposed to save your skins? Incredible!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028252" id2="17" version="1065353216">Had we known Toborro was insane, we never would have supported him. He is no longer Hutt Cartel. We formally shun him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028254" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cargo? Are you delusional? Your bodies take up more room than a dozen good people!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028256" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah! One of the Republic's greatest heroes. Just the person we could use to bring some wisdom and perspective to the discussion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028257" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here we are! The Republic's greatest heroes, ready to settle this matter with wisdom and perspective.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most of my negotiations occur with a lightsaber, but I'm always open to alternatives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028258" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no diplomat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028259" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutt leaders on Makeb sent an expendable diplomacy droid for a reason. Cowards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028261" id2="17" version="1065353216">In my experience, wisdom and perspective are necessary qualities for anyone who desires harmony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028261" id2="17" version="1065353216">The path to peace isn't easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where was the Hutts' wisdom when they mined my world to death?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's my wisdom....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028264" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I call my weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028266" id2="17" version="1065353216">And this is my perspective. Start talking, but don't waste my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028267" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like your negotiating style, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028269" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wisdom's overrated, but I'm all about perspective. From where I'm standing, I heard someone mention &quot;generous compensation.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028269" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's make a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028270" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing they can offer to repay what they've done to Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028272" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me see if I understand: Toborro's former friends got on his bad side. Now they need to get off Makeb, so they've come to us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028272" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's going on here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028273" id2="17" version="1065353216">The major Cartel leaders have decided Toborro is bad for business. They want peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028275" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've stabilized Makeb for now, but we need those fuel rods. Get rid of these clowns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop wasting time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028276" id2="17" version="1065353216">My sentiments exactly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most revered Republic champions, my masters apologize for this unfortunate situation. Surely we can reach a state of mutually beneficial recompense and earn passage aboard the ark?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028280" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people deserve rescue. The Hutt Cartel's leaders can't just beg their way out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028282" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shalim's right, but these are the most powerful Hutts in the galaxy. We can name our price to save their lives--and think what that means for defeating the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028283" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think we should combine forces with the Hutts and attack the Empire together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028283" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hutt allies could end the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028284" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't lose sight of the real enemy here--or how much the Hutts fear you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028286" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll say anything to get what they want, and the minute we turn our backs, they'll stab us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028286" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't trust them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028287" id2="17" version="1065353216">They wouldn't dare. You hold all the power here. You can force them to commit their fleet to our side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028289" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you planning to run for Senate as soon as we leave the planet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028289" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're such a schemer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hadn't really thought about it. My point is, you have the power to force the Cartel to commit its forces to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toborro has lost his mind, and these Cartel leaders know it. They can't go back to him--they need us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028294" id2="17" version="1065353216">Honored Republic heroes, you are known for mercy and greatness. Can you find it within yourselves to forgive our profound error in judgment?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028295" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll consider it, yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028297" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's easy to have a change of heart when your life is in danger. Show me that you won't revert back to your old ways once you're off Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028299" id2="17" version="1065353216">In many ways, we are defined by our mistakes. We can let them destroy us or use them as opportunities to grow. Tell me, are you truly prepared to change?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028301" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you boys learned your lesson not to mess with Havoc Squad. What we really need to answer is, have you gained any humility? Let's find out....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028303" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know me well. Mercy? I've got it. Greatness? Definitely. And I don't like to write off any opportunity for mutual profit. If you're serious about business, so am I.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028304" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're going to grovel, first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028306" id2="17" version="1065353216">As a Jedi, the Sith are my greatest enemy. One day, there won't be any of them left to fight. Are there any reasons I shouldn't eradicate the Hutts next?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028308" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right. The Jedi are known for their mercy and greatness--to those who deserve it. Your masters are venal, corrupt and untrustworthy. Convince me not to see them extinct.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028310" id2="17" version="1065353216">You make me sick. You knew exactly what you were doing when you let Toborro lead you into this. Give me a hundred good reasons not to leave you here....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028312" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know what holovids you've been watching, but &quot;mercy&quot; isn't something I'm known for. In fact, it's pretty much the opposite. Let's start with you begging for your lives....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Honored Republic negotiators, my masters will happily continue debasing themselves, but Makeb's time grows short.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Honored Republic negotiators, I hope we have demonstrated our sincere contrition and the many benefits of restoring our neglected friendship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028319" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you provide safe passage for my masters and their cargo, they will fully commit the Cartel to an alliance with the Republic. Surely you find this agreeable?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Inform your masters that they'll be allowed to board the ark with the other refugees. Personal belongings will be loaded as space permits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, we'll be reasonable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028322" id2="17" version="1065353216">First priority will be given to food, medicine and other items essential to survival. Aurodium-plated statues will not qualify.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028324" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll negotiate exactly what responsibilities the Cartel has to the Republic once this crisis is over. We'll expect full cooperation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028325" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll commit a lot more than &quot;fully.&quot; The Cartel cost the Republic time and credits that could've been spent defeating the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1028325" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will serve and obey us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028327" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll need your technology, your mercenaries, your warships and your money. Keep giving them until we tell you to stop.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028329" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's our offer--take it or leave it. Your masters can enjoy Makeb's destruction from front-row seats for all we care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028332" id2="17" version="1065353216">My masters wish no further hostilities with you. The offer is accepted without condition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028334" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you're the first in galactic history to force the Hutts into a deal they can't afford.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028336" id2="17" version="1065353216">My masters compliment you on your negotiating skills and agree to this bargain without further comment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not only did you forge an alliance, but you made the Hutts be quiet. Win-win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1028340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now all we need are those fuel rods. Doctor Oggurobb is with Shalim. You should coordinate with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1029322" id2="17" version="1065353216">However, in breaking ties with Toborro, we find ourselves stranded on Makeb with you. We are prepared to offer generous compensation for seating and cargo space aboard the ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1029356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop appealing to our sentimentality. Forgiveness isn't the issue here. Your masters want a ticket off Makeb, and we'll consider providing it--for the right price.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1029356" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is strictly business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1051690" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your bargaining skills are most impressive. I have been forced to add several new negotiating subroutines because of our interaction.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
