<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>45</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/bronze/imperial/lethal_attraction/sergeant_namada.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318938" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rumor is, those Killiks come as big as a troop carrier. Not sure I believe it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318940" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Brood Totem works. It lured the Killiks to the Organa forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318941" id2="17" version="1065353216">The science boys'll be happy. Me, I hope it means we go back to killing aliens instead of baiting them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318943" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been a pleasure to see you in action. You ever need a hive extraction team or a couple tonnes of xenotoxic torpedoes, you give the Bughunters a call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318945" id2="17" version="1065353216">You manage to retrieve that attractor tech and deploy it near the Organas, give us the word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318948" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, you're the team that carved through half of Balmorra!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, look who's here. You're the Sith who carved through half of Balmorra!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318952" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, if it isn't the mercenary from Balmorra. I remember your work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318954" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the mystery troubleshooter from Balmorra--you may execute me for saying so, but I admire your work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Namada, Bughunter Division. My squad came here off Colicoid duty--it's an honor to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bughunter Division?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Special Tactics Group 41-Delta. Geonosians, Gand, Verpine--if it's got eggs and an exoskeleton, we know how to kill it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me--how does the battle proceed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Report, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318961" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you're a fine, devoted servant of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318961" id2="17" version="1065353216">How very polite, Sergeant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah--yes, my lord. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318964" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's my pleasure, Sergeant--but officially, I'm not even here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just don't mention we met.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318965" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then consider this my unofficial report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gets a little old, talking to officers and royalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to meet the grunts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318968" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take your word for it--don't much get the privilege.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318970" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're an idiot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318971" id2="17" version="1065353216">Begging your pardon. I'll get to our status, then, assuming you're interested.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318973" id2="17" version="1065353216">Team's supposed to contain the Killik threat so House Thul's free to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine plan, but Science Bureau has us trying out attractor tech--like this &quot;Brood Totem&quot; device they gave us. Lures Killiks into enemy territory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318976" id2="17" version="1065353216">While you're fighting Killiks, the scientists are trying to study them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Complicating your job?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318977" id2="17" version="1065353216">They talk to the Moff and he gives the orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318979" id2="17" version="1065353216">An impressive device.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318980" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got green lights, smells like iron, makes a high-pitched chittering sound--like what a droid would build if he worshipped roaches.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318982" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's bound to go wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318983" id2="17" version="1065353216">We agree in that. Not my opinion that matters, I'm afraid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318985" id2="17" version="1065353216">We dropped the totem off in Killik territory so it could &quot;synchronize pheromones.&quot; We barely survived; now we need to move it to Organa territory for testing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318987" id2="17" version="1065353216">We carry chitin-piercing rounds and insecticide gas--we can't fight Organa troops. But you assist like on Balmorra, this lure project might move forward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318988" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I can help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318989" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you offering?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318990" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've hired mercenaries before--cheap ones make the best bait, but the funds are there. Grab the device, get to Organa, test it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318992" id2="17" version="1065353216">So long as there's mayhem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318993" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd have to slaughter Killiks on the way to the device, get it near Organa troops and see if the lure works. Dangerous enough?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just be careful you don't lure in too many Killiks. They're not like Colicoids--they take prisoners and... well, better not to know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not interested. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood. We've got some new xenotoxic flechettes; they worked on the Verpines, maybe they'll work on Killiks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Men, check your loadouts--we'll be seeing more Killiks tonight.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
