<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>32</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/world/quiet_kill/garboza.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713318" id2="17" version="1065353216">I bet I get a commendation for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me. I have work to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, if it isn't the best-paid engineering consultant on Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, my lord, I didn't realize--I mean, no one told me you would be Sith. My apologies for the familiarity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713324" id2="17" version="1065353216">But, um, if you don't mind me asking, what is someone like you doing working for Officer Sakoal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713325" id2="17" version="1065353216">I mean, no offense, but you don't exactly look like science corps material, you know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713327" id2="17" version="1065353216">What exactly is he paying you all this for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713328" id2="17" version="1065353216">How much is it worth for you to know about it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="713328" id2="17" version="1065353216">You paying for that answer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="713329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only my duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713330" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure. The kind of servants who kill the master, then run a planetary takeover from his front porch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Usually more of a choke-someone-to-death-with-your-mind kind of servant, though, right? No offense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Usually more of a cut-people's-heads-off kind of servant, though, right? No offense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Usually more of a skin-your-enemies-and-leave-their-bodies-to-die kind of servant, though, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Usually more of a garotte-you-in-the-name-of-Imperial-security kind of servant, though, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure. The kind of servants who'd kill the master, then run a planetary takeover from his front porch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713342" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713344" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can make it worth your while for dirt on how Officer Sakoal's been spending Troida money.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just transfer the credits and don't ask things you don't want to know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="713345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Back off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't ask about things that could get Officer Sakoal in trouble, you mean? Because that's definitely something I want to know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713348" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could add a little something on top of this for information that lets me pass Officer Sakoal at the next evaluation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713350" id2="17" version="1065353216">Call it a tip. Fifteen percent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713351" id2="17" version="1065353216">Officer Sakoal hired me to kill his wife and her rebel boyfriend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="713351" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pay me and I'll talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713352" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pretty little Kelara had Republic leanings, hmm?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooh, that is not going to look good to the clearance board at all....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. Next time you see me, I may be working Troida instead of this pit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713357" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your credits. I'll just take what I'm owed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="713357" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't betray a trust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713358" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suit yourself. I'm sure I can find someone else who knows what Sakoal's up to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713360" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm busy. My evaluation comes up day after tomorrow.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
