<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>17</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/world/imperial/the_devouring_plague/mistressamaran.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="972031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most vengeful and terrible Lord of the Sith. This humble worm begs a moment of your time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="972032" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most clever and most wise Lord of the Sith. This humble worm begs a moment of your time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="972033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent. Defender. Keeper of all the Empire and its people. This humble worm begs a moment of your time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="972034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most ferocious of hunters. Most terrible and deadly of the galaxy's warriors. This humble worm begs a moment of your time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="972035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such august and renowned companions. This humble worm begs a moment of your time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="972042" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have the deep honor to be the messenger and property of the great Lord Serjay Thul, first Sith Lord of Alderaan blood.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="972048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your help is desperately needed back on Alderaan, and Lord Thul has sent me to humbly beg for your return in his hour of need.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="972049" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll go speak to him.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="972050" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me what's happening.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="972051" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have my own obligations.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="972052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. And Lord Thul understands this. Without your help, though, Alderaan will fall and everything you achieved there will have been for naught.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="972053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me, but I cannot speak of such things here. Please, go to Alderaan, meet with Lord Thul or everything achieved there will be for naught!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="972054" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thank you. Alderaan, and indeed the entire Empire, will soon thank you as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="972056" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, meet Lord Thul at Castle Thul on Alderaan as soon as can possibly be arranged.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="972062" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've just arrived. Overwhelming, isn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="972063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, hurry to Alderaan.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="972064" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord has given me permission to stay and explore the fleet. A reward I cherish.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
