<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>43</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/bronze/imperial/a_pound_of_flesh/skav_mora.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171326" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like your honesty, friend. You're okay in my book.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171327" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm picking up some pretty angry chatter on Exchange frequencies. Sounds like you held up your end of our little deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171329" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing I admire more than honesty. The Hutt Cartel will keep the Republic at bay. You can count on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bust up those Exchange organ thieves, and we'll talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171334" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord. Skav Mora. Hutt Cartel. Don't often get to deal directly with someone of your stature, but I hope that's about to change.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171336" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know your kind. Real patriot. Tough. Won't take &quot;no&quot; for an answer. I like that. I need that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunter. From the sound of it, you know which way the wind blows in this galaxy. Empire or bust. So let's make a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171340" id2="17" version="1065353216">You look like a smart person. Good Imperial supporter. Let's make a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171342" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm talking about expanding the mutually beneficial relationship between the Hutt Cartel and the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171343" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. I'm a friend of all Nar Shaddaa's lowlifes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="171343" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've caught my interest.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171344" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not looking for friendship. Know better than to trust a Sith's definition of the word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171346" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must have a lot of guts to try to cut a deal with a Sith Lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="171346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know who I am?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171347" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts don't trust their business to just anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171349" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire likes to keep the upper hand in all its &quot;mutually beneficial&quot; relationships.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="171349" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just remember who's boss.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171350" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutt Cartel feels the same way. But in this case, they're willing to accept less favorable terms.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171352" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire pays me. I don't owe them anything, and I don't do them favors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="171352" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't represent the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171353" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if the Hutt Cartel pays, it's not a favor, is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="171355" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not concerned with Hutts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171356" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts run this planet. They're very good allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171358" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been on Nar Shaddaa long enough to know I should look for strings before I make any deals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="171358" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the catch?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Strings? No, there's no strings. Just a little tit for tat.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems the Republic's meddling in Imperial business. Spreading rumors of hidden torture facilities to scare the gangs, keep them from working with the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171363" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutt Cartel can make it very... uncomfortable for any gang that works with the Republic. But we need the Empire to scratch our backs in return.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="171364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this bribery or blackmail, because I don't respond well to either.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="171364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't twist my arm.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171365" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, I didn't mean it that way. I just think we can help each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="171367" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you need done?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171368" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Exchange has been messing up our slave shipments, taking the low classes and harvesting organs from them for sale on the black market.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171370" id2="17" version="1065353216">You take care of the organ thieves, and the Hutt Cartel will handle the Empire's little Republic problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="171371" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="171372" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have a choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry. It's just good business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="171375" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where do I find these thieves?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171376" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Exchange is in the shipyards, getting ready to move the organs offworld.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171378" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want the organ thieves killed, and the organ shipments destroyed. Show them it's bad business crossing the Hutts, and the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="171380" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a chance. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171381" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your choice, but your Empire can't do anything if the Republic starts laying pressure on the gangs. You need us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="171383" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, I don't got time to talk.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
