<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>95</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/world/republic/cold_war/admiral_revald.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668396" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done good work! The Empire won't know what hit them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations! You've done the Republic a whopping huge service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668401" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arim just gave me the good news. I knew you'd send those pirates packing! Well done!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668402" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pirates copied the Null Cannon. I think we'll be seeing more of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668402" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not over yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668403" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't worry about the pirates. Their puny little copies will be no match for our prototype.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668405" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need for thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668406" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic owes you one, and don't think we're likely to forget it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668408" id2="17" version="1065353216">When your transmission cut out, I thought we'd be delivering the Null Cannon to an empty camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668408" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to see you're okay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668409" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll take more than a bit of ion cannon fire to get rid of me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668411" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a shame about the prototype. Blasted pirates must've mucked it up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668412" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those pirates ruin everything, don't they?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668412" id2="17" version="1065353216">Er... yeah.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668413" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't lie, it's a setback. But working or not, the Null Cannon represents our best chance of beating the Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668415" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's already been shot, smashed and frozen, I'm sure the Null Cannon can be repaired again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't it be fixed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668416" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a setback, but we'll recover. I'm not about to let one little explosion stand between us and victory!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668418" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pity how things turned out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, don't let a little explosion get you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668421" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've hit the Empire where it hurts today!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668423" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've already contacted Republic Command. They know what you've done for us here, and I'll make sure the Senate knows it, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668424" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will you be leaving Hoth immediately?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668424" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happens now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soon! I don't have to tell you how much I'm looking forward to frying some Imperial starships.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668427" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell, Admiral.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Goodbye, Admiral Revald.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668429" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been a real pleasure, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668431" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate that, Admiral.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668432" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're going to go far, Captain. No doubt about it. Wish we had more like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very generous of you, Admiral. Just make sure they spell my name right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds good to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry. If I have to, I'll deliver the report myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668437" id2="17" version="1065353216">My credits?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course! The Republic pays her debts, and don't let anyone tell you different.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668440" id2="17" version="1065353216">Transport is on its way. When the troops hear we're getting off this oversized snowball, they may declare a holiday in your honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668442" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember this day: This is the day the war was won, and don't let anyone tell you different.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668443" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll have the Null Cannon up and running in no time. You ought to come back and see her in action!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668445" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's going to take months, sir. Maybe a year.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Engineers... always predicting the worst. Mark my words, we will have that Null Cannon shooting Imperials out of the sky before you know it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668451" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did good work here. If I had a dozen men like you, this war would be over already!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668452" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to lend a hand at Outpost Senth? Last I heard, Lieutenant Kieral was taking a beating. Probably more blasted pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668453" id2="17" version="1065353216">You ought to find out what's going on at Outpost Cresh. Last transmission was garbled something awful. Something about Chiss? Could be trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find out what's going on at Aurek Base. Haven't heard so much as a peep out of them in days. Got to be trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668455" id2="17" version="1065353216">What're you waiting for? There's a whole mess of pirates out there with your name on 'em!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck out there! Break some heads.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good! Now that you're all here, we can get this party started!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668461" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi? Well, paint me blue and call me Chiss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668463" id2="17" version="1065353216">At ease, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good! I was hoping we'd get someone with real guts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to see you made it! I was starting to think you'd miss all the fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668469" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Admiral Revald. The Zabrak with the sunny disposition is my chief engineer, Arim. Welcome to the best place on Hoth!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shouldn't you be with the fleet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668470" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's an admiral doing here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668471" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should be on the front lines! You see where we are? Take a good look around you. This is the turning point of the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668473" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was starting to think the Republic was just here for the scenery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668473" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a point to all this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha! We've got a real mission on our hands, and trust me, we'll make it worth your while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever is out there, Havoc Squad is ready for it, Admiral.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reporting for duty, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668477" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, Admiral.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668478" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's all this about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668479" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know how much you've seen of the Republic presence on this snowball, but this is what it's all about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668481" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't just a battle for Hoth: We win out here, and we've got the whole war with the Empire in the bag.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668482" id2="17" version="1065353216">What makes this frozen wasteland worth fighting for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is Hoth so critical?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you serious?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668484" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm all for defeating the Empire. Tell me what you have in mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668484" id2="17" version="1065353216">What needs to be done?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spread across that ice field is what's left of one of our capital ships. She was carrying a top secret weapon prototype.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668487" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Null Cannon. It can fry all the machinery on a starship without giving the crew so much as a hangnail!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668489" id2="17" version="1065353216">With that weapon in our hands, we can push the Empire back to the Unknown Regions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something like that could save a lot of lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668490" id2="17" version="1065353216">A non-lethal weapon? Great.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668491" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought there'd be a little more... fighting here on the front.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Salvage? That's it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't you worry, son. We've got more than enough fighting to go around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now don't you worry, we've got plenty of targets out there for you to shoot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668496" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wouldn't still be here if this were a simple salvage mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668496" id2="17" version="1065353216">But there's some complication.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668497" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you're retrieving it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668498" id2="17" version="1065353216">We had a fantastic weapon, until it was broken into little bits and buried in the ice. Great.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does this story get better?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668499" id2="17" version="1065353216">We found the wreckage. Trouble is, pirates got there first--snatched up several pieces of our prototype, striking from a hidden base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668501" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've deployed the Talz and the infantry. They're taking heavy losses out there, and we're not any closer to getting the Null Cannon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668503" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't allow these thieving scum to leave Hoth with a weapon that can take out any starship in the galaxy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668504" id2="17" version="1065353216">One prototype, coming up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668504" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668505" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intercept pirates. Check.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668506" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sensors detect life-forms in the nearby wreckage. The pirates may be making a grab for pieces of the Null Cannon's primary power core.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep an eye out for anything that will help us track the scum back to their lair, and contact me once all the fragments of the power core are secure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go out there and bust some heads!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668512" id2="17" version="1065353216">No thanks. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668513" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's too bad. You'll miss out on a doozy of a fight!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668515" id2="17" version="1065353216">You smell that? Blaster fire! There's nothing like it! You come see me when we've got reports back from the field, I'll see you get in on the action.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
