<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>64</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_12/scene_01_theron_kaliyo_jorgan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172062" id2="17" version="1065353216">SCORPIO cross-referenced all the data Havoc Squad and Kaliyo stole from Zakuul. When we compared the enemy's comm logs to the Spire maps, we found something unexpected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me know when you get to the exciting part.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1172063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yawn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172064" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you'd take my briefing seriously. Lana, you're up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172068" id2="17" version="1065353216">That relay station is our key to the GEMINI frequency. If we can decrypt it, we'll eavesdrop on the enemy and learn his plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think bigger, Lana. We could send fake orders. Have Arcann's own warships blast him off the throne.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1172069" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can take over the Fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172070" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll never get near that relay station. It's ten kilometers underground, and defended by more safeguards than we can count.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172072" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a good thing our data reveals every security measure in the way--and how to defeat them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172074" id2="17" version="1065353216">A strike team can disable the defenses right under Arcann's nose, but only if we send it in now. Our intel's turning stale as we speak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172078" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kaliyo and Major Jorgan are already on Zakuul. They're in position to clear the Commander a path directly to the relay station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172082" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are not sending that terrorist. She's done enough to my world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172085" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senya's right. Can't believe I had to say that....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad was made for this op. We have enough detonite to turn that relay station into a crater. Cut the head off the serpent, throw the Fleet into chaos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172089" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're trusting the fate of the galaxy to a gang of grenade-happy bucketheads? We're only getting one shot at this. Lucky for you, one shot is all I need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172091" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that what you tell all your victims?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172093" id2="17" version="1065353216">The idea has potential. She's an experienced infiltrator who survived on Zakuul for years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172096" id2="17" version="1065353216">She bombed my people. Never again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172097" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroying the relay station is a last resort.  But if things go wrong, I need someone who can get creative. That's Kaliyo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1172097" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kaliyo, you're with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172098" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's like a rancor in a glass factory. This is a mistake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172099" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those are my orders. They're not open to debate. Your job is to keep Arcann away from us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1172099" id2="17" version="1065353216">My decision is final, Jorgan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172100" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm already moving. Be seeing you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172107" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't please everyone. But it may be prudent to consult Valkorion. He built the Spire. He may tell you how to invade it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174652" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a hyperwave relay station hidden ten thousand meters beneath the Spire. It's the only source of GEMINI frequency transmissions to and from the Eternal Throne.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174653" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's how Arcann commands the Fleet. And we know where it is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1174653" id2="17" version="1065353216">We found Arcann's weak spot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174654" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought the Throne controlled the Eternal Fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1174654" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not the Throne itself?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Broadcasting a signal to thousands of ships across the galaxy takes tremendous energy. The relay station's powered by two hundred reactors tapping directly into Zakuul's planetary core.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174657" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have a map. All we need is a route.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1174657" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we reach that station?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why stop there? When the Fleet's under your control, there's nothing you couldn't do with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174660" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we take it out, Arcann won't only be blind, he'll be toothless. The Fleet will sit there waiting for commands that never arrive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1174660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or destroy all communications.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174661" id2="17" version="1065353216">First order of guerilla warfare--disrupt enemy communications. This is a demolition op, all the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroying that relay station is a bonehead play. Send me, and you'll control the GEMINI frequency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174665" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Alliance will never win if we can't function as a team. I need all of you to pull together and do what's necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1174665" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expect you to work together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174666" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not that simple. We need to draw Arcann's attention away from our true goal. That means creating a diversion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174668" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're both accomplished at drawing attention. The real question is, who do you want with you at the relay station?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174669" id2="17" version="1065353216">We also have to make Arcann miserable--and distract him from our real purpose. Havoc Squad can do that better than anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1174669" id2="17" version="1065353216">A decoy mission is vital.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174670" id2="17" version="1065353216">We won't disappoint, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174672" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is safety in numbers... and military discipline. The mission's yours, Major--but we need a diversion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1174672" id2="17" version="1065353216">On second thought, I agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Commander. We're en route.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174675" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want chaos? You've got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174676" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we can't take control of the GEMINI frequency, we'll have to destroy it. Havoc Squad has the firepower for that job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1174676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major Jorgan has my vote.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without me there to slice that relay station, Major Malfunction's suicide run will be a self-fulfilling prophecy. Give me a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174678" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need a perfect diversion, and you're the best around. Just keep it clean. No civilians, got it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1174678" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need you as a distraction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174679" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about pets? Kidding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174681" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're so committed to not setting off bombs, who am I to argue? Major, I need you to provide our distraction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1174681" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won me over. You're in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174682" id2="17" version="1065353216">That actually worked. Hunh. This might be fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174684" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you know what you're doing, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't make me repeat myself. If you want to be useful, distract Arcann's forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1174685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do as you're told.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174686" id2="17" version="1065353216">See you at the rendezvous, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174688" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Kaliyo's idea of a distraction results in harm to my people, I'll kill her myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174690" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I'll help.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
