<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>19</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_12/scene_03_valkorion.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at you. Still nothing more than a common criminal hiding behind a blaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until you embrace your full potential, you will only be a pawn of fate. Never its master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destiny isn't a personal choice. That's the whole point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1172139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mastering fate is impossible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172140" id2="17" version="1065353216">You grasp at understanding like a blind infant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172142" id2="17" version="1065353216">The future is not a river to carry us. It is the ocean in which we drown, if we are not prepared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172144" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have two destinies, Outlander. In one, you defeat Arcann, claim the Eternal Throne, and remake the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172146" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the other... you die alone, unmourned and forgotten. I brought you here to taste that defeat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174715" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force is with you, Jedi, but it will not defeat my son. It never could.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174717" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have survived many battles, but you are still merely a soldier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174720" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have mastered the dark side of the Force. It is not enough. It never was.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your armor, weapons, and instincts are not enough to secure victory, hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174724" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think secrets grant power. That striking from the shadows will be enough. You are wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174725" id2="17" version="1065353216">I follow my own path, Valkorion. Not yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1174725" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop trying to manipulate me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174726" id2="17" version="1065353216">You truly believe that. How pathetic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174728" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you have all the answers, let's hear them. Start with why you let your son betray you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1174728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then show me how, old man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arcann saw what he wanted, and claimed it. What is your excuse for failing to do the same?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
