<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>32</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_12/transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172131" id2="17" version="1065353216">A path has been laid before you, but you refuse to tread upon it. That will change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172132" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a destiny to fulfill. I am tired of being disappointed by your lack of progress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172133" id2="17" version="1065353216">My son struck a killing blow against you. Had I not interfered, you would be dead. Perhaps I should have let you go then....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172134" id2="17" version="1065353216">Despite your precious warship, a legion of allies, and my immense power at your disposal, you remain... incomplete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172230" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no greater challenge than to change from within. But that is what we all must do to survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172231" id2="17" version="1065353216">On countless worlds I watched Jedi sacrifice themselves to delay inevitable defeat. We will not let you meet their fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172232" id2="17" version="1065353216">The most powerful among us couldn't stand against the endless legions of Zakuul. Even the Sith Empire learned that lesson too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172233" id2="17" version="1065353216">I went to Zakuul in secret to see the Eternal Throne myself. I still bear the scars of that journey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172234" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will not be enough to defeat Arcann. His Eternal Throne and the fleet it commands are the greatest threats our galaxy has ever faced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172235" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force is in motion, and we must follow. The old ways aren't enough. We'll show you the new way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arcann won't be conquered through passion, or righteousness. He has emptied himself of weaknesses like sentiment and morality.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your enemy stole his empire through deceit and murder. He's accustomed to the dark. You must strike where he's blind. From within.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172271" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith Code teaches us to break our chains. But freedom is not your ultimate goal. You must anchor yourself to power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172272" id2="17" version="1065353216">In life, I dismissed the Jedi Code. I was wrong. There is no death. There is only the Force. And it has a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172275" id2="17" version="1065353216">When Arcann lies defeated, your destiny is to take the Eternal Throne. Any other path will lead only into chaos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172276" id2="17" version="1065353216">The will of the Force is a flowing current. You can follow or fight it, but it is always there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you sense the predators closing in? They smell your weakness. They would feast on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176613" id2="17" version="1065353216">My son blindsided me because I allowed it. But you were weak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176614" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galaxy is finally united under a single banner. It should have been yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176615" id2="17" version="1065353216">The change Valkorion made within you is unprecedented. You'll never truly be Jedi or Sith. You stand outside the border separating light from dark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget what your old masters taught you. Not even Valkorion understands. The Force is not an ally, slave, or transaction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unlike us, you come to the Force as a blank slate. You have no codes to forget. You can accept the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176618" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force is a paradox. It empowers, and imprisons. It destroys and unites. It binds the galaxy together, and tears people apart. It has a will... but needs a commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1187748" id2="17" version="1065353216">For millennia, Jedi and Sith archived their knowledge in holocrons. These legacies preserve the wisdom of great minds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1187750" id2="17" version="1065353216">The focus was often on exploring mysteries of the Force, not the practical matters of government.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1187752" id2="17" version="1065353216">After all, Jedi do not seek to lead... and it is in the nature of Sith to force their wills upon others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1187754" id2="17" version="1065353216">But a few sought to understand what it truly means to lead a civilization. These are their teachings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1187756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only those connected to the Force may use these devices. Valkorion's influence has granted you limited access, but it will be enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1187758" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is wisdom in these holocrons for one who would create lasting change in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1187759" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have gathered great wisdom. Now, show me what you've learned and place the holocrons where they belong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1187760" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, you don't understand. Focus your mind, and try again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1187761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, that's correct. You're learning well. Press forward.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
