<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>16</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/ziost/class/sith_warrior/zujen_vale.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1084792" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many Sith are fueled by their passion for destruction. Why are you suddenly shying from violence?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1084792" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Sith avoiding a bloodbath?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1084793" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better if we fire Ziost's ion cannons. With them, we can disrupt enemy communications, cripple Apex Station and avoid a senseless bloodbath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1084794" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer bombardments with a more ravaging impact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1084794" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too merciful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1084795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Execute a dual strike, and we can knock out their shields with ion cannons before razing Apex Station with a missile bombardment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1084795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why not fire both weapons?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1084804" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, ion blasts will expose the Jedi to our direct attack. We'll tear them apart up close and personal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1084806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Missiles are direct, clean, guaranteed to maximize casualties and devastate defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1084807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing brings me more pleasure than butchering Jedi, my lord. I merely prefer to hobble them first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1084812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever your call, the weapon emplacements have been seized by Republic squads. Special forces--tough company, love knocking Imperial transports out of the sky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1084822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time's short, and Apex is too heavily shielded. Only a concentrated barrage will punch through their defenses fast enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1084836" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you reclaim our weaponry, I'll have Armageddon Battalion ready to charge before the final volley.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1100670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you crazy? That's the Emperor's Wrath!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1100672" id2="17" version="1065353216">My pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1100674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, we'll take our chances. He's holed up in Apex Station.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
