<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>44</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/02/ep_04/companion_exchanges.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208222" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the record, I wanted to go find you. Theron ordered me not to. I almost punched him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208223" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know better than to worry about me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208224" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who said I was worried? I just wanted to go for a nice walk with my favorite commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208228" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're all five by five, Commander. It's no Havoc Squad, but your people are good soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208229" id2="17" version="1065353216">I imagine you had it the easiest out there, with your experience.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208230" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not the first hostile landing zone I've been dropped in, but it's definitely the strangest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something about this place reminds me of training camp. The random drop zones, scattered resources, progressive enemy patrols...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208233" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think we're in some kind of simulation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208234" id2="17" version="1065353216">This weird little remote patched me up a couple of times. Everything else wanted me dead. Like I said... strange.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208239" id2="17" version="1065353216">I love it when you come back smelling like blood and ozone. Did you miss me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208240" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exploring would've been a lot more fun with you. I had to settle for the Mandalorian.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208241" id2="17" version="1065353216">Poor baby.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208245" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to your home away from home, Commander. Theron says you've been busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208247" id2="17" version="1065353216">So... how many Zakuulans did you get out there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208248" id2="17" version="1065353216">I forgot to count.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208249" id2="17" version="1065353216">I bagged twenty-six and a half. Wonder if whoever dumped us here noticed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208250" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe they're seeing who's stronger before they pick a side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208251" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or they just enjoy the show, like me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for the vote of confidence. You won't regret it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208261" id2="17" version="1065353216">You change your mind about things, I'll be here... trying not to get shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still sore from that punch you gave me. Now's probably not a good time to talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208270" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I could think about outside was finding you. I still don't understand how we wound up so far apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoever's doing this isolated us for a reason--but they could never separate us for long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208272" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got that right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad you're okay, Commander. I'm, uh, not much for talking right now. Jaw's a little sore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208280" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear Vette found something in that monument. She's waiting for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208283" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that you're here, I feel a lot better. We all do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208284" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seem to have done all right on your own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208285" id2="17" version="1065353216">This planet's no place to fly solo, I can tell you that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208287" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something happened on my way here. I met a Zakuulan naval officer from the Eternal Fleet. He wanted to surrender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208288" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't see him. What happened?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208289" id2="17" version="1065353216">Crazy droids attacked us. He tried to run, but they got him. I felt bad for the guy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208291" id2="17" version="1065353216">He told me everyone in the fleet is terrified of Vaylin. I don't think it'll take much to turn them against her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208296" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I woke up on this world and couldn't contact you... I've had too many awful moments like that, lately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208297" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss, Dromund Kaas, and now this place. We never seem to get a break.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208298" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remind me to schedule some personal time when we're home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208302" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander, I'm glad you're safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron thinks we're in a sanctuary, but I'm not convinced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208305" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's better than what's outside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly. The other structures were destroyed long ago, but this one's perfectly preserved--almost as if we're meant to take shelter in it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208307" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone brought us to this world. Until we know why, we can't take anything for granted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208308" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208311" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave the home improvements to me. You should find Vette.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1208314" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll secure this entrance while you check on the others.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
