<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>86</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/ord_mantell/class/smuggler/reki.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pardon me, but I have several young widows who require my immediate attention. Thank you for bringing those supplies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630651" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're certainly not a resident here, and you're no separatist. You must be that hotshot freighter captain Viidu described over the holo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630653" id2="17" version="1065353216">He didn't tell me how gorgeous you are. I find your people irresistibly charming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630655" id2="17" version="1065353216">He failed to express how beautiful you are, though. Color me impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630657" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm amazed you made it here in one piece. You must have a scoundrel's luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630659" id2="17" version="1065353216">These poor, starving ladies and I are very grateful for the supplies you've brought. If I wasn't so exhausted, I'd throw you a party.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630660" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need a party--just information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630660" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's really not necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630661" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. That's my main stock in trade these days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630663" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are all these women doing here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Starving ladies?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630664" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their husbands died defending Talloran against the separatists. Poor things. Now I look after them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Credits are better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, fine. I'm too tired to argue with you. I'll arrange for some credits to be transferred into your account.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Viidu said you're seeking information on a particular separatist named Skavak. The only place to find personnel data like that is at Mannett Point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630671" id2="17" version="1065353216">The separatists have a computer station on that island, but security there is rather insane. You'll want to use my lucky secret entrance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like the man says, it's better to be lucky than to be good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always pick luck over skill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630675" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer to be both, but to each their own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630677" id2="17" version="1065353216">And just how would you know about any hidden doors?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Secret entrance?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds pretty far-fetched.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630679" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand your skepticism, Captain, but I assure you it's entirely misplaced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630681" id2="17" version="1065353216">I used to acquire quality goods at a discount on Mannett Point. I discovered all manner of shortcuts through the island's warehouses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630683" id2="17" version="1065353216">I kept detailed schematics of every maintenance passage and tunnel there. Unfortunately, I had to abandon those schematics when I fled Mannett Point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lost schematics aren't exactly helpful, pal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then they're no good to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630685" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never said they were lost. I'm sure they're right where I left them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630687" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you know how to get them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630688" id2="17" version="1065353216">I always have a brilliant plan. It's why I'm still alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630690" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want your precious kit of supplies? Give me something useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630690" id2="17" version="1065353216">No schematics, no survival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630691" id2="17" version="1065353216">How could I refuse such a friendly bargain?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630693" id2="17" version="1065353216">My schematics are still in my former home. However, I short-circuited the building's door and sealed it shut when I left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630695" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only way to re-open the door is by disrupting Mannett Point's power relays.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630698" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's gotta be an easier way to get inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't I blast it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630699" id2="17" version="1065353216">I secured my home quite thoroughly against unwanted intruders. Criminals frighten me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630701" id2="17" version="1065353216">You expect me to run around separatist territory shutting down their power?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630701" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's crazy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630702" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never said this was going to be easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630705" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you think so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you gain entry, you'll find my schematics cleverly disguised as an extraordinarily tedious treatise on bird watching.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630709" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, I'll teach you the code I used to conceal my schematics. You won't die of boredom reading about rare waterfowl.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630712" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I do all this for nothing, I'll be back for you, pal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630712" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd better not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfectly understandable. I hope you'll at least be sporting and give me a head start.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630715" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630716" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teach me, already!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630717" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, Captain--you really must learn to slow down and enjoy life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now pay attention and listen carefully, because you really don't want to hear this twice....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630721" id2="17" version="1065353216">... and replace every mention of the Mantellian flutterplume with the number three. Did you get all that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630722" id2="17" version="1065353216">I nodded off once or twice there. You weren't kidding about the boredom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630722" id2="17" version="1065353216">More or less.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imagine how dull it was to write the blasted thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630725" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the most sadistic way to hide information I've ever heard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630725" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast, that was awful!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you clearly haven't lived enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't treat me like an idiot unless you want a face full of blaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630728" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not stupid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apologies, Captain. I was simply trying to spare you the agony of running all the way back here for another go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630731" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you read my schematics, the way into the separatist computer station will become clear. Unfortunately, that only solves half your problems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630733" id2="17" version="1065353216">The separatists encrypt all their files. You'll need special equipment to decipher their data. That's Viidu's area of expertise, not mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630736" id2="17" version="1065353216">How am I supposed to remember all these blasted instructions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630736" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is way too complicated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630737" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a clever sort. I'm confident you'll be just fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630739" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of gadget will decode those separatist files?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630739" id2="17" version="1065353216">Special equipment?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630740" id2="17" version="1065353216">At the very least, you're going to need a top-quality slicer kit. Viidu is probably your best bet for obtaining one of those.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630742" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate complications.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Try taking care of a half-dozen war widows sometime. It's a wonder I get any sleep. Not that I'm complaining, mind you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630745" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take those supplies now, if you don't mind. These poor ladies could use some cheering up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630746" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're sure you want to stay here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why not leave?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, I could never abandon these darling women. Whatever would they do without me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630749" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's disgusting how you take advantage of these women.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630749" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a pig, Reki.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630750" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you suppose the separatists would do to them without me around? I'm doing them a favor, trust me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630752" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be so quick to judge. These ladies adore me for a reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="630754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630755" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed it is. Life here may be perilous, but it has its benefits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630757" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck on Mannett Point. I suggest you plot your next move with Viidu before going there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enjoy your bonus with my compliments--it should arrive in your account shortly. Farewell, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be a sport and kill some separatists on your way out of here. Goodbye, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="630762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, we don't want any trouble. We're just trying to survive this siege.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
