<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>66</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/ord_mantell/class/smuggler/trymbo.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631161" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're not still carrying my chemicals, because that would mean you're dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631162" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't--don't stand there. That spot is reserved exclusively for my gundark friends. You're clearly not a gundark. Your ears are too small.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen, do you smell that? There's a pot of Alderaanian stew bubbling. But how could I smell it all the way on Ord Mantell?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Viidu sent me to pick up a canister of chemicals from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631165" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must be Trymbo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631166" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's a &quot;Viidu&quot;? Some kind of musical instrument? Is that what keeps playing that awful tune I can't get out of my head?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because you're nuts?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insane? What? How--how dare you--oh, now I'm smelling Bakuran cloudberries. By the stars, those--those would taste awful in an Alderaanian stew.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631171" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's quite a stench you've got going, crazy old man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631171" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I can smell is you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stench? Impossible. I bathe eight times a day. It's the only way to keep that invisible Kowakian monkey-lizard from drinking all my blood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm... I do recall a man saying to expect a stranger coming for my chemicals. You seem pretty strange. Was he talking about you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631175" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've inhaled a lot of chemicals, haven't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631175" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm the strange one?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did my wife tell you that? She's been dead twenty years now. Don't listen to her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why else would I be here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631179" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you been diagnosed with a terminal illness? Are you trying to avoid marrying someone? There are better ways to kill yourself, you know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631181" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just give me your chemicals before I shoot you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631181" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have time for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631182" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd be careful about firing a blaster in here. You'll wake the rancor, and he's very disagreeable when he hasn't had enough sleep.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631184" id2="17" version="1065353216">People haven't had much luck getting my chemicals. Know why? Those Ugnaught assassins in the woods attack everyone who visits me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugnaught assassins? Don't you mean separatists?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631185" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're very confused, pal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631186" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who do you think really controls the separatists? Those crafty little swine, that's who. But we can beat them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631188" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just hand that thing over, Captain Crazy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631188" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who cares, nutjob?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631189" id2="17" version="1065353216">How dare you--I'm a colonel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631191" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll just kill everyone who tries to stop me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631191" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm good in a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631192" id2="17" version="1065353216">That hasn't worked out well for the others who took on the Ugnaught assassins, but maybe you'll be the lucky one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631194" id2="17" version="1065353216">What you really need is a precision teleporter, but a former assistant crashed my prototype into the sun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631196" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck, my friend. If you should explode, please feel free to come back and tell me all about it. Everyone else has.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631198" id2="17" version="1065353216">I saw a herd of rancors advising the village mayor in the town square yesterday. They're very political beasts, those rancors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631201" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck delivering my canister of chemicals. Your only hope to avoid the Ugnaught assassins is that stealth field generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631202" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take a chemical canister from the storage unit and try not to explode. Good luck!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631203" id2="17" version="1065353216">Test out the stealth field generator, then take a chemical canister from my storage unit and run for your life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631205" id2="17" version="1065353216">When danger calls, I prefer to saunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631205" id2="17" version="1065353216">Running isn't my style.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631206" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been great, Trymbo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631207" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't take anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631208" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you activate the stealth field generator, you'll have to move slowly to avoid enemy detection. That's its only limitation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631209" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happens if I attack while I'm in a stealth field?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631209" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I fight?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any sort of violent movement disrupts the stealth field. So no fighting, running or improvisational dancing unless you really mean it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631212" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631213" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough babbling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631214" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's important to understand how to use the device. There's nothing worse than not being invisible when Ugnaught assassins are around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631216" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, here you go. Wait, those are my old suspenders. Don't worry, I know that stealth field generator is around here somewhere....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631218" id2="17" version="1065353216">One last thing: Don't sneak all the way to Fort Garnik. My formula turns explosive after a short time. Deliver it before that happens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631219" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631220" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the spirit. Look on the bright side--if you fail, you probably won't even realize it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631222" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Ugnaught assassins slow people down, and that makes my chemical canisters explode. Can you be invisible so the assassins won't see you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631223" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one will see me. I'll blend in with the shadows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631223" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, I'm stealthy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631224" id2="17" version="1065353216">No good. There aren't nearly enough shadows, and you can't trust them anyway. They move when you're not looking. You need technological assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631225" id2="17" version="1065353216">How much time do I have until the canister explodes?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631225" id2="17" version="1065353216">How long is that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631226" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a good question. I really ought to time it one of these days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631229" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to avoid them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631230" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, you must never trust them. They'll ply you with cheap Mandalorian wine and whisper sweet nothings while they stab you in the back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631232" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a stealth field generator that works like a charm. You just turn it on and &quot;poof&quot;! You're invisible. But there's a catch....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631233" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want credits for this thing, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631233" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's expensive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631234" id2="17" version="1065353216">Goodness, no! The belt is a gift, your highness. Please give the people of Alderaan my best when you get home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="631236" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not following any of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="631237" id2="17" version="1065353216">The stealth field generator bends light around its wearer so he can't be seen. Handy for escaping boring conversations, but there are limits.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
