<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>25</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/event/rakghoul/imperial/imperial_announcer.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123939" id2="17" version="1065353216">The spread of rakghoul plague on Tatooine has caused the Ministry of Logistics to place Mos Ila Spaceport under null-tolerance lockdown protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention: Travel to Tatooine is strictly banned by Imperial edict until the rakghoul outbreak has been contained.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention: Travel to Alderaan is strictly banned by Imperial edict until the rakghoul outbreak has been contained.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123943" id2="17" version="1065353216">All trade with the houses of Alderaan, including Thul and Panteer, has been placed on hold until the planet's rakghoul infestation has been suitably contained.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123944" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone suspected of illegally traveling from Alderaan is to be scrutinized for signs of rakghoul contamination and, if deemed appropriate, eliminated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those willing to risk everything to combat the plague on Alderaan should consult with a representative of the Hyland Organization for Rakghoul Neutralization onworld.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123946" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should the rakghoul problem grow out of hand, the Imperial First Fleet is preauthorized to commence full-scale orbital bombardment of Alderaan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123947" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone suspected of illegally traveling from Tatooine is to be scrutinized for signs of rakghoul contamination and, if deemed appropriate, eliminated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123948" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those willing to risk everything to combat the plague on Tatooine should consult with a representative of the Hyland Organization for Rakghoul Neutralization onworld.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should the rakghoul problem grow out of hand, the Imperial First Fleet is preauthorized to commence full-scale orbital bombardment of Tatooine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123950" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you are infected with the rakghoul plague, please arrange for your immediate incineration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123951" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remain vigilant during this rakghoul emergency. Use of lethal force against plague carriers is authorized and encouraged.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123952" id2="17" version="1065353216">Per Ministry of Biotic Science guidelines, airlock expulsion has been approved as an acceptable method of rakghoul-plague carrier disposal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123953" id2="17" version="1065353216">All citizens are required to seek out signs of genetic mutation due to rakghoul-plague exposure, and neutralize the afflicted as necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123954" id2="17" version="1065353216">THORN representatives tending to the rakghoul situation are in need of volunteers. Caution: in volunteering, you place both your life and citizenship at risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention: Travel to Quesh is strictly banned by Imperial edict until the rakghoul outbreak has been contained.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone suspected of illegally traveling from Quesh is to be scrutinized for signs of rakghoul contamination and, if deemed appropriate, eliminated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those willing to risk everything to combat the plague on Quesh should consult with a representative of the Hyland Organization for Rakghoul Neutralization onworld.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should the rakghoul problem grow out of hand, the Imperial First Fleet is preauthorized to commence full-scale orbital bombardment of Quesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123963" id2="17" version="1065353216">Despite rumors to the contrary, rakghouls are fully immune to the toxic atmosphere of Quesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention: Travel to Corellia is strictly banned by Imperial edict until the rakghoul outbreak has been contained.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone suspected of illegally traveling from Corellia is to be scrutinized for signs of rakghoul contamination and, if deemed appropriate, eliminated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123968" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those willing to risk everything to combat the plague on Corellia should consult with a representative of the Hyland Organization for Rakghoul Neutralization onworld.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should the rakghoul problem grow out of hand, the Imperial First Fleet is preauthorized to commence full-scale orbital bombardment of Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123971" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take note: the rakghoul outbreak poses more of a threat to Imperial interests on Corellia than those of the Republic.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
