<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>5</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/event/rakghoul/imperial/tunnel_mission_terminal.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1126873" id2="17" version="1065353216">THORN ASSISTANCE REQUEST
Rakling Collection

To eradicate the rakghoul plague, there is much that THORN still needs to fully understand about it. Research indicates that the packs of small rakghouls found underground called &quot;raklings&quot; are created as opposed to being turned individuals.

Injecting a pheromone catalyzer into fungal flora pods will attract any nearby raklings. The pheromone will then turn them docile enough to follow you for a time. The more raklings we can collect for study, the better chance we have of learning what purpose they serve in the rakghouls' strange underworld ecosystem.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1126874" id2="17" version="1065353216">THORN ASSISTANCE REQUEST
Rakghoul Mutagen Samples

THORN hopes to find a way to revert those turned into rakghouls to their original state. The key to infected individuals turning appears to be a mutagen produced by the rakghoul virus.

Samples of this mutagen can be found in the most recently infected and turning, who are located near The Spike's point of entry into the rakghoul tunnels.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1126875" id2="17" version="1065353216">THORN ASSISTANCE REQUEST
Skeletal Remnant Scans

No matter the planet, rakghoul populations consistently collect the remains of the deceased within their mysterious underground lairs. It is largely unclear to THORN researchers whether these remains belong to the turned, to victims, or to the already-deceased--or even why rakghouls collect these remains at all.

The more scans of skeletal remnants our researchers can assemble, the greater chance we stand of discerning a common thread among them, which in turn will help us better understand the rakghoul plague. A THORN medical scanner will be made available upon acceptance of this request for assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1126876" id2="17" version="1065353216">THORN ASSISTANCE REQUEST
Tunnel Navigation Analysis

Whenever The Spike plants itself into a rakghoul tunnel network, it fires beacons designed to seek out pockets of air deep within the bedrock with the intention of forming a navigational framework that THORN volunteers may use to help them combat the rakghoul plague where it lives.

For these beacons to be of any use, they must be individually scanned so that their data arrays may be analyzed and mapped by trained technicians. A THORN navigational beacon scanner will be made available upon acceptance of this request for assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1126877" id2="17" version="1065353216">THORN ASSISTANCE REQUEST
Rakghoul Fungal Specimens

THORN has uncovered in its study of rakghoul plague that striking similarities exist among rakghoul tunnel networks on planets where the plague is active. One such similarity, the recurrence of particular plant life, suggests a robust fungal signature exists within the rakghoul virus's genetic code. Access to samples of fungal growth found within the rakghoul tunnels could boost THORN's neutralization efforts greatly.

WARNING: The fungal specimens being sought are found at the epicenter of rakghoul activity. EXTREME CAUTION is advised.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
