<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>28</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/dromund_kaas/bronze/personal_challenge/vort_norman.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess I owe you that drink after all. Never thought I'd see Deth Kregg go down so easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Far as I've heard, Kregg's still out there. I'm interested to know how you plan to beat him.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681672" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you're the group that took over the Black Talon for Moff Kilran. Word travels fast in this sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681674" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wonder if you might be interested in a bigger challenge. Maybe put a few credits on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mandalorian named Kregg hunts the big game out in the jungles on the way to Kaas City, but he's gotten tired of sport-hunting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="681677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mandalorian?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="681678" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what's the challenge?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="681679" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should I be intimidated?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681680" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mandalorians are what you'd call a loose association of clans. Aliens, humans, bounty hunters, mercenaries. But we all got one thing in common.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681682" id2="17" version="1065353216">We fight to be strong. We fight for honor and glory. The bigger, smarter, faster the enemy, the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681684" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's why we're working with the Empire: for a crack at the Jedi. That's why Kregg went deeper into the jungle, why he's issued his challenge: defeat him, win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="681685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds wonderful.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681686" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know why, but I get the feeling Kregg's about to meet his match.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="681688" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mentioned a wager.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="681689" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not so sure about this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681690" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not afraid, are you? Well, maybe you should be. I've seen a lot of guys go into those jungles. Kregg's still out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681692" id2="17" version="1065353216">I said there was a wager. Everyone who tries puts a little money in the pot. Anyone defeats Kregg, they win it all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681694" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll warn you, though. Once saw Kregg rip the arms off a gundark bare-handed. 'Cause he got bored killing them with blasters. Best know what you're getting into.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="681695" id2="17" version="1065353216">For big credits? Sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="681696" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="681697" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never turn down a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681698" id2="17" version="1065353216">One more thing. Kregg's not alone out there. He's got more than a few followers. Strength attracts strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681700" id2="17" version="1065353216">You beat Kregg, and I'll send the credits your way. It might just cover your med bills. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunter. I've heard of you. You've been making a ruckus on Hutta.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Dromund Kaas, my lord. You need anything shot, stabbed, or otherwise crushed in a blaze of glory, you let me know.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well if it isn't one of the Empire's own. Pleasure to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681708" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wonder if you'd be interested in a challenge. Maybe a friendly wager.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="681710" id2="17" version="1065353216">You heard of Deth Kregg? Thinks he's the greatest warrior on Dromund Kaas.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
