<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>36</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/voss/bronze/republic/more_clever_than_youd_think/officer.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84841" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been underestimating the Gormak. They're more dangerous than we thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="84843" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found out what happened to the Voss. They were killed by beasts the Gormak modified with cybernetic technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84844" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cyber-beasts. Huh. I'd heard the Gormak had a way with technology, but I never imagined anything like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess this planet's full of surprises. I better file a report to my superiors. Thanks for looking into this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84850" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me know what you find when you investigate the wreckage of that walker.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Usser. Pleased to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84856" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to see a Jedi here. I'd heard rumors your order had reservations about the Voss. Understandable, I guess.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always nice to chat with a fellow soldier. I've been stationed on worse worlds, but this place can wear you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always good to speak with someone who believes in the Republic cause. Dealing with the Voss all day is exhausting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84862" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not that the Voss are bad people. Just a little... different. But they seem to like the Republic well enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="84863" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think they have a preference between us and the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="84863" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss are neutral.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Officially, that's true. But the Voss aren't so bad. A few of them even offered to help me out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="84866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting opinion.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84867" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss sound cold and aloof, but that doesn't mean they actually are. A few of them even offered to help me out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="84869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Getting the Voss to join us could be a key to defeating the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="84869" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to win them over.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84870" id2="17" version="1065353216">Truth is, I think they're already halfway there. A few of them even offered to help me out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84872" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's an old Republic walker out in the wilds. Left over from when we first came to visit.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84874" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss volunteered to investigate the wreckage for us. Only they never came back. Starting to think they walked into a trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="84875" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need the Voss to trust us. We can't be sending them off on missions where they never return!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="84875" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a diplomatic disaster!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84876" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't ask--they volunteered! Probably didn't want a bunch of outsiders tromping all over the place.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, the Voss did us a favor by investigating that walker. The least we can do is find out what happened to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="84879" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess you're right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="84880" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's going to cost you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell you what: Find out what happened to those Voss, and I'll find some credits to cover your &quot;expenses.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="84883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84884" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice. We'll never win the Voss over with that kind of attitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="84886" id2="17" version="1065353216">So do something about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84887" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't leave my post. Officially, I'm not even supposed to get involved. But I can't just ignore this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="84889" id2="17" version="1065353216">What can I do to help?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84890" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was hoping you'd say something like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84892" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss helped us out. Now we can return the favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's the location of the wreck. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="84898" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss claim to be neutral, but I think deep down they're actually on our side.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
