<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/war_world/quesh/bronze/republic/extracting_the_scientist/sis_chief.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70991" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've set the Imperial Quesh Venom project back months. I love it when everything works according to plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent Meldo's taken Doctor Orlian to one of our safe houses. The mission achieved one hundred percent objective completion, thanks to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70997" id2="17" version="1065353216">On behalf of the SIS, I officially offer my gratitude and appreciation for a job well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="70999" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's nice to know there's someone we can turn to when an op goes off the rails.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71003" id2="17" version="1065353216">I received Agent Meldo's report. You have to get Doctor Orlian out of there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71007" id2="17" version="1065353216">My mission's on hold until I find out what happened to my contact.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71011" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi. Excellent. I'm Senior Field Agent Suria with the SIS.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah. The famed captain of Havoc Squad. I'm Senior Field Agent Suria with the SIS.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain. I'm Senior Field Agent Suria. I understand you've done extensive work with the SIS.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71017" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Senior Field Agent Suria. I understand you've done extensive work with the SIS.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71019" id2="17" version="1065353216">An operation I'm overseeing has run into complications. Fortunately, requesting assistance from you falls within mission protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71020" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do the mission protocols have to do with asking me for help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71020" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean by that?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71021" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't ask someone for help if they don't meet proper security briefing clearance levels. Fortunately, you do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me what you need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71024" id2="17" version="1065353216">The SIS can't do anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71025" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our success ratio is exemplary. But you only hear about the missions that go wrong. Otherwise, it stays in-house.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71027" id2="17" version="1065353216">My current assignment is focused on Doctor Orlian--a key Imperial scientist from the Quesh venom processing lab. He wants to defect.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without him, their adrenal production operations will be crippled. Getting him to come over to the Republic is a huge win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71030" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is he defecting?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71031" id2="17" version="1065353216">What did you offer him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71031" id2="17" version="1065353216">How'd you win the doc over?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71032" id2="17" version="1065353216">The usual: asylum, credits, the chance to head a Republic research team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you trust him?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71035" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a reason we're taking this slow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't start patting yourself on the back too soon. He could change his mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71037" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's not here yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unlikely. We didn't just jump into this blind. We did all the appropriate background research.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71040" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have an undercover agent inside the Imperial facility. He's handling all the details of the op. But he missed his last two check-ins.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71042" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a delicate operation. I need to make contact to find out what's happening.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71043" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find him.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71044" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? No--you'll blow his cover! We need to be discreet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71046" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's your plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71047" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want you to knock out the Imperial facility's security stations, then go to this designated rendezvous point.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71049" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Agent Meldo hasn't been compromised, he'll follow mission protocols and meet you there. Get his report and bring it back to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="71051" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm busy. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. I'll find someone else. Just don't go blabbing this info to everyone you meet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="71056" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't talk now. I'm busy.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
