<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>102</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/world/imperial/the_hailstorm_brotherhood/captain_eth.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now if only you could do something about the weather....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Sav is dead. I found him in the ice fortress and cut him down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then the Brotherhood will be broken. Their cult of personality has lost its savior.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669020" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will contact Dorn Base to send supplies to us. It won't be long before we clear out the Brotherhood's remnants.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Sav is dead, and his successor is leaving for another planet. I trust this will help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669023" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are a drink of water to a dying man. Yes, yes, it will help us greatly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669025" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm contacting Dorn Base. They should be able to bring us supplies if the Brotherhood is truly leaving the mountain passes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669027" id2="17" version="1065353216">But Master Sav was just one of many. Soon we'll go after the big game: Boss Undro, Ellis Tarn and the other White Maw kingpins.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669028" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do I get in on this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sign me up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admiral Holtz is going to order an attack on key White Maw members, but I don't know when or how.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never heard of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669032" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's how they like it. Low profile. But Intelligence has worked up a list of their names. Admiral Holtz is going to order an attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669034" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got enough scars from your ideas. Don't try to rope me into more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669034" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've done enough for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669035" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, no, I'm barely involved. But Admiral Holtz is supposed to be putting together a final assault on key White Maw figures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fixer 308 at Zerek Outpost would have the details. The outpost's in the ship graveyard, prime White Maw turf.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669039" id2="17" version="1065353216">If anyone's come up with a way to hammer the pirates right off this rock, the Fixer would know. Give her a try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at the misery here. Then bring that misery to the Brotherhood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669042" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hailstorm Brotherhood make camp in an open-air fortress cut out of the ice not far from here. I guess caves were too easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669044" id2="17" version="1065353216">They obey what their beloved Master Sav tells them to. He's their legend, a man who can survive anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kill the head of their little personality cult, and the body will fall apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669047" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sorts of things has this &quot;master&quot; survived?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669047" id2="17" version="1065353216">How unkillable is Sav?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669048" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few poisoning attempts, walking on lava on Mustafar and fighting just about everybody on Hoth at one time or another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669050" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's got &quot;master&quot; in his name... is he on the Jedi Council, or is it just a nickname?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669050" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is Master Sav a Jedi?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669051" id2="17" version="1065353216">We assume he doesn't use the Force, or else he wouldn't be able to teach his skills to so many.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669053" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's tapped into something in the human body which makes him and his followers plenty dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669055" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you go into that ice fortress, don't give him any chances.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669056" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm up to the task.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669057" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you're taking on the right maniac. Sav's fought just about everyone and everything on Hoth at one time or another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669059" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even when his men were killed at the Battle of High Ridge, he lived in the snow, hunting wampas with a spear made from an icicle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three weeks later, he strolled back to the ice fortress, none the worse. So if you see him... don't give him any chances.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Criminals, no matter how hardy, will not defy our Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669062" id2="17" version="1065353216">As the Empire requires.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. Once he and his followers are scattered, we'll be able to get what we need shipped here from Dorn Base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669065" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until then, we'll hold out. There's no way this filth will win through attrition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669067" id2="17" version="1065353216">The more you talk about this guy, the higher the bounty gets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669067" id2="17" version="1065353216">He sounds expensive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669068" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I sent you in saying he was a soft target, chances are you wouldn't come back alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669070" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like killing cultists. It makes me feel like I'm tidying up the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669070" id2="17" version="1065353216">This ought to be fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669071" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. But I have one final request.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. Now to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Sav is responsible for this. For me, for my men.....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669078" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you kill him, you let him know what a mistake he made leaving me alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669081" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found the Hailstorm Brotherhood you spoke of. The pass is clear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that so? Glad to hear their bodies are finally getting colder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669084" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those maniacs have laughed at us for far too long. But here's something they don't know--we found out where they hide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669086" id2="17" version="1065353216">The sooner the Brotherhood loses some lives, the happier I'll be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please return to the medical bay. You may further injure yourself by walking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669089" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard you the first five times. Now be silent, I have an outpost to defend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669091" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, you made it past the pass in the mountains. I'm surprised the Hailstorm Brotherhood let anyone through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669092" id2="17" version="1065353216">You speak as if we are familiar. We aren't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669092" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669093" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry. It's just good to see a new Imperial face. Captain Eth, at your service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669095" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your old friend is alive and well. Hoth is turning our way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669095" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Revar says hello.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669096" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revar... it is too long since I've heard from him. Apparently not doing so well he could send a fighting force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669098" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was nothing special.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669099" id2="17" version="1065353216">Survival itself is to be celebrated around here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669101" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been cut off from the other outposts by the Hailstorm Brotherhood, a cult of madmen in the White Maw pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669103" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who's in this &quot;brotherhood,&quot; exactly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669103" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never heard of this bunch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669104" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're a cult within the White Maw pirates. Humans from some other ice planet that test themselves living in the cold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669106" id2="17" version="1065353216">They survive in the snow even better than the Talz, and they've cut us off from any hope of supplies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669108" id2="17" version="1065353216">You see this wound? Dressed it with seasonings from the rations when we ran out of kolto. In a few days, we'll be eating boot leather to survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669109" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no glory in dying. Can you make it back to another outpost?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669109" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should you retreat?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669110" id2="17" version="1065353216">No retreating. I've spent too long in this ice patch to be driven off by some half-dressed freaks. Besides, they'd track us and attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669112" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you going to take this indignity from a handful of pirates?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669112" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is intolerable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669113" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're weaker from hunger than I'd like to say. They're starving us out, and it's working.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669115" id2="17" version="1065353216">One defeat would be our last. What about you? Could you face them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669116" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we fight back?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669117" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a simple one, but those are the easiest to execute.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669119" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hailstorm Brotherhood are lying in wait in a pass between hills near here. You may be able to find them and wipe them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could you do this? Could you face the Brotherhood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669122" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will do more than face them. The snow will melt with their blood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669122" id2="17" version="1065353216">Easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669123" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes! Let not one of them stand, or crawl, or limp away. They will face retribution for those they have killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669125" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will break their ranks, and send them screaming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669125" id2="17" version="1065353216">It poses no difficulty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669126" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. Turn their ambush against them and cut them down as they flee.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669128" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've hired yourself a hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669128" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you pay, sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669129" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. We will see how they fare when someone else has the advantage of surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669131" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll never know what hit them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669131" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can and will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669132" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. Bleed them white so that any who find the bodies know the might of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669134" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669135" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every brother you can find, put in the ground. They may try to surround you, so watch out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669137" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then, when you have the bodies piled--ack! Curse it, another stitch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, I did say you need to be on bed rest....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669141" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well. The Brotherhood like to use downed speeders as bait. They should be easy enough to find. Good hunting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669143" id2="17" version="1065353216">If your men are too weak to fight, retreat is the only option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669143" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669144" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say what you will. I am not leaving until I impale these madmen on a spit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669146" id2="17" version="1065353216">My concern is with the Hailstorm Brotherhood.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
