<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>160</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x3/raid/terror_from_beyond/republic/major_cobus.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006874" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a gray nonagon that was. Here's hoping I don't live to see another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006875" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take that shuttle down to Asation. We're up to our eyeballs in blue scalenes and yellow spheres!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006878" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought we'd had it, Chancellor. That Trandoshan might as well have been made of durasteel, and that hypergate just kept spewing machines and beasties....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me, Major. Machines? Beasties? Perhaps you're not quite recovered from your exertions in the field.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's your handpicked squad now. Maybe they can explain it better than I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006884" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to take my word for it. Our Jedi friend can explain everything. I hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, Havoc Squad led the charge. Better let their commander brief you instead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like your privateer's found her way back. Maybe ask her what happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like your privateer's found his way back. Maybe ask him what happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome. I hear you're to be congratulated. Kephess is dead, the hypergate is closed, and our Gree allies on Asation are safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006893" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gree are too special to be wiped out by mindless beasts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to hear it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006894" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm pleased you think so. They seem to have taken quite a liking to you, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006896" id2="17" version="1065353216">I rarely get the chance to tackle such... unique challenges.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006896" id2="17" version="1065353216">I enjoyed myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006897" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm certain there will be others. The galaxy is a unique and dangerous place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006899" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ground's secure and the situation's normal. The Gree can handle things from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006899" id2="17" version="1065353216">Affirmative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you've been around the galaxy a few times, you learn how to handle the unexpected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006900" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006901" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still don't know what a green perpendicular is, but I think I killed a lot of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006901" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006902" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and me both, friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006904" id2="17" version="1065353216">The next time the Gree need help, maybe you should handpick someone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006904" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never doing that again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006905" id2="17" version="1065353216">Considering the outcome, I think my judgment was sound enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006907" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been in contact with Gatemaster Beltek'k. He's very grateful for your assistance and wants to present you with a reward. Of sorts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006908" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gree owe me nothing. Closing the hypergate helped us all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006908" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006909" id2="17" version="1065353216">You deserve this honor, Master Jedi. We couldn't have done it without you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please tell the gatemaster that I would be honored to accept.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006910" id2="17" version="1065353216">How kind of him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006911" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think he was going to take &quot;no&quot; for an answer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why not? I think my dress uniform's got room for another medal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our war against the Empire has only just begun. I'm certain there will be many more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to bring out some of that sweet, sweet Gree technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jackpot!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006915" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure how... material a reward they have in mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006916" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did the gatemaster say what this reward is, exactly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006916" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meaning what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006917" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major Cobus and I were unable to translate, but he seemed very enthusiastic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006918" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't take much more colorful geometry, Chancellor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006918" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I have to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006919" id2="17" version="1065353216">I insist. Victory over the Empire will depend on our alliance with the Gree--and whatever technology they are willing to share.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most agreeable salutations, Republic bisectors. From Crafter to Administrator, all castes are aware of Asation's perpetuation.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without rapid battle-aid-response, this would have been unattainable. What purple tangent your arrival has been!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006925" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must aggrandize you for your efforts. We have made a promulgation to all Gree: You are red rhombus. Felicitations!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006926" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was my pleasure, Gatemaster. I hope Asation will recover from this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006926" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006927" id2="17" version="1065353216">With further collaboration from our Republic bisectors, all will be orange sphere soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006929" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, Gatemaster. I'm not sure what that means... or how I should feel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Red rhombus?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be purple parallel, little sentient! You are absolute, unequaled, without defect!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006932" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. Purple perpendicular to you, too. Can I leave now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006932" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, brother.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006933" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is most complaisant of you to attempt Gree articulation. Your inaccuracies are delightful!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006935" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have never designated red rhombus without the Ritual of Blue Vertex. We will begin this observance now....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006937" id2="17" version="1065353216">...finally, white equilateral! We thank you for your allotment of minutes, Republic bisectors. Farewell, red rhombus!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006939" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should be honored. It doesn't translate well, but Gatemaster Beltek'k just gave you the highest title in Gree society.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006940" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm happy to help the Gree, red rhombus or not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still, not necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006941" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate the act, even if I didn't fully understand it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006941" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am honored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kind of glad they didn't put all that on a medal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pretty long title.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006943" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least I'll get free drinks in all the Gree cantinas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006943" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good enough for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006944" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will the Gree be able to protect Asation on their own?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006944" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happens now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006945" id2="17" version="1065353216">We won't leave the Gree to fend for themselves. We're allies for life now. That was the Republic's reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006947" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's twenty minutes of my life I'll never get back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006947" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was pointless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006948" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll note your distaste for honors and accolades in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006950" id2="17" version="1065353216">As long as we're handing out rewards, here's mine. Me and my boys never would have survived Asation if you hadn't shown up. Thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006952" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is in your debt as well. We may never know why Kephess opened the hypergate, or what the Dread Masters were planning, but you stopped them here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006954" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wherever the Dread Masters may strike next, I hope we can call on you again. Until then, safe travels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006956" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd better get down to the surface, and fast. My boys don't know a black bisector from a green perpendicular.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enemy's closing in, Major. This thing's huge! It's got five--no, six arms! How should we proceed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stand by, Sergeant. Gatemaster, that creature's wiped out six squads already. Give me something I can use!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006963" id2="17" version="1065353216">I regret I am not Warrior caste, Republic bisector. I am all yellow acute in this sphere. Perhaps additional bisectors?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006965" id2="17" version="1065353216">There you are! The Supreme Chancellor said she was sending help. Do you know what any of this crazy math means?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006966" id2="17" version="1065353216">He called you a bisector. Maybe you need to send reinforcements?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006966" id2="17" version="1065353216">More men, I think?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006967" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're my reinforcements. But we'll never get you down there in time--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your guess is as good as mine, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006969" id2="17" version="1065353216">No idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006970" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just... fall back! Retreat, Sergeant! Do you hear me? Retreat!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006972" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was told Major Cobus was cool and calm under pressure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006972" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're falling apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006973" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was cool and calm two weeks ago. Now I'm just trying to save my men--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006975" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's too late! They're everywhere now... we're being torn apart... ahh!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess that's as good a way as any to start this briefing. I'm Major Cobus, in command of Republic forces on Asation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006979" id2="17" version="1065353216">The planet's been overrun by nasty things I don't even have a name for. They're all coming out of this portal the Gree call a hypergate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006981" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Gatemaster Beltek'k. He was in charge of the hypergate before it opened up. I'll let him try and explain the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006982" id2="17" version="1065353216">The gatemaster and I can take it from here. Whatever &quot;it&quot; is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just relax, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006983" id2="17" version="1065353216">You Republic bisectors are so facilitating. I will attempt to be the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006985" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a hard time understanding the Gree language.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006985" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll try to listen.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006986" id2="17" version="1065353216">I beg atonement. We find our adaptation most purple--most preferable to your own. I will attempt clarity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006988" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm guessing &quot;gatemaster&quot; is more of an honorary title, then?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006988" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is his fault.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006989" id2="17" version="1065353216">You misunderstand, Republic bisector. I will elucidate matters now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since the hypergate opened, only hostiles have emerged. Some are sentient, some automatons. Many Gree and Republic bisectors have been terminated.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006993" id2="17" version="1065353216">My mortification is most acute. As gatemaster, defense of the hypergate is my first function. But I am Administrator caste--wholly unsuited to this task!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006994" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you did as well as any other Administrator could have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't blame yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006995" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are all blue obtuse, Republic bisector, but you do not comprehend our affliction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006997" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are these hypergates, exactly? What do they do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006997" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need more details.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006998" id2="17" version="1065353216">The hypergates were constructed by our progenitors. They allow immediate egress from one sphere to another, but not in reverse.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1007000" id2="17" version="1065353216">The origination point of the Asation hypergate is unknown. It must be a yellow sphere indeed, for it has caused much dissolution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't the Gree have soldiers or mercenaries or... anything?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007002" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right about that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1007003" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Warrior caste has never been required. The Crafters built military units instead--an imprudent resolution!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1007005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our military units are in disorder. They have rejected their directives and turned on their Operators. They were the only bisectors we possessed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1007007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, the hypergate will never be closed. Asation will grow barren. The green perpendiculars will spread, and all will be yellow concave!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007008" id2="17" version="1065353216">If a rogue droid army is the worst thing down there, we'll be fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007008" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1007009" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that were only truth, Republic bisector. These perpendiculars are unlike any we have seen before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you open the hypergate on purpose? Or was it an accident?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007011" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did this happen?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you shouldn't have relied on droids to protect you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007012" id2="17" version="1065353216">That'll teach you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1007013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even now, our Crafters are disassembling units. But this is yellow tangent.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1007015" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did not administer the hypergate's opening. The causation of this event was all white convex until the Republic bisectors' arrival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007017" id2="17" version="1065353216">We reviewed the Gree droids' security recordings. Kephess--our old Trandoshan friend from Denova--was lurking around the hypergate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Denova was intense. I can't believe he survived that fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not him again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007019" id2="17" version="1065353216">From what I hear, he had some help. Some pretty unnatural, disturbing help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007021" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't remember Kephess. Or Denova, for that matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007021" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who's Kephess?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mercenary. Republic hired him to protect our interests on Denova. Seemed to be working out, until he betrayed us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007024" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is Kephess hoping to achieve by attacking the Gree?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007024" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are his motives?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007025" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've fought one Trandoshan, you've fought them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007025" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not scared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not like Kephess. This one's got some new implants and some powerful friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kephess is working for the Dread Masters now--a group of rogue Sith trying to start their own Empire. Not sure how opening a hypergate helps.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1007030" id2="17" version="1065353216">The one you call Kephess is now perpendicular to the hypergate. He must be terminated, but we do not have bisectors capable of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007032" id2="17" version="1065353216">Neither do I. My last squad of bisectors just got eaten by a six-armed beast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007034" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Supreme Chancellor said you were the best. I hope she's right, because you're the only shot the Gree have left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007035" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't leave Asation until that hypergate is closed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007035" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't fail you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your men won't have died in vain. I promise you that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take heart, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just give me your orders, Major, and I'll move out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007038" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a great shot. A good-looking one, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007038" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's very right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isn't there anyone left on Asation who can help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007039" id2="17" version="1065353216">So no backup?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007040" id2="17" version="1065353216">If any of my men are still alive, they're just fighting to survive. You're on your own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to pick up the Republic's slack again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007042" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can see that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007043" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, I asked for the best. Next time I'll ask for someone nicer, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1007045" id2="17" version="1065353216">My expectations are heightened, Republic bisector. May there be infinite grey tangents along your path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007047" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a shuttle prepped and ready to take you to Asation. Here's hoping we find those grey tangents soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would someone please tell me what a grey nonagon is?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
