<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>52</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x3/raid/terror_from_beyond/republic/minister_sosa.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007050" id2="17" version="1065353216">Na-TaK tells me everything is orange parallel, thanks to you. That's good, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007051" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find Major Cobus with the fleet. I'm sure he'll know what the Gree need you to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Na-TaK is worried Asation will be yellow concave soon. Please, do what you can to help the Gree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007055" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic steward does not comprehend. This unit's makers require instant alleviation, or all is yellow concave!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007057" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, Na-TaK, try to calm down. I'm sure everything will be black and blue soon--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007059" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic steward is attempting verbal wordplay. This is most disproportionate at this interval!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007061" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Supreme Chancellor's squad! What luck--I was ready to send out messengers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi! If half the stories about you are true, the Gree have nothing to fear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007065" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi! It's an honor to meet the person who recruited the entire Rift Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major! I'm so glad you're here. See, Na-TaK? The Republic's finest, come to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain! Oh, thank goodness you're here. The SIS had given up tracking you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007071" id2="17" version="1065353216">Minister Sosa, special envoy to the Gree Enclave. We have a crisis that requires the Republic's immediate response. Supreme Chancellor Saresh recommended you by name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007072" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm honored to help the Republic in any crisis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007072" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever you need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever the situation, I'm certain we can resolve it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, calm yourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007074" id2="17" version="1065353216">An orange vertex is our immense desire, gentle sentient.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad is always ready and willing, ma'am.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007077" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can tell the Chancellor I've been dropping her name a lot, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007077" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's sweet of her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007078" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm... sure I will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007080" id2="17" version="1065353216">You had some trouble with your machinery on Coruscant, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007080" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gree sound familiar.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007081" id2="17" version="1065353216">All who serve the makers recollect you, black bisector. Coruscant is all orange parallel thanks to your purple vertex!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007083" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been in a lot of enclaves. Remind me which one is the Gree?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007083" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gree?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007084" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our very old and very advanced allies. They use Basic in terms that they understand. It's our job to try and keep up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your droid sounds a few bolts short of a motivator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007086" id2="17" version="1065353216">That droid is fried.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007087" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's how the Gree speak Basic. The colors and the geometry all mean something... I'm just not sure what.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007089" id2="17" version="1065353216">The trouble is on the Gree world of Asation. Their droid military forces have been overwhelmed. They say the jungles are full of... what did you call them, Na-TaK?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007091" id2="17" version="1065353216">Green perpendiculars. And blue scalene, and white convex--all is yellow concave if you do not accelerate!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007093" id2="17" version="1065353216">In any case, Major Cobus is in command. He's used to more... unorthodox missions, and he can explain further. Can I tell him to expect you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007094" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever's threatening the Gree, I'll put a stop to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007094" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can both relax.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007095" id2="17" version="1065353216">I look forward to hearing the major's explanations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007095" id2="17" version="1065353216">This should be interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007096" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's really the perfect officer for an operation like this. He even did a month-long tour with the Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007098" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell the major we're armed and ready for deployment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007098" id2="17" version="1065353216">On the double.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007099" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are truly advantageous to have such a bisector. I wish most purple tangent for you, sentient.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007101" id2="17" version="1065353216">What Na-TaK said, I'm sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007103" id2="17" version="1065353216">An unorthodox mission means an unorthodox reward, I hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007103" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the pay is good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007104" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will be compensated profusely, sentient. Gree technology is red equilateral!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007106" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not signing up for anything orange, yellow or otherwise until I know more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1007106" id2="17" version="1065353216">He better have answers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry. Integration with local military forces is the major's specialty. He'll explain everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007109" id2="17" version="1065353216">The shuttle can get you to the fleet, and from there to Major Cobus's ship. Good luck, and thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1007111" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too weird. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1007112" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, I don't have time to talk. I'm trying to figure out what it means to be white scalene....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
