<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>6</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/heroic_weekly/mission_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173171" id2="17" version="1065353216">Amille Razna has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Republic Resettlement Zone sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Amille Razna's message may be played from her droid G-5KN. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Volunteer Operation 78775-R

Objective: Warhead Retrieval
Contact: Major Teranos
Brief: One of our transports came under fire from Mandalorian raiders just after she broke Taris atmo. Cargo was class seven anti-ship warheads--all ejected safely. Can't say the same for the crew.

The Mandos are already headed for the warheads' landing site--need volunteers to intercept them and signal for pickup when the warheads are secure.

Anyone that gets it done gets double hazard pay. We ID'd the Mando commander as Duran Gorr--the guy takes down Jedi for his day job, so expect major opposition.

This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Reldar Kandik has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Brell Sediment sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Captain Reldar Kandik may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Private Selro has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Tularan Marsh sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Private Selro may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kord Murdok has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Tularan Marsh sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Kord Murdok may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Larris Cozekk has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Tularan Marsh sector of Taris. For additional details about the mission, Larris Cozekk may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
