<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>40</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/world/indelicate_operation/devon_race.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546502" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you, my friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to see you again. Incredible. You actually went through the ruins?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546505" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here it is--the history of the Jedi on Taris. Artifacts I don't even recognize. Exactly what we need to rebuild the order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546506" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wonderful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546507" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't know what this means. I'll get them back to the Masters unharmed, I swear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to my work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546510" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not one to argue. I couldn't have done it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546512" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll remember your help here. Thank you, my friend--thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546513" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546514" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a good deed done. But I can... compensate you somehow, if you like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, my friend. Thank you. And may the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546518" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi Enclave may be long gone, but we can hope they left something behind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546521" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a Jedi! It's--I didn't know anyone else was out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546523" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Devon Race, lady. I have permission from Master Silvarte to be on Taris--exploratory mission to the old Jedi Enclave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546524" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Devon Race, sir. I have permission from Master Silvarte to be on Taris--exploratory mission to the old Jedi Enclave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Officer! I'm--it's good to see someone else out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stand your ground! You're... hired help, with the reconstruction? Not a scavenger, I take it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546529" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Devon Race. The Jedi Masters gave me permission to come planetside--exploratory mission to the old Jedi Enclave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546530" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't heard anything about a &quot;Jedi Enclave.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi Enclave?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546531" id2="17" version="1065353216">You look hurt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546532" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a little scraped up, but I can keep going. I have a mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at you. I'm surprised a Master would let you wipe your own nose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stupid kid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at you. I'm surprised a Jedi would let you wipe your own nose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stupid kid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Begging your pardon, I've nearly finished my training.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Centuries back, the Jedi had an outpost on Taris. They left shortly before the world burned--I'm here to recover anything left behind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546540" id2="17" version="1065353216">But between the fauna and the looters, I haven't had much luck. We were hoping for holocrons, diaries--Jedi history! In truth, we knew it was a long shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546541" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you didn't think you'd find anything, why bother?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546541" id2="17" version="1065353216">So why come here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546542" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the order in disarray and the Coruscant temple lost, we need to tap every resource we can find. We're building a future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me join the search.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps. I am a bit... overwhelmed, and we need to find everything we can to help build a future for the order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546547" id2="17" version="1065353216">So who do you think will get you first? The rakghouls or the pirates?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546547" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're in over your head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546548" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't intend to die. Look, if you want to help, help. If you want to leave, leave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Silvarte warned me that any artifacts left behind would be hidden. Protected. Sealed in ferrocrete pillars or disguised as statues.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546552" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our tools are lightsabers and blasters. If you can cut away the outer layers, find anything from the enclave in these ruins... bring it to me. I'd be grateful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546554" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me. There are... creatures out there, and now really isn't a good time.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
