<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>49</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/rishi/hub_1/welcome_to_rishi/shared/kareena.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132255" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you find Kai Zykken, do me a favor--don't bring him here, okay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132257" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know, a few blaster marks is one thing, gives the place some charm. But this....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132258" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you heard Gorro before he died, you know I run the Howling Tempest Gang, and you know better than to cross me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132258" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Address cantina as a pirate]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132260" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone is about to tell me how everyone on Rishi seems to know I was on my way here. Who will it be?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132261" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen up: I'm here on official Imperial business. Interference of any sort will be considered an act of sedition, punishable by death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132261" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Address cantina as Imperial]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, with that in mind, who's ready to provide the name of anyone spreading lies about me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132264" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Address cantina as yourself]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen to me. I am the Emperor's Wrath. I am hate incarnate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132268" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to know who is claiming I'm some imbecilic pirate, and I want to know now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132270" id2="17" version="1065353216">You see before you a Dark Councilor of the Sith Empire. I should demand that you kneel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132272" id2="17" version="1065353216">Instead, all I ask is that you give me the information I seek. Who is responsible for this ludicrous charade?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alright, all you scum. You know who I am, and you know I can probably find a contract out on every last one of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132276" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just point me to the joker behind all this &quot;Howling Tempest&quot; junk and I won't go claiming any bounties. Fair enough?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132277" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone's talking about you. Couldn't tell you how it all got started, but I can tell you who gave Gorro the idea to come after you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't do it, Kareena. You know what Margok would say about ratting out a resident.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132281" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Margok ever pays the tab all you Nova Blades have run up, then maybe I'll start to care what he thinks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132283" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guy you want is Kai Zykken, leader of the Corellian Run Scoundrels. A real gem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132285" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gorro said Zykken owes you a pile of credits. He hired Gorro to take you out for a fraction of what it would cost to pay you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132286" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where do I find him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132287" id2="17" version="1065353216">Beats me. It's not like I hang out with the guy. Ask Zykken's crew--they're all over Raider's Cove. Like stink-flies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Others might not appreciate your cooperation, but I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132289" id2="17" version="1065353216">Figure it's either help out or have a bigger mess to clean up. I can handle the Nova Blades being sore with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132291" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for the tip. What are you doing later?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132291" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Maybe we can hang out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cleaning up this mess, serving drinks, getting two seconds' sleep, then serving some more. Sweet for asking, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132294" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to assume you're telling the truth. If I have to come back here, it won't be pleasant for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132294" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better not be lying....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132295" id2="17" version="1065353216">As opposed to all the pleasantness of this visit, right? Hey, I told you what I know. Best I can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132297" id2="17" version="1065353216">See ya, Gorro. Hope your brother doesn't decide this was my fault....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132301" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to the Blaster's Path. She's all mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugh... this is the worst mess yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134038" id2="17" version="1065353216">You... uh... you're not gonna eat him, are you? That's the last thing I need people hearing about my place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please listen to me: I am not a cannibal. I am not a pirate. I just came for information. I didn't want any of this to happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134039" id2="17" version="1065353216">No!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, well, Gorro did. When he sees... saw... a chance for blood, he always went for it. No talking him down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134041" id2="17" version="1065353216">The... uh... Red Hulls only eat people during raids. That's our code.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134041" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Pretend to be a pirate]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh... okay. Good to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134043" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know who told Gorro about me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134044" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are going to tell me exactly what I want to know. You won't use the words &quot;cannibal&quot; or &quot;pirate&quot; or any of that nonsense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1134044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut up and give me answers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who told Gorro about me? I want a name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kai Zykken. He's an idiot that runs one of the crews here in town.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gorro had just come from one of Zykken's sabacc games when he started talking you up. Had to be him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134051" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't let Zykken or his goons into my place--you'll have to find them out in town somewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134053" id2="17" version="1065353216">And watch out for Gorro's brother... he's a handful.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
