<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>63</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/rishi/hub_1/welcome_to_rishi/shared/qaraah.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kareena's charging three hundred for a holo of you taking it to Gorro. Three hundred! What a ripoff! Think I'll pay, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132165" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wanna see you fight Gorro--especially if someone gets tossed out a window. I love that!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132170" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132172" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rumors were true! You're here! You're really here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132173" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132174" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132175" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, sure. I've heard you described in great detail. Great detail!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132177" id2="17" version="1065353216">You run the Howling Tempest Gang! The most daring, ruthless pirates of the Gordian Reach--wherever that is!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132178" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know what you think you've heard, but you're mistaken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not even close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132179" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice try, but there's no mistaking the talk of the town!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132181" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a strange one. Can't say I've ever met an alien quite like you before....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132181" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132182" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Rishii. You wouldn't have met anyone like us on any other planet. That's what everyone in town says, anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132184" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right. What's it to you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132184" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll play along....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just like a pirate! You're all so touchy. I love it. You'll fit right in here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132187" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems like everyone in Raider's Cove is going on about you and all your insane adventures. Talk about your tough customers!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132188" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your Basic, it's very natural.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132189" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people pick up languages and stuff real easy. Some of us like to be formal. I'm more of a cantina-talk type.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132191" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speaking of cantinas, you'll wanna watch for Gorro. He wants to fight you so bad it's not even funny!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132192" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's a &quot;Gorro&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132192" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132193" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rodian. With the eyes and ears and the snout? He's a supreme... something-or-other. I forget. Really tough for his size.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132195" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wants to fight me? What did I do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132195" id2="17" version="1065353216">What for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132196" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd have to ask him. Considering what a big deal you are, it's probably just for bragging rights.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132198" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me where to find him. I'll see he gets what he's asking for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1132198" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132199" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gorro's at the Blaster's Path. Local watering hole. Probably washing down some tonitran jerky with some Mantellian fungolager.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1132201" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not allowed in there anymore--long story--so I hope someone holos your big fight. I wouldn't wanna miss a single, bloody shot!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh... uh... hello! You're from the Red Hulls, aren't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Raider's Cove! Nothing but fellow pirates here--you and your crew don't have to kill or maim or eat anyone! Right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kill or... what? Eat people? What are you talking about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133980" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's what you do, everyone knows! And it's no big deal! I'm sure those people your crew ate on Taloraan had it coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133982" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we're all friends here, right? No need for any massacres or cannibalism here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133983" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've mistaken me for someone else. I'm a Jedi--a peacekeeper. Not a killer or... cannibal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1133983" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not who you think I am.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133984" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I look like some cannibal space pirate to you? I'm a soldier for the Republic. You're confusing me for someone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1133984" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not who you think I am.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133985" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoa, whoa, whoa... take it easy, friend. Is this the face of some brutal killer or... person... eater?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1133985" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not who you think I am.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133987" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am a captain, but the rest you've got wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133988" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have to hide, everyone's heard of you. And no one is disgusted or terrified of what they've heard! Not at all!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh... except Gorro, I guess. He's been saying you'd show up, and that he'd love to take you on. But he doesn't speak for the rest of us!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh... as captain of the Red Hulls, I promise, no massacres or... cannibalism. Definitely no cannibalism.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1133991" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Pretend to be a pirate]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, that's a relief! After everything Gorro was saying about you, I mean....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133994" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's the one who said you were coming. He won't shut up about it. Said he really wants to take you on--I'm sure he's just bluffing, though!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133995" id2="17" version="1065353216">I might start doing one of those things if you don't give me some straight answers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1133995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut up and give me answers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh no! No, no, that won't be necessary! I can tell you whatever you need to know!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone told you I was coming--told you all these stories about me. Who was it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh... well... word's kind of been going around, but I heard it from Gorro. He told everyone that you were coming, even knew what you'd look like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134000" id2="17" version="1065353216">He said he was going to kill you as soon as he saw you. I'm sure he was just bluffing, though! You know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where can I find this &quot;Gorro&quot; person?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh... the cantina. Probably. He hangs out there a lot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134004" id2="17" version="1065353216">They serve good food there! No need to eat anyone!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134889" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh... have a nice day!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1151049" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Please note that by continuing this conversation, you are missing out on the Shadow of Revan Prelude.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1151051" id2="17" version="1065353216">[The Prelude introduces you to new allies, sends you on exciting story missions, and includes a cutscene with companions aboard your ship.]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1151052" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start Shadow of Revan Prelude]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1151053" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Continue this conversation]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
