<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>9</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x4/daily/belsavis/imperial/section_x/bounty_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059196" id2="17" version="1065353216">SECTION X TACTICAL DISPATCH / IMMEDIATE ACTION REQUIRED

Scouts have discovered Republic forces working to reactivate an ancient Rakata war droid in order to supplement their military strength. 

Preliminary scans indicate the droid's armor and shielding are all but immune to infantry small arms. Aerial strike is recommended, but Imperial starfighter resources are unavailable.

Recommend seizure of Republic targeting beacons and air strike authorization codes. Let our enemies destroy their own greatest weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059197" id2="17" version="1065353216">SECTION X TACTICAL UPDATE / TARGET DESTRUCTION CONFIRMED

With the Republic's droid reduced to smoking debris, our enemies' delusion of standing against us has been shattered. 

The whole of the Empire's might can now be focused toward obliterating the treasonous Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059199" id2="17" version="1065353216">SECTION X TACTICAL DISPATCH / IMMEDIATE ACTION REQUIRED

Scouts have located the Dread Guards' primary base of operations. Strange activities were observed inside that warrant urgent intervention.

Wounded Dread Guards are taken to the camp and placed inside &quot;energy tubes&quot; of unknown design. They emerged fully healed, far faster than any known treatment could account for.

This technology offers our enemies an unacceptable advantage. A task force is needed to raid the Dread Guard camp, eliminate all Dread Guard leadership present, and scan these &quot;energy tubes&quot; for analysis before destroying them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059200" id2="17" version="1065353216">SECTION X TACTICAL UPDATE / DATA RECEIVED

The raid on the Dread Guards' headquarters will drive their forces into confusion, giving our soldiers a much needed advantage.

Data from the strange &quot;energy tubes&quot; has been forwarded to the Science Bureau for investigation. If the design can be replicated, it could offer dramatic improvements to Imperial medical technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059202" id2="17" version="1065353216">SECTION X TACTICAL DISPATCH / IMMEDIATE ACTION REQUIRED

Gamorrean and Trandoshan warriors who had agreed to fight for the glory of the Empire are instead being captured and pressed into service by minions of the Dread Masters.

Our alien allies must be freed immediately, beginning with their clan leaders. They are held in a Dread Guard internment camp at the attached coordinates.

Enemy guards are numerous, but they should be carrying the shackle controls necessary to free the aliens and their leaders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059203" id2="17" version="1065353216">SECTION X TACTICAL UPDATE / RESCUE COMPLETE

All liberated Gamorrean and Trandoshan forces have reported to Imperial authorities for debriefing and preliminary assignments.

As they learn to embrace the superior tenets of our culture, our new allies are sure to battle fiercely on the Empire's behalf!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059205" id2="17" version="1065353216">SECTION X TACTICAL DISPATCH / IMMEDIATE ACTION REQUIRED

Minions of the Dread Masters are using an unknown mutagenic compound to transform local creatures into vicious beasts.

An Imperial lab researching counter-mutagens that would weaken the beasts has been overrun by enemy forces. Completing this research is of paramount importance.

Samples of the Dread Masters' beasts should be collected and inserted into the overrun lab's computers for analysis. If a counter-mutagen can be created, immediate field testing is requested.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059206" id2="17" version="1065353216">SECTION X TACTICAL UPDATE / EXPERIMENT SUCCESSFUL

The new counter-mutagen will allow Imperial forces to easily defeat the beasts employed by the Dread Masters' servants.

With much of their strength lost, our enemies will fall easily before us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062241" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Empire by completing the following daily missions in Section X on Belsavis:

[DAILY] Hyperbiology
[DAILY] March of the Dread Guard
[DAILY] Data Raid
[DAILY] Targeted Misfire
[HEROIC] The Aurora Cannon
[AREA] Lost Reconnaissance</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
