<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>46</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/world/imperial/revenge_of_the_bane_brigade/khun_tazith.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669360" id2="17" version="1065353216">The first member of the new Bane Brigade. It is my pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669361" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should speak, but not here--these meetings will draw suspicion. Return to the landing pad and I will contact you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever you do, whomever you kill, it will add to the legend of the Bane Brigade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669365" id2="17" version="1065353216">...if the Bane Brigade is alive, we need reinforcements on Hoth immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="669367" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they're alive, yes--but I saw them die years ago. No one survived that explosion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669369" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Bane Brigade destroyed my people's capital. We must know the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669371" id2="17" version="1065353216">We intercepted that holocall an hour ago. The Republic will soon send its elite troops into Clabburn Tundra, seeking the Bane Brigade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669373" id2="17" version="1065353216">There, our foot soldiers will set ambushes, collapse mountains... Clabburn is a natural death trap, and we need only sacrifice a few pawns to destroy the enemy's champions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669374" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see why you wanted to speak privately. The Bane Brigade is an illusion--the bait in your trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669374" id2="17" version="1065353216">So there is no Bane Brigade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669375" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was real once, but no more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669377" id2="17" version="1065353216">You talk about sacrificing Imperial troops... how many?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669377" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many Imperial casualties?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669378" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few thousand, perhaps. A few might dig out of the ice--that's not the delicate part.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669380" id2="17" version="1065353216">What makes you so sure the Republic will send anyone? Those generals didn't sound convinced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669380" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe the enemy won't come.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669381" id2="17" version="1065353216">A... delicate question.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669383" id2="17" version="1065353216">You see, the Republic was right to think the Bane Brigade destroyed; those men and women died heroes. Thus the secrecy, and your presence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669385" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must strike so fiercely, hurt the Republic so deeply, that they believe the Bane Brigade still lives. Only then will they commit their most elite forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669386" id2="17" version="1065353216">You spread the rumors, I convince the Republic they're true--and they come chasing ghosts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669386" id2="17" version="1065353216">We become the brigade. Clever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669387" id2="17" version="1065353216">What defeated the brigade?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669388" id2="17" version="1065353216">They attacked a Jedi encampment--slaughtered the lot, but they lingered too long and the Republic responded with an aerial strike. They deserved... better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669390" id2="17" version="1065353216">You told me the Bane Brigade was here. You told the troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669390" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been lying to everyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669391" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rumors must begin somewhere. Information leaks, after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669393" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will do tremendous deeds in the Bane Brigade's name, and only you and I shall know the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669395" id2="17" version="1065353216">And once you have finished, you shall leave Hoth and continue your work elsewhere--but the myth of the Bane Brigade will live on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669396" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will be the final chapter of the Bane Brigade's legend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669396" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will have your myth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legends and heroes are easy enough to manipulate. True power is rarely so blatant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Myths are my toys.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669398" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't agree more, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intelligence specializes in this sort of operation. I'll give the Republic whatever proof they require.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave it to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669401" id2="17" version="1065353216">I kill people so you can build someone else's myth? It's a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669401" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've taken stranger jobs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669402" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do I get in return?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669403" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you have no sense of duty, then I will open my vaults to you--I've developed quite a collection over the decades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669405" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry--I'm quite used to working with mercenaries, and I think you'll be pleased.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669407" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Republic must fear someone, let them fear me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669407" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather act in my own name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669408" id2="17" version="1065353216">In days to come, they may. But your name is not yet legend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669410" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can direct you to where your presence will be most impactful--soldiers who will show you the Republic's vulnerabilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669412" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the snow is hot with blood, leave the rest to me and the ghost of the Bane Brigade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669414" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please excuse me. I have a war to win.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
