<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>3</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/world/imperial/revenge_of_the_bane_brigade/khun_tazith_message.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="979792" id2="17" version="1065353216">ENCRYPTED MESSAGE BELOW:

My lord. Excuse the widely sent message but even my contacts had no knowledge of where you might be in the galaxy at any moment. We are attempting something unique and quite possibly revolutionary on Hoth, and your presence could make all the difference. Is it possible to destroy thousands of Republic troops and drain billions of their credits with minimal manpower? If it's the right manpower, I think it is. Meet with Captain Graich at Dorn Base on Hoth. He'll know how to get in touch. 

Yours respectfully,
Khun Tazith, Special Advisor to the Minister of War</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="979796" id2="17" version="1065353216">ENCRYPTED MESSAGE BELOW:

Agent. Excuse the widely sent message but even my contacts had no knowledge of where you might be in the galaxy at any moment. We are attempting something unique and quite possibly revolutionary on Hoth, and your presence could make all the difference. Is it possible to destroy thousands of Republic troops and drain billions of their credits with minimal manpower? If it's the right manpower, I think it is. Meet with Captain Graich at Dorn Base on Hoth. He'll know how to get in touch. 

Yours respectfully,
Khun Tazith, Special Advisor to the Minister of War</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="979804" id2="17" version="1065353216">ENCRYPTED MESSAGE BELOW:

Hunter. Excuse the widely sent message but even my contacts had no knowledge of where you might be in the galaxy at any moment. We are attempting something unique and quite possibly revolutionary on Hoth, and your presence could make all the difference. Is it possible to destroy thousands of Republic troops and drain billions of their credits with minimal firepower? If it's the right firepower, I think it is. Meet with Captain Graich at Dorn Base on Hoth. He'll know how to get in touch. 

Yours respectfully,
Khun Tazith, Special Advisor to the Minister of War</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
