<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>116</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/voss/world/republic/tip_of_the_spear/master_halykus.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Qualie sent word of the ancient ship. I congratulate you, friend, on doing what I could not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find Qualie at Pelath Point. Please. There may not be much time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571889" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've returned just in time. You did well, but the Gormak have outmaneuvered us. Outmaneuvered me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571891" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was focused on scattering their troops at the dam. So focused, that the Gormak managed to slip a small force past our scouts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are they planning another attack? Trying to escape?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571892" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are the Gormak up to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then let's go after them!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571894" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should have anticipated this!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why weren't you more vigilant?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571895" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aren't Jedi supposed to predict this kind of thing before it happens?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571895" id2="17" version="1065353216">You dropped the ball, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571896" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think I don't see my own failure?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571898" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak were seen carrying excavation equipment. If the Evuk-Nosk isn't near the dam, then... then they must have found its true location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is my anger at the Gormak still blinding me? Did I overlook something, just for a chance to attack them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anger is the hardest emotion to control, and you had good reason to feel it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571901" id2="17" version="1065353216">We aren't perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571902" id2="17" version="1065353216">You acted as a Jedi should. Don't condemn yourself for not being perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571902" id2="17" version="1065353216">You ask too much of yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571903" id2="17" version="1065353216">And yet if others suffer for my failings.... No. I will make this right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571905" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak got through. Why they got through isn't as important as stopping them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571905" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's focus on fixing this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. A disciplined mind is a powerful weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571908" id2="17" version="1065353216">You say that like feelings can be stuck in a bottle, or plotted on a graph.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571908" id2="17" version="1065353216">People are complicated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wisdom is found in the strangest places. Very well, let us make this right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571911" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Gormak have found their relic, we don't have much time to waste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571911" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going after the Gormak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571912" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need to snap out of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571913" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right. I cannot compound my failure by dwelling on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571915" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak have taken up position near Pelath Point. It's one of the surviving research camps, a neutral Voss outpost. My Padawan, Qualie, is there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571917" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trust her to help you find this Evuk-Nosk. More than I trust myself at the moment. Please, go quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571921" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must scatter the Gormak forces from the dam before they find what they're looking for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571924" id2="17" version="1065353216">The expedition passed on their thanks for your help. And your education in Findsman &quot;signs&quot; has proved useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571926" id2="17" version="1065353216">These discoveries complete a larger pattern. All these ruins explored or approached by the Gormak, belonged to the ancient Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even the ruins Padawan Kosh investigated were once besieged by them. Meaning, this Evuk-Nosk the Gormak seek must be a Sith relic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Allowing the Gormak to possess such a thing would be disastrous; for them, and for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we must find it quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any relic would have to date from the time these ruins were built, perhaps as much as a thousand years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571930" id2="17" version="1065353216">It must be truly ancient.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or longer. And we both know how many terrible things the ancient Sith created.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571933" id2="17" version="1065353216">With respect, Master Halykus, I'm a soldier. Handling Sith relics is better left to Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571933" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is beyond my training.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571934" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think of it as keeping a dangerous device out of enemy hands. That's certainly your jurisdiction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571936" id2="17" version="1065353216">The more I find out about this Evuk-Nosk thing, the less I want to go running after it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571936" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not liking this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Caution is often wise. But I must ask for your help again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571939" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only thing Gormak like more than abandoned technology, is abandoned technology that can kill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Likely a Sith weapon, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think what Gormak technicians could make from such a relic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571942" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd call that a stretch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571943" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could show you the correlations between months of our survey data, and what the Findsman taught you, but time is short.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571945" id2="17" version="1065353216">The main Gormak invasion force has been sighted. They've committed their forces to capturing a large Voss dam across the marches.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571947" id2="17" version="1065353216">This whole region was once covered by flood waters, driving the Gormak out. Now I fear they've discovered the Evuk-Nosk near the dam.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571948" id2="17" version="1065353216">Relic or not, if the Gormak have control of that dam, they can flood us out any time they want.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571948" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dam itself is a risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571949" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can stop them first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, I've come this far....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571951" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speak to our scout Beryl; he brought news of the dam's capture. Doctor Chull has also sent reports of Gormak stealing equipment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571953" id2="17" version="1065353216">More worryingly, another scout and a Voss commando were investigating Gormak movements. But only their astromech droid, T5-BD, has returned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those scouts must be found. The Gormak have caused enough suffering in this senseless rampage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571956" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see that the Gormak leave empty-handed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571956" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571957" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I didn't know better, I'd say that Gormak attack left you with more than just a scar.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571957" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really don't like Gormak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gormak are dangerous. Whatever my personal experience, ignoring that would be irresponsible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time for the Gormak to pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not be overcome by the need for battle. Do only what is necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571963" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you. The Evuk-Nosk cannot fall into Gormak hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wen and Padawan Kosh's investigations may lead us to this Evuk-Nosk. Not to mention the Findsman, if you can understand him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571970" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, friends. Though I'm afraid we can't offer hospitality for so many.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome. It's good to see another of the order, though we're in a poor state to greet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, friend. Though it's a poor welcome we can offer at the moment, I'm afraid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571976" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're facing a Gormak invasion. Their forces have destroyed every research camp between here and Pelath Point, and ransacked our equipment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571978" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've had my own clashes with the Gormak. But I've never seen them this relentless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571979" id2="17" version="1065353216">The lieutenant in Voss-Ka said you had a theory about why the Gormak are here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571979" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do the Gormak want?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571980" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force must have been with you, to survive such an attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571980" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is quite a scar.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571981" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak really did a number on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571981" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is quite a scar.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since then, I've tried to study the Gormak only from a distance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571984" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Gormak go on the offensive, they don't hold anything back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571984" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you haven't been looking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571985" id2="17" version="1065353216">We discovered that, centuries past, this entire region was Gormak territory. I believed their return was no coincidence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571987" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sent scouts to eavesdrop on the Gormak patrols. The Gormak are looking for something, left behind long ago. They call it the &quot;Evuk-Nosk.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knowing the Gormak, I imagine this isn't just some harmless cultural artifact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571988" id2="17" version="1065353216">That can't be good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps this is something the Voss have encountered, or heard stories of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do the Voss have any insights?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our Voss friends had no idea; and &quot;things of the Gormak&quot; don't interest them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571992" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I saw Evuk-Nosk do a set, at the Smiling Snivvian on Carratos--amazing vocals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a cantina band.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not now, friend. Too many have died.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571995" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is an Evuk-Nosk, and why is it worth bringing an army?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571995" id2="17" version="1065353216">The &quot;Evuk-Nosk&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571996" id2="17" version="1065353216">The meaning of the word has defeated our linguists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="571998" id2="17" version="1065353216">That means nothing to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571999" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak spoke of the Evuk-Nosk as capable of scorching the sky, and turning Voss-Ka to rubble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572001" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Evuk-Nosk would present a terrible danger in Gormak hands. We must discover what it is, and where, before they do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572002" id2="17" version="1065353216">They have an entire army to search with, not to mention any clues they brought with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572002" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak have a head start.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572003" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the Gormak have only recently returned. We've been working here for months.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave this to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572006" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know this area best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572007" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Evuk-Nosk is tied to this area's history, I would speak to the remaining members of the expedition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wen, a Jedi Knight, was looking for artifacts alongside the Voss. And Padawan Kosh--he and his Master were investigating a local Jedi ruin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572010" id2="17" version="1065353216">It sounds like we had a heavy investment in these excavations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was this a Jedi expedition?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572011" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi seem to have taken a large stake in these excavations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was this a Jedi expedition?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572012" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, we were simply... better equipped to defend ourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572014" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hardly a challenge, but fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, and a Gand Findsman came to the camp yesterday, offering his help against the Gormak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572018" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's rather... strange. But anything that helps us establish a pattern could be invaluable. Go safely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572022" id2="17" version="1065353216">These lands have so much potential. Perhaps once the Gormak are gone....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
