<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>91</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris_imp/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112547" id2="17" version="1065353216">This planet unnerves me. I sense such suffering here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112548" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never seen destruction on this scale before. It's almost beautiful. Like sculpture.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="112549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Death has been here. She is merciless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112550" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire really destroyed this place, huh. I mean, you'd think in a few centuries, the Republic would've rebuilt something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112551" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is what happens to a planet when the Empire's through. Something to think about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112552" id2="17" version="1065353216">Taris must have been glorious... a long time ago. We will dream of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112553" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never seen so much... destruction. Even on Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112554" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew some folks who were smuggling relics off this giant landfill... wonder if they bugged out yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112557" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch your step--one false move and you're going to need a major bath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112558" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should proceed cautiously--it would be difficult to plan a retreat from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="112559" id2="17" version="1065353216">More toxic chemicals for you to wade in, my master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112560" id2="17" version="1065353216">Junk looks caustic. Reminds me of this one Hutt who used to joke about teaching his enemies to swim. In acid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112561" id2="17" version="1065353216">Buddy of mine used to use chemical spills to punish people--he'd hang them upside down above a wreck, make them breathe the fumes. Kept them in line.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Death in water. It is an unfortunate thing to happen to a planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something tells me we don't want to go for a swim. I hope all the water here isn't that toxic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Care to take a dip? I'm sure a chemical peel would do wonders for your complexion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112567" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure hope this place is airtight--that gas cannot be healthy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112568" id2="17" version="1065353216">ChemWorks plant of some sort. Looks vile.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="112569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reminds me of the air on Urkupp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112570" id2="17" version="1065353216">Care to place a bet on whether that stuff's safe to breathe?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's not stick around, okay? I like my lungs the way they are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112572" id2="17" version="1065353216">We visited the industrial plants on Fest, once. The toxic zones were much like this; so many workers were sick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112573" id2="17" version="1065353216">This can't be healthy. I think my next investment is going to be a top-of-the-line rebreather.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112574" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know if this gas is poisonous, but I do know I'm never going to get the smell out of these clothes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112577" id2="17" version="1065353216">The skeleton of a rather large beast. Luckily, I believe it's extinct.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112578" id2="17" version="1065353216">This doesn't exactly make me feel welcome. But I suppose that is the intent.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="112579" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only bones. A shame. It's been too long since I've been tested.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112580" id2="17" version="1065353216">Big fella. I hope the Empire's bombs killed him and not something bigger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah... I've seen critters that big, giant things, and they don't live on a planet like this. They just... don't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112582" id2="17" version="1065353216">The nest can strip a creature that size down to bone in minutes. But it takes an entire nest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112583" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't think whatever owned those bones was alive when Taris fell, do you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, at least the wildlife is smaller these days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112587" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a sneaking suspicion we're going to be up to our necks in those rakghoul things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112588" id2="17" version="1065353216">I feel a strange kinship with these nekghouls. But it's still fun to watch them die.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="112589" id2="17" version="1065353216">These creatures taste of Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakghouls, nekghouls, whatever you call 'em, they still die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112591" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is that stink? That's not just rakghouls, that's gotta be something else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112592" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no natural life here. What we smell is... wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112593" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place is in pretty good shape... comparatively.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112594" id2="17" version="1065353216">I say we just cave in the entrance and call it a day, what do you say?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112597" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Endar Spire, my lord. The destruction of this ship was legendary. It set in motion the series of events that led to Darth Malak's bombardment of the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112598" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Endar Spire. I remember studying it in school. Those who didn't die in the crash were killed when Darth Malak destroyed the surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="112599" id2="17" version="1065353216">The great Tulak Hord once pulled a ship this size from the sky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112600" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Endar Spire! Ship's a legend. Mostly because the Empire shot it down, but still. Never thought I'd see it in person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bad way to die, crashing a ship into a planet. There're worse ways, though; suppose it doesn't hurt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112602" id2="17" version="1065353216">We recall that ship from the histories. A Republic vessel, brought down by Darth Malak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112603" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think that's the Endar Spire. It got shot down just before Taris got sacked. Can't think of any other ship it could be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112604" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's the Endar Spire. Lot of history attached to that ship. I've heard that if it had never been here, Taris would still be standing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112607" id2="17" version="1065353216">My father always said, &quot;Never bite off more than you can chew.&quot; Well, I like to think he would have, anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112608" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's humbling to know and hard to imagine that this place was once a bustling metropolis.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="112609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfinished or ruined, there is no difference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112610" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm guessing they started that before this place got blown to pieces. 'Cause this sure is a strange place to build a high-rise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some people can't take a lesson. You build something like that, you're asking to get it torn down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Strange, to see something new here. A flower blooming among metal skeletons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112613" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's all new construction over there. The Republic were really starting to make some progress. Shame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112614" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't see why the Republic bothered with all this construction. What's this place have to offer beyond a miserable life and a miserable death?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112617" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is an excellent staging site. Easily defended and built for quick mobilization.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112618" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a good day for a maiming. Let's get what we need here and move on to where the action is.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="112619" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire will overrun this planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't take long for the Empire to settle in, build a base, set up some really big guns. You guys really take your destruction seriously.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reporting in, sir! Rakghoul stole my helmet, sir, scared me white!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112622" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Diplomatic Service sometimes sends people to the front line to negotiate a surrender or a treaty. We always admire the soldiers stationed in places like these.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112623" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's already taken a base out here? They're really pushing hard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like this used to be a Republic outpost. The Imperials are really cleaning the place out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since it's just you and me, I can safely say, I don't like this &quot;attacking the Jedi&quot; one bit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112628" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time to spill Jedi blood. Look, I'm getting goose bumps.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="112629" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope there are many Jedi inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112630" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thought I was done seeing the insides of Republic spaceports a long time ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, this planet is a mess and I need a drink. Let's do what we have to and wrap this up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112632" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are deep within the hive of the enemy. We should be cautious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112633" id2="17" version="1065353216">This spaceport's the Republic's lifeline to Taris. It'll be where they make their last stand. Let's be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112634" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Empire's pushed the Republic all the way back to the spaceport, then they're on their last legs now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="112637" id2="17" version="1065353216">The guts of the dead city.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112638" id2="17" version="1065353216">Place has a creepy kind of vibe, huh. I mean, who knows what could've moved in here since the planet was destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Used to sneak around in the transport stations on Brentaal. High-traffic hours, you could really mess people up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112640" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are alien scents here. Beings not from Taris.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like some kind of transit system. I doubt it still functions, but it looks like it held up to the destruction pretty well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like a train station, or something. Is it too much to hope we can catch a ride?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I ever mention I have a fear of dying from radiation exposure?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112646" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is our only lead for finding General Frellka. I hope Lieutenant Pierce's intel is reliable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023203" id2="17" version="1065353216">Appraisal: This is what a planetary liquidation looks like. The Maker was busy here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023206" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warning: The acid levels of this lake are corrosive to my servomotors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023209" id2="17" version="1065353216">Testimonial: It is places like this where I most appreciate my lack of olfactory sensors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023212" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis: Whatever this beast was, it has been thoroughly liquidated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023215" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speculation: If I were a rakghoul, I might make a nest here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023218" id2="17" version="1065353216">Information: This is the fabled Republic warship &quot;Endar Spire.&quot; Fame notwithstanding, it is mostly scrap metal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023221" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observation: Look, master--another failed Republic effort. They truly never learn, hmm?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023224" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prediction: All Republic undesirables on Taris will be fully liquidated within ten standard weeks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023227" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anticipation: I can almost smell the undesirables, master. Let's hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023230" id2="17" version="1065353216">Statement: It's some sort of mass transit network that survived destruction. Perhaps we can rectify that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023724" id2="17" version="1065353216">Praise: The undesirables picked an especially clever hiding spot. All this radiation interferes with my sensors.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
