<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>8</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/generic/breadcrumbs/story_mission_breadcrumb.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1190705" id2="17" version="1065353216">INCOMING DATA STREAM... DESCRAMBLING REPUBLIC COMMUNIQUE... Supreme Chancellor Saresh requests an urgent meeting with you via secure channel. Timing is critical--proceed to your starship's mission console at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1190706" id2="17" version="1065353216">DECODING IMPERIAL FREQUENCY... TRANSMITTING MESSAGE TEXT... Your assistance is urgently needed on the planet Makeb. Mission details will arrive at the mission console aboard your personal starship. Proceed there immediately for further information.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1190709" id2="17" version="1065353216">OFFICIAL REPUBLIC COMMUNICATION... YOUR EYES ONLY... DECRYPTING... The time has come to strike a decisive blow against Imperial leadership. SIS reports indicate your participation is critical to mission success. Proceed to Carrick Station and contact astromech droid designated T3-G2 for further details. Discretion is essential.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1190710" id2="17" version="1065353216">INCOMING IMPERIAL TRANSMISSION... RECIPIENT CONFIRMED... DESCRAMBLING... The Jedi Order has committed a grave error, and the time has come to strike. In recognition of your past victories, you will lead this assault. Proceed to Vaiken Spacedock and locate astromech droid A7-M1. Make sure you are not followed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1190713" id2="17" version="1065353216">EMERGENCY PRIORITY MESSAGE... All available Republic field operatives are needed for a Code Omega crisis event in the Ziost system. Details are available at the mission console aboard your starship. Please respond immediately!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1190714" id2="17" version="1065353216">INCOMING CRITICAL ALERT... All loyal servants of the Empire must defend our gateway planet of Ziost immediately. Mission details will be provided at your starship's mission console. Proceed there at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1190717" id2="17" version="1065353216">INCOMING MESSAGE FROM SUPREME CHANCELLOR SARESH... The Sith Emperor remains at large and even his own people want him dead. A joint task force has formed to end this threat for good. I want you representing Republic interests. Proceed to your starship's mission console to join the hunt.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1190718" id2="17" version="1065353216">DECODING PRIORITY SIGNAL FROM DARTH MARR... Emperor Vitiate escaped Ziost, and we must hunt him down before he destroys another of our worlds. The threat he poses is greater than the war between Republic and Empire. I will accept any aid to eliminate this threat forever. Contact my flagship from your starship's mission console and join the task force.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
