<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>149</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/manaan/imperial/lana_beniko.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125032" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome. So good to see you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125034" id2="17" version="1065353216">As implied in our last, brief communication, Darth Arkous is at the center of a grand conspiracy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, I have disturbing news. My suspicions about Darth Arkous's motivations on Tython and Korriban have been confirmed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125309" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arkous had the Jedi Temple raided to acquire knowledge of Rakata technology that he could use to harm the Empire. Even now, he plots against us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arkous is a fool to think he has the power to fight the Empire. This plot will end badly for him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'll stop him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125311" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree, Lord Wrath, but we must remain vigilant all the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125313" id2="17" version="1065353216">And he calls himself my equal? Darth Arkous tarnishes the entire Dark Council with this treachery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125313" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's pathetic and unworthy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125314" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know, Dark Lord--and for having played my part in serving him, I apologize.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125316" id2="17" version="1065353216">There a price on his head yet, or what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does this make him a bounty?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125317" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is still just between us, Hunter. No one else in the Empire knows what we do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125319" id2="17" version="1065353216">A secret conspiracy? I have some measure of expertise in that area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125319" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is right up my alley.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, Commander. A blessing you're here. I'll admit I'm a bit out of my depth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125322" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know Arkous was a mentor to you. This can't be easy to take.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125322" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're okay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125323" id2="17" version="1065353216">He had me fooled for some time, but I see his true face now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125325" id2="17" version="1065353216">What can you tell me about this tech?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing, I'm afraid. He smartly kept the details hidden from me, but we're very close to the truth now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125328" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've followed Arkous to a secure undersea laboratory here on Manaan, where he's working with a Selkath geneticist on... something. I've been trying to learn more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125330" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've also discovered that Colonel Darok secured passage to the same laboratory. He was behind the Republic's raid on Korriban.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125331" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seems to me that Arkous and Darok are working together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125331" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125332" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's my feeling as well, but we won't know for certain unless we get into that laboratory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dark Council members make for attractive targets. This Darok might be ending the Arkous problem for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darok may be after Arkous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125335" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you say, he's our problem, meaning we need to resolve it ourselves. We must confront Arkous in that laboratory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125337" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm guessing you have a theory as to why.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125337" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's your take on that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125338" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a hunch. Until we learn what's happening inside the genetics lab, I'd rather not jump to conclusions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125340" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I said, it's a well-protected facility. You'll have to make your way through heavily armed Selkath and dismantle their security grid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125341" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not coming?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125342" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd intended to confront Darth Arkous myself, but I sense a presence here--a potential ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125344" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll remain in touch and let you know how my search progresses. May the Force be at your service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back. Once again, you've displayed a skill and determination that few possess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125437" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps I should make proper introductions....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125441" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to tell me who I'm addressing. I'm Theron Shan--Republic SIS, and your new ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125442" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not presume to choose who I align myself with, nor allow them to address me as their equal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125445" id2="17" version="1065353216">First Arkous starts working with a pawn of the Republic, and now you expect me to do the same?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125446" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're supposed to go ahead and trust this guy? He's a spy. Said it himself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125447" id2="17" version="1065353216">So I'm to trust this man based on your word? He's a professional liar; I should know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125448" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fully understand your reluctance, but please--allow us to explain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125450" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Care to defect, Shan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125451" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Lana vouches for you, I'll let that be enough--for now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Strange, but... okay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fair enough, Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fair enough, bounty hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fair enough... Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125458" id2="17" version="1065353216">The way we were fooled by Darth Arkous--the same happened to Theron, except with the colonel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125460" id2="17" version="1065353216">And between what you found down in that lab, and what Lana and I pieced together, I can tell you they're both traitors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arkous and Darok are in league with a dangerous movement: a shadowy cult known as the Order of Revan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125463" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Order of Revan's no secret to me--I had a run-in with them on Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125463" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125464" id2="17" version="1065353216">In an earlier incarnation, perhaps. They seem to have grown strong, and bold. Very bold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125466" id2="17" version="1065353216">Secret or not, I feel I should've heard of this order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125466" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bring me up to speed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125467" id2="17" version="1065353216">They follow the teachings of Revan--a former Sith Lord who later became a Jedi knight, in case you didn't know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan is no longer among the living. I made sure of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan's dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every indication is that Revan died. Surely, he's not in control of the order that bears his name...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is Revan behind this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125471" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not Revan himself, but those who follow his doctrine we're concerned with. They seem to have grown rather bold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125473" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they're a danger, they should be stamped out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's destroy them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125474" id2="17" version="1065353216">You underestimate the devotion that Revan's life and teachings have inspired.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125476" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Order of Revan used to operate in the shadows of Imperial space, but now their ranks include at least one major Republic figure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125478" id2="17" version="1065353216">That means I can't trust my people, and Lana can't trust hers--present company excluded. And if the Revanites are building an army of cyborgs....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125817" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was about to send out a search party.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry. I had to confirm some things before coming to see you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125820" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I suspected, the Order of Revan as it once existed is no more. A bit of a shame, really.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125822" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Revanites' pragmatism may have been anathema to the Sith, but there was something appealing about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125823" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Emperor wanted a pragmatic Empire, that's how it would be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their ways are irrelevant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fair enough, but we are still capable of independent thought--even you, Wrath. But this is all pointless conjecture.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125826" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Revanites had their way, they would supplant the Dark Council, filling the Empire with feeble Jedi notions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125826" id2="17" version="1065353216">You speak heresy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125827" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did not mean to suggest I advocated your ouster, Dark Lord. Regardless, it's entirely academic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think I'd get more work from the Empire with the Revanites in charge, or less?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever makes me money....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125830" id2="17" version="1065353216">They would take less kindly to you, but only a little. Not that we'll ever find out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125832" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd much rather do without mysterious enclaves and secret orders, thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cults make my job a pain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125833" id2="17" version="1065353216">They are good for job security, if nothing else. But if they get their way, you won't have a job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125835" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should know that I was made a Revanite.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125835" id2="17" version="1065353216">They inducted me once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125836" id2="17" version="1065353216">After crossing Darth Arkous, I doubt your membership stands. Not that the Revanites of now resemble the group as you understood it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you trying to tell me you see yourself as half Jedi?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125838" id2="17" version="1065353216">How so?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125839" id2="17" version="1065353216">I may not take a title, but I am Sith. I'm simply open to possibilities. The Revanites aren't one of them, though--not anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sign me up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not everything is so clear-cut as dark side or light side. They may be onto something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125844" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing wrong with being practically minded. Maybe they're not so bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125845" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm with you on the sentiment, but I wouldn't be so quick to subscribe to their ideologies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125847" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Order of Revan, as it stands now, doesn't wish to change the Empire from within. It aims to destroy us completely, and the Republic along with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125849" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've not yet learned why or how, but Theron Shan might. He appears to be rather good at his job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125850" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're on the verge of giving me a complex. Are you suggesting Shan's better than me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125850" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I'm not?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125851" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would never dream of it, Commander. I only mean to say that he'll make a fine ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125853" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't trust him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125855" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you know what you're doing, working with the enemy like this. An SIS operative, no less.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125856" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guy's a Republic spy. We shouldn't take anything he says at face value.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125857" id2="17" version="1065353216">After what Arkous has done--after betraying me, the Empire--I'm not eager to trust anyone. I still believe Theron Shan will make a fine ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125859" id2="17" version="1065353216">With ears in both camps, we'll be better off against whatever threat the Revanites pose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teaming with him was smart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125860" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you feel that way. I admit I was concerned you wouldn't take to the idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125862" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good at his job or not, he's not bad to look at.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125862" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's quite attractive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, he does have a certain way about him....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125865" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so. I've been too preoccupied by our state of affairs to notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was there anything else you wanted to discuss?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125868" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Wookiee smuggler and his droid--how do they fit in?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will Jakarro be of use?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125869" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not entirely clear to me, but Jakarro will prove useful to us. That much I sense unmistakably.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125871" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do we know about Colonel Darok?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about Darok.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like Arkous, Darok held a great deal of sway. With the two of them combined, there's no telling how many are secretly working for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125874" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should get to my investigation. Whatever Arkous's Revanites and their Infinite Army has in store for the galaxy, it can't be good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125876" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force ever serve you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125877" id2="17" version="1065353216">That time we spoke after reclaiming Korriban, I thought we shared something. A connection. Was I wrong?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125877" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] What about us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125878" id2="17" version="1065353216">After what you just said about Theron Shan, I thought maybe you'd moved on. But no. You aren't wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125879" id2="17" version="1065353216">You also admitted an attraction to him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125880" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suspected you might be trying to tweak me. I suppose I tweaked back. No hard feelings, I hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125881" id2="17" version="1065353216">You aren't wrong. I wasn't sure if I should bring it up now, but... I've missed you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125882" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I'm starting to warm up to you, Lana.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1125882" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Yes--you and me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that right? You should know that the feeling's mutual.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125885" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have to go now. There's much yet to uncover about the Revanites' plans--and the formation of this Infinite Army of theirs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125887" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be thinking of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125891" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you'd like to join the Empire, I could put in a word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125892" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could always join the Empire. I think you'd make a welcome asset.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125893" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm oddly flattered. Not even going to consider it, of course, but flattered.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1125896" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not care about any of this! I want revenge on the Pub and the Imp who left me to die--twice!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125897" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Jakarro.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125898" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I am Ceetoo Deefour, former translator to Her Imminence, Queen Lina of Onderon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, Jakarro--how would you feel about helping me track those two down?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1125902" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can help. I have many contacts all over the galaxy. But I do the driving!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125904" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll talk about it. Lana, will you be joining us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125906" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't yet know how deep the Revanites' influence runs. I must learn what I can from within the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125908" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done well here, as expected. We'll speak again soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1126276" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakata technology?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126278" id2="17" version="1065353216">What can you tell me about this technology?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our work here is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126750" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force ever serve you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126751" id2="17" version="1065353216">We cannot let Darth Arkous pursue his betrayal of the Empire.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
