<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>59</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/world/republic/the_stasis_generator/general_skylast.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine work out there. That stasis generator is completely totaled--no use to the Esh-kha now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706321" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hate to target our own infrastructure, but it had to be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thing you caught onto their plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could have been worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank the Rakata for that. Heck of a surveillance system they built here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706325" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about other generators? This can't have been the only one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706325" id2="17" version="1065353216">This could happen again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706326" id2="17" version="1065353216">You gave those Esh-kha an awfully good licking back there. I doubt they're anxious for another dose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706328" id2="17" version="1065353216">We finished?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706331" id2="17" version="1065353216">I actually had a chance to watch your scuffle over the monitors--you took down those Esh-kha like a pro.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for the help. Skylast out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706335" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Esh-kha manage to steal that generator, it'll mean some long and tortured lives for me and my men.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706336" id2="17" version="1065353216">--should be getting a clear image now, sir--uh, hold on. Is... someone using the terminal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impossible. That whole sector's... well, shut my mouth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706340" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Skylast here. Surprised to see people still alive at that station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Skylast here. Nice to see you again. Can't say I expected to find you at that tech station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi--General Skylast, Republic Infantry. Could use your help containing a class-A security breech in your sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706350" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is General Skylast. You're with SpecOps, aren't you? We've got a class-A security breech in your sector and could use another blaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706352" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Skylast here. Didn't expect I'd find anyone at that station--anyone alive, that is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surveillance just picked up a team of Esh-kha commandos uncoupling one of the prison stasis generators. Looks like they mean to steal it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706355" id2="17" version="1065353216">How'd you even know to contact us here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706355" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is... unexpected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706356" id2="17" version="1065353216">How'd you even know to find me here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706356" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is... unexpected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706357" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coincidence. We were trying to access that tech station's monitor systems. Wanted a better handle on the situation down there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706359" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's a stasis generator?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stasis generators?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706360" id2="17" version="1065353216">These generators must be important if the Esh-kha are interested.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706360" id2="17" version="1065353216">That can't be good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got that right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706363" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those generators are a technological souvenir from the prison's Rakata builders. Kept the nastiest inmates in stasis--inmates like the Esh-kha.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706365" id2="17" version="1065353216">The technology isn't just for pacifying criminals. Those fields will immobilize just about anything--even an entire battalion. We're talking permanent suspension here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706366" id2="17" version="1065353216">An eternity of imprisonment... I can't even imagine what that would be like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706366" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds dreadful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706367" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Esh-kha know better than anyone. Probably why they want that tech so bad--it's poetic justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706369" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't let the Esh-kha get their hands on that kind of technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706369" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep it safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706370" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad you think so. Our best option is to destroy the generator so the Esh-kha can't use it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706372" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the Republic's just been sitting on this technology?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why aren't we using it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706373" id2="17" version="1065353216">All the prime Rakata technology was sealed away in the vaults, but we didn't dare open them. The Imperials didn't share our reservations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706375" id2="17" version="1065353216">Allowing the Esh-kha to access that kind of hardware is like giving a rancor a missile launcher--just making a bad situation worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706377" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have time for anything fancy. I just need you to scrap that generator before the Esh-kha get ahold of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706378" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those monsters will have to get through me if they want that generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706378" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706379" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let anyone unleash such a weapon on the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706379" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706380" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few well-placed explosives will keep that tech out of enemy hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706380" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave it to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706381" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only thing the Esh-kha are gonna get their hands on is the underside of my boot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706381" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave it to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706382" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sure hope so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706384" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't you do it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706385" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our troops can't even access that part of the prison, let alone defend it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706387" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Esh-kha have sent their best on this one. They've had thousands of years to mull this operation over, so stay sharp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706389" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop the Esh-kha and disable that generator beyond repair. Contact me when it's done. Skylast out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="706391" id2="17" version="1065353216">No deal. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="706392" id2="17" version="1065353216">Might change your tune if the Esh-kha ever get their hands on you.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
