<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>178</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/world/republic/allied_forces/lieutenant_kieral.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668677" id2="17" version="1065353216">We managed to raze the base. They're sending resupply convoys now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668680" id2="17" version="1065353216">Move a muscle, Captain Biron, and you will be shot. Take his weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668682" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this how the Republic treats its allies? You have more in common with the Sith than you realize.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668684" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had no knowledge of this plan, Captain, but once begun, it would be suicide not to follow it through in all its aspects.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668685" id2="17" version="1065353216">I initiated the plan. It was self-preservation. You would have betrayed us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668685" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another captain, perhaps. I had no such intentions, nor the manpower to do so effectively.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Katcho remembers you as a treacherous snake, Biron. Remember him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Credit our Sergeant Katcho.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, so this is petty revenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668691" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's more about not taking chances with dangerous opponents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668693" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dangerous. You tell yourself that. You honor nothing and reward betrayers, just as the Sith do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668695" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take him away. And gag him so he can't listen to the sound of his own voice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668697" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's only complaining because he couldn't betray us first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668697" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no sympathy for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Betray you? What good would that have done us? Another costly fight when we're at less than half strength?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your words mean little at the moment, prisoner. Take him away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668702" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was unpleasant. I never got the impression he was as sadistic as the other Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668703" id2="17" version="1065353216">He would have turned on you in a second.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Believe it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668704" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is one thing to know that intellectually, and another to believe it with the whole heart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668706" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we have defeated the Hailstorm Brotherhood today and acquired a valuable Imperial captive. It's hard to be sour with that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668708" id2="17" version="1065353216">I delivered both the Hailstorm Brotherhood and the Imperials to you in one move. Appreciate it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668708" id2="17" version="1065353216">We won. Be happy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668709" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed, thank you. Using our valuable captive, we can force concessions from the Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668711" id2="17" version="1065353216">He seemed genuine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668711" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm having second thoughts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668712" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry about him now. When we get information out of him, he'll be traded back to his people soon enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668714" id2="17" version="1065353216">And with the casualties we inflicted on Biron's soldiers, his outpost is ready to be taken. This is quite a day for the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668716" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard about the situation over the comm. Master Sav is dead and half the Brotherhood tried to flee by jumping off the cliff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668718" id2="17" version="1065353216">A well-executed plan. Of course, the irony is that with the Brotherhood gone, we'll be free to focus our tactics on one another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668720" id2="17" version="1065353216">What would you suggest, Lieutenant? A twenty-four-hour truce as we return to our outposts?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668722" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could grant that when it involves my men. I cannot, of course, speak for others. What do you think?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668723" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you ever need to defect, you know who to call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668724" id2="17" version="1065353216">A fine compliment--but after today's negotiations, I will likely be watched carefully.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, you risked much by coming here, Captain. If only more Imperials were like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668728" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's got twenty-three hours and fifty-nine minutes to go. Get moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time's wasting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Point taken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668731" id2="17" version="1065353216">I look forward to never seeing him again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668731" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get him out of here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668732" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes... the feeling is mutual.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668734" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell, Captain Biron. If only there could be more Imperials like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful what you wish for, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well. The day's not over yet, and already you brought about the end of the Hailstorm Brotherhood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668740" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a bigger war out there on the ice, and for once, the Imperials aren't the worst of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just point me to where I can help. I'm getting used to the cold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then where's the big fight?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668742" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never thought we'd see the day the Imperials were second on the list.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668742" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pirates are really worse?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me neither.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668745" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm here for my own reasons, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668745" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got things to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood. But there's a lot of good you could do out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668748" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admiral Revald commands the Republic fleet on Hoth. From the surface, no less. He's fighting tooth and nail with the White Maw leaders every day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668750" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can do for him what you did for us, the White Maw could be a thing of the past. And we would all sleep easier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major Vinson at Cresh Base has been sending us messages on the priority frequency, but they're too garbled to decode.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668753" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd swing by there in case it's a real emergency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668754" id2="17" version="1065353216">We lost contact with Aurek Base. If they've been offline this long, I can only imagine they'd need help worse than we did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well. The Hailstorm Brotherhood's come to an end, and we have no other crisis breathing down our necks. I almost feel relaxed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668758" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been an honor to serve with you. Be careful out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our scouts say the Brotherhood is bandaging up. We need to hit them now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668760" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the remainder of their force is grouping at the ice fortress, they've been badly hurt. It's time to finish them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668762" id2="17" version="1065353216">The captain's right. We're not going to get this chance again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668763" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not giving this group a centimeter of purchase. They're all going down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668764" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668765" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. Our priority target is Master Sav. A cult without its beloved leader is a beast without its head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668767" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like the idea of taking out every last one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668767" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't butcher.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668768" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree, it's not practical. We should aim to stop Master Sav. Without his leadership, the cult would be a disorganized mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668770" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sav is a legend among the Brotherhood. We stranded him in the snow once and left him for dead in wampa country.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668772" id2="17" version="1065353216">He strangled one with a tauntaun femur and skinned it with its own claws. He showed up in the ice fortress weeks later, quite alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Getting rid of him sounds like a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take out the leader. Got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668774" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't give him a chance. Now what do I have to do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668774" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talk about the mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668775" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll need you to spearhead the team eliminating Master Sav--others will secure the turrets and the perimeter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668777" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ice fortress will be swarming with Brotherhood. We'll have the teams meet up again in the audience hall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668779" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll remember that story next time I'm a wampa.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668779" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a stupid story.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668780" id2="17" version="1065353216">The point is, Master Sav is not to be underestimated. We'll need you spearheading the attack on him while we secure the fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668782" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will split into multiple squads, then meet up again in the audience hall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be warned, the hall is a defensible area--they'll move the big guns there once they know we're attacking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668785" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get them out of commission so the rest of the men can work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668785" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll remove them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hiding behind their hardware will not avail them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Faith in weapons won't help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just in case, you'll have backup. Meet up inside with Sergeant Ennlicher and Sergeant Katcho.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing like artillery to get the blood pumping.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668789" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668790" id2="17" version="1065353216">With all of us coming down on them, they're in for some bad times.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668790" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't stand a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Undoubtedly. Meet with Sergeants Katcho and Ennlicher inside the fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668793" id2="17" version="1065353216">Done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668794" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. We'll monitor the situation from here. Meet up inside with Sergeant Katcho and Sergeant Ennlicher.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their men will reinforce you as you push to the audience hall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668798" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I end up as a pair of smoking boots, I'd just like to say, &quot;I told you so.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668798" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's never easy, is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668799" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be backed up by Sergeant Katcho's men and Sergeant Ennlicher's from the Imperial side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668801" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they can't get you to Master Sav in one piece, no one can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go quickly. Let's not give them time to get back on their feet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668805" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did it! I haven't seen that many dead Brotherhood since we first came to the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. It was efficacious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668809" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll assume that was the Imperial equivalent of enthusiasm, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668811" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was. My scouts are in pursuit of the fleeing Brotherhood now. We'll see what they find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now is not the time to underestimate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wise plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668813" id2="17" version="1065353216">My thoughts exactly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668815" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're on the run. What could your troops possibly learn?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668815" id2="17" version="1065353216">An empty gesture.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668816" id2="17" version="1065353216">We know we hurt them; the question is, is it enough to prevent future attacks?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668818" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the follow-up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668819" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now we maintain our truce until we determine if our knockout blow was delivered. My scouts should report in at any moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Snow Raptor, this is Hatchling. Come in, Snow Raptor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go ahead, Hatchling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668825" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've spotted the remainder of the enemy force entering the ice fortress. Coordinates attached.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get that flare flying. We'll see if the Imperials pick up their end of the bargain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668828" id2="17" version="1065353216">I conferred with every man in the platoon. Even if we sent everyone we have, we couldn't strike the Brotherhood effectively.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you see my point. A combined operation might have a chance--you didn't say you had visitors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668832" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you doing here? We haven't seen a new face in weeks. How did you make it past the Hailstorm raiders?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who is this and why isn't he in chains?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668833" id2="17" version="1065353216">You first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668834" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no idea who you're talking about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make it past who?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you are lucky not to have encountered them in the passes. The Brotherhood are White Maw pirates, the worst of the lot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668837" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's an Imperial doing here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Biron is here attempting to solve a mutual problem--a group of White Maw pirates called the Hailstorm Brotherhood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668840" id2="17" version="1065353216">They are savages, frankly. Cultists and marauders from some other ice planet that came to Hoth to test their limits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668842" id2="17" version="1065353216">They hunt and murder those who cannot survive in the cold as they do. Republic and Imperials alike.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668843" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you came to talk, talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then say your piece, Imperial.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668844" id2="17" version="1065353216">My men are in the same situation as Lieutenant Kieral's; cut off with no resupply possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668847" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Brotherhood don't dare attack us in our outposts, but they're devastating to anyone out on the ice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668849" id2="17" version="1065353216">That means our supply convoys are constantly being intercepted. It won't be long before they starve us out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Biron came with an offer--that we join forces long enough to defeat the Brotherhood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure we can trust him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668852" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's too convenient.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668853" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you thinking? Nobody's worse than the Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get rid of him!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668854" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take that as a compliment. But the Hailstorm Brotherhood have proven otherwise, with acts too depraved to list.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668856" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Brotherhood have cut our outposts' resupply lines and are picking off anyone that ventures into the snow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668858" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we don't join forces, they'll whittle us down until we leave our outposts in search of food. Then we die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668859" id2="17" version="1065353216">How does that compare to being betrayed at some critical point by the enemy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial &quot;help&quot; is no better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without help, our deaths are a certainty. Anything is better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668862" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like it, but I gather neither of you do, either. What's our plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668862" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668863" id2="17" version="1065353216">What we need is for someone to bait a trap. If we fire a distress flare out on the ice, the Brotherhood will come running to attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668865" id2="17" version="1065353216">When that happens, my squad can surround them and wipe them out. All the bait would need to do is last until they arrive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668866" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Brotherhood will find I am not easily overcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668866" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668867" id2="17" version="1065353216">They rely on surprise and savagery. Without the former, they can be killed like any other barbarians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668869" id2="17" version="1065353216">If these fanatics are truly such a plague, I will stop them however I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668869" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will do this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668870" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your valor is appreciated, Master Jedi. It takes a strong heart to volunteer for such a duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668872" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it. But make sure you show up fast. I work quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668872" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be your bait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668873" id2="17" version="1065353216">I serve with disciplined men. We will be on time, no sooner, no later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668875" id2="17" version="1065353216">Feels a little like pushing me overboard and saying all I have to do is swim.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668875" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is nuts, but I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668876" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hadn't thought of you volunteering, but we welcome the help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have no fear. My men are eager for payback. When the Brotherhood comes, the Empire will be hot on their heels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then it's agreed. Here is the distress flare and directions. Find a good, vulnerable-looking spot in the snow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668882" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd better show up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668883" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assure you, if I wanted to ambush the Republic, I've already had plenty of opportunity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's the distress flare. Fire once if all is as planned, twice if the Imperial help isn't enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668887" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck out there. The Brotherhood knows that ice better than their own backsides.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668889" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not fond of this &quot;get myself surrounded by Imperials&quot; plan. And you shouldn't be, either.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668889" id2="17" version="1065353216">No way. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I suggest you leave, Captain Biron. Your welcome is wearing thin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Allow me to stay and make my case, Lieutenant. It would be my shame if the Brotherhood took your head simply because I argued poorly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668893" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials have tricked us too many times for me to fall for this one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668893" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a trap. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then our options are limited. We shall see how long we can last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668897" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's alright. He's with me.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
