<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>19</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_13/scene_00_lana_theron.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still no word from Major Jorgan or Kaliyo?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything within a kilometer of the Spire has been locked-down. No signal gets in or out of that zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196401" id2="17" version="1065353216">I warned you that GEMINI frequency mission was dangerous. If they're alive, it won't be for much longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196402" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gravestone could take the enemy by surprise. Buy me enough time to get our people out of the Spire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1196402" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should go extract them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196403" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoa, whoa, whoa. We can't throw the Gravestone into the fire unless we know they're alive to rescue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196405" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too much remains unknown--and the enemy has had time to prepare its defense. We cannot risk any rescue operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196407" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't be certain of anything. If they're safe, they'll contact us. If not... Arcann will make a public spectacle of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1196407" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't know that, Senya.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196408" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't say I'd feel too bad about losing Kaliyo, but Jorgan's a good man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regardless, any rescue attempt on our part would be suicide. Their fates are in their hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196412" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they're dead, so be it. We still need to sabotage the Eternal Fleet, and the GEMINI frequency is our best chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1196412" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our goal can't die with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196413" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't get anywhere near the Spire without fighting every defender on Zakuul. We don't have the forces for that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196415" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's always another way. We'll find it. Destiny's on our side, remember?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destiny must wait for the proper time. Now's not it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196419" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll alert you the moment I hear anything, but until then... we're just wasting time here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196421" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could all use a break to regroup. That includes you, Theron.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196649" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm too tired to argue. Oh, almost forgot--Hylo Visz asked to see you, Commander. Wouldn't say why, but it sounded important.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
