<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>73</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_13/scene_10_gault.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, there's nothing like coming home from a job well done. Especially when you've ruined a huge jerk's day in the process.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Couldn't agree more. Come to think of it, our plan was lacking in one department.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192470" id2="17" version="1065353216">An actual escape route?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192472" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was the scenic route. Can't argue with the view.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192474" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, the one thing missing was a way to see the look on Arcann's face when he got the news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192475" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope it has an effect on more than his ego.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1192475" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not so important.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192476" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't expect an overnight collapse, but when his highness's checks start bouncing, it'll shake things up. Count on that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192478" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a pretty big oversight, Gault. It's coming out of your cut.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1192478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Crying shame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's not get carried away, we're talking a fringe benefit at best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192481" id2="17" version="1065353216">He doesn't have much of a face anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1192481" id2="17" version="1065353216">To hell with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, it's probably better in my imagination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, how about we get on with my favorite part and divvy up the loot?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192486" id2="17" version="1065353216">This money isn't ours. I don't mind taking it from Arcann, but I want nothing to do with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192488" id2="17" version="1065353216">It does feel wrong to keep it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our goal was to fund the Alliance, not personal gain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who says it can't be both? You just need a little ambition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192532" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll give you rundown of the books as soon as we've got real numbers to work with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192536" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd like to distribute our surplus back to the worlds Arcann plundered. I don't care how.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1192536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Return it to the people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192537" id2="17" version="1065353216">A fruitless gesture. That wealth will return to the Eternal Empire so long as they remain in power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192539" id2="17" version="1065353216">People are suffering out there. What are we doing if not trying to help them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192541" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you are confused, our objective is not to alleviate suffering. It is removing the Eternal Empire from power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192543" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's the right thing to do. I gladly give it up to help atone for my part in taking it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192545" id2="17" version="1065353216">A sentimental decision. Flawed and foolish. Ultimately we will regret it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192547" id2="17" version="1065353216">No fools in accounting and no accounting for fools.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192552" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand you decision, Commander. I only ask that you not lose sight of the bigger picture while serving your ambition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192554" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, more shares for you, am I right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192558" id2="17" version="1065353216">This stuff sells for more than most freighters. Grab some glasses and get to know what success tastes like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Already taken care of. You, Vette, and Dretcher are already paid out. I took the liberty of skimming what you still owe me off yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take all the fun out of it why don't you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your idea of fun is why your divvying privileges are still revoked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193926" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seconded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, I only ever cheated you before we started working together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just what did you do, exactly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ran out on me with the biggest score of our careers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193932" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I regretted it ever since. Well, after the shine wore off. A little older, a little wiser, you know? Okay--maybe a lot older. It was a formative moment!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193934" id2="17" version="1065353216">The point is we're on to bigger and better things. Like melting a mint down into an ocean of liquid happiness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, however you want to spend your cut is none of my business, but if you want to say, triple it, I might have a little something in the works.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193938" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or, you know, you could try giving. Maybe just once, see what you've been missing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193940" id2="17" version="1065353216">My share's going toward buying back some of the artifacts stolen from my people, freeing slaves... giving Twi'leks a better place in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Honestly, we've got way more than we need for operations. It'd be good to have a plan for the excess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193943" id2="17" version="1065353216">Start putting together a plan to expand. Every credit we have needs to go towards overthrowing Arcann.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1193943" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep it in the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193944" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make sure the ends justify the means.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193946" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're in no position to be proud. Necessity will ask us to consider much worse before this is all done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193948" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wasted opportunity, chum, but I won't fault you for playing it safe under the circumstances.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193949" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not going to pass up an opportunity to triple our take, just keep an eye on that investment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1193949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give Gault what he needs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, don't worry, I'll make sure he coughs up every last credit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193952" id2="17" version="1065353216">I kinda thought the point of this &quot;alliance&quot; was to do some good in the galaxy, but I guess I'm not really surprised. Everybody's got an angle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193967" id2="17" version="1065353216">It appears our business is concluded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193968" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, I don't know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193970" id2="17" version="1065353216">It looks like we're settled up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193971" id2="17" version="1065353216">I figure you'll be seeing me around. You've got a handy little outfit here. Besides, I wouldn't want Hylo to get lonely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193973" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph, as if.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193975" id2="17" version="1065353216">If your Alliance happens to need a morale officer, I'm game. Kicking Arcann's butt should require a full-time party planner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speaking of parties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1193978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right now, I think we've earned a long night of not thinking about tomorrow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander... Major Jorgan and Kaliyo just landed. They're in the docking bay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196423" id2="17" version="1065353216">So much for celebrating. Go ahead. We'll be right behind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196671" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll start with her fingertips and work my way up. Take one knuckle at a time... then her hands....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you remember Mother? Not what she is now. When we were children.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196675" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remember her telling Father I was dangerous. How I had to be controlled. She always hated me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196677" id2="17" version="1065353216">She never understood us. Or Father.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196679" id2="17" version="1065353216">She helped the Outlander steal our pretties. They took everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those things can be replaced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196683" id2="17" version="1065353216">When all the worlds we've conquered find out what's happened, they'll think we're weak. Test us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196685" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remain the greatest power the galaxy has ever seen. My enemies know what I'll do to them if they cross me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196687" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fear is always free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1196689" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will be generous with it.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
