<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_13/scene_03_gault_forger.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189697" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not ready yet! Just tell me when we have to do this and I'll... come out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, come on! That's not how this was supposed to go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still can't roll with the punches. You perfectionist types never learn--there's no such thing as a &quot;sure thing.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189712" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are we trying to recruit someone who wants to kill you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1189712" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is pointless, Gault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because Dretcher's literally the only one I trust to pull this off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189717" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's the one with the grudge! After I made that body double he went and swindled half of Nar Shaddaa, in my name!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189719" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's taken everything I know to stay hidden in this little prison. Every time I start to think I can leave, someone snitches on my new identities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gault....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189721" id2="17" version="1065353216">That true?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189722" id2="17" version="1065353216">So maybe I encouraged Dretcher's early retirement. This little box is cozier than a coffin, and a better place to reflect on how stupid trying to blackmail me was.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189726" id2="17" version="1065353216">But hey, ancient history, am I right? I'm more than willing to forget about our past disagreements, if you do one more job for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like I'd ever help you again!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189729" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't imagine you want things to continue as they are. You can get your life back. With interest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1189729" id2="17" version="1065353216">The grudge isn't worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189732" id2="17" version="1065353216">More credits than I've made in my entire career, Dretch. You know that's nothing to scoff at.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189733" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen, Dretcher. I don't know how much you know about life on the outside these days, but it's bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1189733" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even to save the galaxy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189735" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want there to be something left to look forward to when you come out, I need your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189736" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if you think it's hard to live under the scanners now, just wait until the Eternal Empire's fully staked their claim on the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189737" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's asking, I'm telling. You're going to help us with a heist or I'm going to rip you out of there and beat you within an inch of your life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1189737" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's how it's going to be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189740" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph, there's twenty-five layers of durasteel and cortosis between you and me. We'll both be dead of old age before you make good on that!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189742" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's true, we might never get into that safe room of yours... but I'm sure this sonic amplifier I brought will have an interesting effect on the contents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189744" id2="17" version="1065353216">So unless you want to spend your final moments being shaken to death by the dulcet tones of the Kashyyyk Life Day Choir, I'd reconsider.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189745" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd definitely reconsider.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1189745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not how I'd want to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rrrwargh!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1189747" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Wookiee Impression]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189748" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rrwar!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189750" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay! Okay!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or maybe I just drop this box off the pier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1189751" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a simpler method.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine! I'll do the stupid job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sit tight, Dretch, and get reacquainted with the concept of hygiene. We've got one more stop to make before we get to the fun part.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192589" id2="17" version="1065353216">There have to be laws against this. Broad, intergalactic laws.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1192589" id2="17" version="1065353216">This seems cruel and unusual.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1192590" id2="17" version="1065353216">This? Nah, maybe a noise ordinance, at best.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
