<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>46</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tatooine/bronze/republic/astromenace/constable_bakishan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't turn your back on anything around here without a Jawa walking off with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes? Any news about the thefts?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="615995" id2="17" version="1065353216">There was a Jawa controlling the droids remotely. He was responsible for stealing the holocams, but I got them back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="615995" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was Jawas robbing you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, that explains it. Can't trust those little rats with anything that isn't welded to the floor.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for all your trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="615999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here. This should cover any expenses you encountered. Thanks for your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for your help, Master Jedi. I'll be sure to spread the word of how the Republic's helping us out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for your help. I'll spread the word how the Republic's helping us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616003" id2="17" version="1065353216">The droids shouldn't put up much resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi! What an honor! You must know how rarely members of the order visit Anchorhead.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good day, sir. I must say, having a few more soldiers strolling around looking intimidating could bring some much needed law and order to Anchorhead.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, we certainly get plenty of your type here, but I've heard good things about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Anchorhead. I hear you're the type who's willing to do some favors in the name of a good cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any chance you'd be willing to help out with a little law enforcement issue?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616015" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's in everyone's interests to keep Anchorhead safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. The Republic should be welcomed here for that attitude alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616018" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've always wondered how the other half lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616018" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a chance....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ahem... not quite as well as some others, usually.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616021" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the trouble?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't you have police?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616023" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got a militia, but we're better at fighting off Sand People than solving mysteries.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616025" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been having thefts around Anchorhead lately. Nothing violent, so we weren't going to do anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616027" id2="17" version="1065353216">But now the thieves stole the same blasted equipment that was supposed to let us catch them. State-of-the-art police surveillance holocams.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616028" id2="17" version="1065353216">These thieves will think twice about taking on a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616028" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will get them back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616029" id2="17" version="1065353216">I, uh, don't know how easily you'll intimidate these particular thieves, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616031" id2="17" version="1065353216">A guilty heart cannot hide from the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616031" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will find the thieves.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616032" id2="17" version="1065353216">So I've heard, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you want the culprits dealt with in the field, or returned to Anchorhead for trial?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616034" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get these thieves.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Um, we just need the holocams back. And maybe make sure they won't be doing it again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616037" id2="17" version="1065353216">How much are those holocams worth, exactly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616037" id2="17" version="1065353216">State of the art, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616038" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can pay you a fair price for their return, if that's what you're asking.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616040" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a weird thing about these thefts--every time, someone has reported astromech droids in the area right before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616042" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you know?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616043" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've only got one lead. Every witness has reported two astromech droids in the area just before the thefts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616045" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone's controlling them remotely, and I'm guessing we can trace the signal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616047" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can find the droids around the city, you should uncover the control device--and with a little luck, whoever's responsible for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616051" id2="17" version="1065353216">Beneath me. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616052" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand... the security of our poor city isn't worth a few minutes of your time....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="616054" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why does nobody nice ever move to Tatooine?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
