<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>132</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris_imp/class/sith_inquisitor/elios_maliss.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620653" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll need to clear out the patrols before someone sees you meeting with the Padawan and reports it to her Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620655" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, my lord. This was a terrible oversight on my part. Please forgive me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620661" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord! I just heard that the Republic has increased patrols around the enclave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Call the Padawan and lure her out with the promise of the holocron. Its dark side influence will do your work for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620664" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make the deal with Lord Anathemos and lay your trap for the Padawan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620666" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've found the holocron.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent news, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent, my lord. Lord Anathemos can be found at the Empire's current outpost in that region. I suggest you speak with him right away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620671" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I'm pleased to say that I've found the perfect place for you to lure your Padawan to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620673" id2="17" version="1065353216">An area of swamp near enough to Republic territory that she'll feel secure, yet remote enough that she'll be truly at your mercy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you angling for some sort of prize here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620675" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose you expect a reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Certainly not. My duty is to serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Workaholic, much?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620679" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am only doing my duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620681" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suggest you contact the girl using a holocommunicator from a nearby Republic soldier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620683" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the past, Sith often used dark side holocrons to turn weak-willed Jedi. If you can convince the Padawan to look, she'll fall easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have Lord Anathemos's assassins drive the girl to this spot, and then secure yourself a holocommunicator from a nearby Republic soldier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once the trap is sprung, you can call on a Republic frequency and offer help. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620690" id2="17" version="1065353216">The first thing we need is to retrieve the holocron from the abandoned outpost, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620694" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found the databanks. Our Padawan has a bit of a pride problem. She is a less-than-perfect Jedi candidate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620695" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most excellent! In my experience, pride and insecurity go hand in hand. My lord, you went searching for crumbs and discovered a feast!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620696" id2="17" version="1065353216">She feels as though the Jedi don't trust her strength. I must show her that I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620696" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must make her like us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620697" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. Yes. Excellent thinking. Promise her power, or wealth... something to win her trust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620699" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me think, what could we use? It must be something tempting to a young Padawan....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620700" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can be quite charming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620701" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620702" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no doubt of it, my lord, but you are Sith. She will never trust you without encouragement....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have any suggestions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620704" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are your thoughts?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620705" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, my lord, I am hardly an expert on this sort of thing. But let me think....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Money, power, knowledge? A handsome young smuggler?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which is?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620708" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's it! Knowledge! Money, power, love, they're all too obvious, but knowledge, what's wrong with wanting a little knowledge?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, yes, here we are. This outpost here used to be occupied by the servants of a powerful Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620712" id2="17" version="1065353216">Supposedly, they left behind a holocron when they abandoned the site in haste. Its contents are probably beneath you, but what Padawan isn't tempted by the lure of forbidden knowledge?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620713" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a devious mind. I like it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thinking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620714" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am only glad that I can please you, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620716" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tempt her into using the holocron, and let its dark side knowledge do the rest?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620716" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620717" id2="17" version="1065353216">Precisely. Once the girl comes over to the dark side, she will do whatever you ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you think she'll really fall for such a trap?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620719" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Simply pique her curiosity. If you can get her alone, your usual techniques of persuasion will prevail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, you will need to find the holocron first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620724" id2="17" version="1065353216">She is easily frustrated by difficult things. I think she could be made to doubt her place among the Jedi....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620724" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must make her insecure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620725" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. Yes. It would be delicate business, but, if I may proffer my most humble opinion, it's a brilliant idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make her feel threatened. Alone and frightened. And then offer yourself as her sole protector in this harsh, cruel galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620729" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still don't know how I'm going to get her to take me to the ghost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Plan my next move, Elios.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620730" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, if you wish my unworthy opinion, I would suggest preying on the girl's insecurities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620732" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make her believe you're her only hope in this harsh cruel galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620734" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, you'll still need a way to flush her out of hiding and make the threat seem credible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620735" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have any men you could send to attack her? I could fight them off and win her affection.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620735" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why not stage an attack?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zash sent me alone, I'm afraid. But that's an excellent thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620738" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you thinking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620739" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, it's hardly my area of expertise, but it might just be possible to engage in a little artful deceit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620741" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have all day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rumor has it Lord Anathemos of the assassins' pyramid is here in search of a particular holocron.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now what I'm thinking is, and it may be crazy, you can use that holocron to reach an agreement with Lord Anathemos. For the use of his assassins.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620745" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Lord Anathemos can be bought, I'll buy him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620745" id2="17" version="1065353216">The deal will be made.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620747" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess it could work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620748" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry I cannot be more helpful, but schemes of this nature are not my area of expertise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620750" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can acquire that holocron, Lord Anathemos might be convinced to lay a trap for your Padawan. And when the trap is sprung....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620751" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the trap is sprung, I arrive and save her. Very clever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620751" id2="17" version="1065353216">I play the hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620752" id2="17" version="1065353216">I try only to please, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620754" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would certainly frighten her, but how would it win me her loyalty?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620754" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure I understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620755" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the time is right, I suggest you arrive and slay the assassins, becoming her savior.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620757" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't want to kill her, you fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620757" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need her alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620758" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wouldn't kill her, my lord. At the moment of her greatest danger, you would swoop in and save her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620760" id2="17" version="1065353216">First, you must recover the holocron and make your deal with Lord Anathemos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620762" id2="17" version="1065353216">The abandoned outpost is in a nearby region. I'll transfer the location, but be warned, it's swarming with rakghouls and other monstrosities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620766" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need information on the Padawan from the Jedi training databanks before we can learn how to manipulate her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Elios Maliss. You were sent here to investigate a ghost. What did you discover?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620769" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am a busy man, I don't have time for--</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="620771" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh! My lord! I--I, forgive me, I didn't recognize you in your new wardrobe. So grand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620773" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a pleasant surprise. I had heard the most unfortunate rumors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620774" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're better off not believing anything anyone says about me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620774" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't trust rumors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, of course. The grapevine does lie, doesn't it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620777" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful you don't make that mistake again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620777" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're forgiven. This time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, yes, of course, my lord. You are most gracious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620780" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, you were asking about the ghost, yes? Let me see. I assure you I've been hard at work assessing the situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me about the ghost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620783" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. The ghost. Of course. Let me see. I assure you I've been working tirelessly, but....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620785" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's just the Jedi have been guarding the old Jedi Enclave very tightly. That's, um, that's where the ghost first appeared, you see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope the guardians of the light prove open to negotiation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620786" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should pay the Jedi a visit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dealing with the Jedi may be simple compared to seeing the ghost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have there been other appearances in other places?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620789" id2="17" version="1065353216">First appeared?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620790" id2="17" version="1065353216">On the contrary, there have barely been any appearances at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620792" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get to the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620793" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ghost appears only sporadically. Not even the Jedi who guard the enclave can make it appear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620795" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've resorted to using a young Padawan to try to draw the ghost out through blood ties or something. Foolishness if you ask me, but I'm a man of meager understanding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do the Jedi care if the ghost appears?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do they need to see him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620797" id2="17" version="1065353216">My understanding is, the ghost doesn't need to appear to be felt, and the Jedi don't like the dark side lingering in their enclave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems if the Padawan can make the ghost appear, they can &quot;cleanse&quot; it--or whatever it is Jedi do with ghosts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620800" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seems the Jedi have a weak link.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Padawans can be manipulated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620801" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi guard her closely, but I think you may be on to something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many a Sith is formed from a weak Padawan's impressionable mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620805" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need this Padawan, too, in that case.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620806" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you wish to make the ghost appear, then I'd say it's worth a try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620808" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to bind this ghost. How do I make it appear to me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620808" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about binding the ghost?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Padawans are always the weak link. Young, ambitious, naive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620811" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you could manipulate this Padawan--her name's Ashara Zavros--into assisting you, you could gain both the ghost and a new apprentice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620813" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't imagine an impressionable young Padawan being able to resist your particular charms, and it would save you the trouble of fighting a small army of Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620814" id2="17" version="1065353216">I cannot twist her until I understand what tempts her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620814" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must learn her weaknesses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620815" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a good suggestion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620816" id2="17" version="1065353216">I live ever to please. Of course, you'll need to entice her away from her Jedi protectors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620818" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've done stranger things to get what I want.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="620818" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I must.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620819" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume you'll want to entice her, draw her away from her Jedi protectors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620821" id2="17" version="1065353216">You might visit the Jedi training grounds by the waterfall. It's abandoned now, dangerous. The data recorders there may hold certain insights into her personality.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="620823" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the meantime, I will endeavor to learn what I can of her Jedi Masters.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
