<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>15</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/ilum/multi/arkis_wode_holo.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199122" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are in the power core. The brain of this space station, and my domain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199124" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you are not a member of the Schism Collective, turn back. This place is not for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199126" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the right application of technology, the impossible comes to life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199128" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can travel faster than light; we can construct an entire fleet in weeks; and we can make the visible invisible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199130" id2="17" version="1065353216">So when you see my engineers performing feats that make the Force look like child's play, remember that anything is possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199132" id2="17" version="1065353216">The stealth armada. These vessels will shape the galaxy on invisible wings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199134" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such greatness is only attained by the marriage of Anomid engineering and the Foundry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199136" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few upgrades, and the Foundry droids can process Adegan crystals and construct stealth squadrons in record time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Malgus united our technologies, as he will unite the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199140" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may have noticed our recent improvements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199142" id2="17" version="1065353216">Upgraded turbolasers replaced last generation turrets. Specialized flux cannons can disintegrate capital ships with a single blast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199144" id2="17" version="1065353216">But most importantly, we installed state-of-the-art stealth technology. This station is completely invisible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199146" id2="17" version="1065353216">From the skies, our Empire will unite the galaxy, and Darth Malgus will be our Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199148" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to the heart of our new Empire. I am Arkis Wode: engineer, architect, artist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199150" id2="17" version="1065353216">Serve Darth Malgus well, and my technological creations will serve you.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
