<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>24</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/ilum/multi/the_battle_of_ilum_transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck down there. I'll do my best to keep Malgus's forces off your back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199565" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroy the traitor's army. I'll cover you from the sky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199567" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imps are gunning for Malgus, too. Still, I'd keep an eye on them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199568" id2="17" version="1065353216">We may share an enemy with the Republic, but that doesn't mean you should trust them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199570" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like Malgus is true to his word. He's got alien friends all over the trenches.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199571" id2="17" version="1065353216">The trenches look like an alien shooting gallery from up here. They're fools to support Malgus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Woohoo! Malgus's forces are on the run!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent work! Enemy forces dispersing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199576" id2="17" version="1065353216">Head into the mines. It's the only way inside Fort Barrow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199577" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mines will take you straight to Fort Barrow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199579" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enemy chatter's saying Darth Malgus's right-hand man is approaching Ilum. Be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199580" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enemy comm channels are lighting up. Apparently Darth Malgus's right hand is approaching Ilum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast! The base is shielded. Knock out the generators, and we'll cause some damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199583" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't breach the shields! Disable their generators, and we'll come in heavy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shields are down! Repeat, the base's shields are down! Coming in for a bombing run!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work. Their shields are down. Bombing run on my mark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bombs away!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Target locked. Missiles away!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199591" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm tracking a stealth commander fighter. He just took out an Imperial attack wing by himself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast, lost him! He's headed for the base. A thousand credits says that's Malgus's right-hand man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful down there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199597" id2="17" version="1065353216">A stealth fighter's tracking me. No... it's a command ship!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199599" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's skilled. Somebody get this scum off--argh!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shields out. Engines--blast! I'm going down! I'm going--!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
