<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>56</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/ilum/multi/the_false_emperor_transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199605" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is it. Malgus's space station. And thanks to my flying skills, they don't even know we're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome aboard, my Republic friends. This is Darth Malgus speaking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199609" id2="17" version="1065353216">The old Empire may have failed to destroy you, but all it lacked was organization.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199611" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't sound good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here we are. Looks like they haven't detected us yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199615" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Darth Malgus speaking. Make yourself at home. This station recently belonged to the late Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soon you will join him in the ether, and the Empire will be reborn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sensors are picking up movement. Get ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199622" id2="17" version="1065353216">This baby's ready to fly. Heading outside to make myself useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Systems are back online. Taking off to hammer the station from outside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just heard from the Supreme Commander. The Republic fleet is on its way!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grand Moff Regus just sent word. The Imperial fleet will be here shortly!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't shake these fighters. Afraid you're on your own. Maybe you can use the station's defenses against him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't assist! Fighters on my tail! Look for defensive turrets, something to turn against that scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good shot!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199634" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic fleet is here! Good to see you, boys!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199635" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperial fleet has arrived!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199637" id2="17" version="1065353216">These stealth fighters are giving the fleet trouble. I've blasted my share, but they keep coming!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199638" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no end to these stealth fighters. I've scratched dozens, and they're still swarming!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha! The station's cannons are firing on the stealth armada! Whatever you did, it's working!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199643" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lovely. The station is firing on its own stealth armada. I trust you're responsible for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199646" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those cannons just wiped out another Republic capital ship. We can't hold out much longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199647" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperial fleet's taking heavy casualties. If you're going to do something, do it now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199649" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's dead. Darth Malgus is dead!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199651" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let you miss the celebration. Get to the hangars. I'll see you there!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thus the false Emperor is dethroned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199655" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let you join Malgus in death. Hurry to the hangars. I'm coming for you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry! Get in!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199659" id2="17" version="1065353216">Move, move, move!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jindo Krey was among the first to join me. He will become a martyr, and others will flock to continue his fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199664" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Trandoshans' capacity for warfare is remarkable. Your Republic's disinterest in their species led them right into my care. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199665" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Trandoshans are fierce, loyal warriors. Shunning them was the fault of the shortsighted Dark Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look around you. This station's power is a testament to the Anomids' technical prowess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199669" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic claimed the Schism Collective's experiments were repulsive and turned them away. How fatally shortsighted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199671" id2="17" version="1065353216">The old Empire shunned them, but I encouraged and embraced their talents. Thus, tolerance breeds strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your fleet arrived quickly, but it's of little consequence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199676" id2="17" version="1065353216">My station will obliterate them. And in the Republic's defeat, the galaxy will recognize the power of the new Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your fleet is outdated and weak, I will rebuild it from the scraps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199680" id2="17" version="1065353216">My armada will crush them and show the galaxy that a new order has been born.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199683" id2="17" version="1065353216">HK-47 was a psychopath, but he was programmed that way. Remind me, how many thousands have you slaughtered?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199685" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of you has vowed to join the new Empire. But which one? I'm certainly not telling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199686" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand you've been here before, Jedi. But the Emperor you defeated was a shadow of my power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199687" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sense your approach, Jedi. And your fear. Come before me, and I will judge your might with the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad taught you to guard against betrayal, yet your Supreme Commander easily duped you into this futile mission. Once a pawn, always a pawn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199689" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic must be desperate if they're sending a lone smuggler to do me in. Should I be insulted?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199690" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you killed everyone you know? The few survivors must fear you. Even if you return victorious, how long until they turn against you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199691" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dark Council has betrayed you. They manipulated you into coming here. Sacrifice yourself to me, and their deception is complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199692" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at you. A spy without an Intelligence network. Your Empire has abandoned you once, and they will do so again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199693" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Schism Collective has procured your bank records, hunter. The Empire's paid you well. Turn around, or I'll liquidate every last credit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199694" id2="17" version="1065353216">You dare face me alone? How bold... and foolish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199697" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention: Self-destruct has been engaged. Evacuate all vital personnel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warning: Estimated blast radius one point nine-two kilometers. Minimum safe distance: two point four kilometers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199699" id2="17" version="1065353216">Secondary systems failure. Core power levels critical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="199700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reactor overload. Primary systems failing. Meltdown imminent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="472771" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look around you. This station's power is a testament to the Anomids' technical prowess.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
