<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>47</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/world/imperial/spreading_the_word/console.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="649514" id2="17" version="1065353216">[The equipment appears ready to broadcast to Nar Shaddaa and nearby star systems.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Citizens of the galaxy, the Empire and the Republic stand on the brink of war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649517" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a message of peace....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649519" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have seen fire and destruction. I have seen Sith and Jedi fall. But this is not about dark and light.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649522" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen fire and destruction. I've seen soldiers on both sides face death. This is only the beginning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649524" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we continue, no world will be left untouched. No innocent will be left alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649526" id2="17" version="1065353216">I ask you to stop this. Stop the bloodshed before we all pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649528" id2="17" version="1065353216">We may not get another chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Citizens of the galaxy, I speak to you in the name of the Sith Emperor. Today is a day of glory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's begin. [Read the speech.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seven battle cruisers are en route to disputed sectors. They will reclaim our territories within the hour.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Intelligence has arrested over nine hundred dissidents on Sullust and Bothawui. The dissidents will be tried, judged and executed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649539" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a warning to those who oppose us--and an invitation to those who would join us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649541" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire abides by the Treaty of Coruscant. But should the Republic begin the war again, we will strike without mercy....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649543" id2="17" version="1065353216">...and the time for choosing sides will be over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you ever wondered how well the HoloNet is protected?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Galaxy--I'm for hire....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ray shields, battle droids, corporate mercenaries--they're all here. Everyone in the galaxy wants Network Access secure, so the Hutt Cartel spends whatever it takes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649550" id2="17" version="1065353216">But some things can't be protected no matter how much you pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649552" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want to be safe, don't hide from your enemies. Go after them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649554" id2="17" version="1065353216">I got inside Network Access. I can get to anyone in the galaxy. All it takes is a contract and a fee.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Put the word out. I'll find you. Guaranteed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649559" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a message to Nar Shaddaa. I have obtained control over the HoloNet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider this blackmail....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649561" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can no longer rely on encryption and droid security to protect you. Your secrets belong to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649563" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are no secrets from me now--this broadcast is my proof.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649565" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you don't want your information to become public, begin cooperating with the Empire immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649567" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because if I can hijack this broadcast, I can find anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649570" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you can hear me. Frightened children, all of you, trembling in the streets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649570" id2="17" version="1065353216">Galaxy, I am your master!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649572" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are wise to be afraid. Your fear endears you to me. It makes me strong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649574" id2="17" version="1065353216">I rose from slavery to become Sith! I will rise to become your lord and master!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649576" id2="17" version="1065353216">All that you have, all that you are--it shall be mine! Only obedience shall save you from my wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prepare for my coming, creatures of the galaxy. Soon, you will know my name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look upon me, creatures, and know that I am Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="649581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Galaxy, fear my wrath!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649583" id2="17" version="1065353216">The blood of the ancients courses through me. I triumphed in the tombs of Korriban.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since I departed Dromund Kaas, enemies of the Empire have crumbled before me. Others will die soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649587" id2="17" version="1065353216">I come for the Jedi. I come for their Padawans. Everything you love I will destroy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649589" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will burn your cities, your planets, your stars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="649591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kneel before the Empire. It is the only way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="755329" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a message of peace....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="759624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's begin. [Read the speech.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="759626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Galaxy--I'm for hire....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="759628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider this blackmail....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="759630" id2="17" version="1065353216">Galaxy, I am your master!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="759632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Galaxy, fear my wrath!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
