<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>44</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tatooine/world/imperial/thirst_for_glory/major_brega.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607663" id2="17" version="1065353216">My colleagues still talk about how you killed those Sand People. Thank you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607664" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've returned! I was about to pass out from the stench here when I heard reports of your successful massacre.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfection as always, my lord. The survivors are weak and scattered. Once we have the well, there'll be no stopping the Empire's advance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607668" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the Sand People crushed, we can easily take the well. This is a major victory for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quite messy, I hear. I'm sure you did what was necessary. Once the Empire has the well, there'll be no stopping us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607672" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's obvious the Sand People didn't stand a chance. Soon, the Empire will control the well and then... the rest of Tatooine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607674" id2="17" version="1065353216">As for myself, I'll finally be stationed somewhere befitting a man of my status. You're my savior--I can't thank you enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607675" id2="17" version="1065353216">My pleasure. No one deserves to be stuck on Tatooine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to be of service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed. This planet has robbed me of my spirit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607678" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should have known you'd twist my victory for your benefit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607678" id2="17" version="1065353216">You self-serving coward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607679" id2="17" version="1065353216">An unexpected benefit, I assure you. I would never place my needs before the Empire's.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="607681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, I must pack. I won't forget you when I'm sipping Corellian brandy somewhere far from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607682" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm done here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607683" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell. I shall toast you when I'm drinking Alderaan wine somewhere far from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607685" id2="17" version="1065353216">That well should be ours. Do what you must to defeat those Sand People.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607690" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major Brega, at your service. I'm honored that you've graced this dismal planet with your presence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607692" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a pleasure, sir. I'm Major Brega. Glad to see an Imperial of repute on this sordid planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to see you. I'm Major Brega. I trust you've developed the same hatred for this dirty planet as I have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607696" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were so close to expanding Imperial influence, introducing refinement to this rock. If you can spare a moment, we may still have a chance!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607697" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Empire's growth is at risk, I'll remove the threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607697" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. I cannot afford another failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607700" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's growth isn't my concern. I could, however, be persuaded....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only if you can spare credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607701" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assure you, success in this matter will be handsomely rewarded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607703" id2="17" version="1065353216">What did you have in mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607704" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not joining your decorating brigade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't sound like my thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607705" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, it's nothing like that! Not to say this sand scab couldn't use a touch up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607707" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a well, one of Tatooine's deepest and most successful. Whoever controls it, controls this region.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="607709" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Command ordered me to take it, but my men were butchered--by Sand People, no less! This tribe's so ruthless all the other tribes pay them tribute.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607711" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire cannot let these filthy savages control such a priceless resource!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607712" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will end their rule.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607712" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. I get the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. I can't wait to hear of your victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607715" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be able to fill the well with their bodies when I'm done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607715" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll annihilate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607716" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enthusiasm. That's good, but we don't want to poison the water with their foul remains.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607718" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm busy, but maybe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607719" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope so. This planet is in dire need of Imperial order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607721" id2="17" version="1065353216">The well lies deep in the desert. Kill the Sand People who guard it. The Empire will be grateful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607723" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't spare any time. Please excuse me.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
