<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>201</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/open_worlds/class/jedi_knight/the_parting_blow/ship_holoterminal.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090784" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's our status, Master Satele?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090786" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've arrived at New Uphrades, Master Satele. What's the colony's status?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Siege conditions, I'm afraid. Darth Legius's flagship, the Vindicator, dropped out of hyperspace moments before you arrived. I'm still en route with the fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090789" id2="17" version="1065353216">The colony has mobilized its defenses, but the Vindicator's shields are operating at two-hundred-percent. He'll reach the colony long before they fail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090791" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't know Legius's intentions. But the fact that he hasn't changed course, despite taking damage... I fear Sergeant Rusk may be correct.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090793" id2="17" version="1065353216">You assume he intends to stop in orbit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090796" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're saying Legius is going to ram his ship into the colony?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1090796" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's planning to crash?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090797" id2="17" version="1065353216">Losing Project Sever was supposed to be the end for Legius. Has the Empire sanctioned this attack?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1090797" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the Dark Council?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legius fights alone, but if he succeeds, the Empire wins a major victory. They wouldn't dream of interrupting him now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Crashing his ship means everyone on board dies. Even Legius isn't that crazy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1090800" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is all a big bluff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legius is a man of extremes. We cannot underestimate him now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090803" id2="17" version="1065353216">This has trap written all over it. Legius has already fooled us twice--are we really going for a third?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090805" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we are to stop him, we must know his plans--even if it means setting them in motion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fighters from New Uphrades have weakened the shields around the Vindicator's docking bay. You can land inside and infiltrate the ship from there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090809" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't make it with the fleet in time. Whatever Legius has planned, you must stop him alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legius will target the innocent first. The colony should begin evacuating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1090810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warn New Uphrades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090811" id2="17" version="1065353216">Communications are still open. We'll make sure the Protectors are advising.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say I'm killed, or Legius locks me in a force field. What happens then?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1090813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not much of a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090814" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may well be the most powerful Jedi in the Order. If you cannot save New Uphrades, no one can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever happens on that ship, I can promise you Darth Legius won't survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1090816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legius is going down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember your teachings. He is desperate, and we can still offer him a way out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090819" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll continue monitoring the situation, and alert you when we arrive. May the Force be with us all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before we depart, master--a message was left for you. I believe it's from the Protectors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090823" id2="17" version="1065353216">You might not have time to hear this--I barely found time to record it. Here goes anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090825" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and I have unfinished business. I already lost one person I cared about in this--I can't lose another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1090827" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not saying you can't beat Legius, because I know you can. Just... please, be careful. Love, Audra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victorious. Darth Legius is dead, the Vindicator is destroyed, and New Uphrades is safe. The fleet is already returning to the front lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1094397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi + T7 + crew = Republic heroes again!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094399" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Harrower-class dreadnought like the Vindicator would have produced several tonnes of debris. Were there any casualties in the colony?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094401" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some serious damage, but no deaths so far. We're evacuating those areas and treating the injured now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094403" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legius sacrificed everything to destroy New Uphrades, but you still managed to defeat him. The Force was with you today, Hero of Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094404" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Legius had succeeded, every civilian we've saved since Talravin would have been lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094404" id2="17" version="1065353216">Failure wasn't an option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094405" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makes you wonder if we really should have put 'em in one place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094407" id2="17" version="1065353216">My mission was to bring Legius to justice. Now that he's dead, what are my instructions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094407" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happens now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094408" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe they'll start calling me the Hero of New Uphrades. I've certainly earned it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094408" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time for another medal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094409" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll leave that decision to someone who values such things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094411" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've informed Supreme Chancellor Saresh of your victory. She requests that we meet her in person, aboard the Resolute. We'll speak more there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094415" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know what the Jedi say about relationships? How they're dangerous and a path to the dark side and all that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094417" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm starting to think that's true. I've been having all these violent urges lately... usually whenever I see you, or Doctor Kantos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094419" id2="17" version="1065353216">And when I see you together? I mean, wow... kind of makes me want to hit you upside the head, you know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094420" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's harmless flirtation, that's all. You're the one I really care about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094420" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's nothing to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pretty easy to call it harmless when you aren't the one being harmed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094423" id2="17" version="1065353216">We just stopped a Sith Lord and saved a colony from destruction. Can we enjoy that for a second first?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we have to fight now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094426" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rule is against attachment, not relationships. I'm trying to protect myself, and you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094426" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the Jedi way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094427" id2="17" version="1065353216">And how's that working out for you, master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094429" id2="17" version="1065353216">You promised it would be me and only me, forever. Just because it's a secret doesn't mean you can ignore that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094434" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're an amazing woman, Kira. No one else even comes close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094434" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's always been you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better. You still owe me though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094437" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can start with a foot rub. Maybe watch some HoloNet feeds. You like romance vids, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Audra and I have a connection. I can't ignore that, even if it means losing you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, I choose her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good, because you just did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094440" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just following our teachings. If you had other relationships, I wouldn't mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094440" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can both explore options.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094441" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the Jedi who killed the Emperor, you are really stupid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, here we are. Another crazy Sith down, about a million or so to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kinda hard to feed good about this one. Legius wanted to die. Died thinking he won, even.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still don't know how he did it. Giving the order, knowing it's a one-way trip... can you imagine?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094448" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could never throw my life away--not for a cause like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094448" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's unimaginable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legius was trying to do what he thought was best for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094451" id2="17" version="1065353216">He had good intentions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Missed that target by a few kilometers, didn't he?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legius was crazy. Let's leave it at that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why bother thinking about it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094455" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just talking. Not like I want to go crash Kaas City or anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a big fan of dying, personally. Not for the Republic, not for the Jedi, not even for a herd of baby taun-tauns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094459" id2="17" version="1065353216">For someone I loved, though... that might be worth it. Especially if I could haunt him afterwards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck with that plan. I'd die before I let anything happen to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094460" id2="17" version="1065353216">I feel the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094461" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I had all these ghostly future predictions too. Ah, well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094463" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm flattered, but if it's all the same to you, I'd rather we both lived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094463" id2="17" version="1065353216">No dying, please.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh yeah, me too. Wasn't that obvious?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094466" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dying for me wouldn't accomplish anything. No one is worth that kind of sacrifice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094466" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're being foolish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094467" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a romantic! Watch out, ladies, I think I might swoon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on, tough guy. It's been a long day, and I think you've earned a backrub or two.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094473" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, you and Doctor Kantos. Seems to be going well. Almost as well as it went in my head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094477" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're doing this for my benefit, don't. I've got a good imagination. Out here, I'd rather it was just you and me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094478" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I'd known how much you cared, I might not have pursued her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094478" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to hear that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094479" id2="17" version="1065353216">We got married, remember? The droid, the ceremony, the honeymoon? Not sure why you'd need a reminder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094483" id2="17" version="1065353216">I barely escaped that dreadnought alive. Is this really the best time to be picking a fight?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not now, Doc....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094484" id2="17" version="1065353216">What can I say? I like to move fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094486" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you actually think our relationship was for your benefit, you're even sleazier than I thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094486" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a pig!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Call me what you like, gorgeous, but I'm not the one stringing two people along at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell you what: I figure I had this coming. Not for anything I did to you, but maybe a few things I've done over the years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094491" id2="17" version="1065353216">So I'm giving you a free pass. One time only, good for a clean slate and a fresh start. Forget her. What do you say?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094492" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never meant to hurt you. I promise no one will come between us again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094492" id2="17" version="1065353216">I accept, and I'm sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094493" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm gonna hold you to that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094495" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, enough talk. Let's go make up the right way, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Audra and I could become something special. I owe it to us both to find out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Audra means more to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, make sure she treats you right. I would have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094498" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know what you can do with your free pass, Doc?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not in a million years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, I got it. Don't need the Force to see that one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094501" id2="17" version="1065353216">As your doctor, I feel I should advise you: all this fighting? Kinda hazardous to your health.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not that I don't enjoy checking you for injuries--just don't like finding them. You've had enough lately to make it a hobby.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094505" id2="17" version="1065353216">Might be time to start thinking retirement. I could open up a practice, you could be my nurse....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094506" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could never leave the Order, Doc. Not as long as there are men like Legius around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094506" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic needs me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094507" id2="17" version="1065353216">So I'm gonna be dodging blaster fire 'til I'm old and grey, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094509" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd never get anything done that way. All the patients would die in the waiting room.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds too tempting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't you worry, darlin'. Ol' Doc knows how to multi-task.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094512" id2="17" version="1065353216">No applause, no medals, no free drinks? I'd give it about a week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094512" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd get bored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094513" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know me too well. Pretty sure I could still get free drinks, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eh, being a hero's not so bad either. Saving lives, protecting Protectors, taking down the craziest Sith to ever leave Korriban....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094517" id2="17" version="1065353216">After all that, I think you've earned a victory party. We could make an evening out of it. A morning, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094518" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't think of a better way to celebrate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094519" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can. But we'll start small.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094520" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could go to Nar Shaddaa, get a hotel, spend some time in the casinos....</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why stop there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094521" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're reading my mind again, aren't you? I love it when you do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094523" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have a meeting with the Supreme Chancellor. I wouldn't want to keep her waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1094523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1094524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suit yourself. I'll be in my bunk if you change your mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1097257" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does he think will happen when hits orbit? They'll just turn off their guns and surrender?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099437" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm so pleased you're joining the Protectors, master. I estimate your life expectancy will rise by three-point-seven years as a result!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now we all report to Doctor Kantos. Thanks for that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099441" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Kantos has granted us access to Protector resources, and we are registered with emergency services. But our squad operates on its own.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1099443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Protectors = save lives // Jedi + T7 = save lives // Jedi + T7 = chose correctly!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gotta say, I'm a little surprised. I thought every Jedi wanted to be Battlemaster. That, or be Master Satele.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099446" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi's first duty is to protect the innocent. If I can do that without fighting, I will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1099446" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099447" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could recommend you for Battlemaster instead. You're as accomplished as I am.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1099447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go ahead--take the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099448" id2="17" version="1065353216">No second place finish for me, thanks. I'll defeat another Emperor and earn it myself some day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099450" id2="17" version="1065353216">After you've defeated the Emperor, even Battlemaster sounds a little boring.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1099450" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no ordinary Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow, your head really has swelled. I thought it was just the light.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, obnoxious CO or not, this gig is right up my alley. Cute kids, grateful familes, lots of beautiful, desperate women.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099455" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am wondering about our resident Sith Lord, though. The Wrath probably didn't do much rescuing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Battlemaster on deck!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess I better start bowing when I see you. Maybe I was supposed to be doing that all along.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1099461" id2="17" version="1065353216">Battlemaster = great responsibility // T7 = proud of Jedi!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099463" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugh, responsibility. Like you needed more of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099465" id2="17" version="1065353216">You given any thought to how the rest of us fit in with you training Padawans and charging into battle?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099466" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't have come this far without my crew. Whatever comes next, I want you all at my side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1099466" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your help is always welcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099467" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think I'll be spending a lot of time on Tython--not until the war is over. We're needed out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1099467" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suspect we'll be... active.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not so comforting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099470" id2="17" version="1065353216">But not surprising.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't expect me to retire to Tython just yet. My becoming Battlemaster won't keep us from the front.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1099472" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's just one more task.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099477" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about Scourge? Disappointed they passed you up for the battling job?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099479" id2="17" version="1065353216">My opinion is irrelevant. I knew the Jedi would choose this path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099481" id2="17" version="1065353216">How? Because you're such good pals?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three hundred years ago, I had a vision of the Jedi who would defeat the Emperor. Did you think it would be my only one?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099484" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a connection to the Force I've never matched.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1099484" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admit, I'm impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099485" id2="17" version="1065353216">In this regard alone, perhaps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1099487" id2="17" version="1065353216">What did you see?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099489" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you knew I would join the Protectors. Was there anything more?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099491" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you knew I would become Battlemaster. Was there anything more?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099492" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can think of a few times having a Sith who sees the future might have been handy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1099492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now you tell me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099493" id2="17" version="1065353216">I saw nothing of Legius, or his plans. My vision was of your destiny alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099495" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will find peace with the Protectors. Clearing rubble, healing the sick, defending your allies when necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your actions will bring hope to Republic forces, but war will find you once again. When that time comes, how will the Jedi Protector respond?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099502" id2="17" version="1065353216">As Battlemaster, you will lead the Republic to many victories. The Jedi will grow strong. You will grow stronger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099506" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the Empire will rebound. When that time comes, how will the Jedi Battlemaster respond?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vengeance is a battle we can't win. The enemy will always find a way to hurt us--hurting them back won't help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1099509" id2="17" version="1065353216">We act with mercy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Protecting innocent lives must come first. That's what sets us apart from the Empire, and makes all the fighting worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Men like Legius will come and go. But as long as the Republic stays true to itself, we will never be defeated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099514" id2="17" version="1065353216">You saw me defeat the Emperor, but you didn't know how. You've seen where my path leads, but you don't know its course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1099514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's find out, in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099516" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know the enemy's plans. I can't promise kindness or cruelty any more than I can promise victory or defeat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099518" id2="17" version="1065353216">All we can do is fight for the Republic's survival and seek the end of this war--and hope we live to see both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someday, when the Sith are extinct and the Empire destroyed, the galaxy will know peace. Until then, we're at war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1099519" id2="17" version="1065353216">We act with force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099521" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we want to win, we can't hold anything back. We've seen the fanaticism of the enemy--the extremes the Sith will embrace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Next time, we won't wait for them to attack us. The Republic will make the next strike--and it'll be one to remember.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tefani and I have been summoned too. Hopefully we'll get a moment alone afterwards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Safe journey--I'm so glad you're all right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099530" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we're not too busy shining medals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah. Got a few things I'd like to say to you myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099532" id2="17" version="1065353216">If he hopes to destroy it, I see no alternative. I truly hope he'll prove me wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1099759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better now than in front of the Supreme Chancellor, don't you think?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
