<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>51</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/companion_characters/multi/imperial/2vr8/2vr8.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477045" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, master. You're looking fit and deadly, as always.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have I mentioned recently how much I enjoy serving you? I am a lucky droid, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always a pleasure, master. I hope you're having an excellent day and feel no desire to deactivate me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seeing you return to this ship always warms my circuits, master. It reminds me I am still functioning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, master. I cleaned the vessel from stem to stern in your absence. You can smell the difference!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477050" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hail to the Emperor! More importantly, hail to you, master!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477051" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back, master. I've just completed a new meal plan for your culinary pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you require anything, master? A hot meal, perhaps? Conversation? Foot massage? Just say the word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477053" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galaxy will continue trembling at your approach if it knows what's good for it, master. Maker knows, I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477054" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've just finished cleaning the fuel injectors to the sublight drive. You should notice a point oh-oh-oh-oh-eight percent power increase.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477055" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to see you, master. I applied a fresh coat of paint to your quarters. Same color, of course--only fresher!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477056" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am truly honored to serve such a personage as you, master. History will remember your name. Not mine, but definitely yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477057" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh! Ah, I mean... greetings! I am Toovee Arrate, factotum droid for this vessel. You must be my new master. Gentle, kind new master....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I seem gentle to you? Tell me your attack protocols, droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477058" id2="17" version="1065353216">List your combat functions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477059" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was not constructed for violence, master--but I am still useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477061" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you, my personal entertainer? Do you perform tricks?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477061" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're an odd little thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not as such, master. I would be willing to learn tricks if it pleases you, however.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your last master isn't coming back. Got a problem with that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your old master is dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477065" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely not. He called me unpleasant names and never bathed. Not that there is anything wrong with that, master....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477067" id2="17" version="1065353216">A gift from my superior? Here to keep an eye on me, I presume.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keeper must have sent you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477068" id2="17" version="1065353216">My only directive is your satisfaction, master. Besides, my photoreceptors are not surveillance-grade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's not get ahead of ourselves. What's your function aboard my ship?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Depends. What's a &quot;factotum&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477071" id2="17" version="1065353216">So I get a starship and a servant, too? Not bad at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477071" id2="17" version="1065353216">My own droid? Excellent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477072" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am relieved--er, pleased--that you find me agreeable. I will never disappoint you, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477074" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am programmed for a wide array of tasks, including but not limited to meal preparation, ship maintenance, janitorial duty and etiquette.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome aboard this Fury-class Imperial Interceptor, a versatile craft combining a starfighter's maneuverability with armament to rival larger military vessels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477078" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome aboard this Kuat Drive Yards D5-Mantis Patrol Craft. Its speed and firepower are unmatched by other vessels of its class.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477080" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome aboard the X-70B Phantom: an experimental prototype resembling a luxury shuttle that conceals the combat capabilities of a heavy starfighter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477082" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find all of the standard amenities, including your own private captain's locker for storing valuables.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477084" id2="17" version="1065353216">A state-of-the-art enhancement station is available should you wish to upgrade your equipment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477086" id2="17" version="1065353216">The astrogation console contains a constantly updated map of the known galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477088" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interstellar communications are accessed via the ship's holoterminal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477090" id2="17" version="1065353216">Priority alerts that you may find useful are available from the Imperial HoloNet console.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477092" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lastly, the ship's intercom will inform your crew that you wish to issue new orders. Any questions, master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477093" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you at least capable of providing security while I'm not aboard?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477093" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you fight at all?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477094" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a mission to complete. Time to see what this ship can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477094" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready for departure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477095" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank goodness you aren't deactivating me! I mean... good luck!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477097" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop selling me the ship and stay out of my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="477097" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can shut up now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477098" id2="17" version="1065353216">I promise to limit all future conversation to essential information. Premature deactivation is not one of my directives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477100" id2="17" version="1065353216">I regret I am unable to offer you combat support, master. Frankly, my chassis couldn't withstand the stress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477102" id2="17" version="1065353216">However, should any errands arise that are beneath your superior status, please do not hesitate to call upon me. I function to serve you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="477104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whenever you are ready to depart, consult the galaxy map on your bridge. It will program the proper astrogation coordinates and activate the engines.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
