<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>130</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/taris/multi/republic/chief_rannos.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198144" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Tion Hegemony will be a valuable ally against the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198148" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just read the reports from Ord Mantell. We knew Lorrick was dangerous. Didn't realize he was a complete wack-job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198150" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's too bad he took his assistants down with him. Seems like they were actually working on a cure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198151" id2="17" version="1065353216">They tried to stop him. They destroyed his research so nobody else could use it, even though it cost them their lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198151" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were heroes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198152" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see if we can get something to honor their memories. Maybe official Senate recognition of their sacrifice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198154" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were working with a deadly virus in a secret lab with no regard for galactic law. No surprise it ended like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198154" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their research was illegal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198155" id2="17" version="1065353216">True enough, I suppose. Still don't think they deserved what happened to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198157" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ruling family in the Tion Hegemony wanted to express their thanks as well. They appreciate the Republic's help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198159" id2="17" version="1065353216">It would have been handy to have a bioweapon like that in our arsenal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198159" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wish we'd saved the virus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198160" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic would never use something that horrific. Not even on the Empire!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198162" id2="17" version="1065353216">And what would the Tion Hegemony think if they found out we'd seized control of the weapon that wiped out five of their worlds?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Securing an alliance with them was an important strategic victory. Now the Empire can't use their support to rebuild.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our enemy is weaker than they've ever been. Now's our chance to finish them off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198165" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's collapsing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198166" id2="17" version="1065353216">Might be a good time to press your advantage. Maybe take the Empire out once and for all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198166" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's collapsing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198167" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't underestimate them. We've got the upper hand, but they always seem to find a way to claw their way back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198169" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we're lucky, we'll get a few generations of peace before we have to deal with them again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198171" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galaxy has no shortage of despots and tyrants who'll throw their lot in with the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198171" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll find someone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198172" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's why we have people like you on our side. Hope you weren't thinking about retirement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess my work here is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198175" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you've done more than anyone has a right to expect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198177" id2="17" version="1065353216">You probably get tired of hearing this, but I'll say it again anyway: The Republic owes you. Thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198181" id2="17" version="1065353216">The shuttle will take you to Lorrick's island on Ord Mantell whenever you're ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Lorrick is brilliant, arrogant, ambitious and completely amoral.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198187" id2="17" version="1065353216">He fled the Tion Hegemony decades ago after being declared a traitor. Been hiding out on Ord Mantell ever since.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198188" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we know if he had any help from anyone? Like maybe the Empire?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198188" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is he working alone?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198189" id2="17" version="1065353216">As far as we can tell, he's acting alone. But that doesn't make him any less dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198191" id2="17" version="1065353216">Order the authorities on Ord Mantell to take him into custody.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198191" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should arrest him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198192" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. We think it's better if this gets handled outside official channels. We don't want to cause a panic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198194" id2="17" version="1065353216">So all this time he's been waiting to strike back at the Tion royal family.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198194" id2="17" version="1065353216">Planning his revenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198195" id2="17" version="1065353216">His ambitions go way beyond claiming the Tion Hegemony. Kaon and the other infected worlds were just a test.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198197" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lorrick created a new strain of the rakghoul virus. One that infects any living organism.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198198" id2="17" version="1065353216">The virus doesn't just turn the infected victims into mindless brutes, either. I saw them using blasters and other advanced technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198198" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's worse than that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198199" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakghouls running wild are bad enough. A rakghoul army under a madman's control would be unstoppable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198201" id2="17" version="1065353216">We had no idea he was working on this. The attack on Kaon tipped us off to his plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198201" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why risk revealing himself?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198202" id2="17" version="1065353216">He didn't think we'd find out. He wasn't counting on you, and he never imagined that pilot would survive the initial attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198204" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any idea what he's up to now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198204" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's his next move?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198205" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were able to suppress reports of what happened on Kaon. Lorrick doesn't know we're on to him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198207" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we strike at his base now, we'll catch him off guard. Put an end to his experiments before he unleashes another outbreak on the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198208" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume taking Lorrick out will strengthen our ties with the Tion royal family?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198208" id2="17" version="1065353216">The hegemony will be pleased.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198209" id2="17" version="1065353216">It can't hurt. And we could always use another ally against the Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198211" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198212" id2="17" version="1065353216">Simplicity will serve us best in this case. Hit fast, hit hard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198214" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll leave now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198215" id2="17" version="1065353216">The shuttle will take you to Lorrick's island base on Ord Mantell. Do whatever it takes to stop him and his experiments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198217" id2="17" version="1065353216">Officially, the only occupants are him and a few lab assistants. Unofficially, expect a host of mutated guardians around every corner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198221" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice job down there on Kaon. I sent a full report on what you learned to the Tion royal family.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198223" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that we know how the plague is spread, they've been able to contain further outbreaks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198225" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lucky you ran into that pilot on Kaon. What she told you helped us put together a file on Doctor Lorrick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198226" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pilot's dead. Doctor Lorrick couldn't have done this without help. She had to pay for her part.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198226" id2="17" version="1065353216">It wasn't lucky for her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198227" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess it was your call to make. Anyway, we need to focus on Lorrick now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198229" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since Ord Mantell is in Republic space, they agreed to leave Doctor Lorrick to us. I've had my agents put together a file on him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198230" id2="17" version="1065353216">Millions of innocent lives were lost because of his actions. I will bring him to justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198230" id2="17" version="1065353216">He must pay for his crimes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198231" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looking into the mind of a monster is never pleasant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198231" id2="17" version="1065353216">A disturbing task, no doubt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198232" id2="17" version="1065353216">True, but sometimes we have to do things we'd rather not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198234" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killing soldiers on the battlefield is one thing. Slaughtering millions of innocent civilians is different.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198234" id2="17" version="1065353216">Terrorists deserve no mercy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198235" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galaxy will be a better place without him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198237" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll give you the short version. Doctor Lorrick--a few thrusters short of a hyperdrive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198237" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bet I can guess what it says.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198238" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no doubt he's a complete sociopath. But we've gone into a little more detail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198240" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's happening with Melarra?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198240" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the pilot I saved?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198241" id2="17" version="1065353216">We let her go. She wasn't infected with the rakghoul virus. And any crimes she committed were outside Republic jurisdiction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198243" id2="17" version="1065353216">She gave us a lot of useful information on Doctor Lorrick. After that, we let her go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198245" id2="17" version="1065353216">We did as instructed and dropped her off on one of the nearby worlds. She's on her own now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Melarra's not your concern anymore. You need to focus on Doctor Lorrick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198249" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything interesting?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198252" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major Byzal will contact you once you touch down on Kaon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198256" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. You're here. We've gathered more intel on the rakghoul outbreak. Things are getting worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198258" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Tion noble family has quarantined all worlds in the sector--no ships can land or leave without permission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198260" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's an extreme measure that's not too popular, especially with the people on the infected worlds. They think they've been abandoned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198261" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ruling families are turning their backs on their own people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198261" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198262" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're scared. Desperate. Things have spiraled way beyond their control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198264" id2="17" version="1065353216">A quarantine seems like the only way to stop the virus from spreading.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198264" id2="17" version="1065353216">The nobles had no choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe, though I think it's too little, too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198267" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was hoping we'd be able to stop this before any serious damage was done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198267" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is worse than I feared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198268" id2="17" version="1065353216">No such luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Four worlds have already been wiped out. A fifth, Kaon, is down to a handful of survivors battling for their lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198272" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic offered aid. It took a while, but the ruling families finally granted us permission to land on Kaon to help quell the outbreak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198273" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought they'd jump at the offer of help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198273" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why'd they wait?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't seem like the right time to play hard to get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198274" id2="17" version="1065353216">What took them so long?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198275" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Tion nobility were afraid to appear helpless. They're having enough trouble maintaining order as it is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198277" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their hesitation is understandable. They didn't want to give the impression they had lost control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198277" id2="17" version="1065353216">They didn't want to look weak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad their political games cost lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198280" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone could be infected. So when they say &quot;quell the outbreak,&quot; they mean &quot;kill everything that moves,&quot; right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198280" id2="17" version="1065353216">A total purge is a good idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198281" id2="17" version="1065353216">No! They're actually hoping we can end this with minimal civilian casualties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198283" id2="17" version="1065353216">My first priority is getting the people trapped on Kaon somewhere safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198283" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to help the survivors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198284" id2="17" version="1065353216">Several of the survivors are related to the Tion ruling family. That's probably the only reason they let us get involved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198286" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we contain this outbreak, it will go a long way to establishing an alliance between the Republic and the Tion Hegemony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198287" id2="17" version="1065353216">People are dying down there. This isn't about politics!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198287" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that all you care about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything is about politics. Odds are this outbreak wasn't accidental.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any new details on the plague?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198291" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish we knew more, but we don't even know how this started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198293" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clearly someone wants to destabilize the sector. Probably a bid by a rival family to seize power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198295" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to find out... before the plague spreads to the Republic Core Worlds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198296" id2="17" version="1065353216">You planning on sending anyone else on this mission?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198296" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reinforcements would help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198297" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to limit Republic exposure to the virus. But you've dealt with the rakghouls before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems like the best way to keep the virus from spreading is to wipe out Kaon from orbit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just bomb the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198300" id2="17" version="1065353216">That won't tell us how the outbreak started, and it won't win us any points with the royal family.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198302" id2="17" version="1065353216">That won't happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198303" id2="17" version="1065353216">We better hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198304" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a shuttle to take you down to the surface. Major Byzal, head of Kaon security, will contact you when you land.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Help the survivors if you can. But your first priority is to find out how the virus is being spread.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
