<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>57</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/taris/multi/republic/w6_s4.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Officially, what happened with Doctor Lorrick never happened. But unofficially, that was nice work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198314" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chief Rannos is waiting for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198318" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi. Name's Whisper. My boss needs to speak with you. The fate of the Republic is at stake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir. Name's Whisper. My boss needs to speak with you. We have a situation that requires Havoc Squad's unique touch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain. Name's Whisper. My boss needs to speak with you about an urgent--and potentially profitable--matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198324" id2="17" version="1065353216">Name's Whisper. My boss needs to speak with you. Top priority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me a second to set up a secure connection... okay, boss--you're good to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198328" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Chief Rannos, of Republic SIS. I've been looking over your files. Obviously, I'm impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198330" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're quite the collection of heroes. The Republic wouldn't be here if it wasn't for you. Just the kind of team I need for this job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198331" id2="17" version="1065353216">You went toe-to-toe with the Emperor and came out on top. That's the kind of person I need for this job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198332" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic couldn't have survived without the Rift Alliance. That was nice work. Exactly the kind of thing I'm looking for on this job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Taking out General Rakton turned the tide of the war. You know how to get things done. Just what I need for this mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198334" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did a nice job getting Shariss Kartur out of a tight spot. When this mission came up, first person I thought of was you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198335" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got quite the track record. Just the kind of agent I need for this mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198336" id2="17" version="1065353216">My order is sworn to defend the Republic. I take that vow seriously.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198336" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi won't let you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198337" id2="17" version="1065353216">This time the threat is a little different. We don't think the Empire is involved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198339" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt this mission involves the Empire; our recent victories have left them too weak to challenge us directly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198339" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sense a new enemy has risen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198340" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right. We don't think the Empire is involved. But that doesn't make the situation any less dire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wouldn't want Havoc Squad's skills to get rusty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198342" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm always looking for action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198343" id2="17" version="1065353216">No fear of that. The Empire may be staggering, but they aren't the only threat to the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198345" id2="17" version="1065353216">I miss the good old days. You know, when I wasn't the first person everyone turned to when they needed a hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure I like being famous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198346" id2="17" version="1065353216">It can't be all that bad. I hear saving the galaxy can be very lucrative. Look at this job as a business opportunity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198348" id2="17" version="1065353216">You didn't need to send an agent to track me down. It's not like I'm hard to find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why all the cloak-and-dagger?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198349" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a delicate political matter. Discretion is required.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198351" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me the details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198352" id2="17" version="1065353216">You heard of the Tion Hegemony? It's an independent sector located along key hyperspace shipping lanes. Wealthy, powerful and stubborn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198354" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been trying to form an alliance with them for years. So have the Imps. Neither side has made much progress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our recent battles with the Empire have drained resources from both sides. The Tion Hegemony is more valuable than ever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198357" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're looking for someone to negotiate a treaty, you better look somewhere else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198357" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not a diplomat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198358" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand, Chief Rannos. You want me to negotiate the terms of an alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198358" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to secure a treaty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Negotiation was the original plan. But things have gone off the rails. Big time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly how strong are they? Any chance they might try to take on the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are they a threat?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's just say we've been keeping a close eye on them. Good thing, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like SIS business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198365" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to drop the bombshell, Chief.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198367" id2="17" version="1065353216">We intercepted a series of classified transmissions. The Tion Hegemony's in trouble. Their worlds are being overrun by rakghouls!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198369" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unchecked, the rakghoul outbreak will be catastrophic. Billions will be infected. We're looking at the planet-wide annihilation of all civilized life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198370" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rakghoul plague has been successfully contained to a single world for centuries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198370" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did they get off Taris?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198371" id2="17" version="1065353216">Figuring out how it spread to other worlds is of vital importance. The outbreak needs to be contained.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198373" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials were experimenting with rakghouls on Taris. They must have decided to take their research offworld.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198373" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's behind this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198374" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's one possibility. But the Empire's fighting just to stay alive. Why would they mess with the Tion Hegemony now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198376" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on my way!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198377" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not so fast. The Republic has no authority in the Tion Hegemony. You can't just go barging in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198379" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a delicate situation. We still don't have all the details, and the Tion royal family isn't talking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198381" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to meet face-to-face to figure out our next step. Whisper will give you the location of my ship. Rannos out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198383" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's the boss's coordinates. He'll be waiting for you. And if this is as bad as it seems, you better hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198387" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't mind me. Just scoping things out.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
