<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>29</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/class/spy/recording.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488730" id2="17" version="1065353216">Begin playback. Authorization Cipher Nine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488731" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cipher. This is infiltration operative Bax Kholer. I've assembled a list of prisoners with the skills to breach Megasecurity Ward 23.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489219" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Kanjon Slyke: assassin and escape artist. His brother died breaking into the ward some years ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489221" id2="17" version="1065353216">Slyke can reconstruct and reassess his brother's plan. He hates authority figures, Imperials included.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489223" id2="17" version="1065353216">Next, Chaney Barrow: slicer and computer expert. Former top saboteur for the Exchange. Motivated by greed and known to nurse a grudge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489225" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ohta: ex-mercenary and bounty hunter. Cast out of the Mandalorians for dishonorable conduct. He'll provide support and demolitions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489227" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lastly, Paarkos: No information on his crimes, but he's an alien tracker whose species sees through walls--handy to have around traps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489229" id2="17" version="1065353216">These people are volatile and extremely dangerous. Present yourself as a fellow inmate--do not reveal your allegiance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489231" id2="17" version="1065353216">Burly men and touchy alien freaks. It's like running with the old gang.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Somehow, I don't think this group will be together long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enjoy it while it lasts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489233" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like I said.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489235" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're releasing a dark swarm upon this world. These people will be our responsibility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489236" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't cause any problems. I won't let them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489236" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489237" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never met a career criminal before. It's a little terrifying, but I'm kind of looking forward to this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489238" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll meet a lot more in this job. It's how I got my start.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it a lesson.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489239" id2="17" version="1065353216">The career criminal is as predictable and insufferable as a small child. I hope you're a stern parent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489240" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can keep a few gangsters under control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489240" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle the criminals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489241" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. I'll watch your back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489243" id2="17" version="1065353216">Resume playback.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489243" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hear the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489244" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll kill each other if we don't kill them first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489244" id2="17" version="1065353216">This looks like a disaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489245" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll use explosives to free the prisoners. Tag each prison cell with a blasting cap, then head to the Republic security center.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use the security consoles to disable any fail-safes and make contact with the prisoners. You can detonate the blasting caps remotely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489249" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maps and safe house coordinates are attached. You're on your own now.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
