<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>26</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/class/spy/scorpio.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like a child mutilating a doll, you have triumphed over primitive technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508981" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you cannot conceive of the weapons I possess. Things your kind was not permitted to see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508982" id2="17" version="1065353216">You keep talking about &quot;forbidden tech&quot;... how'd you get it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508982" id2="17" version="1065353216">What weapons are those?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508983" id2="17" version="1065353216">My benefactors have been useful, at times.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508985" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen--I'm not here to harm you. I just need information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508985" id2="17" version="1065353216">We shouldn't be enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your weakness is not mine. I find no value in negotiation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your threats are getting old. Let's settle this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508988" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm tired of your bluster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not yet. But everything is on schedule.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508991" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you destroyed the core machine, you unleashed my microdroid swarm. Automata like gnats that can drill through flesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508993" id2="17" version="1065353216">They will infect your associate, and by the time you reach Megasecurity Ward 23, you will stand alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508994" id2="17" version="1065353216">You already stand alone. By the time you reach Megasecurity Ward 23 you will be on your knees, trembling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508996" id2="17" version="1065353216">So few creatures seek to penetrate Megasecurity Ward 23. My benefactors hide themselves too well and deprive me of entertainment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508998" id2="17" version="1065353216">It blinded and destroyed them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508999" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seek what my benefactors hid. For what purpose?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their ambitions are not my concern, but so too are they beyond your understanding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509002" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are now a carrier, too. It is unlikely to kill you, but the symptoms are unpleasant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509003" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is an interspecies disease eliminated in the wider galaxy but secretly stored on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509004" id2="17" version="1065353216">The poor creatures before you are innocent carriers of a plague called the Blue Crescent virus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509005" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you think you're going to find a great secret in Megasecurity Ward 23, I assure you that you will not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509007" id2="17" version="1065353216">My benefactors have put a thousand years of forbidden technology at my disposal, and I can stop you at any time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509009" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only question is how to do so most effectively.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509010" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can see you through my monitors. Away from your gang, you shed your identity and take on new attributes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509012" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer you in this form. You are slightly less predictable, and bear further observation.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
