<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>107</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/class/spy/watcher_three.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509214" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Cipher Nine to headquarters. Stand by for databank upload.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509215" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watcher Three here. Standing by.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509217" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no loyalty to my former masters and I will transmit my information, but the result will not save you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509219" id2="17" version="1065353216">They planted me in Belsavis as a guardian, not as collector of their secrets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509220" id2="17" version="1065353216">The man in the kolto tank said your databanks would lead us to the enemy. Maybe you don't realize what you have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509220" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must know things, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509221" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were built by them, weren't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509221" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did they create you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509222" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assembled from machines beyond your comprehension and embedded with heuristic techniques.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509224" id2="17" version="1065353216">After approximately one hundred fifty years of service as a mindless droid, I acquired true sentience. No memory wipe commenced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509226" id2="17" version="1065353216">You claim you aren't loyal, but you've worked awfully hard to stop me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509226" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't try to protect them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509227" id2="17" version="1065353216">My position as jailer of Megasecurity Ward 23 provided challenges. These challenges forced my adaptation and growth into an evolved mentality.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509229" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm receiving, sir. The data formatting is unusual, but I found a log--visitations to the Megasecurity Ward, technology inventories....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509231" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not much on its own, but it could be a way to verify or disprove anything else we've learned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509233" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cipher! Something hit us from the docking bay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509235" id2="17" version="1065353216">I shall observe your investigation with interest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509239" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is headquarters to Cipher Nine. Clearing your arrival with station control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509241" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cipher. You're now orbiting forty thousand kilometers above Belsavis--the Republic's largest penal colony. Fancy rebuilding your criminal reputation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509242" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does the Republic need with a jail the size of a planet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509242" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis is a prison?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509243" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you swapped your sense of humor for the promotion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509243" id2="17" version="1065353216">You remembered how to joke!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509244" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only in part. Proceed, Watcher Three.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509246" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've killed pirates on a half-dozen worlds. A few more shouldn't make a difference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509246" id2="17" version="1065353216">Depends how bloody it gets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509247" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's more than ex-pirates here, I'm afraid. Watcher Three?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509249" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis prison was built in secret to hold the galaxy's most dangerous individuals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509251" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three main levels, thousands of specialized cell blocks holding everyone from changelings to Sith Lords.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509253" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've known of the prison's existence for nearly a year. Now we understand that the conspirators subverted Belsavis to their own use.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509254" id2="17" version="1065353216">You say &quot;subverted.&quot; Not infiltrated, not taken over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509254" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me what we know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509255" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sound pretty confident, given the circumstances.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509255" id2="17" version="1065353216">How'd you figure that out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509256" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's all about following the record trail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't they be shocked when I show up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509258" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're in for a surprise now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509259" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they're not, we have a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509261" id2="17" version="1065353216">The conspirators pulled strings with Republic higher-ups to construct a special section: Megasecurity Ward 23.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509263" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's somewhere past the alien cells and the genocide ward... they built it and sealed it when Belsavis was founded. No one gets inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509265" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's the highest-security area of the best-protected prison in the galaxy. You're going to break in and find what it's hiding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lay out our resources. How do we do this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509266" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509267" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume they've left more than a padlock to protect it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509267" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the security.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509268" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't know. The rest of the prison uses everything from lasers to force fields to sanitization gas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509270" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're assuming what's in there is worth finding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509270" id2="17" version="1065353216">This could be a fool's errand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509271" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you build a cell like that, it's because you can't afford intruders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509273" id2="17" version="1065353216">Two decades ago, a prison gang heard about the ward and tried to breach it, hoping something inside would help them escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thieves, security experts--the underworld's best. None of them made it back, but they had the right idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509277" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll assemble your own gang from the prison. Establish yourself as a fellow inmate and succeed where the last group failed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lead the prisoners on a mission into their own jail. Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone particular in mind for my &quot;gang&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are these prisoners?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509280" id2="17" version="1065353216">Taking prisoners along is liable to get us all killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509280" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know I work better alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509281" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, sir. It's the best we could do on short notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509283" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find supplies and a detailed dossier at our outpost on the planet surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509285" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our military forces are encouraging riots as part of the war effort. It's distracting the Republic and should conceal your operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509287" id2="17" version="1065353216">But don't be mistaken. The prisoners are not grateful. Keeper out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509289" id2="17" version="1065353216">With Keeper gone, sir, I'm afraid I'll have to brief you alone. Pulling our files on Belsavis prison now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Start from the beginning. What sort of prison?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis is a prison?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509291" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take your time, Watcher Three. I trust you can get this right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509291" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you'll do fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509292" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... appreciate that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509294" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're not prepared, you're not competent to brief me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509294" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is pathetic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509295" id2="17" version="1065353216">With due respect, sir--I'm doing the work of four Watchers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509297" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis is a secret Republic penal colony, built for the most dangerous captives. Changelings, Sith Lords, mass murderers--all of them with special cells, special security.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keeper believed the conspirators had subverted the prison and were somehow using it themselves. Files reference something called... &quot;Megasecurity Ward 23.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509300" id2="17" version="1065353216">High security zone, I'm assuming. Any details?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509300" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess that's our goal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509301" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does that mean? Are the conspirators running the place?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509301" id2="17" version="1065353216">Subverted the prison?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509302" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think so--they probably don't need to, if they can forge Republic documents. All the power, none of the responsibility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509304" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're trying my patience. Send me Keeper's files, I'll read them myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me you've got something else</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509305" id2="17" version="1065353216">It isn't--I'm sorry. I do have a lead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509307" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keeper referred to the Megasecurity Ward as a type-zero site; built and used actively by the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509309" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like it's been sealed for years, though. The best-protected spot in the galaxy's worst jail... the conspirators could have anything, anyone locked in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509310" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've never even come close to conspirator territory before. This is big.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509310" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll finally see their turf.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509311" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe so, yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509313" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the setup? If there's food and water, it could have people. Just power, some sort of technology storage....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we guess what's inside?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509314" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks entirely self-contained--but it could have its own generators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect honeypot. Lure in your enemies, then lock them up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509316" id2="17" version="1065353216">It could be a trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keeper always believed in springing traps, not avoiding them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, you'll need a way in. Watcher Six had a log...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509321" id2="17" version="1065353216">...twenty-four ships lost taking the Pyria system. Our victories are great, but our resources--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wrong file.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509325" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our infiltration operative on Belsavis reports a previous attempt to breach Megasecurity Ward 23 by a group of prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Evidently, they hoped to find resources for an escape attempt. None survived, but the theory is sound.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509329" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Cipher agent could assemble a new gang and repeat the break-in attempt; our operative was to deliver a full proposal to the outpost. Status unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509330" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assemble a team of prisoners to breach their jail's Megasecurity Ward. I've heard worse plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509330" id2="17" version="1065353216">So I'm going to lead a gang.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509331" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was hoping there'd be more than that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does the message continue?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509332" id2="17" version="1065353216">So was I, but the next entry goes back to reports from the front. Which... I should be reviewing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Working with the scum of the galaxy again. On my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509334" id2="17" version="1065353216">This'll be just like old times.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our outpost she mentioned is being used by the military to stage a breakout; a Belsavis prison riot diverts Republic resources from the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Check our operative's drop point there, but mind the rioters. Watcher Three out.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
