<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>234</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/jedi_knight/chapter_3/multi/master_satele_shan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493002" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galaxy is in your debt once again, but I fear this is far from over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493005" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you reforge your connection to the light side, you will be a Jedi Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493006" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rank of Master carries great responsibilities, but you are ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493011" id2="17" version="1065353216">You saved our galaxy from destruction. The Emperor's death has turned the tide of this war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Combined with our success on Corellia and the damage inflicted on Dromund Kaas, the Sith are in chaos. It's glorious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493014" id2="17" version="1065353216">For too long, the Republic has feared the Sith Empire. Today, we've proven they aren't invincible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493014" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was long overdue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493015" id2="17" version="1065353216">You raised the morale of every Republic soldier from Coruscant to Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without the Emperor's control, the Sith might be even more dangerous and unpredictable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493017" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's also troubling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not if we keep the enemy off balance. For the first time since the war started, we have the upper hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Today, we avenged the Sacking of Coruscant and the destruction of the Jedi Temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493020" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll crush the Sith forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, we will tighten our grip until the last Sith is extinct and their Empire crumbles into nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493023" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic stands united in that cause. Even the neutral worlds rally to our side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493025" id2="17" version="1065353216">For your victory on Corellia, General Var Suthra recommended you all receive the Medal of Bravery. But you've earned more than that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493027" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is my honor to present each of you with the Republic's highest award: the Cross of Glory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493029" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will live forever as heroes of the Republic. Jedi Knight Kira Carsen... Sergeant Fideltin Rusk... Teeseven Oh-one... Doctor Archiban Kimble....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Archiban? Seriously?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just call me Doc. Please.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even you, Lord Scourge. Though you joined us for selfish reasons, you saved more lives than your own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scourge will be a Jedi before he knows it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493036" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's learning to be a hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not count on that. I remain only until I am certain the Emperor left us no surprises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493039" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor is dead, and you're still with us. Why?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why have you stayed, Scourge?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where else can he go? The Sith want him dead. We're the only friends he's got.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493042" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not require friends or protection. I will stay until I am certain the Emperor left us no surprises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493044" id2="17" version="1065353216">You didn't hear him telling the others to commit suicide down on Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493044" id2="17" version="1065353216">The man is still a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493045" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your honors. I am not a citizen of your Republic--nor am I one of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until I am certain the Emperor left us no surprises, I will stay. Beyond that, I promise nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493049" id2="17" version="1065353216">And then there is you. How do we even begin to account for the turns your life has taken since you first arrived on Tython?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493051" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dark side has cast its shadow over you. I sense your anger and ambition growing. I can no longer ignore it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493053" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wanted so much for you to become a Jedi Master, but you are not ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493054" id2="17" version="1065353216">What have I done to deserve being passed over? I've saved trillions of people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493054" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493055" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your battles on Corellia cost us Master Kiwiiks and dozens of brave Jedi. Your leadership there was questionable, at best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493057" id2="17" version="1065353216">How much have you sacrificed on your path to victory? What emotions drove these decisions? These are the questions we must answer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493059" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still have much to learn about being a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493059" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are right, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hearing you admit that gives me hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493062" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've done more for the Republic than the whole Jedi Council combined.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493062" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a lie.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, do not make this any harder than it is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493065" id2="17" version="1065353216">You struck a great blow against the Sith, but the war goes on. There will be other opportunities for you to prove yourself worthy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele, this Jedi is one of the greatest war heroes I've ever met. She deserves recognition for her victories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele, this Jedi is one of the greatest war heroes I've ever met. He deserves recognition for his victories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493071" id2="17" version="1065353216">By the authority of the Supreme Chancellor, I hereby grant you the honorary rank of Republic general.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493072" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Admiral. Maybe my destiny isn't with the Jedi Order. Being a soldier feels right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493072" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a pleasure to serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493073" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one salutes an &quot;honorary&quot; officer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493073" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a worthless title.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493074" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assure you, you'll be treated with the respect you deserve. I'll see to it personally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493076" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could learn from the admiral, Satele. He knows how to show his appreciation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493076" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's more like it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me be the first to salute you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493079" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will speak of this another time. For now, let us mourn what we have lost and celebrate all we have gained.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493081" id2="17" version="1065353216">For this one moment, the galaxy is safe. May the Force be with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493082" id2="17" version="1065353216">You embody what every Jedi strives to become. Your courage, commitment and leadership have seen us through this dark time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493084" id2="17" version="1065353216">From this day forward, you are no longer a Jedi Knight. You are a Jedi Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493085" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will uphold the Jedi Code and bring justice to the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493085" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Master Satele.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493086" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a lot of responsibility. I'm so young, Master Satele.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure I'm ready?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Young, yes. Wise and good, even more so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493089" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you'd never get around to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493089" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's about time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493090" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be mindful of your emotions, Master--but I appreciate your honest enthusiasm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493092" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are the moments we strive for, when the hope of victory becomes real. When we can see peace on the horizon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493094" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493100" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele, the Emperor is dead. Do you read me? The Emperor is dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493101" id2="17" version="1065353216">We read you loud and clear. Imperial warships are dropping out of hyperspace all around us. We must retreat from Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493103" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rendezvous with the Republic flagship Valiant at these coordinates. I'll meet you there. Master Satele out....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493107" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see your crew survived without unnecessary heroics from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="493109" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Rusk = saved Doc // Jedi = ignored emergency alert</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="493110" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doc = saved Kira // Jedi = ignored emergency alert</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="493111" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kira = saved Sergeant Rusk // Jedi = ignored emergency alert</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493112" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could either save the galaxy or rescue my crew. I had to focus on the greater good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493112" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was a difficult choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493113" id2="17" version="1065353216">I shouldn't have left it up to anyone else. You people are my responsibility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493113" id2="17" version="1065353216">I regret not going myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493114" id2="17" version="1065353216">This crew needs to stop pretending I owe it anything. My mission is saving the galaxy, not you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493114" id2="17" version="1065353216">You people need to toughen up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493115" id2="17" version="1065353216">If sarge hadn't pulled me out of the fire, the galaxy would be down one Doc. And there's only one of me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have any idea how embarrassing it was to be rescued by that walking hormone?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493119" id2="17" version="1065353216">The operation was successful, regardless. Kira and I inflicted heavy damage on the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493121" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's done is done. Our orders are clear. We should set course for the flagship Valiant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493122" id2="17" version="1065353216">You gave the Emperor time to gather his strength. We are all fortunate to be alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493123" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of my crew was in danger. If I had to make that choice again, I'd do the same thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493123" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did what was right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493124" id2="17" version="1065353216">To repeat a mistake and expect a beneficial outcome is a sign of insanity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493126" id2="17" version="1065353216">Luck wasn't a factor. I trusted my instincts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493126" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force was with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493127" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some instincts are sharper than others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493129" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you seriously criticizing me for not following your stupid plan? I just saved the galaxy, you idiot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493129" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't blame me, you jerk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493130" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's gonna be a long flight. Somebody wake me when we get there....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493133" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele, my mission on Corellia is complete. Republic forces have gained the upper hand, and Master Braga is no longer aiding the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493135" id2="17" version="1065353216">I successfully broke the Emperor's domination over him. Master Braga is on his way to Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493136" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is welcome news. We'll take good care of him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493137" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor's domination of Master Braga was too strong. I had to kill him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493138" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a terrible loss. I'm sure you did your best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493139" id2="17" version="1065353216">I managed to break the Emperor's domination of him. Master Braga is now sabotaging Imperial forces from within.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493140" id2="17" version="1065353216">I worry for him. I hope he returns here soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493141" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've also learned the Emperor is on Dromund Kaas. His efforts against us have weakened him. Our enemy is vulnerable--for now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493142" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor is determined to destroy the galaxy. It's him, or us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493144" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must face the Emperor again. And this time, you cannot fail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493145" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm stronger than the last time we met.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493145" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do my best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493146" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Council should join me. At the very least, you should come.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493146" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're sending me alone?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493147" id2="17" version="1065353216">The risk is too great. You're the only Jedi who resisted his corrupting influence. Others might fall to the dark side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493149" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor won't survive our next meeting. That's a promise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider him dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493150" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be mindful of anger. It is a weapon the Emperor could easily turn against you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493152" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dromund Kaas is the Imperial capitol. Legions of Sith call it home. The remaining population is almost entirely Imperial military.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493154" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're invading a planet of people who want us dead. We'll have to fight for every centimeter of ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493155" id2="17" version="1065353216">We won't even be able to land on Dromund Kaas unless the enemy is too distracted to notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493155" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're going to need help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493156" id2="17" version="1065353216">There must be some way to achieve our goal without violence. Could we disguise ourselves, somehow?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we sneak in?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493157" id2="17" version="1065353216">No spy ever sent to Dromund Kaas has returned alive--and we have no time for elaborate ruses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493159" id2="17" version="1065353216">For once, I won't have to worry about civilian casualties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493159" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least I can kill everyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493160" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are no civilians where we're going. Everyone you meet will be armed and will try to kill you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493162" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must surprise the Empire by doing what they least expect: a frontal assault on their homeworld.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi and Republic warships will converge on Dromund Kaas and engage the Imperial fleet. We will mask your assault on the surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele, that's a suicide mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493165" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll all be killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493166" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you defeat the Emperor, whatever sacrifices are required will not be in vain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493168" id2="17" version="1065353216">The real fight will be on the planet. Can you spare anyone for that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493168" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about ground troops?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493169" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll attract less attention without your forces stirring up the Imperial army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493171" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I try to land, they'll shoot me down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493171" id2="17" version="1065353216">That won't be enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493172" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will help you navigate the planet's defense network and land safely. After that, no promises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your success or failure will not merely decide the galaxy's fate. It will change everything--forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find the Emperor and stop him once and for all. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493183" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admiral Dabrin and his flagship are safe, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493185" id2="17" version="1065353216">We also captured Warren alive, but you'll find he's... changed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493186" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were able to help Leeha Narezz. We'll find a way to help Warren.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493187" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dark side had consumed Warren. He refused to surrender. He's dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493188" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know killing a former ally must have been difficult.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493189" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warren revealed Master Braga is on Corellia. He's the Emperor's secret weapon in the war there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493190" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is sending everything it has to liberate Corellia. If Master Braga is aiding the enemy....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493192" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor has no interest in keeping Corellia. He desires the deaths of billions to fuel his ritual.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493194" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find Master Braga and stop this madness. Set course for Corellia immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493200" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of our missing Jedi has resurfaced, and the news isn't good. Warren Sedoru has attacked and boarded the Republic flagship Valiant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493201" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the Emperor's doing. Warren is being controlled, just like Leeha Narezz was.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493201" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warren is just a pawn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493202" id2="17" version="1065353216">That hardly matters to our military. All they see is a Jedi turned traitor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493204" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is Warren after?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493204" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we know why?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493205" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did an old, pacifist Jedi invade a battle cruiser?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493205" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's only one man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493206" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warren's gift for infiltration is unmatched--and he's backed by Imperial commandos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493208" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Valiant is commanded by Admiral Dabrin, one of our top military leaders. He's inflicted heavy casualties on Imperial forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admiral Dabrin possesses complete knowledge of the Republic's war plans. If the Imperial military gains that information, they'll crush us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493212" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're missing the point. The fallen Jedi serves the Emperor's agenda. We must learn his mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493213" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have plenty of reasons to pursue this. Where are we headed, Master Satele?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493213" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then let's go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493214" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've found Leeha and Warren, but no sign of Master Braga. Maybe Warren knows where to find him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493214" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about Master Braga?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493215" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not everything missing should be found.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493217" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've defeated the plots against Voss and Belsavis. What more can your old boss have planned?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493217" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think there's more?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493218" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor is the most patient being in the galaxy. He's waited centuries to enact his ritual--and he's plotted for every conceivable interference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493220" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Valiant is drifting out of control at these coordinates. Liberate it, save the admiral and learn the Emperor's plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493222" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry--the Valiant's crew can't hold out much longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493227" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele, I stopped Lord Fulminiss. He created a madness-inducing plague to turn this planet's inhabitants against each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493229" id2="17" version="1065353216">If he'd succeeded, Voss would've exploded into mindless violence. The entire planet would be a slaughterhouse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493230" id2="17" version="1065353216">The brutality of the Sith knows no bounds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493232" id2="17" version="1065353216">I applaud you for a job well-done. I know it wasn't easy dealing with the Voss people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493233" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss are strange, but in the end, I needed their help to win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493233" id2="17" version="1065353216">I worked out a compromise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493234" id2="17" version="1065353216">It shows true strength to admit to needing help from others. I hope strength enough for what I must ask of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493236" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss customs are strange, but there is wisdom in much of what they believe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493236" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss aren't so bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493237" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is an intriguing assessment--and the first favorable one I've heard. I will have to investigate your claim, someday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493239" id2="17" version="1065353216">The entire planet has been brainwashed by the Mystics. The Voss can't scratch their own noses without consulting their all-powerful rulers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493239" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a bunch of lunatics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493240" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss show us what happens when the power of the Force is abused. Our order may have to take action against the Mystics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493242" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right now, however, we have more pressing concerns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele... I rescued Jomar and found Leeha Narezz. She's been under the Emperor's control and needs your help. They're headed for Tython now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493249" id2="17" version="1065353216">I also learned a high-ranking Sith named Fulminiss is on the planet Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493250" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is disturbing news. Voss was discovered only recently. Its society is dangerously unbalanced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493252" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people worship an elite group of Force-users who rule with absolute authority. Despite our best efforts, Voss's government rejects the Jedi Code.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493254" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor has always taken a great interest in that world. I thought he sought to conquer it, but clearly he intends its destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493256" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go to Voss. Find Lord Fulminiss and stop his plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493260" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is a rumor of high-ranking Sith gathering at a remote Imperial space station, allegedly on the Emperor's orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493262" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of our best scouts volunteered to investigate. He's disappeared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like there's truth to this rumor. Tell me everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493263" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should look into this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sneaking into enemy territory is dangerous. Who is this scout?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who is he?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493265" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's the man you replaced on Master Braga's strike team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493267" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rumors are good bait to lure a desperate Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493267" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493268" id2="17" version="1065353216">That, or the rumors are correct.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jomar Chul attempted to infiltrate the Imperial space station where the Sith are meeting and hasn't checked in since.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493272" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you and Jomar have had differences, but I believe he's on to something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493273" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Emperor is involved, this may reveal his plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493273" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493274" id2="17" version="1065353216">After the accusations he made to the Council, I doubt he'll help me--assuming he's alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jomar doesn't trust me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493275" id2="17" version="1065353216">My only concern is uncovering the Emperor's plans. We need to know what's happening on that station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493277" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get your hopes up. He's probably dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493277" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're assuming he's alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regardless, you're now our best hope of learning what's happening on that station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493280" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is worth pursuing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493282" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm transmitting coordinates to the space station. I have no advice for getting inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493284" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave that to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493286" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493291" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele, Executor Krannus and his followers are dead. Belsavis is safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493293" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor would never devote all his resources to Belsavis. We must find his other targets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anybody here a droid medic? This little guy took some rough hits. Wouldn't have made it back without him, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493301" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teeseven's in bad shape. He came to help me fight some Imperials, and they hit him with an ion weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your astromech droid was severely damaged, Master Jedi. It abandoned its post to support my mission and was attacked by Imperial forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="493305" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = hero?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493306" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sacrificed yourself to save another's life. That's the definition of a hero, Teeseven.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493306" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right, you're a hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="493307" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = relieved // Sacrifice = not in vain</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493309" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you wouldn't fail me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493309" id2="17" version="1065353216">You always have been.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493310" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're no hero. You're just a machine that carried out my orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="493310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get full of yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493311" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anybody who saves my neck is a hero. I just wish you were flesh and blood. That, I could fix.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't listen to that nonsense, Teeseven. You'll always be my hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493315" id2="17" version="1065353216">As machines go, he's a good one.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="493317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Price of victory = T7's memory core // T7's earliest data records = lost // File corruption = permanent</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493319" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll patch him up and stop that memory corruption before it gets worse. Let's head for the Valiant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493320" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi I gave you to retake Corellia were nearly eradicated. At a minimum, that reflects poorly on your leadership.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493322" id2="17" version="1065353216">For your actions on Corellia, General Var Suthra recommended you all receive the Crescent of Service. But you've earned more than that.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
