<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>98</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/bronze/food_chain/ghitter_mannes.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296918" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now we can get down to the real business of throwing those Imperials out on their ears.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296920" id2="17" version="1065353216">If your device works, the Colicoids should start leaving in droves.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296921" id2="17" version="1065353216">They are! I just got a report from one of my field researchers. There's been more movement away from the nesting sites than we've seen in four years!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Last known course, it looked like they were heading straight for an Imperial encampment!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen for the screams, my friends....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without the Colicoids to divide our attention, we'll turn our full efforts to driving out the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296928" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, give it to me straight. Does the Republic give a womp rat's whiskers for what happens to real Balmorrans?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296930" id2="17" version="1065353216">I mean, no offense to any of you personally.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296932" id2="17" version="1065353216">I mean, no offense to the Jedi Order.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296934" id2="17" version="1065353216">I mean, I know you got your orders to follow and that's that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296936" id2="17" version="1065353216">I mean, I hear you got some kind of connection to the Republic bigwigs.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296938" id2="17" version="1065353216">But so far, they haven't been any more interested in my defense against the Colicoids than the Empire was.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me what you have and maybe I can speak for the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296939" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm interested.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296940" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't speak for the Republic, but if this is something marketable, count me in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296940" id2="17" version="1065353216">I might be interested.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296941" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that some kind of native animal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296941" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colicoids?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colicoids are giant insects. The ones here went feral out of a project breeding for low intelligence and high aggression.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296944" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this a sales pitch?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296945" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been studying the Colicoids for years. They've been steadily colonizing this part of Balmorra. Even drove the Empire out of parts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296947" id2="17" version="1065353216">Made lunch meat from most of the population. But I finally got the secret to driving them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296949" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you spray the pheromones of larger predators on their nesting sites, it sends them running with their tails between their chitinous little legs!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296950" id2="17" version="1065353216">I imagine larger predators don't eagerly give up their pheromones?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296950" id2="17" version="1065353216">You looking for help?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296951" id2="17" version="1065353216">That, ah, is some of the problem. Yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296954" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't my concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296955" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've built a device that spreads the pheromones over a suitable range, but I haven't been able to collect enough to use it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything big enough to scare a Colicoid also sends most sane people running.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296958" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people of Balmorra deserve to be free of this menace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course I'll help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now you're talking, Master Jedi! Make up for walking out on us in the first place, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296961" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no room for fear in the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296961" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am not afraid.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect! I heard you Jedi weren't much on self-preservation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296964" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is our base of operations. How can we retake this world if we're worrying about Colicoids overrunning it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296964" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't ignore the problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296965" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly! They should put you in charge of this operation. Maybe it'd get somewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thing I'm not sane!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't scare me!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296968" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha! I knew I liked you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296970" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you need?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296971" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll show you where to find the breeding grounds for some serious critters. Just collect the secretions there and load them into this aerosol dispersal canister.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296973" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then plant it in the middle of the Colicoid nesting site and turn it on. Simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, and they may attack it before the area's fully saturated, so make sure you keep it safe long enough to work properly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not interested. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296978" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see we can't depend on the Republic to get things done for us....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296980" id2="17" version="1065353216">All this Empire/Republic claptrap makes people forget Balmorra's real problems.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at 'em scurry! Take out the big ones, and the little ones follow. Those bugs aren't as smart as they think.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without the Colicoids to divide our attention, we'll turn our full efforts to driving out the Empire. Thanks again.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461063" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're holding our ground for now. But you'd better get to those Colicoid nests fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461066" id2="17" version="1065353216">A whole squad. The Commander must have been serious about increasing our numbers.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Bugtown, Master Jedi. I sure hope you're here to build up our defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain. I'm sure you're here on an important op, but we could really use your expertise.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461072" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard of you. You're that merc who's been terrorizing the Empire. Need a new job?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Mannes. I've been put in charge of defending HQ from the Colicoids, but frankly, I'm not sure how long we can hold out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="461075" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="461076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="461077" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're overreacting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461078" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think so. Have you seen this place? Eggs, nests, and bugs everywhere! And those are just the ones we can see.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461080" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Republic landed here, we cleared out most of the wildlife, but the Colicoid nests went deeper than we thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461082" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've already regained their numbers. At this rate, the Colicoids will overwhelm us before we ever leave Bugtown.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="461083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not if I can help it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="461084" id2="17" version="1065353216">So leave now, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461085" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a good position for HQ. We've got a clear launch zone and we're safe from the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Empire's got control of Balmorra's satellite system. No way to move troops without them knowing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="461089" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a sorry bunch.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461090" id2="17" version="1065353216">These aren't just bugs. They're giant, flesh-eating bugs, and we've become their only food source.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461092" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not the Republic army, but you're sure close. If you took out the worst of them, we could hold the line.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461093" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoids haven't been hit with the Force yet. If you took out the worst of them, we could hold the line.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="461094" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's my duty to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461095" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to know we've got the Order at our backs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="461097" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't take any risks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461098" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry about us. We can handle the odd spitter.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461100" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got more training than all of us put together. If you took out the worst of them, we could hold the line.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461101" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly. I see why you made Captain so fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461103" id2="17" version="1065353216">You landed in a warzone, so you must be pretty tough. If you took out the worst of them, we could hold the line.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="461104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ready and willing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="461105" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will be easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461106" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say that again after you've had one spit on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461108" id2="17" version="1065353216">The alpha males are the worst. Get near the nests, and they'll come running. Good luck out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="461109" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toughen up. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461110" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll fight until we're up against the wall, if we have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461111" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch out for the Colicoids. They'll eat you alive without blinking.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461114" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been studying the Colicoids for years. They've been steadily colonizing Balmorra. Even drove the Empire out of parts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461116" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoids have always made their nests down here. But ever since the Republic arrived, the adults are hunting on higher ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461117" id2="17" version="1065353216">We want the Empire gone as much as the Republic does. But it's hard to fight when the Colicoids are turning you into lunch-meat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="461118" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry to hear that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461119" id2="17" version="1065353216">Usually the Republic acts like they're fighting alone. But we're all in this together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="461121" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need some backup.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461122" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, the Republic brought this on us. The least you could do is try to make it right.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461124" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your Farnel Outpost used to be Farnel Research Facility. They developed a gas that could wipe out a Colicoid nest in one blast.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461126" id2="17" version="1065353216">We wipe out the nests, we wipe out the bugs. Then Balmorra could start helping the Republic instead of becoming bug food.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="461127" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need someone skilled.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="461129" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you put it like that....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461130" id2="17" version="1065353216">The gas is stored in underground pipes connected to the old facility. There are emergency release valves on each access vat.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461132" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use this canister to collect the gas, and then release it over the Colicoids' nesting sites. Their eggs will splatter everywhere!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="461133" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Colicoids could rip thirty homesteads apart. You have to wipe out their nests.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
