<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>47</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tatooine/bronze/imperial/artificial_intelligence/lieutenant_whist.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616899" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll be compiling this data for some time, I think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616902" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've brought me readings? Excellent!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616904" id2="17" version="1065353216">It looks like you were able to conduct many scans. Did the droids pose much of a threat when you encountered them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616905" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hardly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Truly? Perhaps we should have left them to mature a bit longer... but we can observe prototypes built from this data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616908" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were linked to a powerful central figure. I scanned it as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616908" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, with one exception.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616909" id2="17" version="1065353216">A hive mind, perhaps? Intriguing. I'll make sure your due diligence is properly rewarded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616911" id2="17" version="1065353216">They kept me pretty busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616912" id2="17" version="1065353216">This situation could have been avoided entirely if command would acknowledge my requests for a security detail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616914" id2="17" version="1065353216">I worked hard for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616915" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I have is what's left of my excavation budget, but you're welcome to every last credit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616917" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've ensured that Tatooine will hold no secrets from the Empire. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616918" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd attack before the droids get any smarter and decide to fortify that derelict sandcrawler.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Humblest apologies, but I have a request that requires the attention of highly trained combatants.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh! My lord, my lord! It's so good you're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616925" id2="17" version="1065353216">You there, can you tell your commander--oh, you're with Intelligence. Even better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616927" id2="17" version="1065353216">You there, I'm drafting you into the Imperial Reclamation Service's... service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Band of filthy Jawas cracked into one of the Czerka Corporation's abandoned compounds we recently unearthed. Made off with every droid in the place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616930" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you want the droids back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616931" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jawas may have foiled the ideal recovery of these artifacts, but that doesn't mean the Empire can't still benefit from the technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616933" id2="17" version="1065353216">A terrible loss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616934" id2="17" version="1065353216">Luckily, the only real damage done was to the Jawas themselves. Serves them right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616936" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't waste my talents tracking down petty thefts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunting Jawas is beneath me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616937" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not petty; these excavations produce the only thing of value on this dust bowl. Besides, the Jawas aren't the problem anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616939" id2="17" version="1065353216">You see, the stolen droids activated. Now they're systematically hunting down everything around the Jawas' derelict sandcrawler.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616941" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've observed their behaviors becoming refined, more efficient. Honestly, it looks like they're learning from trial and error.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616942" id2="17" version="1065353216">They sound like standard battle droids acting on their programming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems normal to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616943" id2="17" version="1065353216">Battle droids don't self-coordinate. Without someone giving orders, they follow basic self-defense programming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Really?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616946" id2="17" version="1065353216">If these droids are adaptive and self-coordinating, their applications would be innumerable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616948" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, stop boring me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine--the bottom line is the Empire would benefit from acquiring this technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616951" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scanning the architecture of the droids' memory cores should give us more insight into their uniform design and their individual differences.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616953" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would you all be willing to help reclaim these lost artifacts?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616954" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can the Reclamation Service count on your support?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only if I benefit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616956" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a budget for the excavation that's completely useless to me now. I don't care where it goes as long as something's recovered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616958" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll gladly pay for readings taken with this diagnostic scanner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616959" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616960" id2="17" version="1065353216">So long as you're paying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616961" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's unlikely that the droids will stand idle while you attempt to take a reading. Disabling them will be necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616963" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just try not to damage their memory cores while you're taking the fight out of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616965" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not interested. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616968" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please! I have a situation on my hands. Some other time.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
