<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>47</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/bronze/imperial/information_marketplace/officer_keeling.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170923" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've tripled our encryption algorithms. No one's cracking our security again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170926" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know. I intercepted their listening post's final transmissions. Got some Republic secrets. Even heard their dying screams.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Twice now you've saved Intelligence, and I won't forget it. Now, if you'll excuse me, surveillance duty calls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heads will roll. Promise me that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Intelligence reports you recovered? They're embedded with slicer signatures. Not from some gang, but from the Republic's Strategic Information Service!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170932" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic will answer for their spineless scheme.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170932" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170933" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only the gutless Republic would cower behind a gang of criminals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170933" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cowards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170934" id2="17" version="1065353216">They must have been hiding something. Perhaps a listening post. Maybe they're spying on us right now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170936" id2="17" version="1065353216">The SIS used the slicer gang as a decoy. They must be covering up a listening post.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clever to hide under scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170937" id2="17" version="1065353216">They think they're so smart. But wait, if they have a listening post, they may be spying on us right now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me guess. Intelligence wants the SIS outfit buried.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170939" id2="17" version="1065353216">I bet you want them dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. But first I want them to scream.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170942" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does that mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170943" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic stole these reports, then handed them to the slicer gang. Probably to keep their operation hidden.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170945" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the SIS has a listening post, they may be spying on us right now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170947" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic? You're positive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170948" id2="17" version="1065353216">The signatures don't lie.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170950" id2="17" version="1065353216">The SIS hid behind the slicer gang. But why? Maybe to disguise a listening post... maybe they're listening to us right now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170952" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you hear me, SIS dogs? The dark side is about to crush your pathetic operation. Isn't that right, my lord?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170953" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you hear me, Republic filth? Soon you'll feel the sting of Intelligence! Isn't that right, agent?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170954" id2="17" version="1065353216">You hear me, Republic slime? Nar Shaddaa's most fearsome mercenary is coming for your heads. Isn't that right, hunter?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170955" id2="17" version="1065353216">You hear me, SIS filth? Subterfuge won't save you from the Empire's wrath! Isn't that right, my friend?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170956" id2="17" version="1065353216">You hear me, SIS filth? My friends here are coming to grind your operation into the ground. Isn't that right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170958" id2="17" version="1065353216">You better believe it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170959" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've helped once already, hunter. Do this, and Intelligence will pay you well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure. Why not?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Discretion, officer. If the Republic's listening, they now know we're coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170962" id2="17" version="1065353216">So much for a surprise attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170963" id2="17" version="1065353216">I--I suppose you're right. But there's no time for subtlety.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170965" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only if you pay me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. I'll arrange payment. Whatever you want.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170968" id2="17" version="1065353216">The SIS signatures contained coordinates. Go there. Destroy the listening post. Kill everyone!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="170970" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're insane. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170971" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good idea. Make the SIS think you're not interested, then bam! Wait--where are you going?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170973" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me, I'm on surveillance duty. The things Hutts do behind closed doors....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170974" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is important. Slicers were selling Intelligence reports on the black market. I recovered them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170975" id2="17" version="1065353216">These... these are my reports!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, my lord. No telling what would happen if these fell into the wrong hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent work, agent. Glad to see we still take care of our own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170981" id2="17" version="1065353216">If these had been leaked... Intelligence thanks you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait. These reports are embedded with slicing signatures. This isn't some gang, it's the mark of the Republic's Strategic Information Service!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="170984" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, surveillance duty. Who knew the Republic leadership had such a taste for Twi'lek companionship?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
