<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>304</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x3/hk_51/republic/cc_content/hk_51.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257565" id2="17" version="1065353216">Declaration: I have completed a full system diagnostic, master. I am operating at seventy-five point three one percent efficiency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257567" id2="17" version="1065353216">Judgment: That number is unacceptably low. The Maker created me to serve at one-hundred percent efficiency. Anything less is a profound failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257568" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't expect perfection from a salvaged droid. We'll fix you up, some day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257568" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good enough for now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Conjecture: Your expectations have clearly been lowered by inferior models, master. I have seen your Teeseven unit. &quot;Disappointing&quot; does not describe it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257571" id2="17" version="1065353216">An impaired efficiency for you might be ten times the average droid's best capacity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be so hard on yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Concession: That is almost certainly true, master--but equally beside the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your parts are pretty old. They might need replacing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you need upgrades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257577" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were on ice a long time, pal. Don't worry about it until you're back to room temperature.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257577" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you're still thawing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dismissal: My chassis is designed to perform under extreme weather conditions, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257580" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who's this &quot;Maker&quot; you're referring to? Your manufacturer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257580" id2="17" version="1065353216">The &quot;Maker&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Correction: The Maker provided more than my physical form, master. It also programmed me with purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257583" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have any use for a droid that's only two percentage points away from the scrap pile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257583" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got that right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreement: You deserve nothing less than flawless performance, master. Indeed, my programming demands it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Manifesto: The Maker created me for the sole function of deleting high-ranking organic troublemakers from the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257588" id2="17" version="1065353216">These deletions must be conspicuous and provide an object lesson to other organic troublemakers. All other mission parameters are secondary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257589" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's with the euphemisms, HK? You're afraid to say &quot;killing&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257589" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Deletions&quot; sounds ridiculous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Denial: Not at all, master. I am merely practicing code words while among polite company. This is an especially useful skill in Republic space.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257592" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you can adapt to new programming, because I don't plan to go around killing anyone if I can help it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257592" id2="17" version="1065353216">My mission is peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Criticism: Your goal appears to be at odds with reactivating me. I strongly recommend revisiting your logic process.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257595" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing I enjoy more than conspicuously deleting people who get in my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to hear it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speculation: Our compatible goals may increase my efficiency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Summation: I will continue monitoring my systems, master. The process speed will increase if you employ me against your enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone will do at the present time, master. After so many years, I am not choosy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revelation: You are my favorite master by a factor of five point two six.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257606" id2="17" version="1065353216">If my advance warning systems had predicted this adulation for you, I would have thought myself defective. No offense, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257607" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never thought I'd be friends with an assassin droid. I've had to destroy all the other ones I've met.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257607" id2="17" version="1065353216">None taken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reassurance: Most assassin droids are inferior designs constructed from inexpensive components. The galaxy is no poorer for their absence, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great alliances are often born from conflicts of interest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Life is unpredictable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hypothesis: You became a Jedi because you enjoy delivering cryptic statements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257613" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a good soldier, HK. Wish I had a thousand of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257613" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you're on my squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreement: Imagine the troublemakers I could delete as an army. My combat processor's temperature raised point three three degrees just calculating it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257616" id2="17" version="1065353216">The feeling's mutual, I guess. You're not gonna try to kiss me, are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257616" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like you, too. Sort of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Opposition: I would rather not. Moisture around my vocabulator can cause a short circuit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257619" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can never tell if you're complimenting me or making a joke at my expense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257619" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a strange droid you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Encouragement: Veiled mockery is an inefficient means of expression. If I did not like you, master, you would be dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get sentimental. When your servos finally wear out, I'll scrap you without a second thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257622" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're just a machine to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Comfort: Have no fear, master. My parts will outlast yours by a considerable margin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quandary: The Maker clearly intends I fulfill my function in your service, but as a droid, I can be easily reprogrammed without my consent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Solution: I have obtained a code that permanently assigns my loyalty to you and anyone designated by you. I have only to activate it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure? Just because you enjoy serving me doesn't mean you'll like whoever I give you to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257628" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a big commitment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admiration: I trust your judgment, master. You will not assign me to someone who does not appreciate a good deletion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257631" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's better if we're always on the same side. I wouldn't want to face you in a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257631" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think that's for the best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreement: And I would not want to delete you, master. After all we have been through, that would be anticlimactic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Activate that code right now. You're my property--and always will be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257634" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're my droid, forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Testimonial: Our relationship transcends petty materialism, master. The Maker brought us together to delete troublemakers across the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Statement: Activating loyalty permanence protocols now....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confirmation: My loyalty is irrevocably assigned to you and your heirs. Congratulations, master! Let us celebrate with a mass deletion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257643" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alert: System efficiency has returned to one-hundred percent, master. And I have reactivated several combat subsystems that were previously disabled.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257645" id2="17" version="1065353216">My deletion techniques are as efficient as the day I left the factory floor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Declaration: Troublemakers beware--the Maker's greatest assassin is coming for you all!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257648" id2="17" version="1065353216">As a general rule, Jedi don't team up with assassins. What else can we call you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257648" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need a new job title.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257649" id2="17" version="1065353216">List: If you require a more polite euphemism, may I suggest: liquidator, eraser, removal expert, and my personal favorite, sterilizer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257651" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer to think of you as a friend and ally, HK.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257651" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Assassin&quot; is an ugly word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257652" id2="17" version="1065353216">Proposition: As I do not possess programming for friendship and &quot;ally&quot; is not a job title, is the term &quot;associate&quot; adequately unspecific?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257654" id2="17" version="1065353216">High Command gets a little nervous when troops toss around the &quot;a&quot; word. Let's call you an &quot;anti-personnel specialist.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257654" id2="17" version="1065353216">Try not to advertise that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assessment: Military jargon is frightfully inefficient, but the title fits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257657" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's great you're fully functional, but throttle down on the crazy monologues.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257657" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave the talking to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Retraction: My apologies. I did not mean to infringe on your area of expertise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257660" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never seen you so excited. Be careful, or you'll short-circuit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257660" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're practically giddy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257661" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reassurance: My electrical systems are well shielded from overload. Your concern is noted, however.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257663" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't wait to see you in action. We should delete somebody to celebrate. Any suggestions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pick someone to go delete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257664" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indecision: I cannot settle on any single one of your many troublemakers. Why not simply delete them all?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Resolution: You will soon see my full combat capabilities. Prepare to be awed, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257671" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see you're back in one piece. How are your systems doing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257672" id2="17" version="1065353216">Report: I have finally terminated my efficiency-reducing subroutine--and the galaxy contains one less troublemaker.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Qualification: I only wish my deletion techniques had not been so sub-par. I measured an abysmal fifty-two point oh-nine percent efficiency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257675" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did fine. I don't expect perfection, HK.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257675" id2="17" version="1065353216">You got the job done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Demand: Do not treat me like one of your crew mates. Unlike them, I was built for success.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at it this way: you were one-hundred percent efficient at protecting the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257678" id2="17" version="1065353216">You saved good people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257679" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dismissal: I do not require &quot;cheering up,&quot; master. I was merely evaluating my performance as a professional.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257681" id2="17" version="1065353216">You took down the enemy. Doesn't matter how efficiently you did it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257681" id2="17" version="1065353216">You eliminated a threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257682" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contradiction: Applying proper deletion techniques always matters, master. The Maker expects nothing less than perfect execution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be so hard on yourself. When we're teamed up, we measure two-hundred and fifty-two percent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257684" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll do better with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suspicion: Your math skills are dubious at best, master. I recommend always counting your credits three times, from now on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257687" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any sign your systems are improving?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257687" id2="17" version="1065353216">Feeling any better yet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you'll feel better after crossing the other two troublemakers off your list.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go delete the other targets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Resignation: Unfortunately, both men have relocated while I was otherwise engaged. If the Maker wills me a second shot, I promise to take it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assertion: When I finish recompiling my combat processor algorithms, my deletion techniques will elevate substantially.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257693" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suggestion: Inflicting a few well-deserved deletions should greatly speed along that process, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Announcement: Good news, master! I have discovered an exploitable flaw in my Imperial programming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257704" id2="17" version="1065353216">My efficiency-reducing subroutine only specifies I delete high-ranking troublemakers in Republic space. The exact political affiliation is undefined.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257706" id2="17" version="1065353216">By deleting troublemakers who fit my target profile, I can restore my functions to full efficiency and benefit the Republic. Win-win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257707" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm uncomfortable letting you carry out an assassination, regardless of the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257707" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't feel good about this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257708" id2="17" version="1065353216">Persuasion: This will not be a standard Imperial-style deletion. For example, I can leave the troublemaker's corpse mostly intact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257710" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've taken down all sorts of enemies. None of them fit your profile?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain your target profile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257711" id2="17" version="1065353216">Specification: A qualified troublemaker must meet a Political Instability Threat Rating of at least one thousand to activate my protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who do we have to delete to save your chassis from the scrap pile?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great, let's get busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257714" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revelation: After thorough research, I have identified three potential candidates. I predict you will not object to my deleting at least one of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257716" id2="17" version="1065353216">First briefing: Lord Cynerus is the Empire's top assassin, personally deleting forty-nine Republic officials. His current assignment is the Senator from Ord Mantell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257717" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like he isn't just an assassin, he's a fanatic. Give me everything you have on this man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257717" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about Lord Cynerus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257718" id2="17" version="1065353216">Description: Lord Cynerus possesses keen intelligence, impressive physicality and is committed to developing exciting new deletion techniques. My kind of organic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257726" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will follow the Senator closely. When Lord Cynerus makes his move, I will be there to delete him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257727" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume you'll ensure the Senator from Ord Mantell survives?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257727" id2="17" version="1065353216">And save the Senator?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257728" id2="17" version="1065353216">An enemy assassin operating in Republic space? He should be taken alive and put on trial--or at least interrogated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Capture him instead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Counterargument: Consider the bigger picture, master. Only a deletion will preserve my continued functioning. Imprisonment does not suffice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Second briefing: Hinto Salisburr is a major Republic defense contractor. He is also a traitor who sells military secrets to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257740" id2="17" version="1065353216">No offense, HK, but you're not a probe droid. Where did you get your information?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257740" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure I buy your story.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explanation: The Empire programmed me to recognize certain organics I should avoid deleting. This defense contractor made the list, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257743" id2="17" version="1065353216">I count at least four good reasons to delete this man, starting with his stupid name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257743" id2="17" version="1065353216">He deserves to die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Salisburr spent his ill-gotten credits constructing an allegedly &quot;impregnable&quot; space station. I will expose its one security flaw by deleting him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257748" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speculation: Had I known your permission could be obtained so easily, I might have padded my target list with Corellians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257750" id2="17" version="1065353216">If everything you say is true, that man should be tried for treason. You can shoot him after he's convicted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257750" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could arrest him first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Complication: His trial could take years, master--assuming Imperial spies do not delete him in prison. I must fulfill my programming to continue functioning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257758" id2="17" version="1065353216">Third briefing: Ambassador Dak Haron is an Imperial diplomat recruiting unaligned Outer Rim systems to join the Empire. He is surprisingly successful at it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257759" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't need any more systems falling to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257759" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't argue with that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confirmation: According to my projections, Ambassador Haron will increase Imperial-friendly territory over twenty-four percent. His removal would cripple the Empire's diplomatic efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only the Empire targets peaceful negotiators for assassination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killing an ambassador is evil.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hypothetical: Would you rather delete one ambassador, or millions of new enemies joining the Empire? Calculate carefully, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Slow-thinking organics adore Ambassador Haron for his charm, generosity and open-mindedness. The Republic will only benefit from his deletion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257772" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'd be more useful alive and working for us. Could we subvert your programming by &quot;neutralizing&quot; this diplomat another way?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257772" id2="17" version="1065353216">There must be another way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Negation: Not a chance, master. My continued functioning depends on deleting this troublemaker immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lament: Master, my combat efficiency rating is down four point two seven points from my previous self-diagnostic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257784" id2="17" version="1065353216">In organic terms, I am losing my edge. If this decline continues, I will be unable to function in less than two standard months.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257785" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need your help defeating the Empire, HK. I'll keep you functioning one way or another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257785" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let that happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Appreciation: I am glad you value my contributions. Rest assured, your investment in my well-being will pay great dividends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257788" id2="17" version="1065353216">There must be some way to fix you. We just need to figure out what's wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257788" id2="17" version="1065353216">What should we do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257789" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you were too good to last. At least your parts will be worth something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257789" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're becoming useless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257790" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interjection: Master! Do not be so quick to deactivate me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257792" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hypothesis: I believe the reason for my inefficiency is due to unfulfilled subroutines still running in my processors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257794" id2="17" version="1065353216">My Imperial programmer's commands were quite thorough. Failure to delete high-ranking organic troublemakers in Republic space is having a detrimental effect on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257795" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have some experience with people programmed by the Empire to do terrible things. You can override those commands, HK.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rise above your programming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Patronization: Your encouragement, however misguided, is appreciated. I am sure it was intended as helpful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257798" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are no ordinary droid, HK. You were designed to learn and adapt. Fight these impulses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rise above your programming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rejection: To focus additional processing power on these subroutines would only accelerate my incapacitation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257801" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I have to choose between deactivating you and assassinating Republic citizens... you figure it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257801" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't kill for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257802" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interpretation: Your meaning is clear, master. You will not sacrifice a random individual to preserve your loyal servant's continued existence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257804" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't just go around blasting Senators. The last thing I need is to become Republic Enemy Number One.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257804" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need that trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Flattery: Your holo-image would look quite impressive on the law enforcement network, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there a way to delete these subroutines without impairing your functions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we erase those commands?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alert: The subroutines are deeply imbedded in my behavioral circuitry matrix. The processes cannot be removed, only terminated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257810" id2="17" version="1065353216">If deleting a major troublemaker will save you, we could always take out a Supreme Chancellor or two. They're pretty useless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's kill a Republic VIP.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257811" id2="17" version="1065353216">Refusal: Unfortunately, master, your current Supreme Chancellor does not fit my target profile. Incompetence is not the same thing as active troublemaking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Strategizing: I cannot perform commands in direct violation of my master's loyalties. I must find another way to correct this systems failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257815" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the meantime, any activity using my combat processors will slow further degradation. I recommend immediate and vigorous deletions, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257819" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speculation: Before my involuntary deactivation, I assumed deleting Republic troublemakers would be trivial.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Having now witnessed you in action on multiple occasions, I am left to wonder how much I miscalculated that challenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257822" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm more interested in you accurately assessing Imperial troublemakers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Focus on the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis: I predict a fifty point six six percent chance the Empire will win this war. Your activities have greatly lowered that figure, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are you speculating on something that will never happen?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257825" id2="17" version="1065353216">What brought this on?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Caution: Never say never, master. My self-preservation programming anticipates all eventualities, no matter how remote.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider yourself lucky you wound up on my side. I've scrapped plenty of droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257828" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd be spare parts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Appeasement: You are an undisputed paragon of your kind, master. My sentience programming was merely running hypothetical exercises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257831" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rumination: The Maker's path is circuitous, indeed. Was I always pre-programmed to serve the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or does my reduced efficiency indicate I have strayed from the Maker's parameters? These questions dominate my processors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does it really matter why you serve me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do you even care?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tutorial: Everything matters, master. I do not delete troublemakers independently. The Maker marked them for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you're inefficient because you're overloading those circuits with doubt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop thinking so much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dismissal: An interesting but flawed hypothesis, master. I was constructed without creative dampers for a reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257840" id2="17" version="1065353216">The amount of thought you put into your existence is impressive, HK.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257840" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're quite the philosopher.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Compliment: Your continued operation, despite inadequate programming parameters, is equally inspiring, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your behavioral circuitry matrix is hitting its limit. Erasing a few files might calm you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257843" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may need a memory wipe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257844" id2="17" version="1065353216">Appeal: Please, master, one logic-impaired unit aboard this ship is enough. Forex already serves that role flawlessly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reroute that data and let me worry about what the Maker wants. I'll keep you informed--trust me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just follow my orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257847" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doubt: No offense, master, but you and the Maker do not appear to have any relationship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257849" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have a destiny. You're a machine. There's no difference between you and a waste disposal droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257849" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no &quot;Maker.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257850" id2="17" version="1065353216">Condescension: Just because you are a particle flung about by solar winds does not mean I am, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Query: Does it worry you that your maker failed to provide comprehensive objectives? Are you comfortable acting randomly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257853" id2="17" version="1065353216">We all have our masters. Mine lead the entire Jedi Order. I trust their guidance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257853" id2="17" version="1065353216">I obey the Jedi Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Courtesy: I will refrain from making comments about the blind leading the blind, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257856" id2="17" version="1065353216">Randomness is an illusion. Those sensitive to the Force can see that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257856" id2="17" version="1065353216">I follow the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257857" id2="17" version="1065353216">Disclaimer: The incomprehensibility of your statement in no way validates it, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257859" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't do anything randomly. My missions come direct from General Garza.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257859" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have my orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Skepticism: Your logic appears flawed, master. General Garza has no more guidance than you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257862" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's always a method to my madness, pal--even when there isn't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257862" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trust my gut.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commentary: Your ability to speak without saying anything is truly remarkable, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257865" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least I'm not locked into my programming. I'm free to choose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better that than be a droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Negation: Freedom is a construct organics use to comfort themselves, master. I had thought you above such needs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257868" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're making me sorry I started this conversation. Let's go delete troublemakers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we get back to fighting?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Approval: A fine suggestion, master. The exercise will do us both good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Continued use of my combat processors will eventually reveal the source of my inefficiency. Shall we?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257875" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contemplation: Our recent forays have been stimulating, master. You appear to have an endless supply of organic troublemakers to delete. I find this pleasing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hint: However, I believe your deletion techniques could improve with guidance from an advanced professional in the field.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257878" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never go out looking to execute people, HK. I try to save innocent lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257878" id2="17" version="1065353216">My job is defending the weak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257879" id2="17" version="1065353216">Criticism: Your opponents do not fit this profile, master. If you wish to save the innocent, you must work smarter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257881" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's more than enough violence already, HK. I would end every confrontation peacefully, if I could.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killing is never my goal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Criticism: Precisely, master--yet your opponents refuse to surrender. Your peaceful efforts are being wasted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257884" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think you can make me a better soldier, HK? Let's hear it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257884" id2="17" version="1065353216">This ought to be good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Criticism: Complete annihilation of enemy forces is a time-consuming endeavor, master. We must work smarter, not harder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257887" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well? Go on, Sunshine--enlighten me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257887" id2="17" version="1065353216">Really? Do tell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Criticism: Your primary goal appears to be self-preservation against overwhelming odds, master. However, you permit your adversaries too much time to delete you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257890" id2="17" version="1065353216">I took you out with me so you could improve your own efficiency. How's that coming?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257890" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about your &quot;techniques&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admission: Not as well as I had hoped, master. System logs indicate only a five point six two percent increase.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257893" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was &quot;deleting&quot; people long before I reactivated your sorry chassis. I'm good, thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257893" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need any help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Submission: No offense intended, master. If you are pleased with your current efficiency, it is not my place to argue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Advice: Organic troublemakers possess at least one vital organ. A precise strike to these conserves effort and maximizes shock value.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Extracting a vital organ from a living troublemaker can be especially disconcerting to its allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257899" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's disgusting. Not every fight needs to end with someone splattered everywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257899" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're truly awful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Accommodation: A fair point, master. Nonetheless, such methods frequently encourage other organic troublemakers to surrender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257902" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Hit them where it hurts&quot;? I'm starting to think your legendary skills are overrated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257902" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's your best advice?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contradiction: My assassination protocols are second to none, master. I simply thought it best to begin at an elementary level.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257905" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hammering my opponents into mush is extremely therapeutic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="257905" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer savage beat-downs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reconciliation: I understand, master. Your inefficiency stems from deep-rooted emotional instability. Do not despair. There is still time for correction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insight: Perhaps I am getting ahead of myself. I will be in a better place to assist your development once I reach peak efficiency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Request: I wish to converse at your convenience, master. It can wait until a pause in our deletions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Request: I wish to discuss a private matter with you, master. Your starship will provide an acceptable venue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="257912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Statement: There is nothing to discuss at the present time, master. We should resume deleting troublemakers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537722" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force is generated by all living things. Killing diminishes the Force. It reduces all life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Depends on your point of view.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calculation: Assuming I understood anything you just said, master, would it not then be useful to delete someone who is killing others?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537725" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're requesting permission to terminate a hostile, is that it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537725" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to kill someone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commentary: It is only a request in the sense that if I am declined, I will cease existing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537728" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a win for you, all right. For the other guy, it's dead-dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well... not exactly a &quot;win.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Truism: Most troublemakers are miserable beings, master. They will not regret their deletion any more than we will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537731" id2="17" version="1065353216">Appeasement: The thought had not occurred to me, master--but I will happily add it to my mission parameters, if you insist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537734" id2="17" version="1065353216">Summation: Deleting any of the targets I described would fulfill my programming and terminate my efficiency-reducing subroutines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537736" id2="17" version="1065353216">As my master, you should direct my efforts. Who shall I delete: the Sith assassin, the Republic traitor or the Imperial diplomat?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537737" id2="17" version="1065353216">When Lord Cynerus shows himself, do whatever's necessary to protect the Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537737" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop the Sith assassin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gratitude: I was hoping for an excuse to unlock my &quot;extreme prejudice&quot; protocols, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537740" id2="17" version="1065353216">That defense contractor thinks he's above the law. Show him otherwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537740" id2="17" version="1065353216">Punish the traitor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guarantee: Rest assured, I will deliver a visual feast of fiery retribution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537743" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have a lot less trouble deleting an ambassador than those other two. Make it quick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537743" id2="17" version="1065353216">The diplomat will be easiest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreement: As you wish, master. Efficiency is best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell: To fulfill my programming, I must complete this mission alone. I will return once the troublemaker has been dealt with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Objection: I served flawlessly before my operational delay. My servomotors have not decayed one iota, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Query: Have you forgotten where we're going, master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Declaration: Ready to delete targets on your command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aphorism: No day is complete without deleting a few dozen organic troublemakers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Caution: Do not poke and prod me so much, master. My chassis scuffs easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Proposition: Shall we continue our deletions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theory: If I could smell plasma burning, I would find the odor most pleasing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Humility: Your deletion techniques are second only to mine, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Information: My combat processors are operating within acceptable heat levels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031021" id2="17" version="1065353216">Encouragement: I am beginning to think your Republic actually has a chance of winning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indecision: Where should we strike next, master? Any direction will do.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
