<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>105</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/nar_shaddaa/guss/cantina.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179556" id2="17" version="1065353216">This seedy place. Now Big Boss and Blizz look for shiny Jedi man. He have fish head.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh! Blizz see Jedi man!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179566" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey! Jedi man! Blizz want you to meet Blizz friend!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179570" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't I tell you I was busy! I haven't got any more work--hey, I don't have a price on my head, do I?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe? Blizz not look. Big Boss searching for Forcey-people, so Blizz think Big Boss should meet important Jedi man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your boss is a Jedi--uh, fellow Jedi. Haven't seen you around the enclave. You, um, aren't from around here?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179575" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Master &lt;FirstName&gt;. I'm no stranger to Nar Shaddaa, but I don't call it home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179576" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, I'd offer a fellow master a drink since you're here, but I was just leaving, so just put it on my tab--goodbye!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179578" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Master &lt;FirstName&gt;. Barsen'thor of the Jedi Order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179579" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right, the, uh, Barsen'thor... well, someone of your, ah, station, probably need to see the masters of the enclave. Just over that way!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your boss is a soldier? You don't want me to lead some sort of daring attack, do you...? 'Cause I could--but I'm real busy with Jedi business right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi. I didn't come to speak with you about any specific operation, but I am looking for help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, that's too bad. I, um, I'm over on my help quota right now--Jedi union rules. Maybe try the enclave, may the Force be with you and all that!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain! Is that really you captain--or am I having a vision? Either way, good news!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why, Languss Tuno, as I live and breathe. How're the gills?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, words I would not use to describe Guss: shining anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remind me to buy Sana some Force-glasses before we leave.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooo! Can Blizz try?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Si-- Si-- Sith...? Yes! Of course they would, alien filth. The, ah, foolish creature can't tell a Sith from a Jedi. You address Lord Struction.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179592" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Darth &lt;FirstName&gt;. Formerly the Emperor's Wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179593" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Darth Nox. Formerly of the Dark Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179594" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Darth Imperius. Formerly of the Dark Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179595" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Darth Occlus. Formerly of the Dark Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179596" id2="17" version="1065353216">D--Darth--I mean, I'm honored great... murderous... one. Surely I'm beneath your notice, so I'll just....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179598" id2="17" version="1065353216">The little Jawa works uh, for, you? If you're trying to squeeze me, he was all I could afford! Jedi aren't made of money, you know!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179599" id2="17" version="1065353216">They tend to be worth more to the right buyer. Not why I'm here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe, er, keep that to yourself next time you see one. Little wisdom from your friendly, neighborhood Jedi Master. Well, nice meeting you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179602" id2="17" version="1065353216">Er.... The, um, alien filth I can understand not getting the message, but you should mind a, ah, Sith's wishes. Why do you bother Lord Struction?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Korriban must have been very unpleasant for a Mon Calamari. I'm sure it shaped you into a formidable Sith, Lord Struction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course it did! You would be wise to grovel before me, but, uh, later. I'm busy right now, so....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179606" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the shining man from Sana's vision?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blizz think fish-head man look kinda wet and shiny. Maybe he sweat lots?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, Captain, I'd hug you, but after my experience with Akaavi my understanding of personal space has been forever altered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179611" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I'd known it was you the Jawa was insisting I talk to I would have been on the first shuttle off Nar Shaddaa!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, I'm flattered, but I can never keep too far from this scuzzy little rock for long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179613" id2="17" version="1065353216">About that, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179615" id2="17" version="1065353216">The little guy is like a magnet for interesting characters. And garbage.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blizz only wanted compactor parts!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179618" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I'd known it was you, I would have conserved the fuel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aw, I know you don't mean that, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179621" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been gone a long time. Nobody'd seen or heard from you. Just poof, vanished out in Wild Space.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179623" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought maybe you pulled a Nok Drayen.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179624" id2="17" version="1065353216">I kind of did. He still holds the record for most time as a metal popsicle and he can keep it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, really? What's it like? Were you tucked away--or, ah, maybe on display like a bronzed award for daring and, um, pulchritude?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179627" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had you all on my mind, there just wasn't much I could do about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179628" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the feeling. I spent a lot of time thinking about what happened. It, uh, feels bad... being helpless when it really matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179630" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really thought I'd just ditch my ship, my crew, and my legacy to hide someplace until all the trouble blew over?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Um, no, not... when you put it like that. I just, you know, liked it better than believing you died out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179633" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been kind of lost without you. I drifted... then I settled. Finally I thought maybe if I'd been a real Jedi, you know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179635" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found a new master here. Nothing like my old one. Kind of like me, but successful.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Huh, maybe there was something to all that mystic nonsense Sana was spouting after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179637" id2="17" version="1065353216">See! Blizz good at this!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179639" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's great! With a little training I'm sure you'll be the fastest Force-kick in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or at least Force-pinch. I'm trying to keep my expectations reasonable.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Haven't given up on that pipe dream?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179643" id2="17" version="1065353216">We both know I'm not cut out for being a proper Jedi, but with the right teacher I might shine!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe fish head really is shiny-man! Boss old friend is Jedi, and stick in mud like colorful-lady say!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stick in the mud? Have you even met another Jedi? Wait--I think that might be the only part I understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179648" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a mystic friend who had a vision about me finding a Jedi. Blizz thinks it's you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179649" id2="17" version="1065353216">I--I got my own prophecy? Even destiny picked me last! Captain, will you call me Chosen One?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179651" id2="17" version="1065353216">How about you join back up with me? I've got this new thing going, kind of a big deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179652" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, Captain, I was really thinking about giving up the Jedi dream for good, but now that you're here... it's like a second chance!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179654" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nevermind him, tell me about this master of yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, uh, master might be stretching it. I haven't exactly gotten him to teach me anything yet, but I'm wearing him down!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179657" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you should meet my master. If anyone can convince him to train me, it'd be you!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179659" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you take me for a fool?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179660" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? No! I'd never think... that. You're important, I can tell! I shouldn't waste your time--I'll just be going....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179662" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wasn't born yesterday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like that's any feat--I mean, wisdom comes with more than age. Look deeply... maybe over that way.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179665" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey! Blizz promise Big Boss that Blizz find shiny-man so Big Boss and shiny-man can talk. Fish head better listen!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179667" id2="17" version="1065353216">I--uh, yes, sir. Don't let the lack of ears fool you, I'm hanging on every word.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Answer me one question: are you really Force-sensitive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, that much is true. I haven't really used it, per se--I mean, I want to! I've always wanted to, but Jedi life....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179671" id2="17" version="1065353216">See, Big Boss! Just like colorful-lady say! Fish head mope here in dark all the time instead like he not know where to go!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179673" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've gotten off on the wrong foot. Blizz spoke highly of you, so I wanted to meet. That's all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blizz think maybe fish head is shiny-man from colorful-lady's vision.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179676" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen enough. This has been a complete waste of my time, Blizz.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179677" id2="17" version="1065353216">But, Big Boss, what about colorful-lady's vision? Shiny-man supposed to be important!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179679" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fish head man all sweaty and shiny in the light, have wide eyes that point two directions, and Jedi like Big Boss wanted!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait! Hold on! Let's rewind back before the Jawa's insensitivity toward the moisture-dependent--this shining man someone important? Respected?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179682" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you didn't want to talk?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179683" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't--I mean, I didn't. But then you started talking about some lady's visions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Possibly. All we really know is a Voss Mystic believes he can help us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, uh, when you put it like that, it sounds pretty important.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of which you are neither.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Things you're not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179690" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to be rude about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179692" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's just--I'm thinking: what if destiny's finally knocking? Like it's been at the wrong doors for years and by the time it reaches yours nobody's really expecting an answer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179694" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was just about to give up on getting trained again, then you show up!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179695" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't come here to train you in the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179696" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, I'm glad I made you reconsider, but that's not why I'm here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179697" id2="17" version="1065353216">Again? How many times have you quit?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179698" id2="17" version="1065353216">I lost track of the number of times I thought about it, but this time would have been my second... the last time stuck for a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179700" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need a Jedi academy wash out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179701" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never even entertained the possibility, but, er, maybe you help me prove myself to my master? Like a spiritual tutor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179703" id2="17" version="1065353216">You ever consider maybe I'm supposed to show you who you're looking for? Like some mystic guide?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179705" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should take you to my master!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179706" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've come this far.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe we really are on to something.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179708" id2="17" version="1065353216">See! Blizz good at colorful-lady's games!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1179710" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're any indication of his ability, I'll pass.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179711" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master might be overstating it... more like advisor. Okay--guy I've been pestering to train me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179713" id2="17" version="1065353216">See, Blizz told Big Boss that Blizz find Jedi!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1179715" id2="17" version="1065353216">Big Boss should go! Blizz wait for Big Boss, smuggle-moon have lots for Blizz to do. Bye-bye fish head!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179717" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's not far! You won't regret this--I swear on my Jedi honor.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
