<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>117</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/nar_shaddaa/guss/shops.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1179997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any more sage advice? I could climb onto the counter and meditate until they offer me a snack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180004" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the point of being Sith is being angry, at least that's working.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180005" id2="17" version="1065353216">There you go. Anger is easiest to wield. Now show what you can do with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alright, Guss, it isn't helping. Just do whatever makes you comfortable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180007" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, I know you're trying to help. I'll maybe just wing it this time, I'm kind of used to that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing's working. When you're bad at being Jedi and Sith, what else is left?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180012" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're an odd one. Trying to fit you into a prescribed mold might be the real problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi sometimes waver, but they persevere. You need to as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most Sith don't get the luxury of trying again, so make the most of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180015" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was a lot less embarrassing than the first time. I still don't know what I'm doing wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180016" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least your morale seems high. Try it again, like last time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180017" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get it this time, I'm sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180019" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're dwelling on pride and fear. Let it go.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180020" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need to grasp for a more powerful emotion and feed on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would it be too much to ask to leave the usual Jedi dogma out of this? I at least left with my dignity the first time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180024" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have to put aside those feelings of fear and embarrassment. Can't you see that's why you're stuck?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180025" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not a droid! I can't flip a switch and stop caring--hey, maybe that's it. I'll just pretend I'm a droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, you're too emotional for Jedi teachings. We should take advantage of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ball up my anger into a webbed fist and shake it until I get what I want. I can try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180032" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, can we safely rule out the intimidation tactics? There was definitely a lack of murderous intent the first time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180033" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want cowardice to continue to be your first response to everything, by all means.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180034" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's worked so far. Okay! Fine!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pushing you hasn't worked in the past, I shouldn't have expected it to be different now. Go at your own pace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180037" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to give talking another go, at least I can fail with my dignity and person intact.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180039" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you never took to Jedi training, but it has to be more effective than what you've been doing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180040" id2="17" version="1065353216">If at first you don't succeed, wear success down with constant badgering. Got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here goes nothing!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180046" id2="17" version="1065353216">I tried, I really did, but she was flirting with me and that never happens. I have a pack of Tarisian ale, a holo address and shame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turns out making an attractive Mon Calamari cry is a real wet blanket on the whole &quot;rage&quot; thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180050" id2="17" version="1065353216">That went a lot better than the last couple times. We had a lot in common--and those eyes--the mind trick thing came off a little weird though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180052" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time to face the music. If music was mostly long sighs and eye rolling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180054" id2="17" version="1065353216">Third time's the charm, that's what people who aren't me say anyway. You're pretty good luck, I haven't been kicked out once!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180055" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talking is your comfort zone. I think it's helping.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180056" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is sort of a defense mechanism... until I put my foot in my mouth.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Staying optimistic is good, but you still have nothing to show. It's time to think back to your Jedi training.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180059" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have no more opportunities to play nice. Assert yourself before you have to return a failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah. You're right. My master didn't send me out here to boost my self-esteem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to shine!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180066" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did it! I really did it! I'm mostly certain--beyond a reasonable doubt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180068" id2="17" version="1065353216">I put on my most placid, soulless face and was ready to serene my way to mild victory, but my heart wasn't in it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180070" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had my meanest sabacc face on--the one by the end of the night when I'm broke--but tonight's been pretty good, actually.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180072" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the clerk smiled, I just knew what to do. We got to talking about how good the urchin is, and we both hadn't eaten all night.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180074" id2="17" version="1065353216">So I say, &quot;you should have one,&quot; and then she says &quot;you should have one,&quot; and hands it to me. So we split it and I got the Tarisian ale.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180075" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've taken your first steps on a new path.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180076" id2="17" version="1065353216">See, you always had it in you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180077" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess I have.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180079" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just hope it wasn't a coincidence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180080" id2="17" version="1065353216">A genuine Force intervention is the only explanation I can believe.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah! Can't wait to rub this in that old geezer's face!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180083" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll practice my Huttball goal zone dance. That'll be the cue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180085" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't wait to show my master!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180087" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Cheat] I'm done with this. Take a few credits and buy what you need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180088" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah... you've been more patient with this than I could expect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180092" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the place. Dumpier than I remember... I probably shouldn't say that out loud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180096" id2="17" version="1065353216">I spent years getting the &quot;master your emotions&quot; drummed into my head, I'm not sure a few more times are going to make the difference.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180097" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stick with it, Guss. Getting it right the first time isn't the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180098" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was never good at telling the difference between perseverance and futility.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180100" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do what comes naturally.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180101" id2="17" version="1065353216">Embrace them then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that how most Sith get their start? Lectured straight into the dark side?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180106" id2="17" version="1065353216">Having a scrapper like you to back me up is reassuring, but I'm not really sure the whole &quot;rule through fear&quot; is my strong suit.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quit wilting at the first sign of difficulty.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180108" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not something you can fake. Just try being yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180109" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know that anyone has ever said that to me with any sincerity. I like it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180111" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can't use your emotions, they'll only distract you. Find peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180112" id2="17" version="1065353216">The owner probably doesn't get a lot of compliments. Maybe I should lead with that and see where it goes?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180113" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's what feels right, who am I to say otherwise?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180114" id2="17" version="1065353216">An actual Jedi?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180116" id2="17" version="1065353216">A real Sith?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180118" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or is that your sideways way of saying use my intuition?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180120" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, Guss, just act natural.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180122" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's as good a plan as any.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180123" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was hoping for a greater vote of confidence.Tacit approval is a step up though.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180125" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think we're distracting you from your true purpose. Focus and discipline are required to master the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180126" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought that advice would make things easier, but I think it's just distracting you. Keep your mind focused on the task.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180127" id2="17" version="1065353216">Back to Jedi basics....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180129" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've coddled you enough. You're supposed to be learning to bend the will of another.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180130" id2="17" version="1065353216">Playing nice was probably a mistake. You need to get serious, show them who's boss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180131" id2="17" version="1065353216">That always worked better when I was waving the lightsaber instead of my hands... I'll try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180133" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think, Lord Struction. Be, Lord Struction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180139" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm calm. I'm calm. I'm. Calm. Do Jedi know how dumb they look when this doesn't work!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180143" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you think being laughed at instead of attacked counts as progress?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180145" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never knew running a dumpy shack could be so complicated. You know there's Hutt-mandated shabbiness zoning?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180147" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before you ask, no, but the gentle letdown is a first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on, there's one more place I can try.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180151" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Cheat] This is ridiculous. Just grab what you need and let's be done with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180152" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admit, it does feel pretty ridiculous to fuss over grocery shopping, and I'm well acquainted with ridiculous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180154" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, I think I'm still allowed into this one. I guess you should wait out here. Maybe cross your fingers, duck preemptively.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180155" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're smarter than that old goat. Just buy his stupid Tarisian ale and pocket whatever else you want.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why? I'm good at lying and stealing. How's that help me get good at anything else?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180157" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fair enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180158" id2="17" version="1065353216">May as well get it over with.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180159" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm yourself, Guss. That fear and doubt won't serve you here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180160" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sound just like my old master. You know just saying &quot;feel this way&quot; doesn't really help? Breathe... breathe.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180162" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fear. Doubt. Resentment. Don't fight them. Seize them. That raw emotion is a strength you've been taught to leave bound up and useless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180163" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must be the deadliest untapped weapon in the galaxy then. Guess it couldn't hurt to try once.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just relax. You're probably just getting performance anxiety.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180166" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose I should be more prepared for failure by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget the errands, go in there and make a friend. It'll be easier to convince the owner if you're well-liked.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180169" id2="17" version="1065353216">A mind trick works most easily if the suggestion is something the being would do anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180170" id2="17" version="1065353216">The old Languss Tuno charm is a force I can handle.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Domination is the key. Make eye contact and focus everything on projecting your will.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show some spine. If you don't even believe you can change their mind, why should they?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intimidation, right. I've got the Force, what have I got to be worried about from a clerk!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here I go!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180178" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Cheat] Just do it, Guss. Your master is only jerking us around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180179" id2="17" version="1065353216">He... I mean, I guess I see that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180181" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just like trying. It feels like playing a lottery, the odds of winning are nil, but you can dream.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180183" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll just be a minute.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180187" id2="17" version="1065353216">Piece of cake, or urchin roll. Used to make these fresh back on Varn, you have not lived until you've had one with coffee.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180189" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd better get back to my master. You do not want to see the guy without his Tarisian ale.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180191" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember how we were talking about being calm?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180193" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was doing great. The other guy... he wasn't so calm after the third try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180195" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd better go before he finds his blaster. There's another place we can try not too far from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180196" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't work!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180200" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know what happened. I thought we were really bonding over the last Huttball playoff, but Frogdog solidarity stops at free samples.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180202" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think there's another place we can try nearby. Maybe Rotworm fans are more generous?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
