<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>76</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/world/crisis_in_galactic_city/captain_winborn.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684316" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Migrant Merchants' Guild is dug in hard. Gonna be a while before we can push them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got my hands full down here. What you do with that holorecording is your business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684322" id2="17" version="1065353216">My men told me what you people did. Heroic doesn't even come close to describing it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684324" id2="17" version="1065353216">My men can't believe you took on all those gangsters--and lived. You're a blasted hero, you know that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684326" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the network terminals locked down, the speeder traffic is secure. Now all that's left is pushing out those gangsters for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684327" id2="17" version="1065353216">There was some kind of encrypted message on the network. Looks like a recording.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me see that... hmm... it's an old Migrant Merchants' Guild code. Think I can decrypt it.... Here we go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684330" id2="17" version="1065353216">You accepted our friendship, Senator Kayl--and credits. It's time you paid us back. All we want are the housing projects you promised our people. Now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your people will have to wait their turn like everyone else. I owe you nothing. If you continue pushing me, I'll destroy you all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senator Kayl and the Migrant Merchants' Guild are at war? That's what this was all about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684333" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't good news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684334" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe Senator Kayl would deal with gangsters. Could that message be forged?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that really the Senator?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684335" id2="17" version="1065353216">The call was placed directly to her office.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should've known Senator Kayl was too good to be true. She's an even bigger crook than I thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, that figures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't make sense. There's gotta be an explanation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your extortion attempt has failed. My people are pushing back your little army as we speak. It's over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody breaks a deal with us, Senator. We'll have what we want, one way or another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684344" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is way above my pay grade. I'm not destroying the reputation of Coruscant's most popular politician. Take the recording. I don't want it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684345" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you wear that uniform, you're upholding the Republic's ideals: freedom, integrity and honesty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684345" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have an obligation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684346" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nobody more qualified to handle this than you, Jedi. I know you'll find the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be strong, Captain. Exposing corruption is rarely easy, but you have an obligation to this world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let fear control you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684349" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm risking my life every second I spend down here. The Jedi can sort this out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684351" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I ask you to shine my boots? The recording is criminal evidence. That's your department.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684351" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do your job, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684352" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're Republic military. You outrank me. Besides, this can't be what it looks like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684354" id2="17" version="1065353216">A security captain who gives away evidence to complete strangers? How did you get this job?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684354" id2="17" version="1065353216">So much for ethics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684355" id2="17" version="1065353216">I follow my conscience. Whatever's happening, there's a reasonable explanation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684357" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take it to the Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684358" id2="17" version="1065353216">She'll have a good explanation. She has to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684360" id2="17" version="1065353216">What makes you think I want the blasted thing? Keep the recording or throw it away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684360" id2="17" version="1065353216">Neither do I.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Somebody should take it back to her. Give her a chance to explain. There's gotta be a reason for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684363" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senator Kayl has done great things for Coruscant. She's a good woman. Give her a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684365" id2="17" version="1065353216">My men and I will stay down here. You should go back to the Senate tower.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684369" id2="17" version="1065353216">Push back those mobs of gangsters and lock down the network terminals. Hurry--we're running out of time!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cut power to the whole blasted planet if you have to! We can't let those crazies take over the network!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Winborn? Senator Kayl said you need backup. What's the situation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684374" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're getting cut to pieces down here. We're not trained to fight an army of killers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684376" id2="17" version="1065353216">These gangsters are smart--organized. Clearly trained offworld. They'll kill thousands. Might even destroy the Senate tower.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684377" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pull your men back, Captain. Let me handle the criminals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684377" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave the fighting to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684378" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not that simple. They came here with a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684380" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senate tower is nowhere near this sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684380" id2="17" version="1065353216">How is that possible?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684381" id2="17" version="1065353216">The scum found themselves a way around that little detail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684383" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look on the bright side: Politicians are easy to replace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684383" id2="17" version="1065353216">No great loss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684384" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell that to the people flying speeders up there. They'll die first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684386" id2="17" version="1065353216">The gangsters brought slicers to access every network node in the sector. They're trying to take over the automated speeder flight paths.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684388" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll cause thousands of mid-air collisions. It'll rain debris on the Senate tower like a meteor storm. No telling how many will die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684389" id2="17" version="1065353216">These criminals have gone too far. I'm taking them down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684389" id2="17" version="1065353216">One is too many.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684390" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best news I've heard all day, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684392" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're criminals, not terrorists. They wouldn't do this unless they stood to gain something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684392" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gangsters need a motive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's ask them--after we crush their army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody's torching General Garza's office. Time to frag some criminals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough explaining--let's move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope you brought plenty of ammo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684398" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure, the Senate tower is a little gaudy--but that's no reason to burn it down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684398" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aw, but I like that place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you? No, forget it. Don't care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684401" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send a man to warn the Senators. They need to find shelter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684401" id2="17" version="1065353216">Evacuate the Senate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684402" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sent word right before you got here, but there isn't enough time to save everyone. We have to stop this here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684404" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have to hand it to the bad guys--they know how to put on a show.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684404" id2="17" version="1065353216">These criminals think big.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684405" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're here to help us, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684407" id2="17" version="1065353216">The gangsters have armed patrols guarding the network access points. We need to push them back and manually lock down the terminals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get enough terminals, and we might just pull this off. My men will back you up. Good luck in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684415" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't want to be here. Whole place is crawling with gangsters.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
