<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>145</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/world/crisis_in_galactic_city/minister_imogh.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="684416" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is always a pleasure to see you again. I wish I had time to speak, but matters of state cannot wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="684419" id2="17" version="1065353216">So good to see you all again. It is always a pleasure to serve Senator Kayl's esteemed friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="684420" id2="17" version="1065353216">How lovely to see you again. Any friend of Senator Kayl's is a friend of mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684422" id2="17" version="1065353216">That will be all, Minister. Dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684424" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Winborn contacted me. You thwarted an attack that would've killed thousands. You have my gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, you also have a holorecording I would like destroyed. Its contents will only cause harm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684427" id2="17" version="1065353216">You committed a crime, Senator. Do you really expect to get away with it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684427" id2="17" version="1065353216">You dealt with gangsters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684428" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's so much you don't understand about the situation. The Jedi Order left us to rebuild Coruscant alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know how many lives have been lost because of your deception, Senator?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684430" id2="17" version="1065353216">You withheld the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684431" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought the only life I risked was my own. I expected assassination attempts, not war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684433" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been lying to everyone, Senator. The only reason those gangsters attacked us was to get at you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684433" id2="17" version="1065353216">This attack was your fault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684434" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand your anger, Lieutenant. But you need to understand--things here are complicated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684436" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't expect much from my elected officials, but taking credits from gangsters? Seriously?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684436" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been a bad Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many choices only appear foolish in retrospect. At the time, it felt like the right thing to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did your security chief spoil the big surprise?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Winborn told you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684440" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Migrant Merchants' Guild warned me. They're courting my favor as if bargaining were still an option. It never was.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684442" id2="17" version="1065353216">How much is your reputation worth to you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684442" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything is negotiable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Despite what you must think, I'm not wealthy. Everything I've earned has been invested in Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684445" id2="17" version="1065353216">My opponent in the elections was a vile man: lazy, stupid and corrupt. He wasn't interested in building, only taking. I had to win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684447" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I didn't possess as much wealth as he did. When those gangsters approached me, I accepted their &quot;donation&quot;--and I'd do it again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you hear yourself? After everything that's happened, you still won't admit to being wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684448" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've learned nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684449" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not wrong. If you'd witnessed the suffering on this world--the poverty and despair--you'd know that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684451" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people choose their leaders by popular vote. What difference did it make how many credits you had?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why was wealth important?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be naive. Wealth can purchase influence--and influence sways popular opinion. My opponent understood that too well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684454" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing I wouldn't do to stop my enemies. Sometimes you have to break the rules.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684454" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't blame you at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684455" id2="17" version="1065353216">I regret nothing, but I've worked hard to atone for my compromises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684457" id2="17" version="1065353216">I stole from those criminals to rebuild Coruscant for its people. Set things right. I'll bring the Migrant Merchants' Guild to justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684459" id2="17" version="1065353216">You hold the power to ensure my success. Let me finish healing this world. Please destroy that recording.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684460" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you really love the people of Coruscant, you'll admit what you've done. Let them decide whether or not to forgive you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684460" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, the truth must come out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684461" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think I'm dishonest? I'm just a realist--but there's no point arguing it with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684463" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't force you to go public. I'll call an emergency meeting in the Senate. Tell them the truth. Let them decide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coruscant will be rebuilt, with or without you. I promise to help finish what you've started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684464" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's for the best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps you should run for office.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684466" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll hang onto the proof, just in case you get cold feet about confessing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684466" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep this recording.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684467" id2="17" version="1065353216">I already made one mistake today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684468" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope they send you to prison for a long time. Can't believe I liked you....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684468" id2="17" version="1065353216">You deserve a harsh sentence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684469" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are many kinds of heroes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684470" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're all clear, Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684470" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. [Destroy recording]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. I won't forget what you've done for me--for Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684472" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you need help making this world strong, I'll always be here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684472" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll help with the rebuilding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684473" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a true friend and patriot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684474" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure if I did the right thing. I'm counting on you to convince me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't make me regret this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684475" id2="17" version="1065353216">I swore to uphold the people's faith when I was elected. That hasn't changed. It won't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684476" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was my pleasure. I hope we'll continue working closely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684476" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] For us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684477" id2="17" version="1065353216">I promise you won't only hear from me when there's a crisis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since you're feeling generous, how about a donation to my favorite cause?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684478" id2="17" version="1065353216">For compensation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Certainly. Take it in the spirit of friendship--and discretion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684481" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see to it you're properly recognized for your heroism in the old Galactic Market. Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="684489" id2="17" version="1065353216">We haven't heard from Captain Winborn since he and his men entered the old Galactic Market. I hope they're safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="684492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, at last! One moment, please... Senator? Your special appointment has arrived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for coming on short notice. I'm Senator Vanara Kayl. Forgive my abruptness, but time is a luxury I don't possess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684496" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you may have heard, Coruscant is overwhelmed with refugees fleeing Imperial tyranny. Many have been here since the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684498" id2="17" version="1065353216">The refugees took over the old Galactic Market sector, huddling in shops and warehouses that were abandoned during the Sacking of Coruscant. They refuse to leave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684499" id2="17" version="1065353216">There has to be a better place for these refugees to live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684500" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've offered to resettle them offworld, but they're demanding to remain here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684502" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is the Republic doing anything to provide for these refugees?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684502" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's being done to help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Resources are scarce. There's only so much we can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684505" id2="17" version="1065353216">They should be thankful. If this were the Empire, they'd be slaves--or worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684505" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least they have homes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684506" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fear their current situation is little better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684508" id2="17" version="1065353216">As so often happens when fear and poverty dominate, a criminal element has risen to take advantage of the situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684510" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Migrant Merchants' Guild began as a political advocacy group for refugees. Over the years, it transformed into a ruthless and murderous criminal syndicate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684511" id2="17" version="1065353216">As if these people didn't have enough problems, now they're being controlled by gangsters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684511" id2="17" version="1065353216">The poor refugees.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684512" id2="17" version="1065353216">These criminals exploit the very people their guild allegedly protects. They rule through intimidation and extortion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do the gangsters have a power structure? A leader?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who's in charge of it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684515" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a consortium of powerful crime lords. When one falls, another takes his place. It makes them difficult to defeat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why haven't you forced all the refugees out? Once they're gone, the gang goes with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just evict them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Past attempts to forcibly relocate refugees ended poorly. The criminals helped the people resist, and came away looking like heroes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684520" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Migrant Merchants' Guild has grown increasingly hostile and violent. Their criminal enforcers have acquired military-grade weaponry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Earlier today, their thugs took to the streets. They attacked our security personnel, set fires, began rioting. We're facing an armed insurrection.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684523" id2="17" version="1065353216">With all due respect, Senator, are you sure this requires Jedi intervention?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi aren't police officers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your order has been away from Coruscant too long. It's time the Jedi took a direct hand in protecting the Republic capital.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684526" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've negotiated with hostile parties before. Put me in touch with these criminals. I'll do what I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Diplomacy is my specialty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi are warriors as well as diplomats. If diplomacy fails, we must use force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684529" id2="17" version="1065353216">You just described the last enemy I fought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like Ord Mantell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684530" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need your expertise, Lieutenant. We can't rule out the possibility of Imperial influence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684532" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know what you've heard about me, but I've got nothing to do with criminal activity--promise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure why we're talking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684533" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm told you're very good at dealing with armed insurgents. That's my interest in you, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have these gangsters made any demands?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684535" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do they want?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684536" id2="17" version="1065353216">They only seem intent on destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684538" id2="17" version="1065353216">A battalion or two of the Republic's finest will solve that problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send in your army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684539" id2="17" version="1065353216">A full-scale military response is out of the question. The collateral damage would be more than we can bear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684541" id2="17" version="1065353216">For generations, the old Galactic Market was Coruscant's central trade hub. Its importance isn't merely economic--it's a symbol of the Republic's freedom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684543" id2="17" version="1065353216">The comm channels are jammed. We've lost contact with our security forces. I need your help ending this crisis. The criminals must not win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684544" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll focus on saving the people caught in the cross fire. Punishing criminals isn't a Jedi's duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684544" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do what I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684545" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suspect they'll punish themselves by attacking you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684547" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there's any way to settle this dispute without further violence, I'll find it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684547" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do what I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not restrain yourself too much. These men are thieves and murderers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684550" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll push those gangsters to the bottom of Coruscant, if that's what it takes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684550" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do what I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Burying them may be our best option, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684553" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a pretty good shot. Figure I can take at least half these guys by myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684553" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do what I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684554" id2="17" version="1065353216">Considering your accomplishments on Ord Mantell, that's no exaggeration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684556" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've hired the best, Senator. Just sit back and relax.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684556" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684557" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't promise that, but at least I have hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684559" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've won me over, Senator. Whatever you need, I'll do my best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684559" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] They won't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684560" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't doubt it, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684562" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on my absolute commitment, Senator. I won't disappoint you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684562" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] They won't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684563" id2="17" version="1065353216">I look forward to your return, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684565" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll be my pleasure, Senator. You've inspired me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684565" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] They won't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684566" id2="17" version="1065353216">The feeling's mutual, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave everything to me, gorgeous. When the bad guys are all gone, I'll take you out for dinner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684568" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] They won't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684569" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a generous offer. We'll discuss it later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684571" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the situation's as bad as you say, your people didn't survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="684571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your forces are probably dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684572" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's still hope. If my security forces were dead, those gangsters couldn't resist letting me know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="684574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do whatever you must to save innocent lives from that criminal filth. Find my security chief, Captain Winborn. He'll help. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="684578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, you'll have to make an appointment. No, I don't know where the administrator is. Now excuse me....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
