<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>66</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tatooine/world/imperial/supply_lines/captain_cibinel.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607822" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place will be an Imperial territory before the year's out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah. I recommended the lot of you for medals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah. I thought about asking for a medal, my lord, but I figured that was probably beneath your dignity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah. I asked to have you on track for a medal, but the Intelligence service declined.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607831" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah. I tried to get them to give you a medal, but they said that's reserved for commissioned officers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our spy droids are already picking up a change in the chatter. Villages talking about surrendering rather than starve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607835" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume we have you to thank?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607836" id2="17" version="1065353216">This insurgency will resist us no longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607836" id2="17" version="1065353216">We all serve the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Puddle farmers and tusk-faced morons cannot stand against the might of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607839" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather not have my name attached, you know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607839" id2="17" version="1065353216">No thanks necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607840" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be happy to take the credit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your soldiers need serious training if those guys bested them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607842" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm way better than your men.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="607843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not exactly the best and the brightest who get shipped here. Maybe a march out to view your handiwork will inspire them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607845" id2="17" version="1065353216">All that's left is wreckage and corpses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607845" id2="17" version="1065353216">I made short work of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="607846" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I like to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's talk credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607849" id2="17" version="1065353216">With thanks. Bounties for every caravan that's gone off our radar.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without the support of the Exchange, this planet will be swearing allegiance to the Emperor before you can say &quot;aerial bombardment.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607853" id2="17" version="1065353216">The caravans usually stay clear of our patrols.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607856" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get a shuttle out here to evac the wounded. Corpses stay 'til we've assessed the threat condition.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="607858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now! Don't stand there like some drooling sand-rat, you're an Imperial soldier!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607860" id2="17" version="1065353216">My apologies. This is hardly the way I'd like to introduce my troops to such an illustrious group.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607861" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry you had to see this, my lord. Not one of our army's finer moments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607862" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're here to see our successes in annexing Tatooine, it may be a short visit. We're having a hard time out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607863" id2="17" version="1065353216">You here on your own, or did you come to help? I hear you've done the Empire a service or two.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607864" id2="17" version="1065353216">What fools attack the Imperial Army?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who did this to you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well-armed fools, courtesy of the Exchange.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607867" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least half the dead are yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your troops seem outmatched.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, well, my troops are game, but they're the greenest thing you'll find in this desert, and the Exchange is more than they're up for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607870" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are you talking to me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607871" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should care. The Exchange is our biggest obstacle to claiming this dustball for the glorious Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607873" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ever run into them? Nasty crime syndicate, likes to use Tatooine as a waypoint.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607875" id2="17" version="1065353216">These criminals don't want this rock under Imperial control, so they've been stirring up local resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607876" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is in all of our interests to extend the grip of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I assist?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607877" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you go after them, my lord, they won't last long enough to call for their mothers. No stupid tusker's going to stand against a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607879" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been known to do a little counter-insurgency in my day....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607879" id2="17" version="1065353216">I might be able to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607880" id2="17" version="1065353216">The insurgency's less of a problem than the Exchange. Without their support, the locals'll fold like clean laundry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607882" id2="17" version="1065353216">You looking to take out someone specific?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything in my field?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607883" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have names or anything, but, sure, there's a job here if you're looking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607885" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is one of the caravans the Exchange is using to supply the insurgents. Heavy guard, all tuskers. Each one we've taken costs us dear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607887" id2="17" version="1065353216">What exactly happened here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607887" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those guys don't look local.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607888" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Exchange has been using these caravans to supply the insurgency and keep it active.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every one is guarded by these Exchange tuskers--they're too big to hurt and too dumb to scare, so each one we take down costs us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607892" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was about to tell command we'd need a new combat battalion if we want to take them on, but... any chance you'd like to lend some expertise?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607893" id2="17" version="1065353216">No petty criminals can be allowed to tie the hands of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607893" id2="17" version="1065353216">They must be taught a lesson.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607894" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the price is right, your caravans are history.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure. I'm in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607895" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do I get out of this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607896" id2="17" version="1065353216">The thanks of a grateful Empire? No? Hm... what do you get the man who has everything?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607898" id2="17" version="1065353216">My men got a bonus for every caravan they shut down. If you step up, the reward money's yours, and well-deserved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607900" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to help, go follow the caravan routes and take down as many as you can. The locals will assume the Exchange abandoned them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'll see how quickly those puddle farmers beg us to take them over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="607904" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not my thing. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607905" id2="17" version="1065353216">As long as you're here, it's all of our problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="607907" id2="17" version="1065353216">This territory is closed to all but Imperial citizens!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
