<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>34</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/ilum/bronze/republic/sith_at_the_gates/general_orias.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178872" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard reports a Sith Lord gave the order to attack the temple and take those shields. Probably just a rumor, but we'll look into it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178875" id2="17" version="1065353216">So I hear. There's a lot of Imperials running scared because of you. I'll see the shields are secured for transport.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here. I've had this since I was a lieutenant; it deserves better than catching dust. Put it to good use.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178879" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need those shields back ASAP. Show me what you can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi? I realize your time's short, but I need help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178884" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reporting for duty? Good. Grunts I have, but I need a leader.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, Captain, mind taking some Republic military work? I need every body I can get, and I have credits doing nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mind signing on for a job? I need all the bodies I can get, and I have credits doing nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178890" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're in the final stages of our push to retake the Jedi Temple. Sent techs out to deliver prototype shields to our boys, powered by Adegan crystals.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imps got wise and ambushed the techs. Stole the shields. The men...well, seems like the Imps want that technology, and they're not being gentle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="178893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since they lost Corellia, the Empire needs every advantage it can get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="178893" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're desperate.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just so. They've got nothing to lose, so they'll take any risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="178896" id2="17" version="1065353216">The compassionate don't last long in the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="178896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gentle is not their nature.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Social philosophy's not my field, but sounds like you understand the stakes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="178899" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's because they're scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178900" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like how you think, care to put it into practice?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="178902" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know places where a military-grade Republic shield would sell for a year's salary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="178902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Personal shields are valuable.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lucky for you, I've got no time to ask just how you know that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="178905" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you need help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good, you catch on fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="178908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your problem, not mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph. If you fight like you run your mouth, we might have a use for each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178911" id2="17" version="1065353216">We haven't sighted the shields on the Jedi Temple battlefield, so I'm thinking the Imps took them into the Temple itself. I need someone who can make it inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="178912" id2="17" version="1065353216">You asked the right person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="178913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will I know these shields when I see them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="178913" id2="17" version="1065353216">What should I look for?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like I said, the squad's shields were prototype models. They should all be marked.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178916" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the Imperials won't just hand them back nicely. You've got a hard fight ahead of you. Stay sharp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="178918" id2="17" version="1065353216">No thanks. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178919" id2="17" version="1065353216">You might change your tune if the Imperial military adapts our shielding technology. I've work to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="178921" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take any messages later.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
