<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>100</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/world/imperial/long_cold_silence/commander_tritan_holocom.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670064" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Talz have no fear. Even when their army is at its last breath, they want to take us down with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670066" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they kill the power station, we'll have no heat. We'll have to evacuate, or we won't last past nightfall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't tell me you didn't think of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now we find this out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670068" id2="17" version="1065353216">The station's guards won't be able to hold off the entire Talz force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670070" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670071" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every available gun needs to be saving that station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670071" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send in the troops!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670072" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't send everyone. What if they expect that and surprise us here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670074" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll call for reinforcements from Adamas Orbital. They should be able to land within the hour.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just get to that power station, and quickly!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670079" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here. Let it not be said that carrying such a load through wampas is impossible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670080" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your cargo, Captain Yudrass. In one piece, as am I.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670081" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, my lord. You will be pleased to know that we have kept up our end of the plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670083" id2="17" version="1065353216">The base is prepared for war. We have security fields, sensors, anti-personnel guns... we'll obliterate any Talz that dares approach.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670085" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here you are. Watch out, the Talz will want this back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670086" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe you requested Talz supplies, Captain Yudrass.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. I will search through this once the coming battle is over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670089" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which won't be long. Our sensors will catch the Talz, and our anti-personnel guns will obliterate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670091" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is done. Everything the Talz owns is burnt or broken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670092" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is done. Nothing remains in the Talz cave but ice and debris.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670093" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Talz will come home to find nothing but ashes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670094" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. They will have no choice but to strike, and we are ready for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670096" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Talz supplies are destroyed. Get ready for some angry payback.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670097" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are more than ready. They will find us armed and deadly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670099" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander! Commander! There's reports of a Talz attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670101" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent! What wing are they headed for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670103" id2="17" version="1065353216">No wing, sir. They're at the power station. They're overrunning the guards. They brought bombs!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670105" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have devised a plan to put the Talz in position for a killing blow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their supplies--weapons, medical equipment and the high-calorie food they require--all of it is stored in one central location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670109" id2="17" version="1065353216">They may be adapted to the cold, but without their supplies, they wouldn't last a week. So we will destroy their cache.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670110" id2="17" version="1065353216">I crush foes and souls, not crates and barrels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670110" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is beneath me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670111" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hear me out, my lord. With supplies cut off, all the Talz will be forced to gather and unite on a course of action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670113" id2="17" version="1065353216">They will choose between retreating home or starvation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670113" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forcing a miserable choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670114" id2="17" version="1065353216">That, or one other option that we think the more likely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blaster fire works faster than starvation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why not kill them directly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670117" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd have to stalk them through the snow. But without supplies, all the Talz will come together to plan retribution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670119" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about their inevitable retaliation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670119" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Talz would hit back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670120" id2="17" version="1065353216">We expect it. No Talz commando will give up easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670122" id2="17" version="1065353216">And then what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670123" id2="17" version="1065353216">We want them to panic and launch an all-out, last-ditch attack on us. And we'll be waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670125" id2="17" version="1065353216">So instead of fighting Talz, you want us to fight hungry, angry Talz.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670125" id2="17" version="1065353216">That won't stop them long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670126" id2="17" version="1065353216">They should be able to mount one counterattack before hunger weakens them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670128" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I were them, and suddenly without food, I would raid this base. So we will amplify our defenses here and spring the trap shut.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670130" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, getting at their supplies may be difficult--they are in a series of ice caves overrun by wampas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670131" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds like a pretty unforgiving security system.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670131" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do the Talz survive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670132" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wampas can be fooled. A combination of synthetic pheromones and body language could make them think a Talz is part of their pack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670134" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. A proper fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670135" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that is the case, I suggest an alternative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670137" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are desperately short on supplies here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670139" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you could bring back all you find, it could make a valuable difference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670141" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we'd need over a hundred kilos of food alone. How would anyone carry that and still fight?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670142" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there anything important on this planet that isn't in some snow creature's freezer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670142" id2="17" version="1065353216">More ice and more caves?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670143" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suspect taking over a cave was faster than digging their own shelter. Though I'm not sure how they dominate the wampas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670145" id2="17" version="1065353216">All the more reason to bring back their equipment. We could learn much from the Talz.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670147" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last thing you'd want to do in a wampa cave is weigh yourself down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670148" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd be surprised how much I can carry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670148" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll bring the supplies back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670149" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suspect, even with your associates here, it will be difficult. But it's your decision.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670151" id2="17" version="1065353216">Daring, my lord. I hope you're making the right call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670153" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well, then. Who am I to say if you've gone mad?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670155" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take anything of theirs that gives them aid or comfort. Make them come crawling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670157" id2="17" version="1065353216">Between Talz and wampas, I'll need both hands free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670157" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll destroy the cache.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then it's settled. Destroy anything of use to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670160" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let them know who the masters of this miserable world are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yudrass is here... ah, sir! The reprisal was successful. Look to the holocom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670166" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work. Has the base been informed? How is morale there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gentlemen, the commander wants to know how we feel about the Talz being struck down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670170" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. That's a sound I have not heard in some time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670172" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I understand one of our patrols spotted Talz that fled rather than fight. The tides of war are with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without the advantage of surprise, the Talz are showing their true colors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670173" id2="17" version="1065353216">They are frightened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, we'll let them panic for a while as they try to figure out which body is which.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Next moves?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670177" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your men smell blood. Time to deliver it to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670177" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will bury the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670178" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't agree more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670180" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to hear from you. We've been receiving the feed from the data arrays, and what we learned is quite interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670182" id2="17" version="1065353216">We had assumed there were one, perhaps two groups of Talz out there. We found six.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670184" id2="17" version="1065353216">Had we attacked earlier, we would have gotten one group and the other five would have gone to ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that we've tracked them, it is time to exterminate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670185" id2="17" version="1065353216">They cannot run now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670186" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Tritan and I believe we have the answer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670188" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did well... again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670189" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. I will not underestimate the Talz. Complacency is what got the colonel killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670191" id2="17" version="1065353216">Planning makes the victory greater.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670191" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let this be a lesson, Tritan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670192" id2="17" version="1065353216">It certainly paid off in this case. Unfortunately, we have one more step to take.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670194" id2="17" version="1065353216">The good part is, we know how many Talz there are. The bad part is, we don't have enough forces to hit all six groups at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670196" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes? Yes, you're coming in loud and clear. Good to see you're all accounted for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670198" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello? Good to see you, my lord, we feared the worst.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="670200" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holocommunicator is currently switched off.]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
