<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>183</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/world/imperial/long_cold_silence/commander_tritan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669817" id2="17" version="1065353216">The reserve soldiers are working out very well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669820" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you say this squad--this group--managed to hold off the entire Talz commando force?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669822" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you say this Sith held off the entire Talz force single-handed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669824" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you say the entire Talz force was held off single-handedly by some bounty hunter?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669826" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you say the entire Talz force was held off by one person? And they're not even a Sith?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669828" id2="17" version="1065353216">It sounds incredible, to be sure, but here, I'll let you talk directly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669830" id2="17" version="1065353216">You all have the thanks of the entire base. We were just expressing our amazement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669832" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, we cannot express our gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, our gratitude is overwhelming. We were just talking about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669836" id2="17" version="1065353216">May I introduce Moff Braynor, overseer of the Hoth system, among others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669837" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am surprised you'd take an interest in this humble base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669837" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the occasion?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your base is key to our activities on Hoth, and if not for you, it would have been lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669841" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard you telling the Moff the good news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then our plan fully succeeded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, you've saved us from giving a much bleaker report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669844" id2="17" version="1065353216">If not for you, Dorn Base would have been lost, and all the outposts that depend on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669846" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is for that reason I ask you your opinion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would you say Commander Tritan or Chiss Captain Yudrass was more instrumental in the base's defense?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Tritan's leadership has been forthright and direct.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Tritan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669850" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expected such a response. Tritan works diligently, if not always wisely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669852" id2="17" version="1065353216">He is hereby promoted to colonel, responsible for the welfare of Dorn Base until further notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669853" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish you well, Colonel Tritan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh... thank you. This is... this is really something. I will do my best, Moff Braynor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669856" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel Tritan will have my full support, as always.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669858" id2="17" version="1065353216">See that he does. That will be all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669860" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a lot of responsibility, wouldn't you say, Commander?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669860" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's quite a promotion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669861" id2="17" version="1065353216">He has served us well under fire, and the soldiers respect him. That is paramount.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669863" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope we will not have another leadership crisis any time soon, Colonel Tritan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't make me regret this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never again. This base will be as organized as a repair droid's toolbox.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never again, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never again, sir. You can count on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669870" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I will not disappoint you, Moff Braynor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your recommendation has meant the world to me, but I must turn my attentions to my base immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir... there is still the matter of the pirates at Leth Outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, of course. Captain Revar lost a facility of some sort, yes? If you're in the area you might want to look into it. Terrible pirates out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Yudrass's advice formed most of our key strategies. We relied on him heavily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chiss Captain Yudrass.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669878" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is as I expected. Very well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Yudrass, you are now Colonel Yudrass. I am putting the base's welfare in your hands until further notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669881" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seems you have broken down a few barriers, Colonel Yudrass.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669882" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... thank you. This is unprecedented.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669884" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't believe I've heard of a Chiss ranking so high before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669884" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's quite a promotion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669885" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is unprecedented, but Captain Yudrass is well-known for his skill and judgment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669887" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is one thing to promote an alien, it is another to expect humans to serve him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669887" id2="17" version="1065353216">The humans won't like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better to have soldiers alive and grumbling than happy and dead. Success is the only currency here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669890" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trust you know the consequences of failure at this level.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't mess this up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Believe me, Colonel Vannis's example has made that clear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669893" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do me great honor, Moff Braynor. I will have the base at inspection quality immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669895" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, if I might ask--do you think the enlisted men will have a problem taking orders from Colonel Yudrass?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669897" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mean will they refuse orders from a Chiss? They will at first. Then they will be made examples.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669898" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could demonstrate your commitment by helping win the men over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yudrass will need your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669899" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is an excellent idea. I will begin immediately. Thank you, Moff Braynor, Colonel Yudrass.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make it clear what happens to the disobedient, and you will do fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fear will keep them in line.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669902" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is correct. The fastest remedies to insubordination are force and fear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669904" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will keep that in mind, Moff Braynor. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669906" id2="17" version="1065353216">That will be all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well... that went better than expected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669910" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care. Let's move on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now the base must recuperate from its losses and replenish its personnel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669913" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will leave you to discuss this amongst yourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669915" id2="17" version="1065353216">I cannot thank you enough for the recommendation. Chiss will see the Imperial Army differently now. It will help win their loyalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669917" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose we should be happy we don't have pirate problems here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669919" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes... he's referring to another security failure. Captain Revar at Leth Outpost lost a reactor substation to the White Maw pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669921" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have asked much of you, but Captain Revar has not, and his soldiers desperately need relief at the Leth Outpost. If you have the time, look in on them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quick! To the power station!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669924" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll prepare the base. You provoke the Talz.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Talz will soon know what it means to cross Dorn Base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669927" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are having deep morale issues in the forward outpost. I must show them that we can triumph without Colonel Vannis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now is the time for reprisals. These chittering animals will not get away with this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669931" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want ten of the Republic to suffer for every one of ours dead. I want every last Talz wiped out, their heads on sticks out in the frost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669932" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will find them, and they will die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669932" id2="17" version="1065353216">Done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669933" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we are lucky, it will be that simple, but we should plan for less than ideal circumstances.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their destruction is assured. I only need their location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dead Talz, coming right up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Location is important, but an estimate of their numbers doubly so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669938" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I'm done, this place will be carpeted in Talz fur.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669938" id2="17" version="1065353216">No problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669939" id2="17" version="1065353216">A fine image. Now we need a plan that matches it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669941" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't normally do massacres. But today isn't normal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669941" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, but any campaign of extermination must be predicated by knowing how many of the enemy there are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669944" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything you'd like to add?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669944" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yudrass, what do you think?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669945" id2="17" version="1065353216">The main thrust of the plan is sensible, but given our limited knowledge, I suggest the plan be... refined before use.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669947" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it were that easy, you'd have done it already.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669947" id2="17" version="1065353216">It may not be so simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669948" id2="17" version="1065353216">True. We have the proper intelligence, now we need a plan of action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669950" id2="17" version="1065353216">A covert action is advisable, or we'll end up wiping out one group and causing the rest to go into hiding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669952" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have data arrays we could install in their communicators link. If we did that, we could locate and estimate their numbers before we hit them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669953" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killing is reliable. Technology isn't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669953" id2="17" version="1065353216">We take their heads.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669954" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds like a lesson gleaned from a life far more interesting than mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669956" id2="17" version="1065353216">They weren't carrying handheld comms. They've probably got way-stations. I can bug those.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669956" id2="17" version="1065353216">We hit their communications.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669957" id2="17" version="1065353216">This sounds plausible. As much as I hate to admit it, Yudrass is usually right about these things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander! Come in, Commander!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go ahead, Scout Five.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669963" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've found a nest of Talz on the ice lake--too many to engage. Transmitting coordinates now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669965" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our luck is changing. If you can get those arrays into whatever they're using for communications, we'll soon know what we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect timing. Brutally slaughtering a few dozen should sow fear throughout their little cabal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669969" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you're done, report to the forward outpost. It's closer to the lake, and the men there can see your success in person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669972" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found Colonel Vannis. He was dead, murdered by Republic Talz.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669973" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, we heard as much from the men you freed. Terrifying, cunning beasts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669975" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seems our new responsibilities are as permanent as we feared, wouldn't you say, Commander?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talz. That would make sense. Cold-adapted, Republic-aligned. I've not killed their kind before... what about you, Commander?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669979" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? Yes, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669981" id2="17" version="1065353216">The base awaits your orders, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669983" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're scanning the frequencies for the colonel. So far, nothing but silence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669984" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your advice boils down to doing nothing, and that I cannot do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, I respect your bravery, but if you see this through personally you will be dead, and whose leadership will we have then?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, we've been awaiting your arrival. This is Commander Tritan, and I am known by the core name Yudrass.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669990" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, we're glad you've arrived. May I introduce Commander Tritan, and myself, a humble captain, core name Yudrass.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669992" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Command's description is correct, I believe you're the bounty hunter sent to assist us. This is Commander Tritan, and I am Yudrass.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, the agent. It's good you've arrived. This is Commander Tritan, and I am his advisor, Yudrass.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, I believe this is the visitor Command told us about. Greetings, this is Commander Tritan, and my core name is Yudrass.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Halpern sent word you would be coming, and we've never had greater need of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel Vannis, the commander of this base, is missing. We fear he's dead, along with all the most experienced men from this base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670001" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is pleasant to be among such fine company.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, brother.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670002" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have been here longer than the Empire. It was our breakthrough that first alerted them to the Republic presence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670004" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Chiss have proven their worth to us, Yudrass especially, during this emergency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670006" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expected a commander's counsel to be more... exclusive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670006" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't need alien advice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yudrass and the other Chiss at the base are not part of our rank structure. He is merely advising during this emergency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not many non-humans have the ear of a base commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to see an alien presence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, well--my influence is entirely up to Commander Tritan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our Chiss allies have valuable knowledge of the planet. Yudrass is advising me during this emergency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670014" id2="17" version="1065353216">An emergency that grows more dire every moment the colonel is missing. This was the distress call we received.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me the problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670016" id2="17" version="1065353216">To lose one officer is a casualty. To lose them all sounds like a coup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670016" id2="17" version="1065353216">What treachery is this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670017" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assure you, the last thing I wanted was leadership of this base. I had zero choice in the matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670019" id2="17" version="1065353216">The colonel went out to investigate evidence of a possible spy probe near the ice lake. He was under heavy guard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670021" id2="17" version="1065353216">We received a distress call. It was obvious he found... trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scout One to Dorn Base! Heavy casualties! Taking heavy casualties! We're under attack. We can't see the--aaaaah!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recordings don't frighten me. I'll go see if I can find out what happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670024" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll go take a look.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670025" id2="17" version="1065353216">What on this world could take out an armed group of officers?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670025" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have any suspects?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Besides the Republic, there are wampas, pirates--mostly aliens unafraid of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a lost cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670029" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is what I was trying to tell the commander. We've lost two rescue teams already.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670031" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we can't simply cower in our base when the mission is to damage and exhaust the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670033" id2="17" version="1065353216">And our men can't do it. Commander. This visit is a gift to us from fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ten enemies or ten thousand, I stand ready to strike them down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670034" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am always ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670035" id2="17" version="1065353216">The first priority is to find Colonel Vannis, dead or alive. After that, feel free to wreak as much vengeance as you like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoever is behind this will be nothing but a blot on the snow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670037" id2="17" version="1065353216">They will die before me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed. I have heard of the power of Sith. I only hope that you have not come too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670040" id2="17" version="1065353216">If a man-tracker is what you need, you've got the right person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670040" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find Vannis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. You'll find footprints easy to follow on Hoth... for about five minutes until blowing snow obscures them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670043" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will soon know all you need to. You have my word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670043" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can discover anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. Intel is the priority. We must learn what happened to Vannis... and rescue him if he still lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670046" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will go if the ranking officer wishes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mind your position, Yudrass.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yudrass presumes much, but he's right. You're the colonel's only chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a big problem. Can you tell it to me again in credits?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670049" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's this worth?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670050" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll pay any price you name. Find Colonel Vannis or at least tell us what we're up against.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our best-case scenario is that Colonel Vannis's communications tipped off the Republic, and he's gone quiet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670054" id2="17" version="1065353216">But if I were out in that cold, I'd have called for a rescue. If you can find the colonel, everyone on this base is in your debt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670056" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Commander Tritan's duty. Let him wander around in the snow looking for a lost cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="670056" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not going. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670057" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we know the risks of this mission to be immense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670059" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yudrass, this is no challenge a student of military history cannot overcome. We must ask ourselves, &quot;What would Malak do?&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="670063" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't the time.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
