<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>53</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/bronze/republic/hunting_the_hunter/lachei.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234295" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll salvage droids, use to repair damage to tunnels. Seems fair.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234298" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, yes! Droids are deactivating all over tunnels, we are safe!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234300" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have proven great friendship with us. We will not forget. Here, this we found among droid debris. Is proper to share with your friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234302" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please. Droid cores are the only way to finding Vermilion.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234305" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse, please. You are a Jedi? An ally of us Selonians? Please to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234307" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse, please. You wear Havoc Squad colors. An ally of us Selonians? Please to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234309" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are Republic? An ally of us Selonians? Please to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234311" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are Republic friends? Allies of us Selonians? Please to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our tunnels, our den, are invaded. Not Imperials, but assassin droids. Very terrible... so many den-mates dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234315" id2="17" version="1065353216">But these droids, we know. Belong to local bounty hunter called Vermilion--uses droids for his dirty work. The Empire must have hired to kill us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your people are warriors, hunters. What can a few droids do to you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234316" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't handle some droids?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are specially programmed to hunt us. No scent, silenced... we know nothing until is too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234319" id2="17" version="1065353216">I take it the Selonians crossed paths with Vermilion in the past.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234319" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seem to know him well.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. He accepted contract on a den mother. Learned how to fight us. Must be why Empire chose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234322" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could try sealing the tunnels, maybe set a trapfall for these droids or short them out somehow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's talk defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have tried. And destroyed many, but Vermilion is always sending more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234325" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this bounty hunter was any sort of gentleman, he'd come out and get killed in person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234325" id2="17" version="1065353216">He sounds like scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Must fear Selonians' power. Are we not warriors? Instead Vermilion attacks from distance, like furless coward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234328" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's oddly specific.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our tunnels are major access hub, can get to lots of places. Must be what the Empire is wanting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234332" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we are allies. You will not help? Not even listen?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without finding and stopping Vermilion, attacks will never end. His droids are key to finding. Their memory cores will trace to him.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234336" id2="17" version="1065353216">But droids are designed to fight Selonians. We cannot face and survive. Please, please to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234337" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find Vermilion for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234338" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is kindness--thank you. To find Vermilion should not be difficult.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234340" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mentioned memory cores.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234341" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go into tunnels, destroy droids--many as you can--and take memory cores. Scanning cores should trace where last orders came from.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234343" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then find Vermilion. Strike. Until he is gone, tunnels are death trap for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't help you. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you are no friend to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Empire grows bolder. Sends hunters into our own homes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741708" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi? You go down into the tunnels to strike at Coronet Shipping, yes?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741710" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Lachei. I helped to scout the way for you... and there are more than beasts in those old dens.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741712" id2="17" version="1065353216">Droids--specialized for slaughter of native species--guard the far end of the tunnels. They have butchered more of my people than can be counted. Please--help us stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="741715" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be glad to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="741726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Things are tough all around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="741729" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's terrible.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741730" id2="17" version="1065353216">You understand well. This war is not ours, but it destroys us all the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741732" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have helped us before. Will you not help again?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741734" id2="17" version="1065353216">The droids are crafty, always communicating in secret, always organized--it is how they hunt. One droid, greater than the others, commands their movements.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroy some of the droids and steal their communicators. Use them to hunt the droid who commands and destroy it as well. Without coordination, our foes will become easy prey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="741768" id2="17" version="1065353216">No problem at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741769" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do us a great help. We will never forget.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="741772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse, please. You wear the colors of Havoc Squad--you travel now to the tunnels leading to Coronet Shipping, yes?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse, please. You are friend to the Republic? Traveling down into the tunnels leading to Coronet Shipping?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then our hunt begins. We will avenge our fallen brothers and sisters--all thanks to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741781" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have proven great friendship with us. We will not forget. Please, take this--is proper to share with friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="741783" id2="17" version="1065353216">Droid communicators are the only way of finding their leader./</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
