<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>109</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319381" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a piece of prime real estate. The Thuls built until they ran out of room, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319382" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's pets, House Thul.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319383" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only time I'm ever gonna be in a palace like this--ha! Makes you want to kick out the nobles and run around naked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319384" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's somebody's house? My entire block apartment back on Nar Shaddaa could fit in there...! I'm going to hate these people, aren't I?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319387" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everybody here has a mountain view, but an avalanche would wipe them all out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319388" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alderaan's junk collectors. They make a poor meal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319389" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, we got enough firepower to take this place? 'Cause if we do this right, they'll be talking about us for years....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319390" id2="17" version="1065353216">That should be House Alde's domain over there. They're not supposed to be really active in the war, but they'll definitely fight off intruders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319393" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, I'm not going to count the steps on the way up, so don't bother asking.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319394" id2="17" version="1065353216">The house of assassins and death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lot of stairs, lot of chances to shoot intruders. Keep your head down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319396" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Rist is certainly making a statement with this walkway. I don't know what it is, but they're making it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it just me, or are those ruins smiling at us? Kinda creepy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rocks, nothing but rocks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319401" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ruins of old Alderaan. Pretty holo-image, but they smell like wet mold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319402" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look--I wonder what time period that's from? Alderaan's been inhabited for millennia, every square meter probably has some historical significance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319405" id2="17" version="1065353216">Beautiful planet. But I'm betting those things were built by bugs. Puts a kink in the panorama.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killiks are particularly delicious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319407" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is Alderaan, home of the high-and-mighty. Give it ten minutes before they try to behead us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319408" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh wow, Killik mounds! Killiks are the second largest species on Alderaan, next to humans. I don't really know much about them other than they're giant bugs, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319411" id2="17" version="1065353216">No matter how much you climb on this planet, there's always a higher mountain.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319412" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place is too placid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319413" id2="17" version="1065353216">You figure to run a planet like this, you've got people slaving and freezing to death year-round. Nobles drink, workers bleed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319414" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Alderaanians are big on clean industry. I can see why. If this place turned into another cesspool like Hutta, I'd cry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Elysium ruins. Was a treasure hunter's dream at one point but pretty picked over now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319418" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would seem an impractical way to build.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319419" id2="17" version="1065353216">We had mountains like this on Rattatak. We didn't pretend they were pretty; we just threw people off them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get a look at that view. I think that used to be the Elysium. That's where the nobility would settle disputes peacefully before they blew it up and went to war....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to hit House Organa itself, huh? Sure hope you know what you're doing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319424" id2="17" version="1065353216">A house of Jedi. Fate may smile on me yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, rich guys! You thought you were safe in here? You were wrong!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319426" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's quite a palace; no wonder the Empire considers House Organa a threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319429" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should have bought some snowshoes. Looks like we got a trek on our hands--er, rather, on our feet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319430" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is unwise to bind a force of nature.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319431" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look out there. Blow that thing up, we could get a nice flood going....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319432" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at that dam. It's a big source of natural energy for the region. I'm surprised someone hasn't tried to sabotage it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I ever tell you I have a fear of plummeting to my death?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319436" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful not to fall, little Sith. Ha.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319437" id2="17" version="1065353216">You ever get that urge to look down and just jump? Or push someone?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319438" id2="17" version="1065353216">I really hope Alderaan makes it through this civil war. Not the nobles so much, just... everything else.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319443" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = visited Alderaan years ago // State of war = downgrade</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice mountain view. Too bad it's getting spoiled by all this war.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alderaan is tamed from long ago. Forgotten its nature.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319446" id2="17" version="1065353216">Man... that's the prettiest view I've seen since we left Ord Mantell. Risha wasn't kidding about Alderaan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hard to believe there's still farming going on at a time like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319450" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Organa = loyal friend of Republic // Jedi + T7 = help Organa win this war!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319451" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Organas sure know how to build a palace. Folks on Coruscant must be jealous.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why make shelter so large?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319453" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Organa Palace? Where I'm from, you could fit a whole town in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319454" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Organa. They're the biggest supporters of the Republic on Alderaan--let's hope we can return the favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soil mound = Killik nest // T7 = recommends caution</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319458" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those giant mounds are Killik nests. Anytime you see one of those, keep your lightsaber handy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killiks. Good trophies, but is risky to claim.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319460" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a &quot;live and let live&quot; sort of fella, but the Killiks are pushing my tolerance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319461" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like the Killiks have made themselves right at home....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alderaan = abundant natural resources // Imperial interest = understandable</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never get tired of the scenery here. Sometimes, I almost understand what all the nobles are fighting over.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319466" id2="17" version="1065353216">To swim waterfalls is goodness. Have ever done?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at that view! If this war ever ends, I might just retire on Alderaan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Waterfalls are still partly frozen. I guess winter isn't quite over yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Elysium = important historical site // First Alderaanian king = chosen there</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319472" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what's left of the Elysium. Alderaan's leaders used to settle disputes there peacefully. Shame to see the place like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time has taken Elysium's glory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319474" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the Elysium, Captain. You can tell this place was really something before it got bombed into rubble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wonder how long that structure has been here. Alderaan's been part of the Republic for a long time now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi + T7 = destroy all Imperial facilities on Alderaan!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blasted Imperials. Their architecture really clashes with the rest of Alderaan's décor.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are hidden things here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319481" id2="17" version="1065353216">You just know nothing good is happening in a mountain base that nasty-looking. Gotta be Imperial construction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like some kind of Imp facility. Better stay sharp.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Statue = makes T7 feel small</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319486" id2="17" version="1065353216">How important do you have to be to get a statue that big made of you?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who is, Herald?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319488" id2="17" version="1065353216">That fella must have been awful important to merit such a big statue. Wonder who he was?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319489" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a big statue. I wonder who it's supposed to be?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wardpost Duvaal = Republic stronghold + safe zone</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bet that tower has the best view for kilometers. Handy, when you're watching out for Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tower would be fine scouting place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319495" id2="17" version="1065353216">That tower may be the most secure place in the area, but it's a real eyesore. Blocks my view of the mountains.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like we're coming up on a friendly outpost. Good chance to catch our breath.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319499" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Organa = wealthy + aesthetically pleasing</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319500" id2="17" version="1065353216">Decorating this place must have cost a fortune. Those statues are made with real aurodium. No wonder the Empire wants this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is show of power? For clan's prestige?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319502" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do we do if some duke or baroness shows up? Salute? Curtsy? Wink knowingly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319503" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can really feel the history and tradition in a place like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319506" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Baliss = hostile to Republic</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319507" id2="17" version="1065353216">This must be what Alderaanian nobles call a &quot;country house.&quot; The owners don't seem too friendly.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="319508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems small clan. Will maybe grow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319509" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm guessing the owners of this little homestead aren't partial to uninvited guests.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even the smaller houses have huge mansions. Must be nice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didacticism: The Organa family is committed to peace and diplomacy. Why are we allied with them, master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reassurance: Do not worry, master--I have marked the Killik troublemakers for deletion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023659" id2="17" version="1065353216">Instruction: Waterfalls offer clean disposal of deleted troublemakers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Proposition: The Elysium is the end result of Alderaan's peace process. Let us learn from this example.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023665" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis: That fortress bears the hallmarks of Imperial construction. Recommend deletion with extreme prejudice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dismissal: Memorials to the dead are a waste of resources--and that statue blocks my line-of-sight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023671" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admiration: This outpost offers outstanding opportunities to delete troublemakers at long range.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commentary: I find polished floors highly inconvenient when sneaking up on troublemakers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Declaration: The inhabitants of this estate display hostile intent. Prepare for deletion, organic troublemakers!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023680" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observation: House Thul's fortress appears sturdy enough to withstand aerial bombardment--but not demolition from within. Intriguing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023683" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recommendation: House Alde's neutrality is highly suspect. I suggest liquidating these people before they become undesirables.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Supposition: House Rist designed this staircase as a means of terminating overweight invaders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suggestion: These ruins could block target acquisition, master. They should be leveled from orbit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023692" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warning: Those mounds are infested with Killiks--a highly-annoying insect species that makes excellent target practice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023695" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assessment: Those wind turbines would dismember any undesirables thrown into their blades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guidance: That is the Elysium, a testament to Alderaan's failed peace process.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023701" id2="17" version="1065353216">Approval: House Organa is what I refer to as an &quot;undesirable-rich&quot; environment. Activating liquidation protocols!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calculating: The potential casualties from destroying that dam could reach six digits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insight: This would be a useful spot to make camp--and throw approaching undesirables to their doom.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
