<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>12</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/world/hidden_crimes/datapad.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="713948" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This datapad seems to be a personal journal. The last few entries might explain how all of the residents of this village were killed.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="713950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Entry 27: We're loading up the dewbacks to take our first supply contribution to Sobrik. I think Colonel Adun is going to be very pleased.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="713952" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the trade today goes well, I think we'll have an agreement. The Imperials definitely need these supplies, and we could use their protection.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="713954" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just glad I haven't run into Captain Varmett. With our history together... he could ruin everything. He always said he'd kill me if I left him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="713956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Entry 28: They're all dead. Everyone. Our whole group. We were supposed to meet Colonel Adun with the supplies. Captain Varmett was there instead.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="713958" id2="17" version="1065353216">He saw me, and he shouted something to his soldiers, and they just started shooting. I saw Jev go down. Saw my mother burn.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="713960" id2="17" version="1065353216">I ran. I ran all the way home. But they followed me. I blocked the door. I don't know how long I have.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="713962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Entry 29: He's coming. I hear him outside, shouting to his men. They're going door-to-door. They're killing everyone in the village.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="713964" id2="17" version="1065353216">We just wanted to help. We had extra supplies. We knew the Empire needed them. Colonel Adun promised we'd be safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="713966" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wonder what Captain Varmett will tell him. How he'll excuse murdering his new allies, all because of me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="713968" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just hope someone finds the truth. I hope someone makes Varmett pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="713970" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here they come.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
