<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>36</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/bronze/a_diverting_assignment/reid_ganden.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690098" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't linger down here. There's no telling what the Justicars might do next.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690100" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shipping records from the Justicar docks. This should be everything you need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690101" id2="17" version="1065353216">Couldn't have done it better myself. These records prove the Justicars are getting supplies from offworld.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690103" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll transmit these to headquarters, let them chew on it awhile. You've got my thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690105" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once I have proof the Justicars are breaking the law, we can take action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690108" id2="17" version="1065353216">Traveling together, that's smart. Only way to win down here is through numbers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690110" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi. Don't see too many of you on Coruscant anymore. Certainly not in Justicar territory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690112" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better watch your weapons, Lieutenant. Everyone's desperate for them in Justicar territory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Justicar territory, citizen. Nice to see a friendly face.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent Reid Gandon, Strategic Information Service. Notice anything odd down here? Like how quickly the Justicars took control?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690118" id2="17" version="1065353216">Weapons and armor don't just materialize out of thin air. The Justicars have a supplier, and it isn't the Republic. You follow?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690119" id2="17" version="1065353216">You suspect the Justicars of illegal trade?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690119" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690120" id2="17" version="1065353216">And worse. Black market goods are one thing, but trading with the Empire is treason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690122" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sound like you have your suspicions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690122" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mean the Empire?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690123" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Justicars were supposedly formed by Republic citizens. Fear and martial law's not how the Republic operates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690125" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where else can the Justicars get what they need?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690125" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like who?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690126" id2="17" version="1065353216">If not legally from the Republic, there's a few options--the Exchange, separatists, even the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690128" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you should let Republic security in on your little theory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690128" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell it to the authorities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690129" id2="17" version="1065353216">As ruthless as they've become, the Justicars are keeping the Black Sun at bay. So, Republic security won't move on this without proof.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690131" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not really.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690132" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Justicars are too well equipped for a volunteer militia. I think there's more to their story than keeping the peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690134" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have time for riddles.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690135" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoever's got the weapons runs the show. The SIS needs to know where those supplies are coming from.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690137" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Justicars control their own shipping dock, and I'm sure they keep records. I just need someone who can handle an ambush to get them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Storming the docks might make the Justicars suspicious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there a quieter way?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690139" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there were another way, I'd be topside and long gone by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690141" id2="17" version="1065353216">You found one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690142" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get those records to me as soon as you find them. You don't want to get waylaid by the Justicars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="690144" id2="17" version="1065353216">No thanks. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690145" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't linger. As long as the Justicars are running things, this area isn't safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="690146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch yourself, friend. This place isn't as safe as the Justicars say.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
