<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>149</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/taris/multi/imperial/darth_nurin.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our influence in the Tion Hegemony will continue to grow until we dominate the region.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198395" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Tion Hegemony has sent an official message of gratitude for eliminating Doctor Lorrick. They seem quite eager to curry our favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently, crushing our rivals sends an appropriate message to the rest of the galaxy. I only wish we could have recovered Lorrick's research.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198399" id2="17" version="1065353216">A weaponized version of the rakghoul virus would have been a welcome addition to our arsenal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198400" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor already has me to eliminate those who dare to oppose him. You would do well to remember that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, but unnecessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198401" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will not forget, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198403" id2="17" version="1065353216">The virus is nothing when compared to the power of the dark side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198403" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have no need of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198404" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, my lord. That alone should be enough to secure our position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure I really want the Empire to have that kind of technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kind of glad it's gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198407" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose I can understand your reluctance. In any case, the mission was still a success.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198409" id2="17" version="1065353216">A weapon like that encourages others to come after us. Either to destroy it, or claim it themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198409" id2="17" version="1065353216">And a tempting target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198410" id2="17" version="1065353216">True enough, I suppose. Though I doubt anyone will move against us anytime soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198412" id2="17" version="1065353216">When word gets out of what we've done, others will assume we acquired it. That could also be useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198412" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody knows we don't have it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone's going to assume I got my hands on the virus when I took Lorrick out. You can use that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody knows we don't have it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198414" id2="17" version="1065353216">True. The mere threat of another outbreak is itself a weapon. Though I doubt we will need it anytime soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you disapprove of how I handled this mission?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that a complaint?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me, my lord. My words were just idle speculation. Your mission was a great success.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198419" id2="17" version="1065353216">You got a problem with how the mission turned out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that a complaint?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not at all. Despite the failure to claim the virus, the mission was a great success.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198422" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've eliminated a potential usurper of our power and strengthened ties with the Tion Hegemony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198424" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was a great victory for the Empire. The Republic will tremble in fear when they learn of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198425" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be a glorious day when our ancient enemy is finally wiped out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their days are numbered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198426" id2="17" version="1065353216">A day that draws closer, thanks to your actions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198428" id2="17" version="1065353216">I always try to leave my clients satisfied.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad I could help out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198429" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is vulnerable, but they are far from defeated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198429" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't underestimate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198430" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we have the upper hand, and your actions have only increased our advantage. Their destruction is inevitable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198432" id2="17" version="1065353216">My work here is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell. I look forward to working together again, should the opportunity arise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198437" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to strike at Lorrick now, while he still thinks his identity is hidden!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198441" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lorrick has many admirable qualities. He's intelligent, cunning and totally ruthless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198443" id2="17" version="1065353216">A decade ago, he was declared a traitor. He fled the Tion Hegemony and went into hiding on Ord Mantell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198444" id2="17" version="1065353216">He could be a valuable ally. Maybe we can use him as a weapon against the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198444" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should recruit him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198445" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'd betray us at the first opportunity. He's a megalomaniac; convinced his destiny is to rule the entire galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198447" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Senate finds out what he's up to, they may send their own people in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does the Republic know of him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not to worry. As usual, the Republic is blind. They have no idea of the threat Lorrick represents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198450" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's spent the last ten years plotting a way to get even. Obsessive, but impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Planning his revenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198451" id2="17" version="1065353216">We suspect his ambitions go beyond the Tion Hegemony. He hungers for total galactic dominance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kaon and the other worlds were just a test, a way for Lorrick to study the effects of the modified rakghoul virus he developed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198454" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we can get our hands on this version of the plague, it could be a devastating weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198454" id2="17" version="1065353216">The virus could be useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198455" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is on its last legs. Lorrick's virus could provide the final blow to our enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198457" id2="17" version="1065353216">We had no idea he was working on this. The attack on Kaon tipped us off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exposing his plan was stupid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198458" id2="17" version="1065353216">A stroke of fortune we must capitalize on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lorrick isn't just going to sit around and wait for us to make the next move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198460" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to act fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198461" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reports of what happened on Kaon have been suppressed. Lorrick still thinks his identity is hidden. We have the element of surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198462" id2="17" version="1065353216">His guard may be down, but I still expect stiff resistance. This is going to get bloody. Very bloody.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198462" id2="17" version="1065353216">He won't be defenseless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198463" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can think of no one else more suited for the task.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198465" id2="17" version="1065353216">In addition to eliminating a potential rival, killing Lorrick should secure the allegiance of the Tion Hegemony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Two birds with one stone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198466" id2="17" version="1065353216">At the very least it will keep them from looking to the Republic in the near future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198468" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire better appreciate what I'm bringing to the table. The Tion Hegemony's going to be in your back pocket after this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should be quite the payoff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry. The Empire is known for two things: crushing our enemies, and rewarding our allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198471" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we proceed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198472" id2="17" version="1065353216">No point in being cunning when brute force will get the job done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198474" id2="17" version="1065353216">So let's use it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198475" id2="17" version="1065353216">The shuttle is waiting to take you to Doctor Lorrick's base on Ord Mantell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198477" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hopefully you'll find records of his experiments with the virus. That way, you won't have to take him alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198481" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your work on Kaon was impressive.Your reputation is well earned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198483" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the source of the plague identified, the Tion royal family has been able to contain the outbreak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198485" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's unfortunate we couldn't question that pilot before you killed her. But we were still able to put together a file on Doctor Lorrick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I need to remind you of your proper place, Darth Nurin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198486" id2="17" version="1065353216">You dare question my actions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me, my lord. I meant no disrespect. I was merely making an observation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198489" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pilot had served her purpose. Leaving her alive only opened us up to possible betrayal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198489" id2="17" version="1065353216">She was no longer useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, my lord. I hadn't thought of that. I should have known better than to question your judgment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198492" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you don't like how I do things, go hire someone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that a complaint?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198493" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was merely an observation, not a critique. I am well satisfied with your performance so far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198495" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything else she could have told us would have been lies or irrelevant. I saw no reason to waste your time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198495" id2="17" version="1065353216">I got what we needed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, then, I commend you on your efficiency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198498" id2="17" version="1065353216">You bested the rakghouls on Kaon. I've no doubt you will do the same when you meet Lorrick in person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198500" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't underestimate him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198501" id2="17" version="1065353216">However, they are too timid to move against Doctor Lorrick while he's on a Republic world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198502" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's happening with Melarra?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198502" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about that pilot I found?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198503" id2="17" version="1065353216">We tested her for the rakghoul virus. The results came back clean, so she was released.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198505" id2="17" version="1065353216">The interrogators said she was most cooperative. Once she'd given them all the relevant information, they released her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198507" id2="17" version="1065353216">We honored the deal you struck with her. She was dropped off on a nearby world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198509" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pilot served her role by exposing Doctor Lorrick's involvement. Now it's up to us to eliminate him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pathetic. Guess it's up to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198512" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. Left unchecked, he could become a serious rival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me everything you've learned about Doctor Lorrick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198514" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do we know about him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major Byzal will make contact once you land on Kaon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, my lord. I've been monitoring the situation in the Tion Hegemony. Things are getting worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. You're here. I've been monitoring the situation in the Tion Hegemony. Things are getting worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198524" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Tion noble families have quarantined all worlds in the sector--no ships can land or leave without permission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198526" id2="17" version="1065353216">The announcement was not popular. Those trapped on the infected worlds feel betrayed by their rulers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198527" id2="17" version="1065353216">The nobles had to contain the outbreak using any means possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198527" id2="17" version="1065353216">The quarantine was necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198528" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree, though they should have acted sooner. They waited too long to impose travel restrictions, and the virus spread.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198530" id2="17" version="1065353216">The chaos and confusion can be turned to our advantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198530" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can exploit this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Precisely. And I know the perfect place to strike.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198533" id2="17" version="1065353216">What else have you learned?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Four worlds have been completely overrun. A fifth, Kaon, is down to a handful of survivors battling for their lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Among those survivors are several nobles related to the ruling family. But we will have to act quickly if we want to rescue them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why should we help those too weak to help themselves?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198537" id2="17" version="1065353216">They do not deserve salvation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Having allies in the ruling class could prove valuable in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198538" id2="17" version="1065353216">No doubt they'll be grateful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198539" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you would grasp the full implications of this situation, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198541" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're paying the bills.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198541" id2="17" version="1065353216">A hunt is a hunt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198542" id2="17" version="1065353216">The survivors may know something about the plague's origins. It's our best chance to learn who is behind this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198544" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only reason you'd want to save them is if they had valuable information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198544" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think they know something?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your mind is quick. The survivors may help us discover who was behind the sudden outbreak of the plague.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we have permission to land on Kaon?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198547" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the quarantine?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198548" id2="17" version="1065353216">We do. The nobles are desperate. They believe the plague was unleashed as an act of terrorism.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198550" id2="17" version="1065353216">They see us as an ally against an unknown foe trying to destabilize the Tion Hegemony and seize power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198552" id2="17" version="1065353216">No rakghoul scares me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198553" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rakghouls are not the real enemy. They are only a tool; a weapon for a hidden foe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198555" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoever unleashed this plague is trying to destabilize the Tion Hegemony so they can swoop in and seize power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198557" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone with that kind of ambition could become a dangerous rival if left unchecked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198558" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once we find out who is behind this, I will destroy them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198558" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor hates rivals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once we know who is responsible, we may be able to win them over to our side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe we can recruit them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198560" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just need a name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198560" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198561" id2="17" version="1065353216">Investigating the outbreak is our best hope of learning our enemy's true identity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turning the rakghoul plague into an instrument of war is an impressive feat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198563" id2="17" version="1065353216">They weaponized the virus?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Learning how the virus was synthesized could give us a powerful weapon to use against our foes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198566" id2="17" version="1065353216">So how do we stop them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198567" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have a contact on Kaon: Major Byzal, head of local security. He's cleared a shuttle to take you down to the surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major Byzal will contact you with a situation update after you land.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
