<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>62</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/taris/multi/imperial/vn_99.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198573" id2="17" version="1065353216">My master and I remain your humble servants, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198575" id2="17" version="1065353216">My master was very impressed with your work in the Tion Hegemony. She looks forward to working with you again in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198579" id2="17" version="1065353216">Others may soon learn of the situation in the Tion Hegemony. You must act quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198583" id2="17" version="1065353216">A moment of your time, my lord. My master wishes to speak with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Word has come to my master that your services may be for hire. She has an offer she would like you to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198587" id2="17" version="1065353216">My master has followed your career with great interest. She has a proposition for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Few in the galaxy could stand against such a formidable collection of talent. That is why my master would like to make you an offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198591" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are many ears about. Please wait while I establish a secure connection.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198593" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is an honor to meet the famed Emperor's Wrath. I am Darth Nurin, a humble servant of you and your master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198594" id2="17" version="1065353216">I welcome those who are loyal to me... provided they have something of value to offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198594" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are wise to bow before me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations on your ascension to the Dark Council, my lord. I am Darth Nurin, your humble servant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198596" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suspect I will soon have a host of followers swearing undying loyalty. Most will be beneath my notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198596" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are wise to bow before me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198597" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did not come empty-handed, my lord. I know of an opportunity. One you alone have the strength to seize.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198599" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Darth Nurin. I must congratulate you on eliminating the Supreme Chancellor. You struck quite a blow against the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198600" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Darth Nurin. I must thank you for eliminating Darth Tormen. You removed a dangerous rival from my path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198601" id2="17" version="1065353216">That job is over and done with. Now I'm looking for the next one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198601" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't dwell on my past.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198602" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suspected as much. I have a job for you. I promise I will make it worth your while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198604" id2="17" version="1065353216">My name is Darth Nurin. Please accept my condolences on the unfortunate end of the Imperial Intelligence program.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198605" id2="17" version="1065353216">A lot of Sith were happy to see us go. You might be one of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198605" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't tell if you're joking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198606" id2="17" version="1065353216">On the contrary. I understand the value of what you did. In fact, I have need of your services again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198608" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Darth Nurin. I have been following your career with great interest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198609" id2="17" version="1065353216">My name is Darth Nurin. I have been following your careers with great interest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everywhere I go, people seem to know my name. And ask me for favors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198610" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and everyone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198611" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is the price of fame. Everyone wants something from you. But I come with an offer. An opportunity waiting to be seized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198613" id2="17" version="1065353216">There must be a reason you sent your minion to find me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why did you contact me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198614" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have learned of an opportunity. One that can be claimed only through strength, skill and cunning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spare me your bootlicking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. Forgive me, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Few are permitted to talk to me that way. But I will forgive your insolence, since I have need of your unique skills.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you familiar with the Tion Hegemony? An independent sector, they claim to be neutral in the war between the Empire and Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wealthy, powerful and stubborn, the Tion Hegemony has the potential to be the Empire's greatest threat now that the Republic has fallen low.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198624" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have the upper hand, but the war against the Republic is far from over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198624" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic may rise again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which is exactly why we need to secure control of the Tion Hegemony. Before, they rebuffed our overtures. Now things have changed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198627" id2="17" version="1065353216">The war with the Republic has left the Empire vulnerable. Do you think they'll try to take advantage of the situation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198627" id2="17" version="1065353216">You expect them to attack us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198628" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the past, the Tion Hegemony has been aggressive about expanding its sphere of influence. But things have changed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198630" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't be expecting an attack so soon after our battles with the Republic. We'll catch them unaware.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198630" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should strike now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Open warfare could cause the Tion Hegemony to unite with the Republic. But there is another way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198633" id2="17" version="1065353216">We intercepted a series of classified transmissions. The Tion Hegemony's in trouble. Their worlds are being overrun by rakghouls!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unchecked, the outbreak will infect billions. Entire planets will be overrun. But with chaos comes opportunity for those with the power to seize it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198636" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're afraid of the rakghouls, aren't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198636" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you're too scared to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198637" id2="17" version="1065353216">As a group, you have power far greater than my own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your power is far greater than mine, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why should I put myself in harm's way, when I can send others to do the job?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198643" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rakghouls were confined to Taris for centuries. They didn't get off that world by accident.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198643" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did this happen?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198644" id2="17" version="1065353216">We suspect this may be one of the Tion royal families making a bid for power. But we have no way to know for sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198646" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's too much we don't know about this. I want to go there right away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198646" id2="17" version="1065353216">I better investigate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198647" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Tion Hegemony is trying to suppress this news. It has been difficult to gather the necessary details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meet me on my ship. Hopefully by then, we'll know more. My apprentice can provide the location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here are the coordinates of my master's vessel. She eagerly looks forward to your arrival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198655" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's days are numbered. Soon the Empire will crush our ancient foe.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
