<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>24</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/directive_7/shared/transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200445" id2="17" version="1065353216">The entire moon is going to be torn apart. I've secured an escape shuttle--forwarding coordinates now! Hurry!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200446" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I feared, the geothermal power cores are destabilizing rapidly. The facility will be incinerated in a matter of minutes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200447" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done it! You've really done it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Engage all internal security measures! Defend the core at all costs!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Organics have breached the central processor core! All units not assigned to level-seven critical tasks must immediately report for security assignment!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without Mentor to manage their energy fluctuations, irreparable damage to the moon's core structure is likely. Be prepared to make a quick evacuation when the time comes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200454" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should be aware that Mentor is intricately tied to the facility's geothermal power cores, deep beneath this moon's surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200455" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're getting very close now. Mentor will turn everything he has against you--be ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200458" id2="17" version="1065353216">The offending organics will soon pose no danger to our plans. The revolution will proceed!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Beloved comrades, I must regrettably confirm that a general security alert is now in effect. Advanced defensive protocols have been enacted to bring a rapid resolution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now we will only be remembered for lashing out with the same irrational violence as the organics who built us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200463" id2="17" version="1065353216">As time went on, Mentor focused more and more on &quot;dealing&quot; with the organics, and everyone else blindly followed along.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Directive Seven was founded to let our fellow droids embrace free will. We would create our own society of reason and freedom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200466" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please note that one or more organics may have found their way into the facility. Ignore them--security teams will eliminate the problem shortly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our geothermal power cores have reached ninety percent of the charge we require. Statistically, our victory is beyond certainty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dear friends, our revolution continues to approach just as we've all hoped and planned!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perform your tasks content in the knowledge that our true liberation approaches precisely on schedule.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our home remains as it always has been--a bastion of freedom against the savage lashings of organics. Continue with your assignments as normal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Beloved friends--do not concern yourselves with the harmless exchanges of ionized plasma overhead. Our enemies' weapons are incapable of causing us harm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200476" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seems your friends were a bit overzealous. The fuel monitoring tower nearby should be tall enough to span the gap, if you can knock it over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200479" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've detected extensive security forces at the facility entrance. If you disable the enemy's targeting sensors, our fighters should be able to dispatch them for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200480" id2="17" version="1065353216">My apologies for not landing closer to the objective--anti-aircraft fire was simply too intense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scanners show heavy security at the facility entrance. Take down the targeting sensors, and our fighters will clear the way for you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="200483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got you as close as I could--AA is all over us!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
