<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>70</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world/republic/for_the_record/archivist_varus.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014384" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thank you, and our descendants will thank you, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014387" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay back, I'm--oh, you've returned!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014389" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look! Government bank records. Forgotten starship blueprints. Sealed mining data.... The Hutts could have funded, equipped and hidden entire fleets with this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014390" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's only fitting that these records serve the people of Makeb, if you reach a new home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014390" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now your people can use it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed. Losing our world should not mean losing ourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Varus, that historical data would be invaluable to the Jedi Archives. Would you be willing to give us a copy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would you share with the Jedi?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014394" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure we'd need to remove any sensitive information first, but after that...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014396" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Hutts realize their Tech-Adepts failed, they'll try to get those records back. Make sure they stay classified.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep that information safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely. We can't always rely on outsiders for help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I need to start hitting the library more often.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. I could use a fleet....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014400" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will be a setback for Toborro and the Hutts. One of many, I promise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014400" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts will be stopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014401" id2="17" version="1065353216">From you, I believe that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014403" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now the Hutts will have to find their advantages elsewhere, and I can get back to doing something important.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014403" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this is settled, I'm going.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014407" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have my thanks. I must secure these records at once; hopefully the Tech-Adepts haven't sullied them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful out there. Makeb needs people like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014412" id2="17" version="1065353216">So much history, stolen by unworthy hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, stay low. Are you sure you aren't being followed? Every one of those mercenaries is looking for me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014417" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not enough for the Hutts to rip the heart out of Makeb. They would take our mind, our history, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Hutts are sending their mercenaries to steal our oldest records and antiquities, all our secrets. I must save what I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb has much to offer the Republic. We can't let this disaster take away what makes your people unique.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb's culture must survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, and the magnitude is greater than you may think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014423" id2="17" version="1065353216">The evacuees, and their children, will need those records. If Makeb's history is lost, the evacuees will lose who they are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014423" id2="17" version="1065353216">The past informs the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014424" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Makeb is doomed, its memory must be preserved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Instead of hauling around old junk, how about pitching in with the evacuation effort? There are real people who need help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014426" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should be saving people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014427" id2="17" version="1065353216">What am I to do? My hands shake; I know nothing about first aid. But these I can save, and perhaps more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014429" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're looking to get stuff offworld, no questions asked, I might be able to help you out for... oh, hardly any credits at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014429" id2="17" version="1065353216">I offer great shipping rates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014430" id2="17" version="1065353216">So generous! Perhaps your altruism would extend even further?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014432" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never saw Hutts as the academic type. Those records must have more than history in them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014432" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do the Hutts want them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014433" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are mostly histories. They contain many useful scraps, but the true feast is elsewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014437" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't see any mercenary wasting time over one old man and a pile of junk. Come to think of it, I don't have time for this, either.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014437" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one cares.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014438" id2="17" version="1065353216">W--wait! You could help me! These are just the beginning!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014440" id2="17" version="1065353216">The administrative collection at our Cultural Archives has hundreds of classified documents in storage: military, political, financial. The collection's sealed, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014442" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the Hutts have hired the Tech-Adepts of Yablari: Anomid mercenaries and data experts. Even now, they're raiding the archives. Please, can you help at all?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014443" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts need to learn that not everything on Makeb is theirs for the taking. Let me take care of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014443" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure I can help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anomids aren't much for fighting at the best of times. These Tech-Adepts shouldn't be a challenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tech-Adepts don't sound tough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clearly, you've never read about the Tech-Adepts' siege at Paigu. Their battle skills are as well-honed as their minds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every culture thinks their history is sacred. I can't see the Hutts getting much from the government documents of a backwater planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your records aren't worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014448" id2="17" version="1065353216">See for yourself before you judge. I'll compensate you, I swear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014450" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't risk my neck for free, especially not over a bunch of musty old records.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only if there's a reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rest assured, I'll pay well for whatever you can find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014455" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are... the most valuable documents. If only we could remove the antiquities as well.... Ah, Varus, you sentimental old fool!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014456" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the most important item in the Cultural Archives, apart from these documents?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014456" id2="17" version="1065353216">What would you try to save?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, I mustn't be seen!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014694" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shipwright's Tools--you saved them after all. How marvelous! And what's this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014696" id2="17" version="1065353216">And it looks like you brought quite the haul.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014697" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should focus on these documents, but if there's something I can look out for, tell me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014697" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could save something small.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, the Shipwright's Tools are on display there....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014700" id2="17" version="1065353216">The first colonists dismantled their ships for tools, you see, and dug the first mines with them. But the documents have more strategic value.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014702" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't save anything if you keep me hanging around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just let me leave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, yes, you're right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014705" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, the Tech-Adepts will be searching for those documents, too. Be sure not to underestimate them.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
