<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>166</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/macrobinoculars/roth/republic/deena_riss.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay back. If you come too close, I'm dead. If I move, I'm dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104280" id2="17" version="1065353216">He was close by. Wanted to watch the destruction. When it didn't happen, he came here. The Shroud. You didn't kill him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104282" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ganging up against a single man. Not terribly sporting. I approve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104284" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello again, Master Jedi. I do hope you're well rested after slashing your way across the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104286" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been too long since I last matched wits with a master Jedi like yourself. I forgot how exhilarating it can be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major. I had hoped to one day see General Rakton's bane in action. You did not disappoint. Well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, Captain. Much more resourceful than I expected--even from the privateer who bested the Voidwolf.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104292" id2="17" version="1065353216">You put a stop to my most ambitious plan to date. I have to say, I'm impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104294" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you enjoyed fighting my double. Not nearly as formidable as the genuine article, but I feel he played his part quite well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104295" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've already lost, Shroud. There's nothing to be gained in threatening the agent's life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104295" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's over. Now let her go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104296" id2="17" version="1065353216">By revealing yourself now, you lose everything that having a double afforded you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104296" id2="17" version="1065353216">You tip your hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104297" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, that's where you're wrong, Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be a sore loser, Shroud. Let the agent go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104299" id2="17" version="1065353216">You lost. Get over it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104300" id2="17" version="1065353216">I might--but it all depends on you, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104302" id2="17" version="1065353216">The old stand-in trick. I'd use it myself, but I can't find anyone nearly good looking enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104302" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sneaky, sneaky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104303" id2="17" version="1065353216">A curious time to make light, Captain, when you hold an associate's life in your hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104305" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you want with Riss?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104305" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's your game?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing. Nothing at all. It's what I want from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104308" id2="17" version="1065353216">You hide behind doubles and holos. What's wrong--too afraid to face me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104308" id2="17" version="1065353216">Face me, coward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104309" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a student of espionage, I see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104311" id2="17" version="1065353216">My double possessed some data he shouldn't have. It's as though everyone's an ungrateful thief these days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104313" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will now wipe the data clean via Riss's console. Do so, and I'll let Special Agent Riss live. I am monitoring the console, so no tricks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104315" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. Don't. Whatever that data is, it's damaging enough for him to stick his neck out after faking his death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Plug it into the console--but upload the data into the SIS secure system instead. Do it. Don't think about me--not for one second.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104318" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Destroy the data]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104320" id2="17" version="1065353216">There. The data's all yours, Shroud. Now do as you promised.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104321" id2="17" version="1065353216">I may be a professional back-stabber, but I am also a man of my word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104323" id2="17" version="1065353216">The collar--it's powered down. It's over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104325" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, but it's never truly over is it? I'm still alive. Still planning. And now I've found a new challenge. Or rather--a new challenger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, but it's never truly over is it? I'm still alive. Still planning. And now I've found a new challenge. Or rather--new challengers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104327" id2="17" version="1065353216">So long as there are brave souls like Deena Riss willing to sacrifice everything to stop you, all you can do is count the days until you're caught.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104327" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll never win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobility and justice and fluffy clouds. You should see by now that none of that matters to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104330" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not your arch nemesis. You're someone who deserves to be brought to justice--nothing more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104330" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't personal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104331" id2="17" version="1065353216">You disappoint me. Ah, but you'll come around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104333" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want an enemy? You got one--but you'll come to wish you never crossed me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Game on, Shroud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104334" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll detonate that bridge when we come to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Score one to you for saving Galactic City from the greatest plot of mass destruction ever conceived--but this game's only just begun. I'll see you around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104338" id2="17" version="1065353216">So many agents died to get us this far. We could have had him! And now....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104340" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. You know what? You saved the Republic capital from utter destruction. You did the noble thing, and--I'll say it, I'm glad to be alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104341" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a credit to the SIS. They couldn't afford to lose you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104341" id2="17" version="1065353216">You deserve nothing less.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hearing that means more to me than you know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104344" id2="17" version="1065353216">How about we celebrate? Hit the cantina, maybe somewhere more private?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104344" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Go for a drink?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104345" id2="17" version="1065353216">That actually sounds great... but I've probably got several weeks of briefings and report filings in my immediate future. Sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104347" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're on borrowed time now. Make the most of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't blow your second chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104348" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been on borrowed time for quite a while already. I don't ever waste it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104350" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you--for everything. And keep the macrobinoculars. You'll most likely need them again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104353" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Upload the data]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104355" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your sacrifice won't be forgotten, Special Agent Riss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104358" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did not think you had it in you. I'd be impressed--if I wasn't so damned infuriated!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104360" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think you've won. But those files are heavily encrypted, and you're down one more SIS agent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104361" id2="17" version="1065353216">SIS will eventually crack your encryption. And more brave people will rise up to replace Deena Riss and stand in the way of madmen like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104361" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll never win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104362" id2="17" version="1065353216">I not only expect to find resistance; I'm counting on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's just skip to the end of all this to the part where you're brought to justice. What do you say?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turn yourself in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104365" id2="17" version="1065353216">And deprive us of the great chase? No, I don't think so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104367" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not the only one willing to cross lines, Shroud. You may want to sleep with a blaster from here on out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104367" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm coming for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104368" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're assuming I don't do that already--or that I even sleep.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104370" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wanted a grand challenge. Laying waste to Galactic City didn't work out, but now I've found a new challenge. Or rather--a new challenger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104372" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wanted a grand challenge. Laying waste to Galactic City didn't work out, but now I've found a new challenge. Or rather--new challengers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104374" id2="17" version="1065353216">I concede this turn, but the game isn't nearly over. Do enjoy my macrobinoculars. I'll see you around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104379" id2="17" version="1065353216">Woo! You did it! We're safe! Galactic City is safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104381" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like you've found a little something extra there, too. Huh. Never seen encryption like that. Be sure to bring it along for your debrief.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104384" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow. I guess the Shroud won't be gumming up the works anymore. Surprised he didn't try to slip away....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104386" id2="17" version="1065353216">What am I babbling about? Hurry--power down the hyperspace beacon before that dreadnaught plows into Galactic City!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104389" id2="17" version="1065353216">This one had schematics for a hyperspace beacon. And part of a message...? I--I don't believe it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104391" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's planted a hyperspace beacon inside Galactic City! That remote-pilot dreadnaught, he plans to pull it out of hyperspace inside Coruscant's defenses! He's going to crash it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Millions will die! We'll get searching for the beacon but there's so little time. You'll have to find the Shroud and shut it down manually.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104395" id2="17" version="1065353216">All those calls he made to you--I was able to triangulate his general position. Please, hurry! Stop that ship from taking out Galactic City!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104398" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're making me long for the days of being a field agent. Tracked down another lieutenant's data hub. We're good to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104400" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're really making short work of the Shroud's best people. He's gotta be fuming right now. Let's see what we can find in here....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104402" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a manual for a remote piloting system. That would be for the dreadnaught. But he can't be sending it to Coruscant; planetary defenses would blow it to space dust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104404" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something's not adding up here and we're running out of time to do the math. Well--let's hunt down the next set of relays.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104407" id2="17" version="1065353216">I keep wondering what kind of person would potentially kill millions just to do it. It's so utterly insane....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry. Thinking out loud again. I've got the coordinates of another lieutenant. You're doing great. Carry on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104412" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice work. Am I glad I got you to help out. Okay, transmission received....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104414" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow. The Shroud bought a dreadnaught. He's rich, but there's no way he could afford to staff it up. Maybe he's... storing something on it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, just thinking out loud. I got some new relay coordinates off the data. We're still on track. Keep it up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104419" id2="17" version="1065353216">My agents haven't found anything suspicious on Coruscant, but they'll keep looking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good news is, you've given me enough to triangulate another lieutenant. You'll have to pinpoint the exact location yourself, but I have total faith. Riss out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104431" id2="17" version="1065353216">And from all that I'm able to triangulate.... Hold on.... There. That's where you'll find the Shroud's lieutenant. Go to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104433" id2="17" version="1065353216">That won't help us triangulate anything--but, you know, that is one of the Shroud's spy droids. Keep an eye out for more of those--they'll be worth tracking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104435" id2="17" version="1065353216">There you go. That's just what we're looking for. Good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, I just had some credible intel come in. Coordinates uploaded. Let's check it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104438" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really need to be out finding the Shroud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104441" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for coming here to meet me. I'm afraid I'm not quite as mobile as I used to be. Shrapnel will do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104443" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've... been losing agents lately. A lot of talented agents. I have nowhere else to turn, so I hope you can help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104445" id2="17" version="1065353216">A galactic legend's been brought out of retirement--a freelance master spy known only as &quot;The Shroud.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104446" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;The Shroud?&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104448" id2="17" version="1065353216">In all my travels, I've never heard of this &quot;legend.&quot; What can you tell me about him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104449" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's been underground so long that he was barely a whisper when I was in the academy. I think that's by design.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104451" id2="17" version="1065353216">I take it by the codename that this legend's specialty lies in remaining concealed. Makes me wonder if he's even real.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104452" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought he was just a myth back when I was in the academy. But he's real, all right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104454" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not up on my spy lore, so I'll take your word on the whole &quot;legend&quot; thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104455" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, I wouldn't have expected you to have heard of him. He dropped off the map before I even joined the academy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't be much of a legend if I never heard of him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104458" id2="17" version="1065353216">He disappeared so long ago that by the time I joined the academy we really believed he was just a myth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104460" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm more interested in the spy standing in front of me now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104460" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Who cares about him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104461" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're very kind, but I'm afraid this problem is far more important right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104463" id2="17" version="1065353216">How is a single spy taking out SIS agents and threatening the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104463" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's only one man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104464" id2="17" version="1065353216">He isn't just a spy--he's the spy, even after years of laying low.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104466" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shroud came back into SIS chatter after the Hutt Cartel contracted him to gather intel on Republic and Imperial interests.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104468" id2="17" version="1065353216">In his spying, the Shroud found something beyond what the Hutts were looking for. A challenge he could undertake. A weakness he could exploit--on Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104469" id2="17" version="1065353216">You make it sound like this isn't personal to him--almost like it's a game.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104469" id2="17" version="1065353216">A challenge?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Word is the Shroud doesn't act out of morality at all, but out of achievement. The more audacious, the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104472" id2="17" version="1065353216">After everything we went through on Makeb, the Hutts are still plotting against us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isn't the Cartel our ally now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104473" id2="17" version="1065353216">First the Cartel invades Makeb, and now they're targeting the Republic directly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104473" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts are behind this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104474" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Cartel commissioned the Shroud in their lead-up to Makeb--but only to spy. They want no part in the Shroud's plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104476" id2="17" version="1065353216">A &quot;weakness.&quot; A &quot;challenge.&quot; Some specific information would be nice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104476" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is all rather vague.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104477" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't know the exact nature of his attack on Coruscant, except that one of his top lieutenants reportedly resigned over its severity. Fled to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104479" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm good at what I do--really good--but all this is so overwhelming. I need your help to stop the Shroud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104480" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no spy. I'd like your assistance in the field.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104480" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll need your help, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104481" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me? In the field? Not since a sabotaged astromech exploded into my leg....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104483" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand this has been a trial, but you have to keep going.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be strong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104484" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no intention of quitting. I'll be with you every step--figuratively, at least.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like I'll be doing your job for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104486" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the spy, not me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104487" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be helping me save Coruscant from mass destruction. But don't worry, I'll be playing my role as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104489" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of our departed agents managed to intercept a shipment of the Shroud's. In it were several pairs of souped-up macrobinoculars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104491" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got budget envy. Data and environmental analysis, communications, even a special Miraluka interface.... Shroud spent a fortune on these things--which, ironically, you'll be using against him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything to make this madman's failure more likely, whether it be the Force or gadgetry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104492" id2="17" version="1065353216">May technology guide me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. But don't be too quick to dismiss the Shroud as mad. He's highly intelligent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104495" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like most schemers, his own dark endeavors will become his undoing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104495" id2="17" version="1065353216">His ambition betrays him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's not get ahead of ourselves. Even stripped of everything, he's still a formidable threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every little edge helps. Tell me where to go with these binocs and I'll bring him back in binders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another tool in the kit. Good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even if it were that easy to get to the Shroud, you'd want to be careful. He's no slouch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104501" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just hope I get to see the look on his face right up and close when he realizes he's busted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104501" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do enjoy irony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104502" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't be so eager to be anywhere near the Shroud. From all accounts, he's no pushover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104504" id2="17" version="1065353216">How will a pair of binoculars help me avert a massive attack?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104504" id2="17" version="1065353216">How so?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104505" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need fancy toys.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104507" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force is my guide. I have no need for trinkets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104508" id2="17" version="1065353216">I mean no disrespect, but unless the Force can recognize discrete data packets and send them to me, you will need this trinket.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104510" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you've seen my jacket. Have I ever had trouble tracking anyone down before?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your stats are impressive, Major, but these are highly-trained covert operatives. Without these macrobinoculars, they're ghosts to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on--look who you're talking to. I always know the best hiding spots. I won't need binoculars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104514" id2="17" version="1065353216">We aren't looking for contraband inside a freighter, Captain. This is far more complicated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104516" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Shroud's data is scattered among his lieutenants. We've got a lead on one, but you'll need to identify key relay points that will help us triangulate his precise location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104518" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll remain in constant contact, monitoring your incoming data to keep up with your progress. Working together, I know we can stop the Shroud. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hi. Sorry I can't talk; I'm really busy right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great work, stopping the Shroud's plan. Thank you.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
