<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>49</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/voss/bronze/republic/cyber_beasts_are_bad_enough/sachal_kand.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85288" id2="17" version="1065353216">With Lakkna gone, her men should scatter. I'll make sure they stay scattered.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85289" id2="17" version="1065353216">My proximity alarms aren't showing more than a droid or two. Looks like you whittled them down nicely.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85291" id2="17" version="1065353216">Though, I guess that means Lakkna's gone, too. She wouldn't have let them be destroyed, not without a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lakkna went easily. I made sure of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85292" id2="17" version="1065353216">She didn't suffer.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85293" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks. If we can't give our enemies some dignity, we're on the wrong side, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85295" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. This is over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85296" id2="17" version="1065353216">She was a danger that needed to be removed, that's all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85296" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be sentimental.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85297" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe so. But she wasn't like other Gormak. Makes you wonder.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here. I appreciate what you did, but keeping Sith droids out of Gormak hands--that deserves more than just a thank-you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85301" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we don't get those droids back, next time Lakkna shows up, it'll be with a small army.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good, at least someone's making it through. She's not found a way past yet....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good, people are making it through. She's not found a way past yet....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85308" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry. You must be here for the ship. The one the Gormak were looking for. Turns out they found more than just a wreck.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85310" id2="17" version="1065353216">The marshes around that ship were full of deactivated war droids, probably its cargo or crew. Now they belong to the Gormak. That's really bad news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85311" id2="17" version="1065353216">You didn't say how many were injured in this raid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85311" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was anyone hurt?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85312" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one. I'm guessing her priority was the droids, not a body count. And by &quot;she,&quot; I mean Lakkna.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85314" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand the risks, but if the Gormak want to learn from us, that could open some channels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85314" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their curiosity may be useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe in twenty years or so, but right now she just wants a droid army. And by &quot;she,&quot; I mean Lakkna.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85317" id2="17" version="1065353216">The more chances they have to study our technology, the worse their weapons are going to get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right. Gormak adapt tech.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85318" id2="17" version="1065353216">And that's just the beginning. I know who's behind this; Lakkna's planning something big.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85320" id2="17" version="1065353216">A whole raid for some scrap metal? The Gormak need to rethink their priorities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not much of a heist.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85321" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know who was leading that raid, and to her, those droids are priceless. Her name's Lakkna.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85323" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the Gormak use those cyber-beasts, but I haven't run into any of their droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85323" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never seen Gormak droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85324" id2="17" version="1065353216">To the Gormak, droids are taboo, abominations. They think she's crazy to go after them. And by &quot;she,&quot; I mean Lakkna.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because salvaging those droids will teach the Gormak how to make their own. And I saw who was leading that raid: Lakkna.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lakkna's a Gormak... warlord, I guess. Tough, ambitious, incredibly smart--she led the Gormak excavation team right here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85331" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate to do it, but we've got to cut through those droids and take her down. I need the best to take care of it. She shouldn't suffer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you tried diplomacy?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85333" id2="17" version="1065353216">My negotiator was chased off with blaster fire. She's not interested in talking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave Lakkna to me. If I can make this painless, I will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85335" id2="17" version="1065353216">She won't, I'll see to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85336" id2="17" version="1065353216">It almost sounds like you don't want Lakkna dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85336" id2="17" version="1065353216">You admire her.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe. I respect her. But if it's a choice between Lakkna and the Voss, there's no question.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85339" id2="17" version="1065353216">All our droids have homing devices, so they don't trample anything the Voss care about. Gives us a lead on Lakkna's base.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85341" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most important thing is getting those droids out of Gormak hands. But be sure you take down Lakkna, too. We'll never get a better chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85343" id2="17" version="1065353216">You handle her. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85344" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. I'll watch out for Lakkna marching at the head of a droid army.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85346" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's too smart for her own good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Things just got worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="515748" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry to lay this on you. But she was deadly enough without a pack of war droids at her command. And by &quot;she,&quot; I mean Lakkna.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
