<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>31</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/bronze/republic/tower_defense/captain_barra.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727771" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got scouts everywhere now. House Thul won't sneak anything by us again.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back. All transmissions from the tower stopped. You must have found House Thul's intel.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727775" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire would have wiped us out if you hadn't come along. We owe you our lives. Thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727777" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get inside the Imperial base, destroy their intel on us, and shut down that tower.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727780" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Glarus Valley. Captain Cahill was smart to recruit a whole squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi, am I glad to see you. Things are even worse than we thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant. Captain Cahill told me support was on the way. Sure glad it's you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727786" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the mercenary Captain Cahill hired. I hope your contract was flexible.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727788" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Cahill mentioned Thul agents were seen near one of our weather towers. We caught a few on their way back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727790" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turns out they weren't sabotaging the tower-- they were converting it for surveillance. House Thul is spying on us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="727791" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's quite a surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727792" id2="17" version="1065353216">We only just found out ourselves. I can't get through to Captain Cahill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="727794" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="727795" id2="17" version="1065353216">They could be lying.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727796" id2="17" version="1065353216">They weren't lying. We picked up some transmissions from the tower itself.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727798" id2="17" version="1065353216">That tower used to scan our weather patterns. Now it's scanning our numbers, our equipment, our positions.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Worse, that intel isn't being sent to some remote Thul outpost. It's going to a fully manned Imperial base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="727801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's not waste time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="727802" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any more good news?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727803" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not hopeless. We know they're watching us now. And we've got you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="727805" id2="17" version="1065353216">You let it happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727806" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Thul slipped this one by us, it's true. But they won't get away with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727808" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've barely got enough troops to defend this outpost, let alone take on the Empire. But you might stand a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get inside the base, destroy their intel, and shut down the tower. My men can repair it after the dust settles.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="727811" id2="17" version="1065353216">No problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727812" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll get a hero's welcome from me, if you can pull this off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="727814" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="727815" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'd better.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry about us. House Thul won't get past us again.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727818" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll keep monitoring the tower. Good luck in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727820" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, can't talk now. Things are pretty busy here.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
