<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>40</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/bronze/republic/tower_defense/captain_cahill.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317665" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to know House Organa can count on allies like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clear out those explosives around the weather tower before you disarm the main charge at the base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="317670" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you doing out here, Captain?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317671" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keeping an eye on some agents from House Thul. See that weather tower way off in the distance?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317673" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're planting explosives in the surrounding area. Trying to replicate a groundquake to weaken the foundation.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then they'll set off charges at the tower's base and bring it crashing down on top of the town below it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="317676" id2="17" version="1065353216">What did that town ever do to them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="317676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why destroy the town?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing. House Thul just wants to cause chaos and confusion. They figure the worse things get, the better their chances of taking over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="317679" id2="17" version="1065353216">So how do we stop them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="317680" id2="17" version="1065353216">So how do we stop them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="317681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killing civilians. Disgusting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317682" id2="17" version="1065353216">What else do you expect from House Thul? They're allied with the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317684" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't spare any troops right now, but someone needs to go up there and disarm those explosives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="317686" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could help... for a price.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317687" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can probably scrounge up a few credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clear out the explosives in the surrounding area first. Then disarm the main charge at the base of the tower.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch out for snipers and Thul patrols. If you manage this, send word to Captain Barra--she's evacuating the civilians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="317693" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then maybe you should go bother someone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="317698" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have time to chat. I'm on duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727821" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you doing here? Get inside that outpost and destroy House Thul's intel!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speak with Captain Barra. She knows the situation with that weather tower.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keeping an eye on some agents from House Thul. See this weather tower, way off in the distance?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those agents took some heavy equipment in that direction. We're not sure what they're up to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="727825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our troops are stretched thin in that area, and Thul knows it. Perfect time for sabotage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="727828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's find out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="727829" id2="17" version="1065353216">So why worry?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727830" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got plenty to worry about. Thul's allied with the Empire. They'll do anything to win.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727832" id2="17" version="1065353216">We haven't lost this war yet, but we don't need any surprises. Whatever's going on at that tower, we need to stop it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727834" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're heading that way, we could use some support. Our troops can't handle the Empire and House Thul alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="727835" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can lend a hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="727836" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of support?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Communication from the area's been spotty. Could be whatever Thul's doing to the tower.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coordinates to the nearest outpost. Captain Barra's in command of what we have left.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Check in with Captain Barra when you arrive. She'll have more intel on that tower.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="727843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727844" id2="17" version="1065353216">My creds are on that town below it. Thul blows up that tower, the debris destroys the town.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="727845" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever Thul is up to, we're not taking any chances. We're evacuating the town. We could use help at the tower.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
