<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>172</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235339" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is where the war is focused, huh? Maybe someday it'll look like Taris.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia represents the Empire's greatest prize. It would be an honor to gift wrap it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235341" id2="17" version="1065353216">War ravages this place--the people will never be the same. It saddens me deeply.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235342" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can feel the war here--it makes the marrow in my bones swell. So exhilarating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235343" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally, Corellia--soon to be the site of the Empire's greatest victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235344" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith clan ravages this place. We want in.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235345" id2="17" version="1065353216">A monument to the foolishness of humanity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Towering buildings, neon signs and big guns. I didn't think I'd ever see this place again after the last time they kicked me out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235347" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd only ever seen Corellia in images. It's even more impressive in person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235348" id2="17" version="1065353216">A city in shambles--an archaeologist's dream, you know. So many layers of history peaking through the cracks, waiting to be uncovered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235349" id2="17" version="1065353216">I distrust cities. Too many tall buildings. Sniper's nests. Ambushes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235350" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knew a Corellian pirate, once. Promised to show me his planet sometime. Don't think anyone here expected this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235351" id2="17" version="1065353216">We never thought we'd visit the Republic Core Worlds. We certainly never thought we'd fight here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235352" id2="17" version="1065353216">A fine planet for drink, and a fine planet for starships... but not one where I'd like to fight a ground war. Whatever the official word, this will not be a swift battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235353" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never thought I'd see the day we invaded the Core Worlds. We should be proud of our troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Encrypted communications traffic is heavy. Republic, Imperial and unassigned channels are active.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235355" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't believe we're standing on one of the founding planets of the Republic. I mean, there was Alderaan, but aside from Coruscant, Corellia is the heart and soul of the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Used to call this place &quot;home.&quot; Don't see that happening again. Just won't be the same once the Imps finish draping their flags over everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235357" id2="17" version="1065353216">Urban war zone. No clear front line, easy to get surrounded or ambushed. Messy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235358" id2="17" version="1065353216">Buildings so tall, and everywhere. Blizz think it must be crowded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gonna be another Coruscant. Got a feelin'. Let's get out there 'fore all the good killing's done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235362" id2="17" version="1065353216">I ever mention I have a fear of dying in a bombing run?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235363" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy was forced to retreat from here. But not far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235364" id2="17" version="1065353216">This has been the site of many deaths. From both sides. The pain of it still speaks to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235365" id2="17" version="1065353216">The scent of death is divine here. I will add my own smell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235366" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heh, Empire blew this area to bits. Wish I could have been in on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry, battles rage without us!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235368" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is the great Corellia. Ha.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235369" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is quite the war, ain't it? I remember these used to be fully functioning factories, pumping out smoke so thick you could choke.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235370" id2="17" version="1065353216">So much devastation. It's not just the buildings. Think of the people who used to work in those factories, the people who used to buy the things they made. This whole war is a waste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235371" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. Factory structure indicates that these were built about a century ago, though the underlying strata suggests industrialization of the area began much earlier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Old industrial center. A good place to strike from. Lots of cover, unstable buildings to throw your enemies off guard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235373" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're not gonna fix this. Even if the Corellians get their planet back, you can't fix this much damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235374" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's unfortunate it came to this. It will take a long time to gain the locals' trust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235375" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive use of explosives--it takes exceptional power to level buildings, and really, the wreckage is quite minimal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235376" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're fighting to take this planet block-by-block. We have to win this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235377" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scanning explosive residue. Detecting radioactive particles.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235378" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place got hit pretty hard. You think there's still fighting in the area? I'm going to keep an ear out for any scheduled artillery... just in case.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235379" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not exactly how I remember the place. Most of the buildings in Coronet City weren't falling over when I was living here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235380" id2="17" version="1065353216">Buildings took a hammering. One of these collapses, won't be pretty. Best keep moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235381" id2="17" version="1065353216">Empire people making big mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235382" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice mess. Gotta be some cannons 'round here. Oughta nab one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235385" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing like a big war to make you feel small. This is the smallest I've felt since--well--the last planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235386" id2="17" version="1065353216">Axial Park will be a challenge to traverse. Many ambush-friendly sites and hard to find cover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235387" id2="17" version="1065353216">A moment of beauty amidst the ravages of war. Gives you hope, doesn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235388" id2="17" version="1065353216">A beautiful place. We will walk our Corellian slaves here as pets when we finish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235389" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is where we should have the parade after we take this planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235390" id2="17" version="1065353216">We belong on the battlefield!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someday, even these fields will be consumed in fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235392" id2="17" version="1065353216">I crashed in this park once. They filled the crater with water and made a lake. Even in this shape, I'd take Corellia over Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Axial Park has a galactic reputation. This was once such a beautiful place. The center of Corellian culture. Now it's as ruined as everything else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235394" id2="17" version="1065353216">To think, someday some intrepid explorer will excavate the ruins of this park and find traces of us. It really puts things into perspective, doesn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Appearances are deceiving. Relaxing. But trees can hide enemies. Mustn't let your guard down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect little battlefield downtown. March across the lawn, shoot from the buildings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235397" id2="17" version="1065353216">They used to film entertainment dramas here. Axial Park was a backdrop to show the Republic at its finest. No longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235398" id2="17" version="1065353216">Axial Park. The site of so many clandestine meetings between spies and politicians... we'll be sorry to see that tradition end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kaas City has an arboretum in the lower levels. I'm sure this was beautiful, but it hardly compares.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Foot traffic is directed into the cross fire at these points. The park is an elegant murder machine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235401" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Axial Park... they're turning it into a killing field. I guess there's nothing the Empire and Republic aren't willing to fight over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235402" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of all the places to fight over, why choose a park? If you ask me, the Empire and Republic are slugging it out just for the sake of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235403" id2="17" version="1065353216">Found my war. Come on, let's show 'em what a Mando's made for.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235404" id2="17" version="1065353216">People forget to build hard ground on this spot?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235405" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm likin' the view. Gonna stand here and let them have all the fun? Let's get in the fightin'!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235408" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take a picture. I'm guessing this place will never be this pretty again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Green Jedi Enclave, my lord. We are likely to face opposition here. And they will defend this place to the end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, I sense the calmness of Jedi here. It's always a burden when we face Jedi--more often than not, violence cannot be avoided.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235411" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Green Jedi hide here, trembling, waiting for us to pry them out of their shells.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235412" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heard some of the military brass saying this is where the Jedi are encamped. Always gets me pumped going up against Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235413" id2="17" version="1065353216">My claws scream for Jedi blood.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235414" id2="17" version="1065353216">I smell Force users.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Place almost makes me want to sit down for a bit, relax. I can almost see what the Jedi like about it. Almost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235416" id2="17" version="1065353216">There has to be some middle ground. You can't force order on nature like this, but is the only other option to destroy it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235417" id2="17" version="1065353216">It really is rather gorgeous, isn't it? I'm usually not one for parks, but I have to admire what the Green Jedi have done here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235418" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trees are good cover. Open spaces, dangerous. Watch for Jedi. Feel their movements. Move faster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soldiers, Jedi, CorSec officers... I think we've got an army to fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Into the gardens. We swarm upon the enemy, and sing the Song of Fury.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235421" id2="17" version="1065353216">The gardens may be well tended, but there are flaws to be exploited in their defenses. Shall we?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235422" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi take good care of their gardens. Shall we see how they fight?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi combat techniques rely on breath control. I can analyze breathing patterns at a significant distance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235424" id2="17" version="1065353216">A lot of care went into these gardens. I bet this used to be a great place to relax.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235425" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is what a Jedi Enclave looks like, huh? Real pastoral. Wonder if they do all their gardening with their lightsabers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lot of window dressing, not a lot of fortification. Never expected they'd get attacked here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235427" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooh, Blizz like green place. Take break?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, ain't this just precious. Thought these wimps were Jedi, look more like a buncha gardeners.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia = key to Republic victory + saving the galaxy // Jedi + T7 = will not fail!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235434" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Republic can't save Corellia, the Empire wins. It's as simple as that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235435" id2="17" version="1065353216">I love Corellia. The people, the night life, the fine beverages.... Let's keep this planet in one piece.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235436" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is it. The battle for Corellia will change everything. For the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, yes. So-called civilization. Look upon Corellia's metal and stone towers. See the insects scurry inside them. Is it any wonder the Emperor seeks to destroy it all?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Empire has struck Republic's heart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, Corellia. Once home to so many bored heiresses. Where are they now, I wonder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235440" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellians never think ahead. This is what happens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235441" id2="17" version="1065353216">I always meant to take shore leave on Corellia one day. Just kept putting it off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235442" id2="17" version="1065353216">Father said we'd visit Corellia together one day. I'm almost glad he didn't see it like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever else happens here, I'm looking forward to kicking the Empire off Corellia. It's payback time, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235444" id2="17" version="1065353216">On Corellia, Bowdaar is not a gladiator. On Corellia, Bowdaar fights for freedom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235445" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can already hear the fighting in the streets. This may be the first time in my life I'm not happy to see a city.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235446" id2="17" version="1065353216">A world at a war. It's like coming home. Let's begin this hunt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235447" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force better be with me. I'm too young and handsome to die on Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imps marching on Corellia, Rakton inside the Bastion... we've got a lot of work to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235449" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen what the Empire can do in a place like this firsthand. We should move quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235450" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will not allow Corellia to fall to the Empire. We will defend our citizens at all costs!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like the Imps have a big head start. We'd better move fast, or there won't be much left to fight for.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235452" id2="17" version="1065353216">War scribes its bloody tale across this once-peaceful place.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235455" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major power station = destroyed by bombardment // Civilian losses = high</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235456" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we don't hurry, this is what all of Corellia will look like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235457" id2="17" version="1065353216">If anybody was alive here when the bombing started, they didn't stay that way for long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235458" id2="17" version="1065353216">The sector suffered heavy bombardment. This must be a major control point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235459" id2="17" version="1065353216">You see the destruction? Every death here feeds the dark side.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cowards to use bombs. No points for such killing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235461" id2="17" version="1065353216">So the Empire isn't interested in taking prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. Empire got a clean hit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235463" id2="17" version="1065353216">Probably a high-altitude strike. Poor souls never stood a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235464" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can the Empire do this? How can they just murder people in their homes?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whew. Hope we don't meet what did all this damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235466" id2="17" version="1065353216">Standing in a crater is bad luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235467" id2="17" version="1065353216">This may be the safest place to stand on Corellia. There's nothing left here to fight over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing left but rubble. The battle here has moved on. Let's find where it went.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235469" id2="17" version="1065353216">I bet a Jedi leveled this building. We're very powerful, you know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235470" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place has taken some major ordnance hits. The Imps will pay for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Extensive bombardment. The Imperials are holding nothing back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235472" id2="17" version="1065353216">All who serve the Empire will face justice for what has been done here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235473" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imps are just smashing everything they can get to, huh? They're going to regret being so careless.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235474" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can our enemies look upon such devastation with pride?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235477" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic forward lines = strong // Imperial resistance = heavy // T7 + Jedi = standing tall!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast the Empire. Forcing us to fight it out in the city's one beautiful place. Typical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235479" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've gotta keep this park from burning down. Corellia's people need something good to come back to when this is over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235480" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fighting's getting heavier in Axial Park. The Empire isn't holding back. We can't, either.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235481" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic should not bother creating bases like this. Axial Park presents nothing but a tempting target.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Living grass among dead buildings. Is good to see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235483" id2="17" version="1065353216">If only we had time for a stroll. Axial Park has a rare charm all its own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperials burned down Balmorra's parks. Corellians should appreciate Axial Park while they have it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235485" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not often we get an actual walk in the park.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235486" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've only seen Axial Park in holos. The smell's... not how I imagined.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235487" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Republic doesn't settle this quick, Corellia's gonna wind up looking like Ord Mantell.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235488" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fighting is worse in this park. Bowdaar is ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235489" id2="17" version="1065353216">This used to be a nice park. I spent a summer living in those trees, just for fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235490" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic has changed the rules of engagement. They're using nature against the Empire. Interesting tactic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235491" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know, I fight a lot better when I've had a good swim. You suppose there's a pond anywhere in this park?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235492" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised the park hasn't burned to the ground yet. Probably just a matter of time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Parts of the park are still standing. At least something has survived the Empire's onslaught.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Into the trees, through the buildings, across the roads! We will find our enemies wherever they hide!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235495" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hard to believe there are still trees around when half of the buildings are leveled. Maybe the Imps won't destroy everything after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235496" id2="17" version="1065353216">This one place reflects the entire conflict: life and death, perilously close.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi + T7 = liberate Corellia's government + restore freedom!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235500" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the seat of Corellia's power. Let's kick the Empire out of here for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235501" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is where all of Corellia's politicians are--even the good ones who got locked up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235502" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we can take the central government sector, we'll own Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235503" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's forces are concentrated here. Break them, and Corellia is yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is where Corellia's elders debated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235505" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Legislature. Another lovely building wasted on politicians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235506" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legislature. Housed Imperial collaborators. Let's burn it down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235507" id2="17" version="1065353216">So that's where Corellia's politicians gambled with people's lives, and lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235508" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's buildings are so huge. Even our royal palace isn't half this size.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at that fanciness. Why is it the biggest scum always get to live in the nicest places?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperials everywhere. Bowdaar could fight here all day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235511" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the government district. If we see any expensive and easily transportable objects, I'm sure nobody will miss them. Just a thought....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235512" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to the home of Corellia's true failure: its spineless politicians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally, a place on Corellia that isn't on fire. Why did I say that? I just jinxed it, didn't I?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235514" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the Legislature. The Imps might think that holding it puts them in charge, but that's not going to happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235515" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe that's the Legislature. Government building and seat of Corellian politics. Captured by the Empire in their first assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235516" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Legislature! Seat of democracy on Corellia, but home to the criminals who betrayed us all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235517" id2="17" version="1065353216">That must be the Legislature building. I'll bet nobody expected the Imps to take that one so easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun believes this is the legislature. Former seat of the Corellian government.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Approval: I do enjoy a large metropolis, master. So many chances to liquidate undesirables.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assessment: Nothing left but to complete the liquidation process. You're too kind, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Complaint: These park lands waste space that could house troublemakers for liquidation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Declaration: I don't care what color these Jedi are--I will liquidate them all!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assurance: Corellia will not fall, master. I'll delete every Imperial troublemaker personally, if necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023566" id2="17" version="1065353216">Extrapolation: It appears the Empire has made significant progress deleting Corellia's citizenry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Encouragement: This small wilderness presents many ambush spots. We should take advantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Summation: An impressive edifice for a corrupt government. I would expect nothing less.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
