<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>232</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/alderaan/lokin/lokin.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170933" id2="17" version="1065353216">My probes notified me of your success. Not a moment too soon, by the looks of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170934" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just hurry, Doctor. I want this over with.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170935" id2="17" version="1065353216">These better work this time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170936" id2="17" version="1065353216">It appears my predictions proved accurate. I'll have to count my lucky stars tonight.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170937" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should test them before we start celebrating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170938" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too true.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take them. The stench is killing me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170941" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have I mentioned that rakghouls primarily hunt by smell?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170943" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've never scoured the aftermath of firaxan shark spawning frenzy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170945" id2="17" version="1065353216">This had better be worth the trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170946" id2="17" version="1065353216">Has my grapple with mortality burdened you? I'll try dying more conveniently in the future. If I have one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170948" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not my first choice for sample preservation, but remarkably effective. I may have to consider sarlaccs for discreet storage in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170949" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a bit early to be thinking of the future. Check the viability of your samples.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Promise not to come to me if you do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170951" id2="17" version="1065353216">Honestly, I'm interested to see for myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170953" id2="17" version="1065353216">That may be the most disgusting thing I've ever experienced. And I've been undercover on Hutta.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170954" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have to identify the genes responsible for your hardy constitution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see what you've pulled from the jaws of death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170960" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're quite lucky. What you gathered was exactly what I needed. This serum should counteract the infection.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't it feel nice to have the weight of your own mortality lifted from your shoulders?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170963" id2="17" version="1065353216">I feel... tired.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes... it's light... dizzy... am I okay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170965" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, you'll be just fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170967" id2="17" version="1065353216">What... what did you do...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170968" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, you're in no danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170970" id2="17" version="1065353216">The sedative will slow your mind and movements, but it causes no permanent harm. Just a precaution, in case you were still harboring any aggressive inclinations toward me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170972" id2="17" version="1065353216">We got off on the wrong foot, but you've been quite useful, so I'm willing to forgive and forget.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170973" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was... a trick....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170974" id2="17" version="1065353216">We both benefited from your work.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine... we'll call it even....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apology accepted.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive...! After this...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170980" id2="17" version="1065353216">Emotional for a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170982" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a lot to ask from a Sith, I know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170984" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see you're the emotional type.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170986" id2="17" version="1065353216">By the time you awaken I will be gone. My fallow years at an end and possessed of a new lease on life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170988" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could go anywhere, do anything. Where do you suggest, Commander?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Odessen... fight... Zakuul.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trade the sound of the sea breeze through the grass for the dank of a foxhole? The gentle warmth of the sun for the glow of a datapad?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170992" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe I shall.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170996" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Reject Companion] To... hell...!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170997" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's what you wanted, all you had to do was wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Next time we cross paths, I hope your mood will have improved. Else I may have to kill you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171003" id2="17" version="1065353216">The moment of truth. I don't anticipate a volatile reaction, but... a little space might do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warm, but not unpleasant. Pulse: elevated. No swelling at the injection site. That will do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some of my cells are showing signs of restoration. The gene therapy appears to be working.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171008" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've held up my end of the bargain.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171009" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's it? You're cured?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171010" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time to put that genius to work for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171011" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose I owe you that much.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171013" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's good news. How long until you have fully recovered?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171014" id2="17" version="1065353216">In a few days the serum should have permeated my system. A week, and my body will have purged my cancers.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171016" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if it doesn't take?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171017" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can rule out complete rejection, but in the event my healing is incomplete I should be able to try variants until I achieve the desired result.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171019" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope this is the last time you meddle with the fabric of your being.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171020" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's sad that SCORPIO was the only one to ever understand my interest in self-improvement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171022" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can already feel the strength seeping back into me. I'll be in top condition before you know it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171024" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was a nice place to escape, but I don't think retirement suits me. Not yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171026" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll join you on Odessen once I've swept the traces of this life away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171030" id2="17" version="1065353216">I received signals from my probes indicating a successful harvest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171032" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me test these samples' viability for your treatment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171034" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to run some tests to see whether these samples will help my condition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent work as always, Cipher. Give me some time to analyze these samples.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171040" id2="17" version="1065353216">No good. This strain has mutated too far from its origin to be useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171042" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a good effort, but these samples don't possess the properties I need to continue my research.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good news: I'm confident that Lorrick's work will lead to a cure. Bad news: the samples you retrieved have mutated too far from my strain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171046" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll have to try a different source.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171047" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you know of one, tell me already.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even if we find one, what's to say it won't be mutated as well?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171049" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are correct, most sources would bear the same results, save one.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171051" id2="17" version="1065353216">You promised me a cure!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171052" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you'll have it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171054" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where next then? Taris?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171055" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Taris strain is likely too close to my initial formula to see results. I need a sample of Lorrick's virus that's been preserved.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171057" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll find the answer. I promise you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171058" id2="17" version="1065353216">You might not be so motivated after hearing what I have to say next.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171060" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're likely to see the same results.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171061" id2="17" version="1065353216">From strains that have been evolving over the years, yes, but not a preserved sample.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know of another one?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171064" id2="17" version="1065353216">It may be our final option.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171066" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure what you're looking for even exists?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171067" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have enough understanding of my condition to know what I'm looking for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171069" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fear there's only one place we can still find it: a sarlacc.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171071" id2="17" version="1065353216">You keep rakghouls as pets and sent me for biological samples at an outbreak location. What aren't you telling me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171072" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm suffering from complications of my own exposure to the virus. It was controlled, but that's no longer the case. Understand my discretion?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171074" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe there is one place where we can still find the strain that we need: a sarlacc.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recall the outbreak on Tatooine? If an infected creature was eaten by a sarlacc it would still be alive, even today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any creature consumed by a sarlacc is slowly digested, alive, over a period of time long exceeding its natural longevity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171078" id2="17" version="1065353216">With Lorrick's lab long since destroyed, it's the only place I can think of where a live sample might be found.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171079" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we get what you need from a sarlacc?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171080" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe that makes sense.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171081" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't expect me to get eaten by that monster, do you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171082" id2="17" version="1065353216">The probes I gave you should be able to traverse a sarlacc's digestive tract safely, provided you deploy them nearby.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171084" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the event they can't... well, more invasive action may need to be taken. Let's hope it doesn't come to that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171088" id2="17" version="1065353216">My stores are fully stocked. All we need are the right samples and a cure will be within our reach.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171090" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd say I've got about half of what I'll need to carry me through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171091" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm still short on raw materials. I'll need those as much as the samples to make progress.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171092" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Give Metamorphic Cell Cultures]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171093" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will help. My thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171095" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have anything for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171096" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then come back when you do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171099" id2="17" version="1065353216">No breakthroughs yet. The materials I need are difficult to obtain, so progress is slow.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171100" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready to help you, Doctor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171101" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171103" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Refuse Quest] Keep at it, Lokin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Encouragement is not what I need. If you don't have anything for me, please leave me to my work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171108" id2="17" version="1065353216">Few people realize the kind of protective instincts rakghouls display for their pack. A rare loyalty these days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171110" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful. Strike two will be your last. Have the scratches begun to itch yet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171112" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find any THORN inoculations rather impotent in combating the strain coursing through your body.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171113" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a cure. You wouldn't risk letting them roam otherwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171114" id2="17" version="1065353216">And what if I'm just mad?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171116" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171117" id2="17" version="1065353216">A monster. But not an unreasonable one. Count yourself fortunate there.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171119" id2="17" version="1065353216">You filthy son of a gundark!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171120" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid I share no genetic stock with those simple creatures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171122" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have the means to save you from the gruesome fate that awaits, but it will require more materials than I have on hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171124" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seems you've just volunteered yourself to replenish my stock.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171125" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do I need to do?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171126" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're lying!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171127" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't needed a cure for a very long time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171129" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll kill you for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171130" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the virus begins to alter your brain, you won't even have the capacity to remember me. All the more reason to cooperate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171132" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd suggest you bring me whatever biochem supplies you can spare, but I'll also need new viral samples to work with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171134" id2="17" version="1065353216">Follow THORN's broadcasts--they'll deploy their Spike anywhere a rakghoul outbreak is detected. Activate my probes in the rakghouls' tunnels, and they might locate useful samples.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171135" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they don't?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we look elsewhere. Quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't you use the virus from your pets?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171139" id2="17" version="1065353216">They will prove useful, but they won't be enough to cure you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171141" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll begin my preparations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171145" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't get many visitors out this way. A delivery droid, a roosting thranta, the odd sail-speeder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171147" id2="17" version="1065353216">Momentary distractions, not always unwelcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171149" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you, I'm actually pleased to see. It's good to know I'll only have to drink for Cipher Twelve in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171150" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seems I've beaten the odds yet again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171151" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think we can safely rule out luck at this point.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171153" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm flattered you kept up the tradition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171154" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give yourself more credit. So long as I linger, I'll remember our time fondly.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171156" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were always eccentric, but never so sloppy. What possessed you to leave rakghouls on the loose?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171157" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never had the pleasure of a Jedi's company for my afternoon recess. I have a sealed tin of jeru tea awaiting such an occasion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171158" id2="17" version="1065353216">A visit from a Sith of your station, however, is quite unexpected. Welcome to my humble abode, my lord. May I offer you some dianogan tea?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171159" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate the hospitality, but that isn't necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171160" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pity. I find tea to be a remarkable emollient. Nothing unfurrows a brow quite like it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171162" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll accept nothing from a man who keeps rakghouls running free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most aren't so well-armed. Should I be concerned?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you Doctor Eckard Lokin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well, we'll pretend you've come all this way without already knowing the answer and I'll humor you for the sake of civility.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171167" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't come to cause you any trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh good, I'm quite sure that would have put a damper on my tea time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171170" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I don't like your explanation for the rakghouls, you might.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171171" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't mind my pets--they were created with a modified strain. Sterile. Harmless. Forty-eight hours after transformation the virus can no longer reproduce.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kowakian monkey-lizards originally. I find them much less obnoxious in this form. They're also remarkably good for pest control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171175" id2="17" version="1065353216">To what do I owe this visitation?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171176" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm organizing an Alliance against the Eternal Empire. I've been told you're a good man to have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171177" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you haven't been told nearly enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171179" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still have need of your skills, Eckard. Now more than ever.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171180" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who says I'm not just sightseeing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171181" id2="17" version="1065353216">By all means take in the sights and be on your way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171183" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps I've simply come to see my old friend?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171184" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps, but we both know you haven't.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171186" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just want to know more about the man who owns this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171187" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just an old retiree trying to escape the tiresome bother of a galaxy in constant strife. I'm certain you'd find me quite boring.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171189" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been nice to have made your acquaintance. If you'll excuse me, I have some things to attend to.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171190" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, Doctor. The galaxy is at stake. Don't pretend it has nothing to do with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171191" id2="17" version="1065353216">Age and infirmity have a way of narrowing one's concerns.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171193" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, wait. I came here to recruit you. The Alliance needs your expertise to combat the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171194" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I suppose you don't intend to simply take &quot;no&quot; for an answer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171196" id2="17" version="1065353216">My health is failing, and I'm afraid that conventional medicine isn't up to the task of stopping my inexorable slide toward oblivion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171198" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the place I've chosen to die, should I fail to synthesize an elixir.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171199" id2="17" version="1065353216">You believe you can find a cure for your condition?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171200" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm nothing if not a survivor.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171202" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't realize. My condolences.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171203" id2="17" version="1065353216">I really shouldn't complain. I've led a long and interesting life, but that offers little comfort when death looms.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171205" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you'd rather squeeze a few more years out of your life than ensure a better future?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171206" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there's going to be a better future, I intend to see it with my own eyes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171208" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have greater troubles on your mind than the travails of an old man... but if you want my help, I want yours first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assist me in discovering my cure and you'll have more than my gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171211" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alright, Doctor. You have a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171212" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need biological samples. Both raw materials and unique specimens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171214" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bring the more common items whenever you have some to spare. As for my special needs, take these collection probes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171216" id2="17" version="1065353216">Follow THORN's broadcasts--they'll deploy their Spike anywhere a rakghoul outbreak is detected. Activate my probes in the rakghouls' tunnels, and they'll gather cultures I may be able to use.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171218" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Refuse Quest] That's not something I have time for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171219" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I must return to finding the answer myself. You know where to find me should you reconsider.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171222" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Draw Weapon] Drop the act.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171223" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember how I said the rakghouls were harmless?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171225" id2="17" version="1065353216">I lied.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171226" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really shouldn't have done that.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171230" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just keeping tabs on you, Doctor. Like old times.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171231" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd come to miss your watchful eye. The game's so boring when played alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171233" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I told you that I got out and retired to this pristine wilderness for a well-deserved rest, would you believe me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171235" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's closer to the truth than you think. I'm dying.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171236" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure the cause is no mystery. What's your diagnosis?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171237" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry. Is there anything that can be done?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something can always be done. The question is: do I have the will and ingenuity to succeed?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171240" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then it's all the more important that you put the time you have left to good use.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171241" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed, but you should know by now that selfless sacrifice holds no appeal for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171243" id2="17" version="1065353216">The alterations I've made to my genes are fraying. With each division, my cells introduce more errors. Cancer is the best I can hope for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171245" id2="17" version="1065353216">Treating the damaged sequences using the strains I have on hand has proven fruitless. I need a stronger virus.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171246" id2="17" version="1065353216">That will be difficult to come by. Outbreaks are eradicated with prejudice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, THORN is aptly named.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171249" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think I like where this is going.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171250" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, I imagine you wouldn't.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171252" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is what you get for using yourself as a test subject.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171253" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a calculated risk. This life was becoming far too dangerous for an old man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171255" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rakghoul strain Sannus Lorrick released years back is perhaps my only hope. I need you to harvest any samples you can find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171257" id2="17" version="1065353216">Follow THORN's broadcasts. Activate these probes in the tunnels anywhere they deploy their Spike. It's all I ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Child's play. I'll contact you when it's finished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171259" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Cipher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171260" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get you fixed, old friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171261" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry you have to see me in this state.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171263" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Refuse Quest] That's not something I can do right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171264" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's disappointing, Cipher. There's time yet for me--you know what I'll be devoting it to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lovely day. Of course, they're all lovely out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171267" id2="17" version="1065353216">You needn't worry--I'm in no danger of becoming a mindless beast. Only a corpse. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171269" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can use these probes to retrieve viable samples. I've prepared a list of locations with potential for useful material. Take a look--it's all I ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171270" id2="17" version="1065353216">The probes will scan for useful samples and retrieve them. I've prepared a list of potential harvest sites. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171271" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've prepared a list of potential harvest sites. These probes should be able to locate and retrieve the materials I'll need.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171830" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Give Anodyne Extract]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171923" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's actually an extra signal coming from.... Now that's above and beyond. I must confess I'm a tad impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171926" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's actually an extra signal coming from... Cipher, you'd go so far for me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps it's just the pending mortality speaking, but... honestly I'm a bit touched.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171930" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know, I must be going soft.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything for you, old friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171932" id2="17" version="1065353216">What can I say, you're my favorite monster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1172371" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1173154" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been infected before, on Taris. I was cured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173155" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cured of one strain, perhaps. But not this one.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1189237" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Give Autoimmune Regulators]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1189238" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Give Hemostatic Gel]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1189239" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Give Rakghoul DNA Canister] What about this?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1189240" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Give Symbiotic Fungal Bloom] Is this useful?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1189241" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Give Exotic Plague Specimen] Can you use this?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1189242" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Limit: 1][Give Barnacle of the Eyeless] Look what I found.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1189262" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be back soon.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
