<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>35</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/universal/space/imperial_fleet_terminal.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Ascendant Pride

The Republic has severed Imperial ties to the Chiss Ascendancy. Alien forces sympathetic to the Republic have blockaded the main supply route from our vital allies.

Chiss resources are essential to the Imperial war effort. The supply lane must be reopened immediately.

Fleet Command calls on the Empire's Fury squadron to assault the alien forces in the Unknown Regions. Blow open the minefield blockade, and assure Imperial victory in the greater conflict.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Raging Dawn

Mission 1: Aeten Defense
War is upon us, and the Republic has responded with treachery. 

Moments ago, traitors aboard the Imperial space station Kilran's Lance disabled the installation's defenses. Simultaneously, the Republic launched a surprise attack.

Kilran's Lance reports critical structural damage. The Empire's Fury squadron is needed at Aeten Ten in the Unknown Regions to save the station from the Republic assault.

Mission 2: Clouds of Vondoru
The Intercessor is the pride of the Republic fleet. The capital ship defended Bothawui and survived the Battle of Hoth; now we will destroy it.

Less than one hour ago, the Imperial fleet ambushed the Intercessor in the skies above Vondoru. Republic reinforcements have already responded to defend their vessel.

Only the Empire's Fury squadron can ensure the Intercessor's complete destruction. Rally at the planet Vondoru in the Unknown Regions and blow the capital ship out of the sky.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Sweeping Menace

Mission 1: Polith Minefield
Imperial convoy traffic through the Polith system is under assault. Pirates have laced the supply route with mines. They have already destroyed three transports and pillaged the debris.

Intelligence identified the pirates' benefactors. The Republic is funding this blockade. 

The Republic pawns must feel the sting of the Empire's Fury squadron. Find them in the Polith system in the Coreward Worlds. Destroy the mines, eliminate the pirates and reopen our supply lines.

Mission 2: Sullust Interception
The Ash Angels, an elite Republic bomber squadron of Sullustan pilots, have gone rogue and launched devastating hit-and-run attacks on Imperial forces.

The Republic publicly condemns the Ash Angels' violation of our treaty, but secretly they applaud the assaults. 

It is time the Ash Angels met the Empire's Fury squadron. Travel to the designated asteroid field in the Distant Outer Rim. Once there, exterminate the Republic bombers.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Rising Fury

Mission 1: Skaross Fortification
The Republic grows bolder by the hour. Despite a strict ceasefire, Republic bombers have attacked a key Imperial manufacturing station.

The Republic shirks responsibility. It has pledged not to retaliate if we strike at the offending bombers--a sacrifice to preserve the peace.

This mission demands the Empire's Fury. Lead your squadron to the Skaross system in the Distant Outer Rim. Destroy the Republic bombers and save the station.

Mission 2: Mugaar Ice Field
Imperial fighters have lured a Republic border patrol from the safety of Republic space.

The border patrol has entered the ice rings of the planet Mugaar. Its communications are jammed, allowing for its discreet elimination.

The Empire's Fury is needed for this delicate mission. Navigate the ice rings of Mugaar in the Seat of the Empire and destroy the border patrol before the Republic knows it is missing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Molten Splinter

Mission 1: Taspan Ambush
The Republic Major Boro Fareed has agreed to defect to the Empire. He was minutes away from meeting Imperial forces when the Republic discovered his betrayal.

Republic ships have intercepted Major Fareed's shuttle and are attempting to capture the defector. This is unacceptable.

Major Fareed's knowledge will expose the inner workings of the Republic military. The Empire's Fury squadron must converge on the Taspan system in the Coreward Worlds and recover the major and his shuttle.

Mission 2: Ezran Outpost
The Ezran pirates are renowned for their corruption, greed and cutthroat tactics. Now they can add &quot;Republic sympathizer&quot; to their list of transgressions.

The pirates' space station outpost has lent aid and asylum to numerous Republic operatives. The treaty forbids attacks against the Republic, but the Ezran pirates are not similarly protected.

The Empire's Fury is to rally in the Ezran system in the Distant Outer Rim. There you will assault the pirates' outpost and cleanse the galaxy of their amoral ways.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Eternal Domain

Mission 1: Nez Peron Sweep
A Republic fighter wing has been sighted over the Imperial-aligned agricultural planet Nez Peron.

The fighters' presence is a challenge to Imperial authority. We will show the citizens of Nez Peron the more powerful fleet.

The Empire's Fury must lead the sweep above Nez Peron in the Seat of the Empire. Neutralize the bold starfighters and demonstrate to the galaxy that Republic activity in Imperial space will not be tolerated.

Mission 2: Sarapin Assault
One hour ago, the Republic warship Enkindle entered Imperial space. When it ignored warnings to turn back, the Imperial dreadnaught Tears of Taris opened fire.

The wounded Republic warship retreated to the upper atmosphere of Sarapin Four. Republic forces are en route to save the Enkindle, but we must beat them to it.

Immediate support is needed to capture the Enkindle within the Coreward Worlds. Cripple the Republic warship, and the Empire will gain a crucial asset in the cold war.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Echo Quake

Mission 1: Cartel Listening Station
The Republic has constructed a hidden listening station in Hutt Space to spy on Imperial operations--a direct violation of the Treaty of Coruscant. 

Intelligence has confirmed that the Hutt Cartel permitted the Republic's actions. In the interests of maintaining neutrality, the Cartel has provided us with the station's detailed schematics.

A full assault is underway, but the Empire's Fury squadron is needed to secure victory. Rally in Hutt Space and aid in the destruction of the Republic station.

Mission 2: Saleucami Fleet Action
Fleet Command has intercepted a distress call. Imperial fighters returning from a classified recon mission have been ambushed by a Republic squadron.

The Republic squadron is no less than the Solar Thrantas, led by the legendary Jedi pilot Nezhel &quot;Sunspot&quot; Othren. Under his command, the Solar Thrantas earned over three hundred confirmed kills in the Great War.

The Republic must be desperate to risk such open aggression in Hutt Space. Save our fighters in the low-orbit asteroid field over the planet Saleucami and eliminate the Solar Thranta squadron.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Silent Roar

Undercover Intelligence agents have secured top secret Republic defense plans. The agents fled for Imperial space in a stolen shuttle, and the Republic has scrambled fighters to capture them.

Minutes ago the Republic fighters caught up to the fleeing shuttle. They trapped the vessel in a tractor beam. Our agents are helpless.

As leader of the Empire's Fury squadron, Fleet Command needs you to defend the shuttle. Hurry to assist near the planet Jobiim in Hutt Space, or years of Intelligence work will be forfeit.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="963208" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

Imperial Intelligence spies carrying vital information on Republic plans are attempting to escape enemy territory in a stolen shuttle. Republic forces are in pursuit, however, and have trapped the shuttle in a tractor beam. Reinforcements are needed to defend the shuttle and ensure the stolen data arrives intact.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="963209" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

The Cartel has allowed the Republic to set up a hidden space station in Hutt Space to intercept dispatches from nearby Imperial operations. All available ships have been dispatched to destroy the station, but additional forces will be necessary to breach the Republic defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="963210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

An Imperial infiltration squadron has been ambushed by Republic forces near the planet Saleucami. The enemy is led by legendary pilot Nezhel &quot;Sunspot&quot; Othren. The squadron needs backup if it's going to survive the battle in the planet's low-orbit asteroid field, but more importantly, this is an opportunity to eliminate the deadly Republic ace.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="963211" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

A Republic fighter wing has established a position over the Imperial-aligned agricultural planet of Nez Peron. Reinforcements are needed to eliminate the Republic vessels so Nez Peron's resources can be secured for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="963212" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

Damaged during a failed incursion into Imperial space, the Republic warship Enkindle is attempting to hide in the upper atmosphere of the planet Sarapin Four. Any available forces should move quickly to cripple the Enkindle before Republic reinforcements arrive.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="963213" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

A key Republic military officer has agreed to defect to the Empire. He is attempting to rendezvous with Imperial forces, but Republic ships have intercepted his shuttle. Immediate assistance is requested in securing the defector before he is captured or destroyed by the enemy assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="963214" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

A space station used by Republic-aligned smugglers has been identified in the Ezran system. All available Imperial vessels should converge on the Ezran system to purge the galaxy of these illegal and amoral pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="963215" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

A key Imperial weapons manufacturing station in the Skaross system is under assault from Republic bombers. Reinforcements are desperately needed to ensure the station's survival.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="963216" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

Imperial ships have lured a Republic border patrol into the orbital ice rings of the planet Mugaar. Communications are being jammed, and the Republic patrol can now be discreetly eliminated. Be aware that a Jedi Master is in command of the enemy forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="963217" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

A pirate fleet has set ambushes and laid an extensive minefield in the Polith system to disrupt Imperial convoys passing through the region. Enemy vessels must be destroyed and the mines cleared to reopen crucial supply lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="963218" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

An elite Republic fighter squadron has been launching devastating hit-and-run attacks on Imperial installations in the Sullust system. The squadron has been tracked to a nearby asteroid field. Eliminating these Republic fighters is vital to the Imperial war effort.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="963219" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

Traitors aboard a space station orbiting Aeten Two have compromised the installation's defenses. The traitors have been neutralized, but the station is defenseless and under attack by a Republic fleet. All available vessels are ordered to engage the enemy forces to protect the station.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="963220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

An Imperial fleet ambushed and damaged the Intercessor, a Republic capital ship, in the skies above Vondoru. Republic reinforcements have joined the battle; it is imperative that Imperial vessels in the area converge to bring the Intercessor down.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="963221" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

Alien forces sympathetic to the Republic have blockaded a primary route to the Chiss regions in an effort to isolate them from Imperial support. For the sake of our Chiss allies, the enemy ships must be destroyed and the minefield blockade neutralized immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1088834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

Mandalorians have stolen construction plans for the Sovereign Forge, the Empire's ultimate mining station and shipyard. The Mandalorian warlord Varek Tarn plots to sell the plans to the Republic at a minefield in the Cha Rabaa system. To save the Sovereign Forge, the shuttle carrying the plans must be destroyed before delivery to the Republic buyers; Varek Tarn himself will be escorting the shuttle and should be treated as a high-priority target.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1088835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

The maiden voyage of the D-1Z prototype bomber is underway. The Empire has invested a fortune in the ship's development, and the Republic now rallies its forces to destroy it. Reinforcements are needed over the planet Lorta to escort the bomber and shield it from the Republic onslaught.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1088836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

Captain Duma is rallying the Republic fleet to ambush the Empire's top pilots: your name is at the top of his list. To disrupt his ambush, the Empire must bring down Captain Duma and every last Republic vessel under his command.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1088837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

A Republic fleet is laying mines in the Bimmiel asteroid field to divide Imperial forces in the Kanz sector. To aid the Imperial war effort, all ships are needed to destroy the mine controller satellites and clear Republic fighters from the asteroid field.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1088838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

The Republic fleet has launched a devastating attack against Kabal Station, a key Imperial outpost in the Distant Outer Rim. Any available ships must destroy the enemy fleet and save Kabal Station from destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1088839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing:

Short-range Republic ships have been tracked to the Far Cradle, a refueling station in the Unknown Regions. Imperial fighter squadrons are needed to launch a surprise offensive and devastate the Republic station's defenses. Expect additional resistance from refueling destroyers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1089259" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Foe-Smasher

Mission 1: Cha Raaba Assault
Mandalorians have stolen construction plans for the Sovereign Forge, the Empire's ultimate mining station and shipyard. The Mandalorian warlord Varek Tarn plots to sell the plans to the Republic at a minefield in the Cha Rabaa system. To save the Sovereign Forge, the shuttle carrying the plans must be destroyed before delivery to the Republic buyers; Varek Tarn himself will be escorting the shuttle and should be treated as a high-priority target.

Mission 2: Duma Strike
Captain Duma is rallying the Republic fleet to ambush the Empire's top pilots: your name is at the top of his list. To disrupt his ambush, the Empire must bring down Captain Duma and every last Republic vessel under his command.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1092136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Far Cradle Strike

Short-range Republic ships have been tracked to the Far Cradle, a refueling station in the Unknown Regions. Imperial fighter squadrons are needed to launch a surprise offensive and devastate the Republic station's defenses. Expect additional resistance from refueling destroyers.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1092137" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Kabal Station Defense

The Republic fleet has launched a devastating attack against Kabal Station, a key Imperial outpost in the Distant Outer Rim. Any available ships must destroy the enemy fleet and save Kabal Station from destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1092138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Kanz Minefield

A Republic fleet is laying mines in the Bimmiel asteroid field to divide Imperial forces in the Kanz sector. To aid the Imperial war effort, all ships are needed to destroy the mine controller satellites and clear Republic fighters from the asteroid field.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1092139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Duma Strike

Captain Duma is rallying the Republic fleet to ambush the Empire's top pilots: your name is at the top of his list. To disrupt his ambush, the Empire must bring down Captain Duma and every last Republic vessel under his command.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1092140" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Lorta Escort

The maiden voyage of the D-1Z prototype bomber is underway. The Empire has invested a fortune in the ship's development, and the Republic now rallies its forces to destroy it. Reinforcements are needed over the planet Lorta to escort the bomber and shield it from the Republic onslaught.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1092142" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Cha Raaba Assault

Mandalorians have stolen construction plans for the Sovereign Forge, the Empire's ultimate mining station and shipyard. The Mandalorian warlord Varek Tarn plots to sell the plans to the Republic at a minefield in the Cha Rabaa system. To save the Sovereign Forge, the shuttle carrying the plans must be destroyed before delivery to the Republic buyers; Varek Tarn himself will be escorting the shuttle and should be treated as a high-priority target.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
