<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>35</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/universal/space/republic_fleet_terminal.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Midnight Freedom

Six weeks ago a Republic transport went missing in the Fondor system. We just received a distress call from the survivors. They were captured by the Empire.

Imperial aggression against Republic citizens directly violates the Treaty of Coruscant. Thankfully, the prisoners escaped captivity and hijacked a shuttle. Imperial forces are now hot on their trail.

Members of the Coruscant Aegis squadron: the escapees' lives depend on you. Go to the Fondor system in the Coreward Worlds, rescue our friends and preserve evidence of the Empire's hostility.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Grand Nova

Mission 1: Kalee Fortification
War has broken out across the galaxy, and the first major victory may belong to the Republic. The crew of an Imperial space station wishes to defect and join our cause.

The desertion of an entire station will shake the Empire's remaining allies. To prevent this disaster, the Empire has dispatched a fleet to destroy the station and everyone on board.

The Republic fleet is rallying to the defense of our would-be defectors. We need the Coruscant Aegis squadron to join the battle and save the space station from the Empire.

Mission 2: Zosha Advance
The Imperial dreadnaught Scream of Ragnos is rallying its escort for a major attack in Republic territory. 

The Scream of Ragnos is the flagship of Sith Lord Javis Koldor. His dreadnaught led assaults in the Sacking of Coruscant and claimed countless Republic lives.

We must destroy this threat and symbol of Imperial might. Join the battle above the planet Zosha in the Unknown Regions and permanently retire the Scream of Ragnos.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Sunder Zero

Mission 1: Hydian Way Blockade
The Hydian Way has been shut down. Mandalorian forces laid a network of mines to blockade the crucial trade route and funnel Republic forces into an ambush.

We aren't fooled. These Mandalorians answer to the Empire, and the Republic will not fall to their proxy attack.

The Coruscant Aegis must reopen the Hydian Way. Travel to the coordinates in the Seat of the Empire, clear the minefield and restore the flow of Republic supplies.

Mission 2: Drexel Sweep
The elite Imperial squadron Rancor's Claw is launching devastating attacks on Republic convoys. Our scouts tailed the squadron to an asteroid field where an Imperial dreadnaught lies in wait. 

The Rancor's Claw hopes to lure us into an ambush. A full-scale assault will violate the treaty, but a successful attack by a small fighter wing will embarrass the Empire and avoid open war.

Only the Coruscant Aegis squadron can complete this mission. Enter the asteroid field in the Drexel system of the Distant Outer Rim, cripple the dreadnaught's weaponry and eliminate the Rancor's Claw squadron.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Glory Cyclone

Mission 1: Pakuuni Defense
Tensions are frayed, and the Empire wants war. For its latest act of treachery, it plans to destroy a neutral space station and pin the blame on the Republic.

The station's loss will give the Empire sufficient allies and justification to launch another galactic war. We will not allow that to happen.

The Coruscant's Aegis squadron is to lead an emergency defense mission. Rally at the Pakuuni system in Hutt Space and save the space station from the Imperial onslaught.

Mission 2: Kovor Ice Field
Fleet Command has received a distress call from a Republic patrol. Our ships were on a survey mission when they were ambushed by an Imperial attack force.

The Imperial attackers are led by Captain Tervor &quot;Riptide&quot; Jheran, an ace pilot who violently opposed the treaty. Now he claims our patrols instigated the attack--an outright lie.

The Republic patrol is outmatched and outgunned. Members of Coruscant's Aegis: Converge on the orbital ice rings of Kovor and save our fighters from Riptide and his deadly forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Ardent Wave

Mission 1: Syvris Evacuation
A secret SIS listening post has been compromised. Imperial forces accused the installation of violating the treaty, and they are moving to capture and destroy years of sensitive intel.

Evacuation orders are in effect, but the Empire is not cooperating. SIS casualties have already been reported and more will die without immediate aid.

Members of the Coruscant Aegis are to rally at the Syvris station in Hutt Space. Once in range, protect the evacuation effort before our people and intel are consumed by the Empire's wrath.

Mission 2: Llanic Station Strike
The Empire's chemical weapons division has developed a deadly new poison: Ziroxin-12. The chemical is being produced in massive quantities at a space station in the remote Llanic system.

Ziroxin-12 was designed to devastate massive populations in wartime. The Empire is preparing for battle, and the Republic fleet must respond in kind.

The Coruscant Aegis is to spearhead our assault on the Empire's chemical station. Find the installation in the Llanic system in the Distant Outer Rim and obliterate every trace of Ziroxin-12.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Noble Gambit

Mission 1: Archenar Interception
In one week, we have lost eighteen Republic supply transports to enemy ambushes in Hutt Space. The attackers' identity remained secret, until now.

Recon drones have detected Imperial fighters hiding in the Archenar asteroid field. They're stationed there now, waiting to strike again.

Instead of a defenseless supply transport, our ambushers will face the Coruscant Aegis squadron. Intercept the Imperial fighters and see that they never terrorize Republic supply lines again.

Mission 2: Makem Te Assault
Less than one hour ago, Moff Jocend launched an assault on Republic borders. His warship, the Overlord, led the attack which ended with his ship severely damaged.

The wounded Overlord has retreated to the upper atmosphere of Makem Te. Moff Jocend will work swiftly to restore communications and call for help. We must act now.

The Republic needs you to rally in the Seat of the Empire. Cripple the Overlord over Makem Te, and we will capture the warship and its bold commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Searing Light

Mission 1: Balosar Outpost
Scouts have located a hidden Imperial space station in the Republic-aligned Balosar system. SIS analysis indicates the station was built as a staging point for covert assaults.

The Republic will not stand still while the Empire stresses the terms of our peace. The space station must be neutralized.

Republic fighters have launched an attack, but resistance is fierce. Members of the Coruscant Aegis squadron are needed to join our assault and destroy the station.

Mission 2: Javaal Fleet Action
A crisis has broken out over the planet Javaal. The deadly Imperial squadron known as the Razor Shyracks has ambushed a Republic patrol group.

The Razor Shyracks are commanded by Sith Lord Kestas Rone (call sign Bloodletter). His fighters are believed to be responsible for six other attacks on the Republic. This is our chance to end their rampage.

Only the Coruscant Aegis squadron is fit to take down the Razor Shyracks. Hurry to the planet Javaal in the Coreward Worlds and save our patrol from Bloodletter's attack wing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing: Operation New Eclipse

The Coruscant Aegis is needed in the Impossible Sector. Its infamously dangerous smuggling route has come under attack.

Privateers reported increased Mandalorian activity in the Impossible Sector. Scans revealed a sprawling minefield which now cuts off the Republic-commissioned smugglers who supply us.

The Republic war effort is counting on the Coruscant Aegis to restore our supply flow. Wipe out the mines at the Impossible Sector in the Unknown Regions. Prepare for heavy resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="963224" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

Mandalorian forces have erected a minefield along a popular smuggling route traversing the region known as the Impossible Sector. The mines must be removed to clear a path for Republic-commissioned privateers supporting the war effort; expect heavy resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="963225" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

Patrols intercepted the Imperial destroyer Scream of Ragnos and its frigate escort deep inside Republic territory. A battle rages above the uninhabited world of Zosha; casualties are high on both sides. Reinforcements are needed to bring the Scream down and prevent it from returning to Imperial space.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="963226" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

The crew aboard the Imperial space station on the outskirts of Kalee was secretly preparing to defect to the Republic. The Empire discovered their plan and sent a fleet to destroy the station. All available vessels must engage the enemy forces while the station's crew and intel files are extracted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="963227" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

An elite Imperial fighter squadron has been launching devastating hit-and-run attacks on Republic convoys. The squadron has been tracked to an asteroid field in the Drexel system. Eliminating these Imperial fighters is vital to the Republic war effort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="963228" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

Mandalorian mercenaries working for the Empire have laid an extensive minefield in order to blockade the Hydian Way trade route and funnel Republic convoys into a deadly ambush. The mines must be cleared to reopen crucial supply lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="963229" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

An Imperial fleet led by Captain Tervor &quot;Riptide&quot; Jheran has illegally engaged a Republic patrol surveying the orbital ice rings of the planet Kovor. Without immediate reinforcements, the overmatched patrol cannot hope to survive against the ace Imperial starfighter or his forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="963230" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

Several Republic privateers have been cornered on a neutral space station in the Pakuuni system. An Imperial fleet is sending bomber squadrons to destroy the station and everyone on board. Republic vessels have been dispatched, but they will need assistance to ensure the station's survival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="963231" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

An illegal Imperial chemical weapons program has been traced to a space station in the remote Llanic system. Republic forces have been dispatched, but additional ships are requested to ensure that the Empire's deadly creations are completely destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="963232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

A Republic SIS listening post in the Syvris system has been compromised by Imperial forces. Immediate assistance is requested in evacuating critical intelligence, personnel and a captured Imperial vessel before they are destroyed by the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="963233" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

Separated from its escorts after a failed illegal assault, Imperial warship Overlord is badly damaged and attempting to hide in the upper atmosphere of the planet Makem Te. Any available forces should move quickly to cripple the Overlord before Imperial reinforcements arrive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="963234" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

Enemy fighters have been detected attempting to slip through the Archenar asteroid field in order to attack nearby shipping lanes. These fighters must be intercepted before they can wreak havoc on Republic supply lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="963235" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

A Republic patrol group has been illegally ambushed by Imperial ships in orbit high above the planet Javaal. The Imperial task force is led by a notorious Intelligence agent, and the patrol needs backup urgently if it's going to have any hope of surviving the Empire's attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="963236" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

The Empire has constructed an illegal hidden space station in the Balosar system to act as a staging point for covert assaults on Republic territories. All available ships have been dispatched to destroy the station, but additional forces will be necessary to breach the Imperial defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="963237" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

An urgent distress signal has been detected in the Fondor system. Republic soldiers and colonists kidnapped by the Empire have escaped confinement and taken flight in a shuttle. All available vessels are requested to defend the escapees and ensure that some proof of the Empire's aggression is preserved.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1089182" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

A Mandalorian warlord has captured the construction plans for the Void Anvil, the Republic's top-secret mining station and shipyard. Warlord Rimark will soon sell the plans to the Empire at a minefield in the Thanium sector. Republic vessels must rally to bring down the shuttle carrying the plans and erase evidence of the Void Anvil at all costs. Warlord Rimark will be in the area and should be considered extremely dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1089183" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

The Republic's prototype bomber--the &quot;Gilded Meteor&quot;--has begun its test flight in the Ferra sector, and the Empire has deployed a dreadnaught to sabotage its maiden voyage. The Republic fleet requests backup over the planet Hypori to provide air support and protect the bomber.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1089184" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

Darth Ordrem is amassing his fleet near Baros to ambush the Republic's most elite pilots: you will be his first target. To save our ships from his wrath, the Republic must launch a preemptive strike against Darth Ordrem and his Imperial fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1089185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

Imperial fighters are hiding in the New Cov asteroid field and fortifying their position with prototype mines, controlled remotely by satellites. For the sake of the Republic war effort, we must destroy these satellites and the Imperial ships that are deploying the mines.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1089186" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

An Imperial fleet has emerged from hyperspace to ambush Ardis Outpost, a Republic space station in the Unknown Regions. Reinforcements are needed to aid our frigates in eliminating the Imperial fleet before the outpost is lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1089187" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing:

The Imperial refueling outpost Regnant Station gives the enemy a vital foothold in the Unknown Regions. To drive the Empire back, the Republic's top fighter groups must launch a surprise attack against the outpost and cripple Regnant Station's defenses. Be wary of refueling Imperial destroyers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1089258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Clean Sweep

Mission 1: Thanium Disruption
A Mandalorian warlord has captured the construction plans for the Void Anvil, the Republic's top-secret mining station and shipyard. Warlord Rimark will soon sell the plans to the Empire at a minefield in the Thanium sector. Republic vessels must rally to bring down the shuttle carrying the plans and erase evidence of the Void Anvil at all costs. Warlord Rimark will be in the area and should be considered extremely dangerous.

Mission 2: Baros Ambush
Darth Ordrem is amassing his fleet near Baros to ambush the Republic's most elite pilots: you will be his first target. To save our ships from his wrath, the Republic must launch a preemptive strike against Darth Ordrem and his Imperial fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1092145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Regnant Station Assault

The Imperial refueling outpost Regnant Station gives the enemy a vital foothold in the Unknown Regions. To drive the Empire back, the Republic's top fighter groups must launch a surprise attack against the outpost and cripple Regnant Station's defenses. Be wary of refueling Imperial destroyers.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1092146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Ardis Outpost Fortification

An Imperial fleet has emerged from hyperspace to ambush Ardis Outpost, a Republic space station in the Unknown Regions. Reinforcements are needed to aid our frigates in eliminating the Imperial fleet before the outpost is lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1092147" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing: Operation New Cov Asteroid Field

Imperial fighters are hiding in the New Cov asteroid field and fortifying their position with prototype mines, controlled remotely by satellites. For the sake of the Republic war effort, we must destroy these satellites and the Imperial ships that are deploying the mines.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1092148" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Baros Ambush

Darth Ordrem is amassing his fleet near Baros to ambush the Republic's most elite pilots: you will be his first target. To save our ships from his wrath, the Republic must launch a preemptive strike against Darth Ordrem and his Imperial fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1092149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Hypori Escort

The Republic's prototype bomber--the &quot;Gilded Meteor&quot;--has begun its test flight in the Ferra sector, and the Empire has deployed a dreadnaught to sabotage its maiden voyage. The Republic fleet requests backup over the planet Hypori to provide air support and protect the bomber.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1092150" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Command Briefing: Operation Thanium Disruption

A Mandalorian warlord has captured the construction plans for the Void Anvil, the Republic's top-secret mining station and shipyard. Warlord Rimark will soon sell the plans to the Empire at a minefield in the Thanium sector. Republic vessels must rally to bring down the shuttle carrying the plans and erase evidence of the Void Anvil at all costs. Warlord Rimark will be in the area and should be considered extremely dangerous.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
