<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>296</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_1/multi/shalim.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052532" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll be safe here, for now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052535" id2="17" version="1065353216">People of Makeb--your heroes return!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch out. Uncle Shalim's running for president of whatever planet we all move to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052539" id2="17" version="1065353216">This heroic Jedi led us to victory against the Hutt treachery. Now we have freedom and an ark that will deliver us to safety!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052540" id2="17" version="1065353216">This distinguished Jedi has protected our oppressed people and bestowed hope on Makeb. The Regulators are defeated--the ark is secured!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052541" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic sent none less than the elite Havoc Squad to save us. They drove back the Regulators and secured the ark!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb's most mysterious ally is now our savior. Thank you, Captain, for driving back the Regulators and securing the ark!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052543" id2="17" version="1065353216">These champions of Makeb bring us not only hope of freedom from Hutt oppression, but deliverance in the form of the ark!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052544" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you're all scared. You have good reason--but the time for fear is ending.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope will free us all!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052546" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts only control you when you are broken and despairing. Look to your neighbors, your friends, your loved ones for strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Through compassion and hope, you will survive this. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb is a paradise. You built this planet, with blood and sweat, patience and love. Now your home is dying, as all things must.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your future lies beyond Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052552" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you won't die with it. You will survive. Gather your memories and your friends close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052554" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cherish the legacy of Makeb, and your world will live on. The Force is with you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb is a proud member of the Republic, and we are all Republic citizens. Whatever happens to this world, we stand united.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052556" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic will save you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052558" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts want to crush your spirits--assault your freedom. But the Republic protects its own. You will have a new home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052560" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stand against your oppressors, and know that Havoc Squad is with you every step of the way. For Makeb! For the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052562" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I landed on Makeb, it was just another job for the Supreme Chancellor. Now, I know you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052562" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm proud to be your hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052564" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've felt your pain. I know the sting of Hutt fury, the destruction of a groundquake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052565" id2="17" version="1065353216">I love you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052566" id2="17" version="1065353216">You, too, sugar.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052568" id2="17" version="1065353216">I love you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Back atcha, gorgeous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyway, my point is this: Makeb's got a bright future, and you're its stars!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your planet's collapsing beneath you, and the Hutt Cartel remains in power. We've given you hope, but we're a long way from being safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb is still doomed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052576" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you trying to cause a panic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just a cautionary reminder, given out of love and concern. Three cheers for our heroes!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052579" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep the spotlight to yourself, Shalim.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052579" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate public speaking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052580" id2="17" version="1065353216">A hero who believes in deeds, not words! How about a round of applause?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052582" id2="17" version="1065353216">I meant what I said. All of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052584" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ark is safe, and we'll soon have it ready to fly. We've earned a moment to celebrate--especially you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Back at the Hutt Embassy, we found a holo that said the ark was being built to transport something called isotope-5.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052585" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have mysteries to solve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052587" id2="17" version="1065353216">When we faced Grevin, he said isotope-5 will change the galaxy--but he wouldn't say how. Does that name mean anything to you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds more like some idiotic Hutt code name than a scientific discovery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe Lemda can show me the sights? This might be our only chance to relax.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052595" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Join me, Lemda?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052596" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll relax when I'm not standing on a planet that's falling apart, but... I appreciate the offer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything that gets you closer to the Republic, right? Are you hoping I'll endorse you for Supreme Chancellor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052598" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a real schemer, Shalim.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052599" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sincerely hope I haven't offended you. I'm merely expressing my gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give it a rest, Uncle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052605" id2="17" version="1065353216">We finally have mighty Toborro the Hutt's attention. Calling to congratulate us, old friend?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1052607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insolent scum! I will kill everyone on Makeb if you do not return my ark! Now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052608" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we give you back that ship, Toborro, we all die when Makeb's core explodes. We're keeping it. Let us know if you need a lift.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052608" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ark is our only hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1052609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thieving filth! You're condemning millions of your pathetic people to a painful death!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052611" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't frighten us, Toborro. If you had anything left to hit us with, you wouldn't be talking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052611" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're out of weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1052612" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still have enough power to kill everyone on this planet--long before it tears itself apart! And my way will be more painful!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052614" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not much of a salesman, Toborro--but I've always wanted to see a Hutt grovel. Can you actually bend over enough to kiss the ground?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say &quot;pretty please.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1052615" id2="17" version="1065353216">I kneel to no one! You will drown in lakes of fire and blood!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spare us your empty threats, Toborro. Makeb is doomed, and the ark is our only escape. If we give it back, we're all dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1052619" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can still evacuate through conventional means. What do you prefer--saving twenty percent of your citizens, or losing all of them?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1052621" id2="17" version="1065353216">You insects don't comprehend the ark! It requires isotope-5 to fuel its engines--and only I possess that substance!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for telling us where to fuel up the ark. We'll be right over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'll come get some.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1052623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fool! Do you think it will be that simple?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you honestly expect us to believe that? You've been lying since you arrived on Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop lying.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1052626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your ignorance is why the Republic will fall!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052628" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've had all I can take of your jabbering. You want to play rough? Be right there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time for you to die.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1052629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, by all means--race to your death!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1052631" id2="17" version="1065353216">I mastered isotope-5 long before your idiotic rebellion. And now you've given me an excuse to demonstrate my knowledge. Behold and despair!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1052633" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is only a sample of the power at my disposal. The slaughter of your people will continue until the ark is mine again!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052635" id2="17" version="1065353216">I recognize where that droid was attacking: Tarlam. It's a small city without defenses. I'll summon a shuttle to take you there. Please, save my people!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052636" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care how big Toborro's weapon is--I've never met a machine that could defeat a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052636" id2="17" version="1065353216">That droid will be stopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toborro's new weapon must be stopped. The Jedi will protect your city.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052637" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll depart immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052638" id2="17" version="1065353216">Machines are made to be broken. Havoc Squad will dismantle Toborro's plaything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052638" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take down that droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052639" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I've learned anything lately, it's the bigger they are, the harder they fall. Toborro's new toy is going down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave that droid to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never trust a desperate Hutt. Toborro's trying to intimidate us with lies and bullying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052640" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a trick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052641" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's working. I need you to stop his madness before it goes any further.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052643" id2="17" version="1065353216">The easiest way to solve all our problems is frying that Hutt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052643" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's just kill Toborro now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052644" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't focus on revenge right now--my citizens are in danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052646" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sending an emergency signal to the Republic. We need a science expert down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052648" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Toborro's telling the truth about isotope-5, we're still stranded--and that Hutt's going to slaughter us all. Hurry to Tarlam and stop his droid!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052652" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't defend the ark against an all-out attack by the Regulators. You have to stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052655" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't thank you enough for securing the ark, Master Jedi. You turned certain death into a chance for survival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for securing the ark, Major. No one on this planet fights with Havoc Squad's heart. You honor us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052657" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really stuck it to the Hutts this time, Captain. Without the ark, the Cartel can't profit from Makeb's destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Word is spreading about the ark. The only reason my people are holding together is because you've given them hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052659" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts won't give up the ark without a fight--and they have an army. Our battles have just begun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052659" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not over yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052660" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've bought a reprieve, but now the Hutts have something to fight for--and their forces outnumber ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052660" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts will retaliate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052661" id2="17" version="1065353216">The battles we've fought till now are nothing compared to what's coming. The Regulators will be gunning for that ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052661" id2="17" version="1065353216">Expect a counterattack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hutts are sore losers. If they can't have the ark, they may blast her just to spite us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052662" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ark is now a target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052663" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're more right than you know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052665" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ark's missing more than a few vital components. We're still a long way off from loading it with evacuees.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052665" id2="17" version="1065353216">That ship needs a lot of work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052666" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't trust that hunk of junk as a doorstop. If you don't have your own way off this rock, you'd better find one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't bother with the ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Foreman Tiero is one of the best ship men on Makeb. He'll get the job done--if we protect his construction site.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052669" id2="17" version="1065353216">We intercepted priority signals from the Cartel. Every Regulator in this hemisphere has been ordered to retake the ark at all costs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ilosov, organize a defense force. Anyone willing to fight gets a blaster and a ride to the ark's construction site. Go now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prepare that place for war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052671" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll need your shuttle, Navigator. Come on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shalim, contact your allies. We'll need all the help we can get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Already done. Impending doom was an excellent motivator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052677" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we knew the Regulator army's staging point, we could potentially cut them off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052677" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to take the offensive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surest way to close any deal is by blocking the competition from bidding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052680" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe the ark could fly somewhere safe to complete repairs?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052680" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we move the ark?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052681" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was my first thought as well. Unfortunately, we're still figuring out how to activate the ark's engines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052683" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some refugees know how to use a blaster. I'll organize a security force to protect the ark. Navigator, we'll need your shuttle--come on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052685" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people are scouting for Regulator activity and reporting what they find. We've identified one major staging area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052687" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Fingers: originally one mesa, until a quake redecorated the place. Now it's held together by a series of interconnected energy fields--light bridges.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052689" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Regulators store heavy artillery and weapon caches there. If those mercenaries rearm, they'll blast us to oblivion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052690" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without their most powerful armaments, the Regulators won't be nearly as dangerous. They might even surrender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052690" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll destroy those weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052691" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll certainly give them something to think about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052693" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mercenaries place too much confidence in force of arms. Destroying their caches will collapse our enemy's resolve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052693" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll destroy those weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052694" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hadn't considered that, Master Jedi--but the thought makes me smile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052696" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ark construction site isn't built to withstand bombardment. We'd better take out the artillery first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052696" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll destroy those weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052697" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll make a fitting display of power, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052699" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds like a good place for me to blow up. The fireworks will let every merc on Makeb know we're coming for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052699" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll destroy those weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052700" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you'll put on quite a show, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052702" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the splintered mesa is barely held together, one strong quake will wipe out these weapons for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052702" id2="17" version="1065353216">A good quake solves that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too much to hope for. Seismic forecast models indicate the Fingers are safe for the short term. If I'm wrong, feel free to complain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052705" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're our best shot at taking out those caches and artillery before the enemy reaches them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Weaponry's useless without someone to wield it. Shouldn't we target the Regulator army directly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that our best target?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052708" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy is still gathering forces, but their biggest weapons are clustered at the Fingers now. We'll never get a better shot at them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052710" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll take their toys away, but I won't be happy until the Regulators have cashed their last credit vouchers. Point me at that scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052710" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to wipe out their army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052711" id2="17" version="1065353216">We know the Regulators' army also includes war droids and a battle platform. We're still scouting for those.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Translation, he's finding lots of ways to risk your life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052714" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're trying to save your people, and we're your best chance. There's nothing to apologize for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052714" id2="17" version="1065353216">We all do what we must.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052715" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who was apologizing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052717" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a good thing I have a reason to always come back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052717" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] I'll survive for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052718" id2="17" version="1065353216">Flirting with disaster--literally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice of you to admit you dragged the Republic into this mess so we could fight your battles for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052720" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're exploiting us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052721" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take it out on the Regulators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you've destroyed the artillery and weapon caches in the Fingers, contact me. I should have additional targets by then. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052725" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ark is our only hope of evacuating everyone off Makeb. We can't let the Hutts keep it to themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find this Project Failsafe. Chief Hurkwill is standing by to assist you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052729" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is nothing, Uncle. I've run the numbers. Two days, maybe less, and your office is at the bottom of a sinkhole.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052731" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least your expensive education has finally amounted to something....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052733" id2="17" version="1065353216">Told you I'd repay that loan. Bet you're wishing you'd listened to me sooner, not dismissed me as a &quot;loud-mouthed conservationist.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052735" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi... Lemda told me of your incredible rescue. Words cannot convey my thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052737" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major, welcome back. Lemda told me all about Havoc Squad's daring rescue. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052739" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, come in. Lemda told me of your incredible heroics. I'm impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back, all of you. Lemda told me everything: the mercenaries, the quake, your amazing rescue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052743" id2="17" version="1065353216">We suspected Makeb was becoming unstable, but I had no idea things were this bad. We never should've let the Hutt Cartel establish their mining operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052744" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't realize the Cartel set up shop on your world before the takeover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052744" id2="17" version="1065353216">How long have Hutts been here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052745" id2="17" version="1065353216">We negotiated mining contracts with them a decade ago. They gave our economy a tremendous boost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052747" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been yelling about that boost for years. Moving on....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lemda mentioned that there's a way to stop this disaster. What is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052749" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to save the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052750" id2="17" version="1065353216">You held back a lot of bad news, Shalim. Why didn't you tell us about the planet's instability?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052750" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been misleading us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052751" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't want to cause a panic. Makeb's people must stand together. Only through unity can we overcome this crisis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Know what doesn't help right now? Speeches. Unless I'm talking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052755" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Regulators who held me hostage were a chatty bunch. Mostly filthy language and bragging about their blasters--but the leader said something interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052757" id2="17" version="1065353216">He mentioned &quot;Project Failsafe&quot;: a Hutt emergency plan if their mining went wrong. That mercenary believed the Hutts have something to instantly stabilize Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052758" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts clearly don't care who gets hurt by these groundquakes. We need to find their failsafe now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052758" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have a goal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052759" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Cartel wouldn't have a failsafe if they didn't plan on pushing Makeb to the brink of destruction. We can't allow that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052759" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need that failsafe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052760" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't count on Hutts to do the right thing. We need to seize that failsafe and put it to use immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Project Failsafe will be ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052761" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts only care about saving their own oily hides. We'd better grab this Project Failsafe before there's another quake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds good. Let's steal it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad you feel that way, because you need to steal it. Assuming we can find it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052764" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did this mercenary say anything else about Project Failsafe? Where it is, how it works?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052764" id2="17" version="1065353216">What else did you learn?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052765" id2="17" version="1065353216">The conversation dried up when you started attacking their camps. Not that I'm ungrateful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could anyone stabilize an entire planet's core and crust instantly? It doesn't seem feasible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052767" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's an unlikely remedy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed--but the Cartel has top-level scientists on their payroll. Who knows what they might have discovered?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052770" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Hutts can save Makeb, what are we worried about? Call and tell them to switch on their failsafe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052770" id2="17" version="1065353216">So the crisis is over?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052771" id2="17" version="1065353216">Millions could die while we wait for the Hutts to act. We need to claim Project Failsafe for ourselves before it's too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talaos City. The Hutt Embassy database.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ilosov's right. Data on Project Failsafe would be stored in the Hutt Embassy's computers in Talaos City. Unfortunately, that's under Cartel control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052777" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need Chief Hurkwill, Talaos City's former security commander. He and a few loyal men have a hidden camp outside the city. They'll get you inside the city and embassy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052778" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll head there now. Tell Chief Hurkwill to get ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052779" id2="17" version="1065353216">How does a security chief know the way into the Hutt Embassy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052779" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're sure he can help us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052780" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurkwill set up the Hutts' original defenses. He built it; he knows how to break it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is he hiding outside the city? Did he get fired as security commander?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052782" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Former&quot; security commander?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052783" id2="17" version="1065353216">In a manner of speaking. The Hutts put a death mark on his head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052785" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts control Talaos City and the surrounding area. You'll have to land a shuttle in the countryside. Expect plenty of Regulators. Chief Hurkwill's camp is hidden at these coordinates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't die. You're all we've got.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052789" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can use my personal shuttle to reach the Frinn Mesa. Please, bring Lemda back alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052792" id2="17" version="1065353216">You honor my home, Master Jedi. I'm Shalim Avesta. The Supreme Chancellor promised us relief, but you're more than I ever hoped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052794" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, Major. I'm Shalim Avesta. The Supreme Chancellor pledged support, but the elite Havoc Squad? It's an honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, Captain. I'm Shalim Avesta. The Supreme Chancellor says you're one of the Republic's foremost experts on the Hutt Cartel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come in, please. I'm Shalim Avesta. The Supreme Chancellor promised to send the best. It's not every day a politician delivers on a promise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052800" id2="17" version="1065353216">My family helped found Makeb. Avesta Mining has led our Business Council for decades. I was practically Chief of State before the Cartel's takeover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052802" id2="17" version="1065353216">It wasn't an easy decision, but if joining the Republic is the only way to reclaim my homeworld's freedom, so be it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052803" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire wouldn't treat you any better than the Hutts. The Republic and the Jedi Order will protect this world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052803" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are much worse allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052804" id2="17" version="1065353216">I only ask that Makeb's existing government retain a voice after this crisis ends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clinging to your past will not save this planet's future. A true leader knows how to relinquish control for the greater good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Know when to let others help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052807" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have my full support, Master Jedi. I trust I'll have yours in return.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody's asking you to step down from office. Once the Hutts are gone, Makeb will need a government.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052809" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can still be in charge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052810" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate that vote of confidence, Major. I hope your Supreme Chancellor honors it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Personally, I would've offered the Republic a little less than your whole planet. How'd a high roller like you get suckered into this deal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Independence has advantages.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Supreme Chancellor Saresh required a full commitment to the Republic. Given the circumstances, I couldn't refuse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052815" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't sound happy about this alliance. What made your decision to accept the Republic's help so difficult?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why wasn't it an easy choice?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb's been independent since our founding. It's always been part of our people's character.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052818" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're your only chance of defeating the Hutts. You either work with us, or take them on alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Obey us, or we'll leave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052819" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me if I sounded ungrateful. Of course we're happy to join your Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ilosov is a former mercenary with the InterStellar Regulators--until recently, Makeb's trusted private army and police force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quit when the Regulators sold out to the Hutts. I don't betray a client for credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exceptions like him notwithstanding, the Cartel bought off the Regulator forces and turned our former protectors against us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052826" id2="17" version="1065353216">A coup of this scale doesn't happen overnight. The Hutts must have had these mercenaries in their pockets for months.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052826" id2="17" version="1065353216">This took long-term planning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some Regulators started doing side jobs for the Cartel a while back. They're all in command positions now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052829" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many ex-mercenaries do you have on your side? Enough to take down the rest?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are there more like Ilosov?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regulators who refused the Hutt buyout either ran or got shot for disloyalty before they could.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052832" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts want Makeb badly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052834" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts wouldn't risk open war, much less pay for a mercenary army, without good cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Planetary conquests aren't typical of the Hutts. Whatever they're after on Makeb, it must outweigh the cost of bribing mercenaries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hutts tend to wallow in their riches, not waste them on pricey takeovers. Any idea what lit the fire under their tails?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052837" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't stick around to hear the whole sales pitch. Wouldn't have mattered, anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052839" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still don't know why this has happened. We've conducted peaceful business with the Hutt Cartel for years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Casualty and damage reports coming in... Talaos City got rattled pretty hard, but no injuries. Lucky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052843" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the fifth groundquake since the Hutts' takeover. The last one leveled the Tigon mining colony. They're still pulling bodies from the rubble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052844" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Supreme Chancellor never said anything about groundquakes. Did you tell her about them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052844" id2="17" version="1065353216">This wasn't in the briefing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052845" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't think it was relevant. The tremors weren't notable--not until recently, anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052847" id2="17" version="1065353216">These groundquakes started after the Hutts invaded? Doesn't sound like a coincidence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052847" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could there be a connection?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052848" id2="17" version="1065353216">You aren't the first to voice that thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052850" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deadly atmosphere, groundquakes and covered in Hutts... real paradise you've got here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052850" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb is one lousy planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052851" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have you know, we've built some of the finest vacation resorts outside the Core systems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't matter if these groundquakes demolish them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052855" id2="17" version="1065353216">My niece Lemda is a respected geophysicist. She joined our resistance to prove there's a link between the groundquakes and the Hutts' deep-core mining.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052857" id2="17" version="1065353216">She was taking seismic readings on a deserted mesa when a whole company of Regulators swarmed in. We've lost contact with her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052859" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sent search parties to bring Lemda back, but they aren't trained or equipped to fight a mercenary force of that size.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052860" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a feeling your niece discovered something--and the Hutts sent the Regulators to stop her from getting away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052860" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mercs are hunting her, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052861" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's my fear as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052863" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of people are in these search parties? Are they at least armed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who did you send?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052864" id2="17" version="1065353216">The bulk of our forces are civilian volunteers. A few know how to fight; most don't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052866" id2="17" version="1065353216">I came to drive the Cartel off Makeb, not investigate ground tremors or babysit your niece.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052866" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just here to fight Hutts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, this is important. The Hutts would never have sent that many Regulators after Lemda without good reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Getting reports from our search parties. Dozens of Regulators have pushed them back to the landing zone. We lose that, we'll never find Lemda.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052870" id2="17" version="1065353216">If your allies can hold out until we arrive, we'll break the siege and rescue your niece. You have my word as a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052870" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell your people help is near.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once they know you're on the way, my people will fight twice as hard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052873" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell your people they'll soon fight alongside Jedi. I know a thing or two about solving mysteries the hard way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052873" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me handle this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope the Regulators are smart enough to recognize when they're outmatched.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052876" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll show those traitor mercenaries what real soldiers look like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad can hold the line.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't underestimate them. A lot of Regulators are ex-military.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052879" id2="17" version="1065353216">The situation's grim, the odds are against us, and the bad guys have the numbers. Good thing you've got me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052879" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't come here to lose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Either Chancellor Saresh has a cruel sense of humor, or you're not just a &quot;Hutt expert.&quot; I hope you make good on that boast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052882" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know the Regulators better than anyone. We could use your help out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you help us fight, Ilosov?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052883" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer that Ilosov stay here. The Regulators don't know about our rebellion yet, but if they find out, I'll need his expertise to survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052885" id2="17" version="1065353216">This could all be a waste of time. If the Regulators found her, she's already dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1052885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't assume she's alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even if that's true, her research findings may have survived. If I have to lose my niece, I'd rather it not be in vain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take my personal shuttle to Frinn Mesa. Lane Ferow is our man at the landing zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1052890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Makeb. Please excuse me--I'm in the middle of planning a rebellion.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
