<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>98</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tython/world/the_last_defenders/master_tillin.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602664" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've increased our understanding of this region and potentially saved many lives. Well done, my friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602665" id2="17" version="1065353216">My scanner's memory is already full? Perfect timing. I'll collate your data with my own readings and analyze them together.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm... it seems the droids were indeed built for war. Twenty thousand years later, they still pursue their primary function. How sad.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602669" id2="17" version="1065353216">These ancient droids were soldiers in Tython's great Force Wars--a time before there were Jedi, Sith or even a Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602670" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never heard of these &quot;Force Wars.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Force Wars?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602671" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was the first conflict between Force users--a horrific battle between light and darkness that lasted for a hundred years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quite a revelation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602674" id2="17" version="1065353216">I almost got killed over a war that ended millennia ago?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602674" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a waste of my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602675" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is why Jedi continually strive for peace. Once a war begins, it is difficult to end.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602677" id2="17" version="1065353216">According to the droid logs, Kaleth was a stronghold of the dark side's forces. They made their last stand here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602679" id2="17" version="1065353216">As they died, the dark siders activated the droids as a doomsday weapon--hoping to ensure the light side's destruction as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602680" id2="17" version="1065353216">For doomsday droids, they sure fall apart easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602680" id2="17" version="1065353216">They don't seem so tough.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602681" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt either of us will hold up nearly as well after twenty thousand years. These machines were quite menacing for their epoch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602683" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clearly, the light side survived these doomsday weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602683" id2="17" version="1065353216">The droids failed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed--and went on to found our Jedi Order. To think what might have been, if the dark siders' plans had succeeded....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have a plan for them?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602687" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Council must deliberate and decide what should be done about the droids. It isn't up to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, have fun with that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602690" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll consult the Jedi Council at once about this. You've been extraordinarily helpful.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602692" id2="17" version="1065353216">By your efforts, we see Kaleth in a fresh light. I will commend you to the Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Continue with your tasks. Make your Masters proud.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602699" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell, Jedi. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602700" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've delayed you enough. I know how important the work you and Orgus do is. Give him my best.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602701" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've delayed you enough, Padawan. Give Master Yuon my best wishes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use the scanner on any Tythonian droids you encounter--and take extra care in those ruins.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here, examine this droid's cognitive unit I recovered from the ruins. Twenty-thousand years old, yet still functional. Our forebears built things to last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602705" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happened to the rest of the droid's parts?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602705" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where's the droid's body?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regrettably, I was forced to dismantle it with my lightsaber.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602708" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you saying the Jedi's ancestors built this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602708" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forebears?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602709" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed--which makes the behavior of these machines all the more baffling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602711" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's amazing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602712" id2="17" version="1065353216">A shame the cognitive unit's owner had to be destroyed. It was a magnificent machine, but quite hostile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602714" id2="17" version="1065353216">Old junk? Who cares?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602715" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you not familiar with the ancient machines inhabiting these ruins? They're a great mystery.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602717" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ruins of Lower Kaleth are filled with droids constructed during Tython's original colonization by the galaxy's first Force users.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602719" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't know the Tythonian droids' purpose--only that they attack anyone who enters the ruins. My mission is to learn why.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why not simply wipe out all the droids?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not to destroy them?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602721" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we can reason with the droids, we stand to learn much about Tython's past.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602723" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of damage can these droids do to people?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone been hurt?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602724" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've had several serious injuries. Left unchecked, the droids are going to kill someone. We can't let it come to that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever you say.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, please. These droids are growing increasingly lethal. I could use your assistance dealing with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602729" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been millennia since the Tythonian droids were memory-wiped. Their programming lies buried amid trillions of accumulated databits.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602731" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've constructed a scanner to analyze the droids' cognitive units for command protocols, but I need several samplings to sort through the static.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602732" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get those samplings for you in no time, Master Till'in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602732" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me take care of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602733" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. This will greatly accelerate my efforts to solve this mystery and make the ruins safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602735" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need an assistant, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602740" id2="17" version="1065353216">You passed your Jedi trials with ease. I know you can handle yourself in the ruins.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your Master has great confidence in your abilities, as do I. This task won't be simple, but I know you'll succeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a dull chore.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until we understand why the ancient Tythonian droids are attacking us, these ruins won't be safe. Surely that's a problem worth solving?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, all right.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. I'd hate to think you didn't feel some responsibility to the rest of the order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fair enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602750" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602752" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take this scanner. When you encounter Tythonian droids in Lower Kaleth, disable them and scan the remains.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bring the scanner back to me when its memory is full, so that I can analyze the data. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602756" id2="17" version="1065353216">By another. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602757" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well. Thank you again for delivering Padawan Fia's message. Goodbye.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tython's most promising newcomers visit me together? A rare honor, indeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, Padawan--but now I see I am mistaken, you have already completed your Jedi trials. Well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, Padawan to Orgus Din. Your Master speaks highly of your potential.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, Master Yuon's new Padawan. A great Jedi-in-the-making, by all accounts. Greetings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602769" id2="17" version="1065353216">Padawan Fia sends her regards--and this holorecording.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602769" id2="17" version="1065353216">Know someone named Fia?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602770" id2="17" version="1065353216">The poor girl--no doubt apologizing again. She nearly shot me when I approached her on Raxus Prime.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone asked me to deliver a message.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602772" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have something for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh dear. Another one?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thing there aren't children around--you'd scare them to death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602775" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're ugly! [Give message]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Children are never frightened of me--or perhaps they're simply more polite than adults.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see what you've brought me... ah yes. Fia. The poor girl is still apologizing for shooting at me on Raxus Prime.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602780" id2="17" version="1065353216">I forget how violently some humans react when first meeting my species. I don't understand why they always seem to shoot before thinking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602781" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seem to have survived the encounter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602781" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least you weren't hurt.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Luckily, Fia's aim was unbalanced by her fear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't ask me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed. Ah, well--a riddle to be pondered some other time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who knows why humans do anything?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Humans are strange.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602788" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, now. Let us embrace tolerance. Not all beings are as enlightened as we are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="602790" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe because you're a hideous monster?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="602790" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isn't it obvious?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mind yourself, young one. While your honesty is admirable, your tone lacks respect.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602793" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was kind of you to deliver this holorecording, though I should gently instruct Padawan Fia to stop interrupting my work. Speaking of which....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me, Jedi. I must analyze these data readings.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602802" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take care in the ruins of Kaleth, Padawan. The area is hazardous to all who enter.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="602803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tython is a dangerous world even for Jedi. Maintain your visual scanning at all times.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
