<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>28</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/ship/class/jedi_knight/captain_maddox.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, Master Jedi. Hope it's alright if I hunker down here--didn't want to crowd you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068800" id2="17" version="1065353216">This ship's pretty luxurious compared to ours. Protector evac vessels are built for speed and defense, not comfort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068801" id2="17" version="1065353216">This ship's seen more battles than most starfighters, I'm afraid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1068801" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't do comfort either.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068802" id2="17" version="1065353216">Try fighting with five hundred refugees on board. Changes your strategy a bit, I can tell you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068804" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is your convoy following us? What are the other Protectors doing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1068804" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where are your ships now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Already ahead of us, getting set up on Sleheyron. We've got full Republic support there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speeding to Aphelion Six, fast as they can. We're going to need all our resources for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prepping for Bothawui. Haven't been briefed yet, but I can tell this one's going to be big.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068811" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got a few groups on other planets, but most are following your ship's signature.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068813" id2="17" version="1065353216">As soon as the Protectors are safe, you and your staff are leaving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1068813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't expect to stay long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068814" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the record, I appreciate this. We don't deserve it, but the work surely does.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Command thought I was crazy, asking for civs instead of soldiers. Look at us now: over ten thousand lives saved without firing a shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068819" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi advocates peace. The Republic doesn't always listen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1068819" id2="17" version="1065353216">I try to be a good example.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068820" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soldiers are trained to kill. After a while, it becomes a habit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone calls you &quot;captain.&quot; I'm guessing you were a soldier, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1068822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that experience talking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Volunteered at eighteen. Saw more than one treaty get stomped on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most Jedi spend their time meditating. I prefer to take action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1068825" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not your average Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course you do. You're young still, and this is your first war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068828" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen death. Friends, family, teachers. Men I laughed and ate and fought with through three tours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068830" id2="17" version="1065353216">When this war is over, a lot more of our boys will want to be Protectors, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1068832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Conferencing with a team on Balmorra. Can it wait?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1088554" id2="17" version="1065353216">But if anyone has to break that record, I'm glad it's you. I admire your order's ideals--wish our military was the same.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
