<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>31</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hutta/class/spy/holo_archives.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664176" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's it, then. Better hope your boss knows how to make a convincing forgery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, there's going to be a bloodbath once Nem'ro and Toth'lazhen see what's on the disc.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664179" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you know what's on the holodisc?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664179" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have some information?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664180" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I know is what your &quot;Keeper&quot; told us. But I'm not stupid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664182" id2="17" version="1065353216">What?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664183" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quiet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664184" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just thought you might appreciate the warning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664186" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that disc really names all of Fa'athra's business partners, it probably identifies half the people in Jiguuna. Merchants, gangsters, debtors--the usual scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664188" id2="17" version="1065353216">When Nem'ro gets ahold of it, he'll want revenge on anyone who dared to go to Fa'athra behind his back. There'll be bodies clogging the gutters for weeks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664189" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you up to, Kaliyo? I wouldn't think you'd care what Nem'ro does.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664189" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you're concerned?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664190" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't. But I thought you might.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664192" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's brutal--but if it helps Nem'ro, it could help our position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664192" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't that strengthen us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664193" id2="17" version="1065353216">It would make Nem'ro happy, but I doubt it'd actually help his business. Different things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664195" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any particular reason I should be bothered?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664195" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664196" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only if you plan to stick around and watch the excitement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664198" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're feeling queasy, you could always erase the extra data and scratch up the disc. Make it look like only the doctored recording &quot;miraculously&quot; survived the damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664200" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, we deliver Keeper's forgery without the real data. Nem'ro doesn't get his revenge spree. The risk is that Toth'lazhen figures out you erased the good stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664201" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not endangering the mission to protect the lowlifes of Hutta.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664201" id2="17" version="1065353216">No taking chances.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664202" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aw--aren't we dedicated? I knew I'd learn something about you on this mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664204" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no need to let Nem'ro carry out a massacre. We'll be as careful as we can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664204" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's erase it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664205" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your call, agent. I knew I'd learn something about you--just don't expect me to defend you if someone realizes the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664206" id2="17" version="1065353216">So erasing the data is risky. I thought you enjoyed a little risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664206" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll chance it. It'll be fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664207" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who says I don't? I'll do the damage--we'll see how far we can take this con.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664209" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, let's get that thing to Toth'lazhen and see what happens....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
