<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>214</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hutta/class/spy/keeper.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664740" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your mission is now complete. There's a shuttle waiting for you in Jiguuna; it will take you to Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you've arrived on-planet, report to Imperial Intelligence headquarters in the Citadel. I'll debrief you there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664744" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a few things to take care of, first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664744" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need a little time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do what you have to, but be quick about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't make me jump through bureaucratic rings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. Paperwork.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664748" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want another assignment, you will follow orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664750" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kaliyo--you will also report to Dromund Kaas. I assume Nem'ro won't be surprised by your sudden disappearance?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664752" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'll be hurt--but no one'll be surprised that I left with the Blade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664754" id2="17" version="1065353216">And he's certainly not the first employer you've walked out on. In any case, I'll expect to see both of you soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664755" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold on. Who else has Kaliyo betrayed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664755" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Walked out on&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664756" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't the time or place for that, agent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664758" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kaliyo Djannis will also report to Dromund Kaas. She'll accompany you on the journey, and I expect to see both of you soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664759" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're on our way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure about this? I'm not convinced she's worth the trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kaliyo? Really?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we can discuss your reservations in person. You have your orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664765" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's about time I got out of this swamp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664766" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll try to find a planet more to your liking next time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Report to the shuttle as soon as possible. Keeper out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664770" id2="17" version="1065353216">The deed is done, agent. Nem'ro is already contacting Imperial embassies, looking to establish relations; he'll be eating out of our hands within the month.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664772" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the short term, our chemical and stimulant stockpiles will nearly double. In the long term, we're a step closer to bringing all of Hutta under Imperial control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664774" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make my full report to Darth Jadus shortly. I expect he'll be very pleased with our work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664775" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's excellent news, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your future with Imperial Intelligence looks bright--but we can discuss that face-to-face.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assuming he's satisfied--does that mean Jadus will leave Imperial Intelligence alone?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then he's done with us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664779" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't assume anything at this juncture. Besides which, that isn't your concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664781" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mean my work. I had to cozy up to the Hutts. I'm the one who got results.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664781" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Our&quot; work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't overestimate your importance. This operation required the attention of dozens of men--you didn't do it alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three days ago, Karrels Javis's sons encountered a Sith apprentice in Imperial space. A dispute broke out. One son died, and the other was crippled.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664787" id2="17" version="1065353216">When Karrels hears that a Sith slaughtered his child, his sympathy for the Empire will evaporate. We can no longer use him to get to Nem'ro.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664788" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is an Intelligence project. Sith shouldn't be interfering in our work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664788" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith made a mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we keep him from finding out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only if he knows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664790" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. Karrels is close to his sons, and the circumstances of the encounter aren't exactly secret. He'll learn, sooner or later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664792" id2="17" version="1065353216">How could you let this happen?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664792" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is your fault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664793" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith do what they will. We don't control them, and we don't pass judgment on them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664795" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't mean they're right, or that we obey them without question--but we phrase those questions carefully. We bide our time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664797" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, I have a plan to solve our present dilemma, but first we need Karrels out of the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664798" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're asking me to kill Karrels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664798" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Out of the way&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure that's necessary?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664799" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no other choice?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664800" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's unfortunate, but it's the only way to proceed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664802" id2="17" version="1065353216">Done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664803" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sending you an interference program on a computer spike. Go to Karrels's suites in the palace. Activate the spike to black out his security monitors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664805" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be able to eliminate Karrels and his bodyguards without being seen. When Nem'ro's people investigate, they'll recognize the jamming program as Republic technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664806" id2="17" version="1065353216">So we frame the Republic for the murder of Karrels Javis. Why?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664806" id2="17" version="1065353216">To what end?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664807" id2="17" version="1065353216">One step at a time, agent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep going.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664810" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure I want to do this, Keeper.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664810" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664811" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have to be sure, so long as the job gets done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664813" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toth'lazhen--Nem'ro's Twi'lek advisor--already expects Fa'athra to seek revenge for the destruction of his mines. Our job is to show that the Republic helped Fa'athra kill Karrels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once Karrels is gone, speak to Toth'lazhen about his suspicions. As Karrels's friend, you'll promise to do whatever it takes to find the assassins.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that right? How am I going to find the &quot;real&quot; killer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664816" id2="17" version="1065353216">The &quot;assassins&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664817" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toth'lazhen doesn't trust me, Keeper. That won't change just because Karrels is dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664818" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one will believe that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664819" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe not, but we need to put all our pieces into play for the endgame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664821" id2="17" version="1065353216">For now, get to Karrels's suites and use the computer spike. We'll discuss more once Karrels is eliminated and Toth'lazhen's suspicions have been aroused.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keeper out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664825" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand Nem'ro's shvash gas production is back on schedule, agent. Excellent work. Keep it up, and Darth Jadus may loosen his grip on operations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664827" id2="17" version="1065353216">However, I'm afraid... unforeseen circumstances have caused a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664828" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of problem?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Problem?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664829" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mean the people who broke into my room?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those dead guys back there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664830" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. That's a separate matter, and one I advise you to watch closely; but it isn't what concerns me now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right. Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664834" id2="17" version="1065353216">On to more immediate concerns: Nem'ro operates a major shvash gas mine on Hutta. The Empire wants access to Nem'ro's refined gas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, Fa'athra is tapping the same gas pocket as Nem'ro. We need to destroy Fa'athra's operations in the Rust Yards before Nem'ro's grinds to a halt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664837" id2="17" version="1065353216">So it's a sabotage mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664837" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664838" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's correct.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't we just buy the gas from Fa'athra, instead?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664840" id2="17" version="1065353216">So why do we need Nem'ro?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nem'ro's refineries produce shvash usable as a precision explosive. Fa'athra can't refine the gas to the same degree, and he's wasting it by trying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664843" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't know how long I've been waiting to blow something up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664843" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664844" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you may enjoy this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664846" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will travel to Fa'athra's mining facility and place explosives in the drill shaft, destroying the equipment and collapsing part of the gas pocket.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664848" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll need to strip a uniform and credentials off the facility guards to pass the final security checkpoint. A working disguise is imperative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664849" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if I can't find a guard in my size?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Might not be easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664850" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you'll make do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who needs a disguise when I can shoot my way in?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664853" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shoot your way through the Rust Yards, if you like--but the automated security won't let anyone unauthorized into the drill chamber.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664856" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your disguise may not hold up under close inspection, so avoid conversation. The explosives have already been delivered to your room.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you're finished, go back to Karrels Javis and make sure he knows what happened. Take the credit, if you like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664859" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll be handled. Is there anything else?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664860" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't be long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664862" id2="17" version="1065353216">One more thing, agent: Darth Jadus pays increasing attention to your work. He will reward success or failure appropriately, and I will not intervene.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664865" id2="17" version="1065353216">How exactly does a Dark Lord of the Sith reward failure?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664865" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Or failure&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best not to dwell on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664868" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. Then we don't need to discuss it further.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664871" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sort of rewards are we talking about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reward?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664872" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're well aware of what I mean, agent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Report back after you've destroyed the mine and informed Karrels of the results. Keeper out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664876" id2="17" version="1065353216">The operation is proceeding well, agent. Thanks to your intervention, Karrels Javis will once again have Nem'ro's ear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664878" id2="17" version="1065353216">I took note of your meeting with Nem'ro's security chief, Kaliyo. You handled yourself well. Still, be on your guard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664880" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've identified her as a freelance assassin, enforcer and anarchist. She's been attached to a dozen employers in half as many years, using several different aliases.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664881" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's she doing with Nem'ro?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any more information?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unknown. In all likelihood, she needed the credits--and if she truly has no loyalty to the Hutt, we may be able to use her in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664884" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killing her wouldn't be any trouble. I can lure her somewhere isolated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Want her dead?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664886" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's a wild card. She may prove a liability, but she could also prove very useful. Watch her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664889" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Intelligence has determined that Nem'ro's human lieutenant--Karrels Javis--is the weak link in his operation. You're going to twist the man until he serves us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664890" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't see it--he didn't seem particularly disloyal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664891" id2="17" version="1065353216">He won't be any trouble to manipulate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664891" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll be simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664892" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're telling me I have to work with Nem'ro's thug?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Karrels? Ugh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Karrels has advised the Hutt for many years, and he's sympathetic towards the Empire--he admires our efficiency, and he prefers humans in authority. He'll do for our purposes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664895" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, Karrels is on the verge of disfavor with Nem'ro, while the Twi'lek lieutenant--Toth'lazhen, I believe--is Nem'ro's rising star.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664897" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want you to go to Karrels and offer your services as the Red Blade. Do whatever is required to bring Karrels glory in Nem'ro's eyes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664898" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does Nem'ro have against Karrels?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is he out of favor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664899" id2="17" version="1065353216">Karrels's work has been suffering due to the interference of the Fa'athra clan. Nem'ro finds that an unacceptable excuse for failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664900" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of help should I offer? We can't afford to make him suspicious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664900" id2="17" version="1065353216">How?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664901" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the Blade. You're a pirate and a trader. You want him as an ally. You're acting as a mercenary. Work it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664902" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I must.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed you will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664905" id2="17" version="1065353216">One other thing, agent: This operation of ours has drawn the attention of a member of the Dark Council--Darth Jadus himself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664907" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Council's authority is second only to that of the Emperor. It's a rare... honor for an Intelligence operation to be overseen in this way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664908" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe I understand, sir. I won't disappoint you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664908" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664909" id2="17" version="1065353216">With all due respect--what does the Dark Council care about Hutta? This operation isn't exactly a threat to the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664909" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Darth cares about us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664910" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know why Lord Jadus is interested. Nor is it our concern--the Sith aren't obligated to share their reasons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664912" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't need the oversight of Sith to do our job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664912" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's interference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch what you say. We answer to the Sith, whether you feel we need them or not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Report back once you've rendered whatever aid Karrels requires. Keeper out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664917" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done, agent. The listening device is working perfectly, and Nem'ro can keep no more secrets from us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Secure transmission established. This is Keeper. We may speak freely, agent; prepare to receive your orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664924" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready, sir. What's the assignment?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664925" id2="17" version="1065353216">In short? Subversion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664927" id2="17" version="1065353216">I take it you're my handler?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664927" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're in charge?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Correct. I'm speaking to you from service headquarters on Dromund Kaas. I'll be directing you personally on this mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keeper--should I be thanking you for these lovely accommodations?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get cute, and don't waste my time. You're here to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664933" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were chosen for this operation because of your exemplary performance during training. Imperial Intelligence needs agents capable of working independently in the field.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now you apply your training to the real world. Nem'ro the Hutt and his organization run Jiguuna, and you're in town to convince Nem'ro to supply the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664936" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand. How do I proceed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me background. What are we working from?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664937" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want all the details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664938" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jiguuna is an industrial town, and Nem'ro runs most of the industry. The Hutt plies weapons, drugs and raw materials--but not to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664940" id2="17" version="1065353216">We believe Nem'ro has been reluctant to lose Republic customers by publicly siding with the Empire. It's time he overcame this reluctance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664941" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664942" id2="17" version="1065353216">By force? Or did you have another method in mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664942" id2="17" version="1065353216">How?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664943" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's too early to say for certain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664945" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I'm your means of making that happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664945" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you come to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664946" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's correct, agent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664948" id2="17" version="1065353216">You realize I'm not exactly a diplomat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664948" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not my specialty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664949" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the situation requires a diplomat, you will become a diplomat. But for now, a lighter touch is required.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664951" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to know what Nem'ro and his advisors are thinking before we can act. I want you to obtain access to the Nem'ro clan's inner circle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664953" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll require a cover identity. One of our contacts--an alien named Jheeg--has prepared a background for you and will provide the details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664954" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do I find him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664954" id2="17" version="1065353216">So where to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664955" id2="17" version="1065353216">So who am I going to be?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cover identity?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664956" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be taking the role of a visiting pirate and trader. As I said, our contact will give you the details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trust me, Keeper--I don't need any help to get close to a Hutt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, this is easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't underestimate the Nem'ro clan. The galaxy has seen more effective gangsters, but rarely more sadistic ones.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jheeg will be waiting for you at a safe house. Locate him, take what he offers, then report to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are we sure this contact is trustworthy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is Jheeg reliable?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664963" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jheeg won't betray us; whether he succeeds at his assigned tasks is another matter. I'd be more concerned with the rest of the populace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664965" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should I expect to find trouble?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any dangers?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most of Jiguuna is caught up in a turf war. Some of the gangs involved belong to the Hutts; others are independent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your combat training should see you through, but expect brutality, and expect to be targeted. Jiguuna isn't friendly to strangers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664973" id2="17" version="1065353216">Noted. Anything else before I go?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664973" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Neither am I. I can handle myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="664975" id2="17" version="1065353216">So?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664976" id2="17" version="1065353216">One last thing: Ingratiate yourself with the locals. Get what information you can from them. It may prove useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now find Jheeg and report back to me. Keeper out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="664980" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a private conversation. Remove yourself.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
