<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>43</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/bronze/republic/unheard_frequencies/monitoring_station.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="288580" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Larek? I'm uploading the memory cores now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything looks in order... fascinating. Alarms, new defenses, whole wings of this prison we didn't know about.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288583" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll forward this straight to Command--see if we can get some of these systems up and running. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="288585" id2="17" version="1065353216">[You activate the monitoring station terminal and set it to the Republic frequency.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288587" id2="17" version="1065353216">AG-15, do you copy? AG-16, please respond. Blasted droids... is anyone there?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288589" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't look Imperial. I think I see a full squad behind you... the more, the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi! I didn't expect to see robes in the lower levels. Not that I'm complaining.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288593" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Havoc Squad officer. Thank goodness the Republic's finally got some real muscle.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288595" id2="17" version="1065353216">A mercenary? What in blazes are you doing down there? Never mind, I need your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Larek, field research. I'm looking for my droids. They were gathering data that could help us regain control of Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="288598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to know the scientists are fighting, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to have the help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288599" id2="17" version="1065353216">So much of the history here has already been destroyed. Now we have a reason to preserve it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="288601" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're not down here with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you safe at least?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288602" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me, against Esh-kha and escaped murderers? Only a fool would go down there... no offense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="288604" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to push the Empire offworld first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288604" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll take more than that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288605" id2="17" version="1065353216">Half our resources are tied up chasing escapees. If we secure the prison, we'll be at full strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="288607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody here but me and the Esh-kha.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Haven't seen them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288608" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was afraid of that. I'm out a few thousand credits if they're lost. But that data's too important.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about this data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Science is boring.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, please! You're the only one to answer who didn't bellow Esh-kha at me. I need your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288614" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're seeking ancient Rakata security droids. There are many disabled defenses in this prison. These droids would know how to reactivate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288616" id2="17" version="1065353216">My droids were to pull their memory cores and upload the data to me, but they haven't answered my comms. They're probably scrap by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="288617" id2="17" version="1065353216">A lot of droids have survived down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288617" id2="17" version="1065353216">You might be wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please. They were built to gather samples and conduct tests, not survive a war zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I do something?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I do something?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288623" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want the Empire to control this place? We're all in trouble if we can't find an edge.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288625" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last transmissions from my droids indicated they had found a vault full of active Rakata security units. Their memory cores were intact.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288627" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've sent the droids' last coordinates. If you could recover those memory cores, we could beef up prison security and push the Empire out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288628" id2="17" version="1065353216">In that case....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288629" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288630" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't sacrifice my team on a hunch. Those droids were expensive.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you find the memory cores, upload the data to this terminal. Good luck out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="288634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Waste of time. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="288635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then please, get off this channel. I need to keep trying my droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288637" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This monitoring station appears to be deactivated.]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
