<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>48</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris_imp/bronze/leading_the_pack/doctor_wylenn.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="111983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mimi and the remaining rakghouls are exhibiting heightened violence levels. I almost pity their Republic victims.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="111985" id2="17" version="1065353216">I killed the rakghoul leaders and released the pheromones. The pack reacted violently--just as you expected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="111986" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew it! With my hypothesis validated, our relationship with rakghouls...! I mustn't get ahead of myself. This requires further study.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="111988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your assistance has proven invaluable, my lord. My findings will reflect your influence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="111989" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will forever be a friend of science, agent. I won't forget you when drafting my final report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="111990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your services have furthered both science and the Empire's cause, hunter. I call that a job well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="111991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to you, we've proven rakghouls' use beyond blaster fodder. I'll include your help in my report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="111993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eliminate the alpha rakghouls, then stir up the nest. My remote sensors will record everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="111994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Day 43: Mimi continues her antisocial behavior. Rex exhibits Force sensitivity and asserts his dominance over the pack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="111996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pardon me, my lord. Sometimes I lose my head in my work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="111998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me, agent. Sometimes my pursuits threaten to consume me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please excuse me. If I don't record my observations, they simply float away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112002" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Doctor Wylenn, xenobiologist, specializing in rakghoul behavior.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112003" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought we came here to destroy Taris, not study the local wildlife.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="112003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Education isn't our priority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sometimes the two pursuits are one and the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="112006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any rakghoul breakthroughs?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112007" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last week alone has produced incredible insight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="112009" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really study those freaks?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112010" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm completely serious. There's more to the creatures than simple bloodlust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakghouls are pack hunters, led by alpha hunters. Socioeconomic status prior to infection has no bearing on their place in the herd.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112014" id2="17" version="1065353216">These alpha hunters are magnificent, fierce warriors. Without them, the pack is lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112015" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you aren't developing an affinity for those bloodthirsty monsters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="112015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I detect awe?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112016" id2="17" version="1065353216">I simply respect their strength, my lord. If handled with caution, we could even use it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cut down these alphas, and the monsters will bow to a new master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="112018" id2="17" version="1065353216">They must be made to serve us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112019" id2="17" version="1065353216">A wise perspective, my lord. With the rakghoul leaders dead, the next step is simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112021" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kill the alpha leaders, and the entire pack is ours to manipulate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="112021" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could lead them instead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Precisely, agent. And once the alphas are dead, the next step is simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't tell me you're a rak-lover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="112024" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're killers, not pets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112025" id2="17" version="1065353216">Goodness, no. My job is to discover how to use the rakghouls, and I've done just that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="112027" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm fiercer than any rakghoul.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such bravery is precisely why you're fit to apply my research.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="112030" id2="17" version="1065353216">How is this useful, doctor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exterminate the alpha leaders, and the rakghoul pack is destabilized--and ours to manipulate. The next step is simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112033" id2="17" version="1065353216">You see, rakghouls possess incredible olfactory strength. I've engineered an alarm pheromone that peaks their fury.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Simply release these pheromones in the rakghoul warrens, and the frenzied, leaderless beasts will sate their bloodlust on the nearby Republic outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="112036" id2="17" version="1065353216">The beasts will soon serve us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="112037" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle the rakghouls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Science thanks you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="112040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. I'll toy with your raks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember, first assassinate the alpha leaders, then release these pheromones. That's all the encouragement the rakghouls need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="112043" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe later. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I'll continue my research. Mimi still sleeps, but I wonder how many lives Rex will take today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fascinating creatures, rakghouls. Simply fascinating.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
