<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>9</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/event/gree/imperial/mission_terminal.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1110568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Honored Imperial contributors! As you enhance the combative analyses of Gray Secant, please consider additional opportunities for purple obtuse.

Recovery and recycling of data implants from Gray Secant combat specimens would surely facilitate efficient acquisition of blue acute.

Samples from local crystal formations and wildlife would also contribute valued understandings.

May your activities proceed to red tangent!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1110578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Potent bipeds of the Sith Empire: your contributions to the combat understandings of Gray Secant are greatly appreciated!

To directly facilitate red radian, please activate any of the pylons spread through this region to begin Gray Secant's combat assessment program. Challenging opponents will be engaged immediately, and your displays of prowess recorded for all time!

The Gree Enclave happily advances blue parallel to all who participate!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1110579" id2="17" version="1065353216">OBJECTIVE UPDATE--TO ALL IMPERIAL PERSONNEL:

The Gree insist that their starship is studying our combat methods for purely academic reasons. However, the Dark Council requires more than mere assurances when it comes to our military activities. We must determine what data the Gree are gathering.

Therefore, all field personnel are directed to tap into any Gree probe relays they encounter. The protocols necessary to access these relays can be retrieved from the Gree combat droids currently wandering this sector.

Proceed with caution: the probe relays are likely to be heavily guarded. If questioned or confronted by the Gree, feign ignorance; we do not wish these aliens to know we're listening in on them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1110581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Red parallel! Your advanced battle contributions have been deemed worthy for the highest of honors: a journey within Gray Secant itself!

Opponents embodying green perpendicular await within the vessel's corridors. Face them and rejoice in unparalleled data generation!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1110583" id2="17" version="1065353216">OBJECTIVE UPDATE--TO ALL IMPERIAL PERSONNEL:

Pirate scum known as the Tonvarr have managed to locate Ilum and land several raiding parties. They are already attempting to loot weapons and other advanced technologies from the Gree droids present in this sector.

Gree technologies must go to the Empire alone, or we will lose any advantage they give us. Eliminate all Tonvarr forces on sight, particularly crew captains and starships. Any Gree materials in Tonvarr possession should be recovered for Imperial use.

If possible, also recover any hyperspace navigation logs carried by the group's navigators. These pirates have found an undetectable approach path to Ilum; such a hyperroute could be useful for our own efforts in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1110585" id2="17" version="1065353216">OBJECTIVE UPDATE--TO ALL IMPERIAL PERSONNEL:

Republic troops have been seen scavenging damaged military vehicles in this sector. We believe they are attempting to recover sensitive data from their lost assets, but they are clearly gathering intelligence from disabled Imperial equipment as well. This must be stopped.

All forces are directed to recover any data left behind in inoperable vehicles--whether Republic or Imperial--and return that data to command personnel immediately.

Do not hesitate to neutralize any enemy forces encountered. If enemy forces include droids, retrieve their memory cores as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1110592" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Empire by completing the following missions in the Western Ice Shelf on Ilum:

[DAILY] External Variables
[DAILY] Supplemental Research
[DAILY] Confirmation Bias
[DAILY] Advanced Analysis
[HEROIC] Primary Testing</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1110593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Noted data generators! Gray Secant's Interactive Research Liaison, Xenoanalyst II, is prepared to assess your group combative dynamics!

Board Gray Secant and demonstrate your unified capacity for blue parallel!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1110594" id2="17" version="1065353216">OBJECTIVE UPDATE--TO ALL IMPERIAL PERSONNEL:

Scouts have confirmed the presence of Gree pylons and energy condensers in the contested area of the Western Ice Shelf. Sensor data indicates that these objects match those found on Seline, where they have demonstrated considerable destructive power. 

It is imperative that we secure these pylons before they fall into the hands of the Republic. Collect the energy harvested by the condensers and use it to charge the pylons.

Due to the volatility of the pylons, small unit tactics with four-person teams are considered ideal to minimize potential personnel losses.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
