<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>16</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hutta/bronze/a_slight_lean/morsel.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666831" id2="17" version="1065353216">You saved my life. Saved it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666832" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to say a thing. I got a very polite holo from the chief enforcer. Very polite. And here, my good mercenary, are your credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666834" id2="17" version="1065353216">The sooner the chief enforcer sees I mean business, the sooner I can make Nem'ro happy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666835" id2="17" version="1065353216">You! Yes. Oh yes. Oh, saved. Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nem'ro the Bounteous takes me from the swamp, yes? He gives me new name, new job. He makes me Morsel the Administrator!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nem'ro orders me to keep work camp enforcers in line, but they hired to bully Evocii--they laugh at me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me who you need dead and how much it's worth to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="666840" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need me to kill someone?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666841" id2="17" version="1065353216">You tell people your name is Morsel and expect them to respect you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="666841" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd laugh at you, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nem'ro didn't think it was funny. There was ceremony and everything! But those work camp enforcers respect nothing!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666844" id2="17" version="1065353216">We talking about gunplay or just a stern talking to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="666844" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what's the job?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666845" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enforcers hard to hire, harder to keep. So they think they can do as please. But we can't kill them....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666847" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go to work camp. Wave your gun in chief enforcer's face. Make him see Morsel no one to laugh at, and I have stack of credits for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="666849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sometimes being honored isn't all it should be.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
