<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>54</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/imperial/industrial_collapse/darbin_sull.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551624" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a private call from Prime Minister Darbin Sull of Corellia. Please hold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello? Oh, good to hear from you. I'm still proud of the work we did liberating Corellia from the rebellion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551627" id2="17" version="1065353216">The way I remember it, you sat back while I single-handedly ended the resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="551627" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did all the work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha! But please--let's be serious. I wouldn't want my secretary mistaking your jests for fact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551630" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trust you're enjoying your role in Corellian politics?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="551630" id2="17" version="1065353216">How's life treating you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551631" id2="17" version="1065353216">This prime minister gig comes with plenty of perks. A private estate, bottomless brandy reserves, you name it. I wanted to share the wealth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="551633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spit it out, Darbin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please accept this gift, a little something from my private collection. The least I could for your help in my promotion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me, Prime Minister. Your next meeting....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551638" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast. Sorry, but planetary matters do come first. Good luck out there, and remember--you've always got a friend on Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prime Minister Darbin Sull. I've spent years dreaming of this day. I won't forget your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551641" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let you down. Imagine me--prime minister of Corellia!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551644" id2="17" version="1065353216">That'll teach you to arrest a Corellian councilor. Who's the idiot now, Master Ramos?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blasted Jedi. They've interfered with Corellian politics for the last time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551647" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's done, Darth Decimus. The Green Jedi Council's finished!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. Without their Jedi, the rebellion will crumble. Nothing will stop this miserable planet from joining the Empire. And we have you to thank.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="551650" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to thank me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551651" id2="17" version="1065353216">That said, I won't let you escape without due reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="551653" id2="17" version="1065353216">My success was a given.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551654" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clearly. And the best deserves worthy recognition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="551656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank me later. Pay me now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551657" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree, but not here. Your payment requires a personal touch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551659" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't forget me, Darth Decimus. I played a big role--big enough for Corellia's new prime minister.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="551661" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's in store for Corellia?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551662" id2="17" version="1065353216">I take over as prime minister, appointed for my loyal service to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551664" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was our agreement, wasn't it? I can see it now: Corellia rebuilding under the glorious leadership of Darbin Sull.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551666" id2="17" version="1065353216">But freedom allows rebellion. And we've had enough of that. Perhaps we erase Corellia's would-be leader and rule with an iron fist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Establish direct Imperial control over this planet. Its citizens will obey or face punishment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="551667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cage Corellia. [Kill Darbin]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551669" id2="17" version="1065353216">And Darbin... people think you betrayed us. Letting you live would be a sign of weakness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551670" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could issue a press release, clear up the whole thing! Please... I'm supposed to be prime minister!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551672" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. We've worked too hard to let Corellia slip through our fingers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chain Corellia too tight and you risk more violence. But show them trust, put Darbin in charge and they'll peacefully bow to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="551674" id2="17" version="1065353216">This planet deserves freedom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly! I'll show them the Empire's looking out for our best interests.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551677" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's enough, Prime Minister Sull. Save your enthusiasm for the official ceremony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551679" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a historic day, and it must be properly commemorated. Report to me at once so the Empire can give you the recognition you deserve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551681" id2="17" version="1065353216">There you are! I was afraid I wouldn't reach you in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551683" id2="17" version="1065353216">My bruises weren't enough to trick the Republic. They accused me of being an Imperial spy... so I threw them something extra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551685" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic didn't buy my story. They accused me of being an Imperial agent... so I tossed them something extra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551687" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... mentioned your assault on the Memorial Garden. The Republic ate it up. They took me in... then sent a strike team your way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551688" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did what you had to do. I'll deal with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="551688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for the warning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551689" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make it up to you once Axial Park falls. Just be careful in there....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551690" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should have known Corellia's esteemed councillor would betray me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="551690" id2="17" version="1065353216">You double-crossing rat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551691" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not like that! Telling them was the only way the Republic would buy my story!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551693" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh, that's my cue to go. I'm sure you'll pull through just fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="551694" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't sound good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551695" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not that bad. Maybe you'll even finish up before the strike team reaches you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551697" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or maybe not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551699" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen--I've got to go. I'm sure you'll pull through just fine.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
