<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>211</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/imperial/industrial_collapse/darth_charnus.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499259" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've achieved more than I could ever imagine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Decimus chose his allies well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Follow me, and you'll swim in the spoils of war. But first, we destroy the rebellion. We must decorate Corellia with their dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take a rocket tram to the ruins of Labor Valley. Help Major Tradik burn the rebels out of hiding. Then we will speak again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Beautiful work. The CEC directors' deaths shook the rebellion. We'll ensure their new leadership is more sympathetic to our cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499273" id2="17" version="1065353216">Outstanding job. The CEC surrender shook the rebellion. We'll mold their board into icons of Imperial loyalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499275" id2="17" version="1065353216">My master wishes to express his gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499277" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Darth Decimus, member of the Dark Council, architect of Corellia's invasion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Baras is right to hate one so powerful. Such strength... it fills the air around you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499281" id2="17" version="1065353216">From slavery rises the most powerful Sith in generations. Darth Thanaton is right to fear you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499283" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand you're unraveling a conspiracy. How fortunate that it brought you here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499285" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been watching you, victor of the Great Hunt, champion of the Blacklist. How fortunate that your latest prey brought you here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499287" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will be the executor of the Empire's victory. It is your destiny.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499289" id2="17" version="1065353216">Power attracts power. How fortunate that you've all gathered here, at the moment of the Empire's greatest fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499291" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia is filled with wretched people... crude, scheming animals, begging to be conquered. We can help them by winning this battle. But I require your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499292" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you wish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499293" id2="17" version="1065353216">Loyalty deserves compensation. Darth Charnus...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499295" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a lot of pressure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499296" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider this an investment in your potential....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499298" id2="17" version="1065353216">My help will cost you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Charity is for the weak and the lazy. The Empire is neither. You'll be well-rewarded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499303" id2="17" version="1065353216">The CEC ion cannons are offline; the rocket trams can run again!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499305" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must celebrate--come to the Tears of Taris at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499307" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good, you made it. The explosives team is standing by with the hull-cracker. But that's not all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499309" id2="17" version="1065353216">A defector inside CEC has contacted us. Claims he has useful information, but he'll only talk to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499311" id2="17" version="1065353216">Benton Maas, say hello to the Sith who's about to destroy your pathetic company.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Benton Maas, meet our top agent on Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Benton Maas, hunter. Hunter, Benton Maas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Benton Maas, say hello to your company's worst nightmare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Benton Maas, meet the crew who's about to dismantle your precious company.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499321" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's an honor, my lord. I'm the only one here who respects your power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bow before me. Pledge your support to the Empire's occupation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prove your respect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499323" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you wish, my lord. Imperial rule is just what this corrupt, Republic-riddled world needs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499325" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I want from you is terror, despair and devotion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499325" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need your respect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your power is beyond comprehension, my lord. That's why I wish to serve you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just the operative I wanted to see! I must talk with someone who's used to handling sensitive information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Discretion is one of my many specialties. What's on your mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499329" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're wise to contact me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499330" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear you're the top merc on Corellia. These Imperials don't understand, but I can level with a pro like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499331" id2="17" version="1065353216">It takes a pro like me to tear down your little company.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499331" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right to respect me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499332" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard as much. Your work's already left a deep wound on this planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you! I need to speak with someone I can respect. Someone with your... unique skill set.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499335" id2="17" version="1065353216">A holocall won't protect you from my power. Explain yourself, quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499335" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will handle this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't shy away from true power. If you want something, address me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499336" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's wrong? Afraid of me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499337" id2="17" version="1065353216">We traced your frequency. Start talking, or I'll track you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me handle this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cut the bootlicking and start talking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499338" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your company's doomed. Trying to jump ship?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you calling to surrender?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499340" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right. I'm too old to be on the losing side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499343" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got the hull-cracker. CEC can't defend against that. But I can make your fight a bit easier... all I'm asking for is mercy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499345" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a back entrance through the manufacturing wing. Get close, and I'll open it for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499347" id2="17" version="1065353216">We already have Czerka's hull-cracker. We don't need a back door.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499349" id2="17" version="1065353216">An explosion'll bring our security forces running. But slip through the manufacturing wing and you'll catch CEC by surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499350" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force more than compensates for a noisy entrance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499350" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith don't need surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499351" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll consider your proposal, Benton Maas. Once CEC falls to the Empire, we will repay your loyalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499353" id2="17" version="1065353216">A clean infiltration will assure our victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499353" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surprise could prove useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499354" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll still be waiting for the blast when you sneak right past them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499356" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fewer guards that see me, the quicker I reach my target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surprise could prove useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499357" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't realize you're coming 'til your blaster's in their face.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work. I'll take your proposal under advisement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for the tip.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499360" id2="17" version="1065353216">Follow my advice, and CEC will fall. Just spare my life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spare me the amateur strategy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499363" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please--I just listened to a security briefing. Those hangars are CEC's vulnerable area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499365" id2="17" version="1065353216">I better go before the directors come looking for me. Remember, the manufacturing wing's your best shot. And long live the Emperor!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Idiot. Still, his information may prove useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499369" id2="17" version="1065353216">Infiltrating the hangars could avoid most security. Czerka's hull-cracker is more direct, if bloodier. I doubt our demolition crew will survive the detonation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499370" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care about casualties. We're blasting our way in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499370" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stick with the hull-cracker.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499371" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. I'll contact the explosives team at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499373" id2="17" version="1065353216">These men are the most proficient engineers this side of the blockade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499375" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never met a bomb we couldn't handle. Watch our backs, and we'll bust CEC's shell for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499377" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then deal with their board of directors and disable the ion cannons. Once the rocket trams are operational, our invasion is back on track.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499378" id2="17" version="1065353216">Safety first. I'll try the hangar entrance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499378" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer a cautious approach.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499381" id2="17" version="1065353216">CEC has held us hostage too long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499382" id2="17" version="1065353216">The CEC droids are in disarray. Find Commander Krade while we have the upper hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499383" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confuse the CEC droids. Then we'll shatter their defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499384" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the hull-cracker in our possession, we can finally shut down CEC and end their attacks on our rocket trams.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499386" id2="17" version="1065353216">But first we must deal with their army. Legions of battle droids defend the CEC fortress. Our explosives team can't get close enough to detonate the hull-cracker.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499387" id2="17" version="1065353216">CEC commands them somehow. Cut the droids off, and they lose control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499387" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we disable them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499388" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right. CEC uses signal towers to direct their army. It's their only weak point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499390" id2="17" version="1065353216">CEC's army will fall before my lightsaber.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499390" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll cut them down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499391" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll melt those CEC rust buckets into a pile of steaming circuits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499391" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can fry CEC's army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499392" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd need a battalion of Sith, all as powerful as you, to put a dent in their numbers. There's only one other solution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499394" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every droid model has exploitable weaknesses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499394" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll eliminate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm, a good point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499397" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the smoke clears, you'll need a microscope to find the droids' remains.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499397" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll disintegrate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499398" id2="17" version="1065353216">The most devastating weapons couldn't wipe out the CEC reserves. There's only one solution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499400" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few scrap-piles with blasters won't save them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Droids? Is that all?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499401" id2="17" version="1065353216">CEC's private peacekeeping force is powerful. But they have a weakness....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499403" id2="17" version="1065353216">These droids take orders directly from CEC. Signal towers transmit commands, and they obey with deadly precision.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499405" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bringing down the signal towers will disrupt the droids. Our explosives team sneaks in, detonates the hull-cracker, and blows the CEC doors wide open.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499406" id2="17" version="1065353216">CEC is about to lose contact with their army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499406" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll raze the towers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499407" id2="17" version="1065353216">If your army pitches in, we can wipe out every last tower.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499407" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't I get any backup?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499408" id2="17" version="1065353216">The CEC defenses are designed to deflect a large-scale attack. I can't sacrifice my men... yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. But I won't enjoy it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499411" id2="17" version="1065353216">The excitement comes when we topple CEC. This is simply an overture.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you remove the signal towers, contact Commander Krade in CEC territory. He'll prepare you for our final assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499416" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here are the detonation codes. Brall Tavar was eager to hand them over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499417" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure he was. Thanks to you, the Czerka Corellia hull-cracker is ours. These codes will awaken its power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Jastal briefed me on your handling of the Brall Tavar situation. His untimely end certainly broke Czerka's resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Brall Tavar's punishment will scare every rebel on Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499420" id2="17" version="1065353216">His death was a warning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499421" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want to really break the rebels' spirits, help me close Corellian Engineering Corporation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tavar didn't stand a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499424" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get too confident. Czerka was insignificant next to Corellian Engineering Corporation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Plus, due to your quick thinking with Brall Tavar, Czerka's learned to appreciate Imperial dominance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499427" id2="17" version="1065353216">The insurgents expect us to be violent. Show benevolence, and they'll forget what they're fighting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499427" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mercy will win over rebels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Compassion has no place in war. Remember that when you call on our friends at Corellian Engineering Corporation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499430" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one can resist my methods.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499431" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may have lured Czerka in, but Corellian Engineering Corporation won't be so easily convinced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough about Czerka.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your talents are needed on the ground to dismantle Czerka's defenses and liberate their hull-cracker.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499435" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't coordinate Czerka's downfall from up here. Speak with Commander Jastal in the field.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499436" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teach Czerka Corellia some manners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coronet City. The jewel of Corellia. Home to the finest trading and ship manufacturing in Republic space.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499441" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soon this will all belong to the Empire--and the rest of the galaxy will follow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where are my manners? I am Darth Charnus, agent to the Dark Council. My master--Darth Decimus--requested your assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499445" id2="17" version="1065353216">He says only the most powerful Sith can help us win Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499446" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will show this planet the Force's true might.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499446" id2="17" version="1065353216">None are more powerful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pity you weren't here to set an example during our initial assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499449" id2="17" version="1065353216">He believes only the Empire's most lethal agent can help us win Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499450" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can deliver this planet. Just tell me how many fatalities are too many.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499450" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would be me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha! Your expertise would have proven invaluable in our initial assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499453" id2="17" version="1065353216">He claims only the galaxy's most notorious bounty hunter can help us take Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499454" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll show this planet how I earned my reputation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499454" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's me, all right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499455" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could have used your blasters during the initial assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499457" id2="17" version="1065353216">He senses your greatness. Only one with your skill can take Corellia for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499458" id2="17" version="1065353216">Search the galaxy for someone who can match my strength. You'll find no one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499458" id2="17" version="1065353216">None are more skilled than me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499459" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure. We certainly could have used your lightsaber during our initial assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499461" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ignoring my strength with the Force would be unwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499461" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't overlook my power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499462" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't dream of it. We could have used your skill with the dark side during our initial assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Defeating a planet requires a deft touch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sometimes you need subtlety.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499465" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't doubt your skills. We could have used them during our initial assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think I'm not strong enough? Tell it to all the bodies I've piled up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh, I'm standing right here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499468" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know your reputation, hunter. If only you'd been here during our initial assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me more about Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499471" id2="17" version="1065353216">This planet was ripe for conquering. Darth Decimus plotted our assault, and we moved in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia? Who cares.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499474" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galactic war's outcome will be decided here. You wouldn't be so carefree if you'd witnessed our initial assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499476" id2="17" version="1065353216">The invasion was magnificent, our occupation flawless. Imperial forces filled Corellia's high-speed rocket trams. We began to cover Coronet City.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then rebellion erupted. Unruly Corellians knocked out the rocket trams. Now our soldiers are stranded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send your troops against the rebels. Don't give them an inch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fight back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our men are barely equipped to hold the spaceport. We need you to go after the insurgents behind the attacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Air-drop your men, send in shuttles. Anything to keep troops on the streets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get different transportation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alternate methods risk being shot down, plus they're unpredictable. I'm afraid our occupation's crippled without the high-speed rails.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499485" id2="17" version="1065353216">And we still haven't attacked?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499486" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're preparing to strike the rebels responsible for these heinous assaults.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499488" id2="17" version="1065353216">The guilty party is Corellian Engineering Corporation. The oldest ship manufacturer in Republic history.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499490" id2="17" version="1065353216">CEC exploited our one weakness. They turned their ion cannons on all outgoing trams, freezing our invasion, trapping us on the doorstep of the Empire's greatest battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Storm the company, and shut them down. It's the only way we'll break their blockade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take CEC over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499492" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree completely. Unfortunately, CEC's shielded against conventional attacks. There's only one way in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroy all guns firing on the rocket trams. Problem solved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knock out their ion cannons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499495" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've tried, but their emplacements are heavily shielded and must be shut down from inside CEC. There's only one way to breach their walls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499497" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't catch a break.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Worse, their ion cannons can only be disabled from inside CEC. They're shielded against all weapons... except one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499500" id2="17" version="1065353216">The hull-cracker--a compact bomb, developed by Czerka Corellia's deviant scientists to punch holes through capital ships. It will get us inside CEC.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499502" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we disable their ion cannons, resume rocket tram traffic and conquer Corellia. Unfortunately, Czerka's joined the rebellion--they refuse to hand over their hull-cracker.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka will cooperate with the Empire or be destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I'll take it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some broken fingers should loosen their grip on this weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499504" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll teach Czerka to share.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499505" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll support the Empire. They just need the proper encouragement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499505" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll pay Czerka a visit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499506" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Czerka won't give their weapon up, I'll take it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499506" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need permission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show them your arsenal, and they may even wrap up the hull-cracker with a bow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499509" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got other business. Still, stealing Czerka's weapon is tempting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I could deal with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it. You're trapped here as long as the rocket trams are down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499512" id2="17" version="1065353216">I may help, but not for free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499513" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be performing a service for Darth Decimus himself. It's safe to assume you'll be compensated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499515" id2="17" version="1065353216">The hull-cracker's under constant guard. Destroy Czerka's assault camps, and they'll abandon the weapon to reinforce their headquarters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you rout the camps, find our Commander Jastal in Czerka territory. Then we'll liberate that hull-cracker.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Decimus will be most disappointed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499524" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a CEC deployment beacon, designed to call their battle droid reinforcements. I suspect you'll find a use for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="539807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our attack is prepared, Darth Charnus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="539832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Storm CEC, then contact me from their security holoterminal. Once you're in position, we'll strike at their heart.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
