<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>124</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/imperial/industrial_collapse/general_hesker.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, conqueror of Corellia. The title suits you well. Wear it with honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, conquerors of Corellia. Wear that title with honor. You all have certainly earned it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499533" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a pleasure to see your powers in action, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive blaster work. You must have ice running through those veins.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive display, hunter. We could learn a thing or two from your tactics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499539" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Green Jedi will fear you now--as will Master Ramos. Impressive work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499541" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm here on strict orders. We're to secure the courtyards and guard your rear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to know the Imperial Guard's watching my back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wish we could see you further. Give Master Ramos my regards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499545" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dark side is the only backup I need to destroy these Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spare me your heroics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Block my aim again, and I won't hold my fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Next time, back off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499547" id2="17" version="1065353216">We go where the Emperor commands. Now that you're safe, we can keep our distance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Back to it, men! Leave no Jedi alive!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499550" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're dismissed, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499551" id2="17" version="1065353216">You heard the man. Start moving. Hunt down every last Jedi!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499552" id2="17" version="1065353216">You heard the lady. Move out. Down every Jedi you see!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499554" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Green Jedi's enclave is under siege. I'll join the attack soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499555" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Decimus awaits your help in Capitol Square.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499559" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've killed the unkillable Jedi. Axial Park belongs to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499560" id2="17" version="1065353216">One absurd rumor of an invincible Jedi safely put to rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499562" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I hear you destroyed the Republic monuments. Patriotism deserves recognition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your powers are only rivaled by the Dark Council itself. It's been an honor, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499565" id2="17" version="1065353216">You set an impressive example for Imperials everywhere. It's been a privilege.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499566" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the first mercenary the Imperial Guard could learn from. It's been a pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499567" id2="17" version="1065353216">Few match the Imperial Guard in lethality, but you've surpassed us. It's been an honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499568" id2="17" version="1065353216">I only wish all servants of the Emperor were so capable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Likewise, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499569" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right to admire me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499570" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is why the Empire still requires your talents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499572" id2="17" version="1065353216">My pay better match my praise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, hunter. I hope this doesn't conclude your business with the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499575" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia still needs me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499576" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Decimus is personally overseeing our final battle on Corellia. He's requested an audience with you in person. A great honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499578" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find him in Capitol Square--the heart of Corellia's power structure. Assist the Dark Lord and secure this planet for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Axial Park won't be ours while General Corin Tok still breathes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contact Lieutenant Roval in our outpost. We'll coordinate your final assault from there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just received a distress signal--our outpost is under attack! Hurry and assist!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work. Now let's use their signals against them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get close to the Republic walkers and set off the flares. Our squadrons will spy the signal and blow the targets away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499589" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's launching a major assault. Kill the commandos leading it, then grab their emergency flares so they can't call in backup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499590" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's moving to flank us. Cut them down!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to hit back. Fight your way into Coronet Zoo. Destroy the Republic's artillery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499592" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave the emplacements for now. Republic troops are crawling behind our lines. Stomp them out!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499593" id2="17" version="1065353216">The battle awaits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499598" id2="17" version="1065353216">You honor me again, my lord. Welcome to Axial Park. Our battle needs your presence, and your lightsaber.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to see you again, sir. Welcome to Axial Park. Our battle has escalated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499602" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect timing, hunter. Our battle in Axial Park is heating up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, we meet again. And just when our battle in Axial Park starts boiling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499606" id2="17" version="1065353216">This used to be the most beautiful parkland in all Republic space. Of course, our fight's changed the landscape considerably. Darth Decimus will brief you on the specifics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive work choking off the Selonians. This fight, however, will demand the full scope of your passion, strength and power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent work securing the Selonian tunnels. But to win here, you'll need every trick of Intelligence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent job stomping out the Selonians, hunter. Win this fight, and you'll more than earn your pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to you, the rebellion in Labor Valley lies in ruin. But the next fight will not be so easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499616" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is going all out to hold Axial Park. They know that control over Corellia hangs in the balance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499618" id2="17" version="1065353216">The park's crawling with shock troops, battle droids and special forces--all lead by one very dangerous Jedi. We've never faced such a massive Republic deployment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499619" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's entire army is no match for the dark side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499619" id2="17" version="1065353216">It won't be enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499620" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won't have to rely on the Force alone, my lord. We have bomber squadrons, special ops and walkers in the field.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic numbers are no match for Imperial strategy. I trust we're responding in kind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499622" id2="17" version="1065353216">It won't be enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Correct, sir. We have artillery, specials ops and walkers on the ground. Bombers in the sky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Match the Republic, blaster for blaster. Make them flinch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499625" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can't hold out forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499626" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're already on the defensive. We've moved in special ops, walkers and artillery. Rocket trams deliver more every minute.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499628" id2="17" version="1065353216">How is the Empire retaliating?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499628" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's our response?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499629" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've blocked off side streets, forcing the Republic into open warfare. On the ground, we have artillery, special ops, walkers--every ingredient for victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499631" id2="17" version="1065353216">But this battle demands more. Corellia won't be ours while the rebels still stand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499633" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll kill them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499634" id2="17" version="1065353216">They deserve punishment, but you won't be the only one meting it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499636" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're hammering the Republic with blaster cannons, special ops and walkers. Rocket trams deliver more reinforcements every minute.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499638" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must crush their army here--break the Republic, and take Axial Park. Then we're primed to strike at the rebellion's heart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499639" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Hesker, tell your men to follow my command. We're going to crush the Republic army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499639" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will lead the attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. But you'll have more than Imperial forces nipping at your heels. You remember the corrupt Corellian councillor, Darbin Sull.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499641" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll check out Axial Park, but no promises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me see what I can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499642" id2="17" version="1065353216">While you're sightseeing, you'll have company. You remember the corrupt Corellian councillor, Darbin Sull.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499644" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are these restraints really necessary?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499646" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darbin is now your prisoner. He will join your foray into Axial Park, and you will deliver him to the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hear that, Darbin? We're marching into battle. I hope you're ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499647" id2="17" version="1065353216">This should be interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499648" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just don't move too fast. These bindings are giving me blisters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Slow me down and I'll kill you myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep up, or you're dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry. I used to jog in Axial Park all the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499653" id2="17" version="1065353216">As tempting as it is, don't kill him. We need Darbin to help us infiltrate the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499655" id2="17" version="1065353216">My prisoner?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499656" id2="17" version="1065353216">The councillor is helping us to infiltrate the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take him into battle as your captive, then &quot;lose&quot; him. Darbin should remember the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like my mother's face. I charm my way into the Republic. Once you win Axial Park, I help bring them down from the inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Precisely. Unleash Darbin, conquer Axial Park and you'll plant the seed for our final victory. Hold nothing back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499664" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at Darbin. The fresh face, cheerful spirit--not damaged enough to be an Imperial prisoner....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499665" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold still, Darbin. I wouldn't want to blind you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499665" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good point. [Hit Darbin]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait--you can't be serious...!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Much better. When the Republic questions your loyalty, show them your bruises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499670" id2="17" version="1065353216">He should save his strength for the battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499670" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'll be fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499671" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right. Besides, I don't need bruises to trick the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499673" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're lucky, Darbin, but not invincible. Don't forget that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499675" id2="17" version="1065353216">You deliver this rodent, and I'll direct your strikes against the Republic Army itself. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia is nearly ours. Turn away, and you surrender everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499680" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is rolling out their best armaments in Axial Park.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well... that was exhilarating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551722" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never fired one of these things before. Maybe I'll get some practice in on my way to the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551723" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire is your master. Don't forget that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="551723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember who you serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551724" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to worry. The Republic's on its way out, and I don't ally with losers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your head down. Try not to blast your face off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="551726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for the concern. I won't stick around any longer than I have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551730" id2="17" version="1065353216">Point taken. I'm good to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551731" id2="17" version="1065353216">General--Darbin's armed and ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551732" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you waiting for, Councilor? Get out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551734" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell. When this is over and I'm prime minister, I won't forget you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell. I'll remember you all when I become prime minister!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally. Now to the battle at hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="551740" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our gun batteries are under assault. Drive off the Republic forces. Once the guns are safe, I'll have additional intel and orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="761202" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to shut up and move.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="983784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let the battle begin!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
