<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>57</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/imperial/industrial_collapse/lieutenant_roval.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552492" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith War Memorial Garden is just beyond our outpost. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552493" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Hesker wants a word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552495" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rebels are massing at the Sith War Memorial Garden--a pit honoring Jedi scum who fell to our first invasion three hundred years ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Naturally that's where the Republic base lies. Guarded by battle droids, Jedi and a battalion of their best shock troops. You name the weapon, they've aimed it our way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552498" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rebels are following orders. Break their commander, and we'll crush their resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552498" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must strike their leader.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552499" id2="17" version="1065353216">A wise strategy, my lord. We've been tracking such a man. Lieutenant, his profile....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone's responsible for this mess. We must enslave him to our will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Break their leader.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552502" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is such a man, my lord. But he won't break easily. Lieutenant, his profile...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make whoever's orchestrating this defense disappear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eliminate their leader.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552505" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed. We've been tracking such a man. Lieutenant, his profile...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone's in charge. If you want me to drop him, give me the details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552507" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need the leader gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very good. We've been following their commander for some time. Lieutenant, his profile....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552510" id2="17" version="1065353216">These rebels must have some weakness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552510" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what's the good news?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps only that they rely too heavily on one man--who should be our primary. The lieutenant has his profile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect stage for a massacre.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552514" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have plenty of hostiles to eliminate--but focus on their commander. Lieutenant, you have his profile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, sir. Master Corin Tok. A Zabrak Jedi Knight, Republic war hero... and veteran of the Sacking of Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552518" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of the few survivors. Many Sith fell to his lightsaber that day. He earned himself a pretty little reputation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Survivors claimed he was invincible. Blaster bolts splashing off skin, lightsabers failing in his presence. I say it's that special armor under his robes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since then, Master Corin Tok has aged into a hardened warhorse; his myth has grown, and he stands between us and control of Axial Park.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia's future lies with the Empire. No Jedi will prevent that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Axial Park will be ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552524" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will attack at once. You'll have the full support of the Imperial military.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legends like that carry heavy bounties. Leave him to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552526" id2="17" version="1065353216">He sounds like a worthy prize.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552527" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you'd recognize the benefits, hunter. Eliminate him, and the Empire will reward your troubles.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552529" id2="17" version="1065353216">A mere Jedi doesn't scare me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to hear it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552532" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a chance I could help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552533" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't delay our assault. I hope you'll lead the charge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant, order your men to strike the Memorial Garden. Hit every monument--erase all signs of the Republic's past victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552537" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need you to spearhead the attack. Storm the Republic base and bury the Jedi Master. We take Axial Park now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank goodness it's you, my lord. It's madness--artillery blasts, Republic troops everywhere. I thought we were finished!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for the assist, sir! It's madness out there. The Republic hit us hard... I was sure we were goners!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552544" id2="17" version="1065353216">A mercenary... and one of ours! Thank goodness! We're low on reserves, and the Republic won't stop hammering us!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552545" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe you made it. The Republic hit us... most of my men are dead... I wasn't trained for this!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Control your fear, Lieutenant, or I'll control it for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Focus yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood, my lord. General Hesker... he awaits an audience with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552548" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're an Imperial soldier, not a child. Act like it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pull yourself together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552549" id2="17" version="1065353216">My apologies, sir.... I was supposed to tell you--General Hesker wants a word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552550" id2="17" version="1065353216">You Imps need to learn how to stay calm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pull yourself together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552551" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right. I'm sorry. General Hesker wants a word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552552" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contact Imperial Command. This battle's not over yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552552" id2="17" version="1065353216">Connect me to General Hesker.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course... I'll put you through at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="552554" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're pathetic, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552555" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry. General Hesker wants a word. Please don't mention this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552557" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work out there. Darbin's met his rebel contact, Axial Park's covered with Republic casualties. But they're not retreating yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="552559" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is our last outpost before the Memorial Garden. We tried to advance, but it's no use.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
