<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>109</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/imperial/industrial_collapse/major_tradik.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543397" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew Corellia would join us sooner or later. Good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543398" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to you, the resistance in Labor Valley's trounced. The rebels too stupid to surrender are falling like flies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wish you could stay and wipe 'em out, but the forces that be want you in Axial Park. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543402" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Selonians are rebuilding the resistance. Take to their tunnels, and hit them where it counts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543403" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work hitting the rebels' weapons shipments. Darth Decimus is expecting our report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543405" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major, Councillor... and my good friend. What news on the rebel supplies?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543407" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major Tradik... Darbin Sull... and my good friends. What of the rebel supplies?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroyed, my lord. The resistance in Labor Valley is defeated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543411" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not entirely accurate. Their weapons are in flames, but the rebellion here's still kicking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543413" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm aware of their persistence, Councillor. Intelligence monitored the rebels' retreat. They slithered into the tunnels beneath Coronet City, like the worms they are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543414" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rebels are pinned down. Those tunnels will be their grave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543414" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can't escape me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assuredly, my lord, but the insurgents will find help. Those tunnels are Selonian territory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunting the rebels will be simple. I'll just follow the stink of their fear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543417" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can't escape me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543418" id2="17" version="1065353216">It won't be long 'til they muster courage, my lord. Those tunnels are Selonian territory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let them run. I'll track the rebels down and end their resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543420" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can't hide from me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543421" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't bet on a quick cleanup. Those tunnels are Selonian territory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543423" id2="17" version="1065353216">What tunnels?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tunnels?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543424" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a network of underground pipelines. Rumor says they stretch kilometers beneath Coronet City. All of it Selonian territory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543426" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must defeat them quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543427" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't rush in without a plan. Those tunnels are Selonian territory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543429" id2="17" version="1065353216">If those furry aliens are part of the resistance, we'll blast them off Corellia!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543431" id2="17" version="1065353216">Patience, Major. The Selonians are fierce warriors, and those tunnels are their nest. Your men wouldn't survive five minutes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543433" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't know the half of it. I've seen holos of a gang that attacked the tunnels... clawed to pieces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543434" id2="17" version="1065353216">These creatures may challenge your street gangs, but they're no match for the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543434" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't suffer the same fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, my lord. But those tunnels are a maze, packed with the savage beasts. Best to keep your lightsaber drawn at all times.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't mistake me for a Corellian thug. I can handle these creatures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543437" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll fare better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543438" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you will. But those tunnels are stuffed with the snarling beasts. Best not to lower your blaster in that maze.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543440" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Selonians can't shake me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543441" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's why you're the hotshot, and I'm the public servant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for the morale boost, Darbin. Exactly what I wanted to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543443" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not raising my spirits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just keeping you informed. Of course, if I was in charge of Corellia, those tunnels would've been cleared out long ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543446" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rebels are down there, collaborating with the Selonians. They're following the orders of Murthil, a vicious warrior, and the Selonians' den mother.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Her tunnels are the rebel's lifeline, moving troops and supplies beneath Coronet City. Take Murthil's lair and we'll fracture the rebellion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543449" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Selonian tunnels will soon belong to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543449" id2="17" version="1065353216">Murthil is finished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Storm the Selonian warren and deal with them. Once you're in, Imperial forces will cut off their escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543452" id2="17" version="1065353216">The more troops join me underground, the quicker the Selonians fall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543452" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could use some backup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543453" id2="17" version="1065353216">The tunnels were built to deflect an invading force. Only after you've dealt with the Selonians can our forces flank them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543455" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it must be done, I'm in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543456" id2="17" version="1065353216">March into the Selonian tunnels, cut down the rebels and deal with Murthil. Once you're in, Imperial forces will cut off their escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543458" id2="17" version="1065353216">As for you, Darbin--I require your unique perspective elsewhere. Take the first rocket tram to Axial Park. Await my orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right away, my lord. Corellia's prime minister-to-be is happy to serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Domesticate the Selonians or kill them. May the dark side guide you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543463" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's grip on Corellia is tightening. Crush the Selonians, and our victory will be that much closer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543466" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rebel weapons shipments are stopped permanently. The resistance is broken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good show. See what a little elbow grease can do, Major?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can it, Darbin. Darth Decimus will want to hear this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Smash the rebels' supplies. I'll hold the fort down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to the blitz, my lord. Darth Decimus told me you'd be gracing us with your presence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to the blitz, sir. Darth Decimus said to roll out the red carpet, but I wasn't expecting such an esteemed operative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543477" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to the blitz, hunter. Darth Decimus said we'd be receiving your services.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Decimus said you'd be coming. Welcome to the blitz.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543481" id2="17" version="1065353216">What we've got here's a cleanup operation. Factories were moving massive amounts of supplies to rebels across Corellia. Bomber brigades came in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543483" id2="17" version="1065353216">We rained fire on their heads, ripped the factories apart. We just need to beat down the rebels hiding out inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith don't bother with table scraps, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543484" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is beneath me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood, my lord. But these rebels are stubborn and armed to the teeth. Darth Decimus knew we'd need your powers to finish them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eliminating the weak hardly requires my talents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543487" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is beneath me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Noted, sir. But these rebels are far from weak. Darth Decimus knew we'd need your talents to finish them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543490" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hunt big game. Not injured rebels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543490" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is beneath me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those rebels may be hurt, but they're stubborn and well-armed. Darth Decimus knew we'd need your skills to finish 'em.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such decisiveness is exactly why the Empire will win Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543494" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm honored to serve. Unfortunately, I've had to deal with some unsavory company in the process.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing like a bombing run to crush their spirit. You're making my job easier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Much appreciated. I'll tell you, it wasn't easy considering the company I had to work with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543499" id2="17" version="1065353216">You haven't attacked them yet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543500" id2="17" version="1065353216">My boys are in the field, but the enemy's tearing them apart. Now that you're here, we can revise our attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543502" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're getting intel from an inside source. Unfortunately, his dalliances with the local women make him perpetually late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Manners, Major Tradik. We all have our vices.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543506" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry--we haven't met. I'm Darbin Sull, Corellia's top councillor, friend to the Empire. I hope the major hasn't dirtied my reputation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543507" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear you're feeding us intel on the rebels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543507" id2="17" version="1065353216">He said you're on our side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is a Corellian aiding the Empire?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are you helping us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543509" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've always been a firm supporter of the Empire. And the promise to become Corellia's prime minister didn't hurt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543511" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need someone to tell me you're a selfish, corrupt dog.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543511" id2="17" version="1065353216">You look dirty enough as is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543512" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm used to veiled insults. I suppose I appreciate the candor, but don't be so quick to judge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543514" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have friends, no... acquaintances... in the resistance. I pretend I'm sympathetic to their fight, they tell me things--like who's supplying them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Certain factories were churning out military-grade munitions, battle droids, you name it--all donated right to the resistance across the Core Worlds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543518" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's why we bombed those factories into an inferno.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not quite the subtle approach I hoped for. The bombardment trapped the rebels in the burning wreckage. Now they're angry, desperate and sitting on the largest weapons stockpile in the Core.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543522" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the rebels get those weapons functional, we may as well abandon Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543523" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll crush the rebels' hoard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave their weapons to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543524" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll burn their weapons to cinders. Then those rebel worms will be ripe for squashing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave their weapons to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543525" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll dispose of the rebels' salvage and break up their little movement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave their weapons to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543526" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rebels will be easy prey once I destroy their stockpiles.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave their weapons to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="543527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch and learn, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Corellians fight dirty. Whatever munitions they've got have downed every squad sent their way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543530" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll do better. Just wipe out their weaponry. If I know my people, they'll bow to the Empire once their hope is crushed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. I'll keep those rebels busy myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543535" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll light up this whole city to burn out the rebels.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="967550" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I must.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
