<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>107</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/companion/ewok/mq12.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094883" id2="17" version="1065353216">On behalf of the Ministry of War, I hope your mercenary serves you well. Good day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094886" id2="17" version="1065353216">A pleasure to greet you, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, hunter. Your name and reputation are known even to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Identiscan complete. Approved for maximum discretion. All records of this meeting will be deleted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings. The Empire proudly recognizes you for your efforts on its behalf.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094894" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am MQ-12, liaison to the Ministry of War's mercenary recruitment division. I find appropriate employment for talented freelance soldiers serving the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would you be interested in acquiring a combatant who achieved a perfect score on the Mekhis Aggression Index?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uncontrolled rage is useless to me. My servants must follow my orders without fail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Obedience trumps aggression.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094898" id2="17" version="1065353216">I predict you will be pleased by this one's eagerness for direction, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect aggression represents a danger to master and servant alike. Luckily, I have some experience keeping my beasts in line.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094900" id2="17" version="1065353216">It had better accept my leash.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094901" id2="17" version="1065353216">This particular individual reserves its aggression exclusively for enemies. You'll find it quite obedient, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094903" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've fried plenty of angry idiots who couldn't shoot straight. Does the merc have anything to back up that hostility?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aggression is overrated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094904" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe this individual can provide a substantial intimidation factor, in spite of its physical shortcomings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094906" id2="17" version="1065353216">The problem with soldiers for hire is that they're always open to better offers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mercenaries can be unreliable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094907" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you say, but this particular individual demonstrates remarkable commitment to honoring its contracts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094909" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never heard of this Aggression Index before. Explain it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me what that score means.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094910" id2="17" version="1065353216">The test measures an individual's psychological predisposition toward violence and effectiveness at channeling hostility during combat encounters. Perfect scores are exceedingly rare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Disposable mercenaries are the best kind. There's a good chance you'll never have to pay them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. The crazier, the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094913" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would hold credits in reserve, just to be safe. Based on its service record, this individual demonstrates remarkable resiliency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094915" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Science Bureau has classified this mercenary as a hopelessly primitive creature from an undeveloped Outer Rim system, but judged it as useful nonetheless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094917" id2="17" version="1065353216">It has served Imperial interests on Balmorra and Taris. Most recently, it proved invaluable to operations on Corellia by assassinating over fifteen enemy commanders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094918" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mercenaries exaggerate their accomplishments, but if that number is anywhere near accurate, I'd say this is someone I should meet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094918" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's impressive, if true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094919" id2="17" version="1065353216">By all accounts, the mercenary was frequently mistaken for a misshapen Drall. By the time our foes realized their error, it was too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094921" id2="17" version="1065353216">It has previously served Imperial interests on Nar Shaddaa and displayed noteworthy commitment to our cause by eliminating a dozen resistance groups on Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094922" id2="17" version="1065353216">Either this mercenary is good, or Balmorra's resistance fighters are inept. Which is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094922" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's impressive, I suppose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps both. As you will see, the individual's physical qualities can camouflage its intentions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094925" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't expect that kind of enthusiasm and devotion from a mercenary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094925" id2="17" version="1065353216">What drives this loyalty?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094926" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Science Bureau performed a thorough psychological examination before releasing it. The subject rated highly for obedience, ambition and excessive pride in its accomplishments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't expect me to be impressed. Compared to me, this mercenary is an amateur.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094928" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've killed far more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps--but an extremely promising one nevertheless. Keep an open mind, and you may be surprised.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Judge for yourself. It understands our language well enough, and will respond in its own crude fashion. The subject calls itself &quot;Treek.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094935" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor's Wrath--greatest Sith in all the stars endless. Slayer of foes many, I salute your power!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your previous employers trained you well. But there's more to serving me than showing respect. In battle, I'll require everything you have to give.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094936" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're off to a good start.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094937" id2="17" version="1065353216">I possess talents and skills many. Ask, and I will give all!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094939" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am honored. You are a mighty Sith, slayer of foes many. You have potential to rule stars and achieve victories endless!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your attitude pleases me--but what will you do to fulfill that vision of my future?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094940" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could serve me well.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094941" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have an obstacle? I will remove it. You have an ally? I will protect it. You have an enemy? I will kill it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094945" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are Darth of the Dark Council, vanquisher of foes many, wielder of powers endless! This is a great honor, mighty Sith!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094946" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your intelligence far exceeds your stature. How could I ever refuse the service of such an ardent admirer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094946" id2="17" version="1065353216">How nice of you to notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094947" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am fated to serve your will. Set a challenge before me. I will conquer it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094949" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are the Sith who rose from slavery to challenge the mighty. You will destroy foes many and achieve victories endless! You honor me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listening to you is like hearing my own internal monologue. I like it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094950" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's exactly what I think.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094951" id2="17" version="1065353216">This meeting is fate. Today, I will join you in conquering destiny.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094953" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're eager to serve. Do you know what it means to bind your fate to a Sith Lord?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094953" id2="17" version="1065353216">And what do you know of Sith?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094954" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith are the Empire's greatest warriors. Where you go, victory follows. Is there more to know? I will learn it!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094958" id2="17" version="1065353216">They say you are the greatest hunter in the galaxy. You have seized victories many, and vanquished foes endless. I salute you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094959" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're friendlier than I expected. Guess I should give you a chance to prove yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094959" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's nice to meet a fan.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094960" id2="17" version="1065353216">I seek tests and trials many. Give them to me. You will be pleased!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094962" id2="17" version="1065353216">They say you have defeated foes many, hunter. You are respected and feared. I am the same. We will achieve victories endless!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094963" id2="17" version="1065353216">One thing's for sure: Inside that furry little body, you've got the heart of a fighter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094963" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admire your spirit.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes! I was the greatest warrior of my homeworld. Now I seek greater glory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094966" id2="17" version="1065353216">No offense, but most mercenaries I've met aren't quite so... round, short and furry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094966" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you survive?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094967" id2="17" version="1065353216">They are all advantages. I am insulated, hard to hit and camouflaged. Secrets of my success.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094971" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear your name whispered in fear. They say you are a shadow who has killed foes many. I bow to your victories endless!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094972" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's most generous of you. I'm surprised you've heard so much about me. I work hard to suppress my reputation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094972" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're kind, but keep it down.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094973" id2="17" version="1065353216">A quiet hunter who stalks unseen? That is a good policy. I respect it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094975" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are top Imperial intelligence operative. Best of the best! Potential for victories many and glories endless. I salute you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094976" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't had the pleasure of encountering anyone like you before. This droid tells me you're quite talented in battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094976" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes! I have skills and edges many. I place them all at your service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094979" id2="17" version="1065353216">A deadly assassin disguised as a household pet. No wonder you've managed to kill so many.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now I understand your success.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094980" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fools many underestimate me, and do not live to regret their mistake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094982" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure what's worse, your appearance or that stupid babble you call speaking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094982" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're ridiculous.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094983" id2="17" version="1065353216">You test me with hateful words, but I pass your trial without failure. Now you can hire me without doubts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094987" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are a hero of the Empire. Foes many fear your coming. I predict victories endless in your future! I am honored to serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1094988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094989" id2="17" version="1065353216">This meeting is fated. I will waste no more time on others. I will join you.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1094991" id2="17" version="1065353216">This must be a joke.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094992" id2="17" version="1065353216">You doubt me? I searched long to find a great warrior worthy of my skills. That is you.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1094994" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're pathetic.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094995" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seek to anger me with hateful words? I stand strong and loyal. I save my anger for your enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094997" id2="17" version="1065353216">I offer you my strong arms and clear eyes. I fight for your cause and do not fail. You provide epic battles. Together, we become legends. You agree?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1094998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to my crew, Treek. Your contract with me begins immediately. Ready?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1094998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I think you're useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1094999" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was born for this moment. We go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095001" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're satisfied with glory, I'll pay well. If it's credits you want, I keep whatever I find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't expect to get rich.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095002" id2="17" version="1065353216">You negotiate fairly. I will take anything you do not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095004" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do exactly what I say from now on. Disobey me even one time, and I'll cancel your contract permanently.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Obey me, or die.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095005" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not fail now or later. You will see.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095007" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are now my chief. I wait for your order. Show me your enemies, and I will show them death.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095008" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are now my chief. I will go claim my place on your starship and wait for orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095010" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am pleased you found my offering worthwhile, my lord. I will report our success to the Ministry of War. Good day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095011" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am glad you found this transaction worth your time. The Ministry of War thanks you. Good day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings. I am MQ-12, serving the Imperial Ministry of War.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
