<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>105</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/companion/ewok/ra30.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Treek has expressed great satisfaction with you as an employer. I hope you feel the same about her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings! My client has never had the pleasure of meeting a member of the Jedi Order. Such excitement!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Salutations! My client will be excited to greet you. We have profound respect for the Republic Armed Forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, Captain! Your reputation precedes you. My client will be thrilled to meet you in person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome! Your recent accomplishments have earned my client's greatest respect. We are so very excited to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095026" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am RA-30 of Interstellar Commandos, Incorporated. I represent an especially gifted individual in the tactical security trade. Do you seek a mercenary to provide assistance with battlefield operations?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095027" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemies I face aren't your typical armed forces. I doubt your employer is trained to fight Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095027" id2="17" version="1065353216">My work isn't for mercenaries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095028" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can assure you this person has never been the least bit intimidated by any combatant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095030" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fear a mercenary might grow restless working for me. Most of my journeys are spent in pursuit of knowledge and understanding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095030" id2="17" version="1065353216">I seek wisdom before violence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095031" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are too modest! The objectives you seek are frequently surrounded by horrible dangers. My employer appreciates that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095033" id2="17" version="1065353216">The soldiers under my command are the best of the best--and they wear a Havoc Squad uniform.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095033" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people serve the military.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course! However, Provision 878-BCM of the Military Defense Act permits Republic commanders to subcontract licensed combat specialists such as my employer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095036" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you've got me confused with someone else. I conduct legitimate business. Also, I'm allergic to blasters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095036" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just an honest captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your gifts for understatement and misdirection are well-known, Captain. Rest assured, my employer maintains the greatest discretion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095039" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need a sales pitch. Just introduce me to this mercenary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where is your client?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rest assured, my employer is en route. In the meantime, I am instructed to provide a proper introduction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095042" id2="17" version="1065353216">If by &quot;assistance,&quot; you mean &quot;someone to draw enemy fire away from me,&quot; then yes--I'm always hiring.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cannon fodder is useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095043" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am confident my employer can survive anything you require.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095045" id2="17" version="1065353216">I warn you in advance, there are some who find this mercenary's physical appearance unusual. However, great warriors come in all shapes and sizes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095047" id2="17" version="1065353216">My client has fought on Taris, Nar Shaddaa and Balmorra. Most recently, she defended the Corellian Engineering Corporation's primary shipyard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095048" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was on Corellia. The fighting was intense. This mercenary must be good to have survived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095048" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not merely survived--successfully fought off a platoon of determined Imperial soldiers. The CEC compensated her well for that service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095051" id2="17" version="1065353216">My client has fought on Taris, Nar Shaddaa and Ord Mantell. Most recently, she guarded commercial freighter convoys against pirate boarding parties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095052" id2="17" version="1065353216">This mercenary must be good. Close-quarters fighting aboard starships isn't easy. One stray shot can decompress an entire vessel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095052" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095053" id2="17" version="1065353216">A fact my employer took advantage of with great success. Many pirates found themselves in hard vacuum that day. The convoy owner was pleased.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095055" id2="17" version="1065353216">This mercenary doesn't have any shortage of employers. I'm sure corporations pay more than I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095055" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't afford to pay much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095056" id2="17" version="1065353216">Simply put, corporate work can be rather dull. You, on the other hand, are involved in exciting endeavors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like this mercenary doesn't lack for a guaranteed salary. My crew works for a commission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095058" id2="17" version="1065353216">I only offer irregular pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095059" id2="17" version="1065353216">My employer is prepared to accept your terms. She is willing to trade a certain amount of security for excitement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095061" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're obviously programmed to make this mercenary sound impressive. It's not working.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spare me the bragging.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095062" id2="17" version="1065353216">How unfortunate. I will have to install an upgraded sales negotiation module.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, here she is now! Allow me to introduce Treek. She has journeyed all the way from an exotic Outer Rim system in search of adventure and purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great Jedi warrior, vanquisher of Sith many and wielder of mighty hummacutter... I salute your legendary victories endless!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095069" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're very kind, but I didn't achieve those victories alone. One of my strongest allies is a droid about the same size as you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to meet a new friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Size provides advantages many on the battlefield. The big enemy always underestimates me and regrets it!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095072" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear rumors of a brave Jedi, vanquishing foes many and wielding a mighty hummacutter. I welcome your promise of victories endless!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095073" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure where you heard all that, but thank you for the vote of confidence. You're the most enthusiastic mercenary I've ever met.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks. It's nice meeting you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095074" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admire a strong warrior of bold cause and great potential. You are one worth serving.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095078" id2="17" version="1065353216">Brave Jedi explorer, seeker of mysteries many, wielder of mighty hummacutter... I stand ready to defend you from enemies endless!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095079" id2="17" version="1065353216">You honor me, Treek. From what this droid says, you're something of an explorer and seeker as well. Perhaps we're meant to journey together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095079" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm pleased to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095080" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was a great pathfinder on my homeworld. I wandered far, conquered challenges many. I seek a new horizon with you, bold Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095082" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are the bold new Jedi explorer, the challenger of mysteries many. You stand with hummacutter held ready. I will stand with you against foes endless!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, there. Considering we've only just met, you're quite committed to forming a partnership.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095083" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a generous greeting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095084" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see potentials many in you. I seek a legendary journey with an ally worthy of my skill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095086" id2="17" version="1065353216">That word you used... were you referring to my lightsaber?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095086" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is a &quot;hummacutter&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes! Hummacutter sounds better. Powerful weapon of a mighty noise. I respect your skill with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095091" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great leader of the mighty Havoc Squad, veteran of battlefields many and destroyer of Imperials endless... I salute your valor!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095092" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't report to me just yet. No need to start polishing my boots.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095092" id2="17" version="1065353216">At ease.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095093" id2="17" version="1065353216">I charge extra to polish things. It is not my specialty. I am a warrior and seeker of great challenges.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095095" id2="17" version="1065353216">Brave Republic soldier, veteran of Ord Mantell's battlefields many and destroyer of separatists endless like me... I salute your potential for greatness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095096" id2="17" version="1065353216">I figured I met everyone worth knowing on Ord Mantell. How'd I miss you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095096" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised we've never met.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095097" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fought for the government and ran night raids on separatist camps. I was always quiet and unseen. Good policy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095101" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are the mighty outlaw captain, plunderer of riches many and conqueror of enemies endless. You honor me, Voidwolf vanquisher!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095102" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care what other people say--you're alright in my book. Please, continue with your praise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095102" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like you already.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095103" id2="17" version="1065353216">This meeting was fated. You are the one I seek to serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095105" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have earned a reputation I respect, Captain. Sources many say you are a mercenary with potential endless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095106" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to hear people say good things about me. Wish I could say I've heard of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095106" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to meet you, short stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095107" id2="17" version="1065353216">My reputation is excellent. Employers many have great satisfaction with my service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095109" id2="17" version="1065353216">No offense, but you don't seem cut out for my line of work. Do you even know how to shoot a blaster?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095109" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure about this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095110" id2="17" version="1065353216">I defeat foes many, and blasters do not save them. There are advantages endless in being a small angry target. Do not doubt me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095112" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can barely translate what's coming out of your mouth. Who taught you how to communicate?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095112" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sound ridiculous.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095113" id2="17" version="1065353216">I speak well. Besides, no need for talking when fighting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095117" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are a great Republic hero! We have both defeated foes many. Together, we will conquer challenges endless!</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1095118" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095119" id2="17" version="1065353216">I seek to join one destined for greatness, like me. You are that person.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1095121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this a practical joke?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095122" id2="17" version="1065353216">You doubt my skills? Do not. I have achieved greatness.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1095124" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me guess: You're nuts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095125" id2="17" version="1065353216">My mind is sharper than any blade. It is my greatest weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095127" id2="17" version="1065353216">I offer simple terms. I provide clear eyes and strong arms. I fight for you. Together we will have even greater victories! You agree?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095128" id2="17" version="1065353216">Treek, I look forward to having you at my side. You'll be fairly compensated for whatever trouble comes our way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095128" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm happy to have you aboard.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095129" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let us seek danger. We go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095131" id2="17" version="1065353216">We haven't discussed your price yet, but I get the idea you're flexible on the amount. Welcome to my team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095131" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll work out your fee.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095132" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not worry, my payment takes care of itself. Enemies offer the promise of good looting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095134" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I've heard so far is a lot of bluster and crazy talk. Show me you can hold your own, and I'll think about paying you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095134" id2="17" version="1065353216">Offer me a free trial.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095135" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will see. Enemies many will fall, cut down by my skills.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095137" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are now my chief. Call, and I will fight for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095138" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are now my chief. I will take my gear to your starship and wait for your orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095140" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am ever so pleased you found my client satisfactory. I wish you both good fortune in your future endeavors. Good day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095143" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am RA-30 with Interstellar Commandos, Incorporated. Have a safe day!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
