<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>281</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/companion/ewok/treekimp.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095145" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume you've settled in?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095146" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope we make space journeys many, Chief. I love the boom of engines, the screech of hyperspace. Good noises. Legendary sounds.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095148" id2="17" version="1065353216">My homeworld has no starships. My people live in the trees, close to the sky, but the stars endless remain out of reach always.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095150" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am alone among my people. No other has flown a starship. That is how I left my homeworld and came here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095151" id2="17" version="1065353216">You flew a starship by yourself? How did you even get ahold of one if your homeworld doesn't have any?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095151" id2="17" version="1065353216">What an impressive feat.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095152" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was not easy, but it is a good tale. I will tell you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095154" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know anything about your homeworld or its people. What are they like?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095154" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about your people.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095155" id2="17" version="1065353216">Home is beautiful. There are mountains few and trees endless. My people are peaceful gatherers, weavers and builders. I had to leave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095157" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fly a starship? You can barely dress yourself. How did you reach the control panel--by sitting on a box?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095157" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't make me laugh.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, exactly--cargo box. Good guess.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095160" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still remember seeing the starship. It roared like a Gorax in the sky, trailing smoke and flame. I followed. It was my fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095162" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found the crew fixing their broken starship. I offered help, but they shot at me and laughed. After nights many, I finally killed them all and claimed their starship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your foes deserved nothing less than death. Your only mistake was offering them help in the first place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095163" id2="17" version="1065353216">I approve. Never show mercy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now I only help when I am paid. It is a good policy--easy to remember.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095166" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. They earned their fates. There's no excuse for rudeness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095166" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was the right thing to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095167" id2="17" version="1065353216">The shooting did not bother me, but the laughing was too far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done. Patience and cunning are virtues in my line of work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095169" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admire your tenacity.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095170" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hunted foes many on my homeworld. No kills made me happier than these.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095172" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have the same approach to solving problems. The only difference is, I would have wiped them out much faster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095172" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would have done the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Traps and lures are slow to build. I learned from that experience. Now, I rush in and overwhelm foes quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095175" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you wiped out the whole crew, who was left to repair the vessel so you could leave?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095175" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you fix the ship?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095176" id2="17" version="1065353216">You hunted down the entire crew over several nights? I bet those final logs were great. &quot;The furry thing--it's coming for us again!&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095176" id2="17" version="1065353216">You killed them? Hilarious!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095177" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, they sounded just like that! Do you know this tale already?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095179" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ship droid was smart. It surrendered, finished repairs, and taught me the controls. Then I flew into space! Zoom to fate!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095181" id2="17" version="1065353216">I landed on a world of terrible smells endless. They call it Nar Shaddaa. I found strong allies and Imperial jobs many to attack Republic targets. Good days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095182" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those friends of yours--who were they? Why did they attack Republic targets on Nar Shaddaa?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095182" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about these allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095183" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clan Ordo--Mandalorian warriors. They gave me food, taught me fighting, and let me charge into battle ahead of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since you aren't flying around the galaxy on your own, I assume you lost that starship you captured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you still have that ship?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095186" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, my transport is long gone after a crash. But it served its purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095188" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nar Shaddaa eats little things like you alive. You're lucky you didn't wind up a slave--or worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095188" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm amazed you survived.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095189" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Nikto slaver put a shock collar on me. Big mistake. He regretted it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095191" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fate brought the starship and Nar Shaddaa to me. Now, fate brings you and your mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095193" id2="17" version="1065353216">On my homeworld, I am a legend. But now, my tale spreads to the stars. We go, Chief!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095197" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's on your mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095198" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have made a choice. I will not seek a new chief. There is none better than you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095200" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am only sorry I cannot serve you to your final breath. Your people live seasons many more than mine. But I will fight for you to my last day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095201" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have served me well, and will continue to do so until our time together ends. That is all I can ask of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095201" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are a valued ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095202" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not worry, Chief. I will not leave your side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095204" id2="17" version="1065353216">What will I do when you're gone, Treek? You're one of my only allies I can truly trust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095204" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will miss you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095205" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are fated for greatness. There will be others who serve you with loyalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095207" id2="17" version="1065353216">None of us knows how long we've got. That's what makes life interesting--and well worth fighting for. Have fun while it lasts, Treek.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095207" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until then, we'll fight hard.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095208" id2="17" version="1065353216">You understand. This is why we seek challenges every day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095210" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may be the most earnest and open-hearted operative in my employ. Your commitment and honesty will be irreplaceable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095210" id2="17" version="1065353216">I value your loyalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095211" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you will remember me? That brings relief.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095213" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many years do members of your species usually live?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095213" id2="17" version="1065353216">How long do you have?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095214" id2="17" version="1065353216">I cannot say with truth. We do not count time like you. Your people live seasons many. Mine only live seasons few.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095216" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody expects their pets to outlive them. I'll make arrangements to replace you when the time comes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095216" id2="17" version="1065353216">No great loss for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095217" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you will remember me, and hold the replacement to my standard?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095219" id2="17" version="1065353216">We still have time for great things many. Foes will fall, and we will make legendary tales together. I hope they last.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095221" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not know what will become of my name after I am gone. Without someone to recite my victories many, the memories many will fade. I will be forgotten.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095222" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can keep your name alive forever. Everything you've ever done can be stored on the HoloNet as data. I'll show you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095222" id2="17" version="1065353216">Put it on the HoloNet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095223" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is much on your HoloNet that no one appreciates. We must set reminders for everyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095225" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teach me how to recite your tale, and I'll teach it to others. No one will forget you, I promise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095225" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep your legend alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095226" id2="17" version="1065353216">You would do this for me? I am honored endless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095228" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing lasts forever, and everything dies--even our names. There's no point resisting it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095228" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's life. Get used to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095229" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith build monuments many to their legends. I ask only for songs.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095231" id2="17" version="1065353216">You celebrate your Great Hunt winners. What I ask is no different.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095233" id2="17" version="1065353216">You choose to fade away, Chief. I would choose tribute.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095235" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I am gone, all that is mine becomes yours. Give those things to those who follow me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095237" id2="17" version="1065353216">My fate is sealed. I have regrets none. We go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095241" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wanted to speak?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095242" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must pay you proper respect, Chief. You are a great warrior--maybe the greatest ever. I have seen it times endless.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095244" id2="17" version="1065353216">You fear nothing. You sweep away all enemies in your path with powers many. If I had your Force, victories endless I would have!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095245" id2="17" version="1065353216">You would be a good apprentice. I would teach you to focus your rage into a weapon, and burn away your compassion for others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095245" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would train you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095246" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is good advice, Chief. I will work on those tasks and hope the power comes to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095248" id2="17" version="1065353216">You, wielding the Force? The expressions of terrified incredulity alone would be worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095248" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would enjoy seeing that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095249" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would be your greatest apprentice, Chief. That is certain.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095251" id2="17" version="1065353216">You surprise your enemies with tricks many. By the time your foes know what you have done, they are dead. I need more devices like yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095252" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't need a bag of tricks. I'm pretty sure the Empire already has you registered as a living superweapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095252" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you're tough enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095253" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think so, Chief? That makes me happy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095255" id2="17" version="1065353216">People like me can do their jobs because people like you attract all the attention. I wouldn't have it any other way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095255" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the perfect partner.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095256" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am glad you find me useful, Chief. I will remember to be louder in battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't try to be more than what you are. When I have complaints with your efforts, you'll know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stick to what you know.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095259" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have seen you express disappointment with others many. I will not wind up like them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095261" id2="17" version="1065353216">No matter how good you get, I will always be better. Never forget that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095261" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll never outshine me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course! You are chief. If I were better than you, I would be chief. That would be wrong. Things are better this way.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095264" id2="17" version="1065353216">This war is not like anything on my homeworld. When the people fight, it is for food or good land. Small battles, simple goals.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095266" id2="17" version="1065353216">My homeworld's fights end quickly and are forgotten, but here, they are battles endless. Do you think the Empire will take mercy on the Republic and offer peace?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095267" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith will only accept the Republic's unconditional surrender. They still owe us a few millennia of slavery for what they did to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095267" id2="17" version="1065353216">There will be no mercy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095268" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not think the Republic people wish to pay that debt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095270" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is led by Jedi fools who will never submit to Sith authority. They'll fight to the death, and we'll be forced to give it to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi won't give us the choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe the Republic people will kill the Jedi in self-defense? It could happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095273" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's not much work for hunters in peacetime. What am I supposed to do, chase down idiot smugglers all day long? Pass.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095273" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope not.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095274" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, keep the war going? Do not fight too hard and win, but also do not offer peace. Good policy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095276" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't about forcing a surrender, or peaceful coexistence. My people will not stop until every system in the Republic flies an Imperial banner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095276" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll erase the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095277" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is a big job. The Republic has systems endless. We should be working, not talking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never say never. The Empire signed a treaty with the Republic before. It could happen again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095279" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope peace is an option.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095280" id2="17" version="1065353216">This makes me wonder what we do when there is peace and no one left to fight. Find another galaxy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095282" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mercy? Peace? I knew you were a primitive little savage, but I thought you might have learned something by now. Never ask that again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095282" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a fool for even asking.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095283" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will obey. No peace, no mercy--ever.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095285" id2="17" version="1065353216">I learn what it means to be a warrior from you, Chief. You are a great teacher, and I will join you in victory. We go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095289" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something is bothering you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095290" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I said I did not miss my homeworld, I was wrong. I miss the food.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095292" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have found no meal here that compares to caranak legs roasted over an open fire. My stomach rumbles just remembering them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095294" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have been curious to try the fish-head people. You call them Nautolans? I have not found one unspoiled. Maybe someday....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095295" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even the Empire frowns on making a meal out of something that can form a complete sentence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095295" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't eat other sapients.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095296" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will not consume my body after I am dead? But I am not your people. There is no shame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095298" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't realize you ate your victims. How many intelligent species have you eaten?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095298" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you eat all your kills?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095299" id2="17" version="1065353216">In your space? None yet. My people do not believe in wasting what nature provides us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095301" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're that eager, we can always go hunting for a Nautolan. The Republic is full of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095301" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd be willing to get you one.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095302" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have important work. The right meal comes, in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095304" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I find good unspoiled Nautolan--or maybe Rodian--I will make a stew.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095305" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will not make a stew out of another intelligent being--especially not aboard my ship. Do you understand me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095305" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are forbidden to do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Resources many are scarce in this war. What if the food runs out? But you are chief, and I obey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095308" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your barks and growls don't translate sarcasm very well. If this is a prank, you'd better say so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095308" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this a practical joke?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095309" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not joke about food. I have gone hungry too often.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095310" id2="17" version="1065353216">xxx</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095311" id2="17" version="1065353216">I highly recommend proper seasoning. Some meats can be a bit gamey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095311" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use plenty of spices.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095312" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer natural flavor. Cooks here use too much salt. It is all I can taste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095313" id2="17" version="1065353216">xxx</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095314" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not like to fight with an empty belly. How do you nourish your body for battle?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095315" id2="17" version="1065353216">I only feed on what I take from my enemies--and I am always hungry for more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spoils of victory feed me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095316" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am the same. It is wasteful to leave an enemy on the battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095318" id2="17" version="1065353216">A steady diet of my enemies' tears are quite sufficient to keep me satisfied.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095318" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fear and terror feed me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095319" id2="17" version="1065353216">You eat only liquids? How did you grow so big on that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095321" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you wear this much armor, you need lots of muscle to keep moving. I get protein however I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095321" id2="17" version="1065353216">Proteins keep me strong.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095322" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am the same. Plants do not satisfy my hunger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095324" id2="17" version="1065353216">In my line of work, one cannot afford to be too picky. I was trained to be omnivorous to ensure my survival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095324" id2="17" version="1065353216">Survival is my top priority.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095325" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is a good policy. I see why you are so strong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095327" id2="17" version="1065353216">I eat food that was grown in light, water and soil--not slaughtered beasts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095327" id2="17" version="1065353216">I eat only vegetables.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only vegetables? How do you grow so big?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095330" id2="17" version="1065353216">It doesn't matter. After this conversation, I have no plans to eat anything that was prepared by you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095330" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't cook for me, ever.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095331" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am sorry for you, Chief. After living so long alone, I am a great cook.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too much talk about food makes me hungry. I will feel better after a good fight. We go?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you want to talk?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095338" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have good journeys, Chief. Rewards many, battles endless. I do not miss my old homeworld. It had nothing left for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095340" id2="17" version="1065353216">My tribe's people are soft and cowardly. They have no spirit. They feared me for being strong. I was not welcome in my village.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095341" id2="17" version="1065353216">They didn't appreciate what makes you special, Treek--but I do. You've found your place in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095341" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're welcome with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095342" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are right. I am happiest here, Chief.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095344" id2="17" version="1065353216">When people are afraid, you're doing something right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095344" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is good to be feared.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095345" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095347" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're an outcast. Get used to it and stop whining.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't ask me to cry for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095348" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am not whining--I am grateful! I do not want to be welcome. Better to be feared.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095350" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are a great hunter and respected warrior. Even the Sith fear you. I have seen it in their little yellow eyes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095352" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your Empire is a tribe of great warriors. You conquer all things in your path. The Republic will not stand against you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095354" id2="17" version="1065353216">I walked my homeworld for seasons many hunting my path to the stars. During the journey, I dreamed of an eternal warrior surrounded by fire. I think that was you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095355" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am a master of the Force, and everyone senses my power--even you on that distant world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095355" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I have a destiny.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095356" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thank fate for leading me to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095358" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who am I to argue with your dreams? Let's just hope those flames were my enemies burning and not me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095358" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything is possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095359" id2="17" version="1065353216">No foe can break your armor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting. Remind me to have you tested for Force sensitivity--and psychosis, while we're at it. Nothing wrong with covering every possibility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095361" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're precognitive, or crazy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095362" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am not crazy. My dreams are true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095364" id2="17" version="1065353216">An eternal warrior surrounded by flames? That could be good or bad, depending on the context. Did you have any other dreams?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095364" id2="17" version="1065353216">What else did you see?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095365" id2="17" version="1065353216">No dreams I remember but that one. But do not fear. It was good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095367" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was only a dream. You probably ate some bad tree bark and had a nightmare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095367" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't take you seriously.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095368" id2="17" version="1065353216">I ate smoked bordok, dried geejaw wings and hakamat berries. No nightmares. My dreams were true.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095370" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have had no better chief in my life. With you, I will conquer worlds and crush foes endless! Our legends will never fade!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095371" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you feel that way, because we're not running out of battles to fight any time soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095371" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate your enthusiasm.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095372" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am ready to fight--always and forever!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095374" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can always count on you to cheer me up. Maybe I should make you my morale officer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095374" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a good friend, Treek.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095375" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would honor you with praise for no extra fee.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095377" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know what they say about great legends... they all end with a heroic death. Are you prepared for that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095377" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just be ready to die for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095378" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. I think about my legendary death always. I would like to go while destroying Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095380" id2="17" version="1065353216">These words make me hunger for a new fight. Lead me, Chief. We go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095384" id2="17" version="1065353216">You look cheerful today.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095385" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are a good chief. We go to exciting planets and destroy interesting enemies many. This is a happy life.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095387" id2="17" version="1065353216">My homeworld chief told me to stay in our village. I would cook and raise children like the other women. Instead, I left and walked across my planet. Legendary journey!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095388" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your leader sensed you were special and feared your power. You are destined for better things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095388" id2="17" version="1065353216">You showed great strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095389" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew that truth even then. I do not regret my choice to leave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never let anyone tell you who you are or what you can be. We make our own destinies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always choose your own path.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095392" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes! You understand. The chief called me crazy as a geejaw. I knew better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095394" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good for you. People like us don't sit around cooking for ungrateful little womp rats. You're a natural-born hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095394" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made the right move.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes! My old chief saw only a woman. He had no vision.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Embarked on a bit of intelligence-gathering? Good for you--knowledge is power. Did you find anything interesting?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095397" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did the right thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095398" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. I found my true self.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095400" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assumed underneath all that fur, you were a man. Are you actually female?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, you're female?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095401" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I am female! How do you not notice this? I am highly attractive! Tribal men endless pursued my favor, but I wanted more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095403" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure someone finds your life story fascinating. You should go find that person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095403" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm already bored.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095404" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did not let me finish. The walk was only the beginning!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095406" id2="17" version="1065353216">My journey lasted seasons many. I saw my homeworld's wonders: Blurrg's Isle, the Desert of Salma, Lake Greetac. I hunted terrible beasts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095408" id2="17" version="1065353216">I warred with a Dulok tribe in the Sagreb Swamps. They regretted challenging me. I claimed Dulok ears for my necklace!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095409" id2="17" version="1065353216">You took on a whole enemy tribe alone... and won? How did this happen?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about this war.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Duloks accused me of trespassing. They sent warriors to skin me. Big mistake. Duloks are tall, but thin. Their legs break easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095412" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's a Dulok?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095412" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dulok?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095413" id2="17" version="1065353216">They are scaly, bony lizards. They have big ears and small brains. My homeworld does not miss their kind when they die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dulok ears, hmm? That's one trophy I'd like to see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show me the necklace.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095416" id2="17" version="1065353216">I lost my necklace on Nar Shaddaa. A vrblther ate it. I took the vrblther's ears as a replacement. They are not as good.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095418" id2="17" version="1065353216">My homeworld journeys left a mark that will not be forgotten. That is why I stay with the Empire. It understands why legacies matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everywhere I look on Dromund Kaas, I see great monuments many. What mark will you leave behind when your end finally comes?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095421" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will hunt down every Jedi in the galaxy until I've choked the life from the last pitiful member of their order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095421" id2="17" version="1065353216">I plan to destroy the Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095422" id2="17" version="1065353216">To wipe out a chosen foe endless... this I will see done!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095424" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be remembered as the greatest Emperor ever to rule the Sith. That'll do nicely, don't you agree?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095424" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will be the most powerful.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095425" id2="17" version="1065353216">That... is legendary. I am proud you are my chief.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095427" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I do my job right, no other hunter will rack up as many bounties as me. That's legacy enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095427" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll always hold the record.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095428" id2="17" version="1065353216">A trophy no other can possess, but will always be pursued? Yes!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095430" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's in the nature of my work to cover my tracks. I'll leave a mark--but it shall be anonymous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095430" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll remain an enigma.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095431" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is unfair. You are a great hero. Others should know it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095433" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need a monument. If I can leave the galaxy a better place for having been here, that's enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095433" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galaxy will be improved.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095434" id2="17" version="1065353216">The best way to keep a legend alive is to make it a happy tale? That is a good policy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095436" id2="17" version="1065353216">The best way to make sure no one forgets you is to stay alive. If there's any way to cheat death, I'll find it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095436" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I just won't die?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095437" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you do not die, your legend has no end. It is incomplete forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095439" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will create a song to honor your deeds. If you should ever fall, know that I will sing your legend to all who will hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095441" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was a good talk, but it is time for more deeds. We go!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095444" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will talk on the starship when you are ready, Chief.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095447" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will show your foes what a legend is, Chief.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095448" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire will conquer to glory. I am happy to join it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095449" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every journey with you leads to great rewards many.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095450" id2="17" version="1065353216">To hunt, to conquer, to yield never... this is why I live.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095451" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have come far since my homeworld. I will go even farther.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095452" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no better chief than you anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Today I woke hungry for challenges. Lead me to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Foes many underestimate me. I make them regret their mistake.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095455" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where you leave, fear remains. That is a good policy. The survivors will remember.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095456" id2="17" version="1065353216">I make songs of our journeys. The language is harsh--not easy to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095457" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no greater happiness than knowing I have fought well and conquered all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095458" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is always an honor to follow you into battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your foes are endless, but so is my thirst for great battles.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095460" id2="17" version="1065353216">You lead, Chief. I go where you say.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095461" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this war takes me to the stars endless, it is always worth fighting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095462" id2="17" version="1065353216">My tribe would not understand our tales, Chief. They are too legendary.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
