<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>292</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/companion/ewok/treekrep.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095572" id2="17" version="1065353216">How are you settling in, Treek?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095573" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have work for me on planets many, Chief? I hope so. I love space travel. Engines booming, hyperspace screeching... these are legendary sounds.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095575" id2="17" version="1065353216">My home has no starships. My people live high above the ground, close to the sky. But the stars endless? They never reach them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095577" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am the only one of my people to be a fearless explorer. I flew a starship to come here. True tale.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095578" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you learn to fly a starship if there weren't any on your homeworld?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me your story.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095579" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fate always brings a way to the bold. You know this well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095581" id2="17" version="1065353216">You left behind everything to see the galaxy. Do you ever miss your people?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095581" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must feel lonely.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095582" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am not like my people. They are quiet, peaceful, and they do not leave home. There is nothing to miss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095584" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think of you as a fearless explorer. You're more like an angry little furball of destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now you fight for a living.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fighting is always better when one explores. How else do we find greater foes?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095587" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remember hearing a mighty starship roaring like an angry Gorax in the sky on my homeworld. I followed the smoke and fire to find my fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095589" id2="17" version="1065353216">The crew did not survive, but their droid did. It fixed the starship and taught me the controls. The engines set the forest on fire, but I zoomed into space!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095590" id2="17" version="1065353216">You had no way of knowing if that ship would hold together. That was quite a leap of faith, Treek.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095590" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were very brave.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095591" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had already conquered challenges many on my homeworld. I had to leave or die trying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095593" id2="17" version="1065353216">A forest fire could have caused tremendous damage. I hope you warned others of the danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095593" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope your people were safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095594" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are fires endless on my homeworld. It is the way of nature. My people are always ready to move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talk about a &quot;scorched ground&quot; policy. I can't believe you survived that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you ever lucky.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095597" id2="17" version="1065353216">The starship was sturdy and my reflexes fast. I had no worries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095599" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds like the first time I flew. Come to think of it, I still can't show my face on that planet....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095599" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and I are a lot alike.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095600" id2="17" version="1065353216">One world is nothing to our kind. The galaxy has stars endless to explore--more than we can ever see!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095602" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people who died on that ship probably had families who'd want to know what happened. Did you tell anyone about them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095602" id2="17" version="1065353216">You just abandoned the dead?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095603" id2="17" version="1065353216">There was nothing to be done. I never learned their names, and I lost the droid and starship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095605" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't take this the wrong way, but you're never allowed on the bridge of any starship we're aboard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095605" id2="17" version="1065353216">Traveling with you is risky.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not worry, I fly much straighter now. I took lessons many from that first journey.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095608" id2="17" version="1065353216">The starship flew me to Nar Shaddaa, a place of terrible smells endless. A stupid other captain collided with me, and my starship crashed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Angry prisoners many surrounded my escape pod. I fought through them and their Shadow Town. That was the first of Nar Shaddaa's great battles!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095611" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's more adventure than most people see in a whole lifetime, and you're only getting started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095611" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is quite a tale.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095612" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was a legend on my homeworld. Now that I am with you, I will be a legend in the stars endless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095614" id2="17" version="1065353216">The next time I'm fighting through Nar Shaddaa, I'll remember to take you along.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a dangerous place.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095615" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will be your best guide. My first advice is to always keep your weapon ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095617" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've met the Empire's prisoners on Nar Shaddaa. You're lucky you got out alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095617" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remember Shadow Town.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not lucky. I am a warrior of skills many, Chief!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me get this straight... you captured a crashed starship, set a forest on fire, had a midair collision, and started a prison riot? And now you work for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095620" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're nothing but trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095621" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on me. I survive everything!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095623" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found fighting jobs many on Nar Shaddaa. It was good work, and brought me to your Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095625" id2="17" version="1065353216">My tale led to you. Our meeting was fate. Now, our legends continue together. We go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095629" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is it, Treek?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095630" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish I had found you sooner. You are my best possible fate. I will not serve another chief in my life.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095632" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will live seasons many. I will not. That is... how would you say it... biology? But it does not matter. I will fight for you to my final breath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095633" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's more to life than fighting this war. The Jedi will restore order to the galaxy--and when we do, you'll have something worth living for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095633" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you experience peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095634" id2="17" version="1065353216">I already have purpose. I wake each day ready for a challenge--and you provide it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095636" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you die of old age still fighting this war, I will have utterly failed you as a Jedi and a friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095636" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would be a sad end.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095637" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, not true! You give me purpose, Chief.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095639" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't want you going down swinging. What good's a war if you can't win it and spend the rest of your life savoring the victory?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope for a better end.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Savoring is for those who do not enjoy what they do. I live to challenge fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095642" id2="17" version="1065353216">This war better be over long before either of us gets old. I've got retirement plans, and you should too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095642" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope we both retire happy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095643" id2="17" version="1065353216">This retirement idea is strange to me. I am good at battle--why would I stop?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095645" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't understand. How do you know you won't outlive me? Do you have an illness?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain what you mean.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095646" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lives are like campfires. Some burn long, others not. My people's fires burn shorter than yours. It is biology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095648" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't know when you're going to die, or how. Stop being morbid and enjoy life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095648" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be so melodramatic.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095649" id2="17" version="1065353216">You misunderstand. I welcome that fate. It is a good death for a warrior.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095651" id2="17" version="1065353216">My end is of no concern, only what comes after. Who will remember my name? Who will sing my legends many?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095653" id2="17" version="1065353216">I ask too much, but when the day comes... will you return my body to my tribe? Will you tell them my deeds so I am not forgotten?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095654" id2="17" version="1065353216">When this war is over, we'll visit your homeworld and find your tribe. You can tell your people all about our adventures, and I'll be there to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095654" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll tell the tribe together.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095655" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people will not understand... but maybe they will remember. It is worth trying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095657" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a better idea. I'll show you how to record all your life experiences and preserve them forever on the HoloNet. Everyone will know you, not just your tribe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095657" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm teaching you the HoloNet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095658" id2="17" version="1065353216">You talk of museums and libraries--places where names go to die. Promise mine will live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget about your tribe. You don't need them. If you want to be remembered, do something so big the galaxy will never forget it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go out in a blaze of glory.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095661" id2="17" version="1065353216">A final legendary feat to beat all others? Yes. That is a good policy. You will help me, I know.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095663" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I am gone, I will not need my gear. It is good and useful. Take it for the one who comes after me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095665" id2="17" version="1065353216">I feel at peace. Your enemies should not. They deserve a crushing. We go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095669" id2="17" version="1065353216">How are you doing?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095670" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believed I knew how to fight, but you showed me I am incomplete. Because of you, I learn new moves many. You are a great teacher, Chief.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095672" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ways endless you sweep through foes with your hummacutter are legendary. I wish I had your Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095673" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force makes me strong but not all-powerful. I know plenty of skilled fighters who accomplish great things armed only with a will to succeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095673" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force is only a tool.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095674" id2="17" version="1065353216">True, but imagine me with my own hummacutter! The things I could do to your foes....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095676" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is more to mastering the Force than knowing how to use it. You would have much to learn. It's a way of life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095676" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is a big responsibility.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095677" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am a good learner, Chief. I would be the greatest Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095679" id2="17" version="1065353216">You crush your foes before they even get close. You have weapons endless, flashing and booming. I think I am too simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095680" id2="17" version="1065353216">Simple is good. Too many soldiers get in over their heads trying fancy maneuvers. I can always rely on you to handle any problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095680" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you're one of my best.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095681" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am proud to obey your commands anytime.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095683" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's my job to dazzle. When I need someone to deliver a brutally effective beatdown, you're the first person I call. Never change, my friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095683" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like your style.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095684" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you are happy, I am happy--but I will keep learning new ways to hurt your foes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095686" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're doing fine, Treek. I don't have any complaints with your performance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095686" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're holding your own.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095687" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your respect means much. I take pride in serving you better than all your other allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Want some free advice? Charging at the enemy and howling at the top of your lungs is not a sound combat tactic. Think strategically.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fight smarter, not harder.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095690" id2="17" version="1065353216">Running in frenzy is always surprising to foes. Strategy can be predictable, but I will think about a new one.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095692" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your war is not like any on my homeworld. We battle over food and territory, not beliefs. When we have victory, we stop fighting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095694" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire fights without end. It battles to destroy all others. Will your Republic do the same? If not, we may be on the losing side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095695" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no Empire, Treek--only people serving the wrong cause. They can serve peace just as easily. When they do, we'll gladly end this war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095695" id2="17" version="1065353216">Peace is always possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095696" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have seen Imperial space? It is not peaceful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095698" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we've learned anything from the Sith Order's continued survival, it's that it is impossible to eradicate an enemy. We achieve a lasting victory only through peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Peace is our goal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095699" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think the Sith do not agree. We will see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095701" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire is smart enough to know when it's beaten. The Imperials will give up--we just need to give them a good reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095701" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire will surrender.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095702" id2="17" version="1065353216">When they surrender, take their weapons endless. Trust me, it is a good policy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095704" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's expensive to wipe out all your enemies. The Imperials will run out of ammo long before they get around to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095704" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire knows when to quit.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095705" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have an escape plan? That is good, mostly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even if the Empire takes over the galaxy, that doesn't mean they'll get us. We'll always find a way out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095707" id2="17" version="1065353216">I plan to survive regardless.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095708" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree. We would hunt the enemy from the shadows, just like back home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surrender is not an option--for us or them. I don't plan to stop fighting until there's no one left in this galaxy to fight back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095710" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll kill everyone, period.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095711" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is a good policy. I respect it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095713" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will fight for you to the end, Chief. Win or lose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095717" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have something to tell me?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095718" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must confess to you. I have a... what do you call it... hobby? I conquer enemies when you are at rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because we are legends together, my reputation grows. I have admirers many: Hutt Cartel, Exchange, even the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095722" id2="17" version="1065353216">They offer rewards endless to join them and betray your trust. They ask me to kill you in your sleep.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since I haven't woken up with a vibroblade stuck in me, I'm guessing you haven't accepted their offers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095723" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume you tell them &quot;no.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095724" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are my chief. I serve no other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095726" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said something about this being your hobby. How is this fun?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain how this is amusing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095727" id2="17" version="1065353216">These fools are stupid, like tree ruggers back home. They underestimate me. Good opportunity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095729" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was willing to indulge your other &quot;legends,&quot; but you're taking things too far. Do you really expect me to believe this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop making up stories.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095730" id2="17" version="1065353216">I tell you true tales, Chief. Do not worry--I will never work for your foes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095732" id2="17" version="1065353216">I pretend to take their offers and bring them your head. They send their people. Sometimes, they come to me in person. Very stupid.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095734" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have killed enemies many while you were busy. I only kept it secret because I feared your other allies might serve these foes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095735" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone has secrets, Treek. But I believe in my people--and I think they believe in me, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095735" id2="17" version="1065353216">My allies are trustworthy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095736" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is why I keep silent. You are free to think. I am free to act.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095738" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would never welcome anyone into my confidence I did not have complete faith in. Learn to trust them as I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095738" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must trust my friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095739" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say--but your foes offer rewards endless. It is difficult to resist for those who are not me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad had its share of disloyal members, but the people I serve with now I trust with my life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095741" id2="17" version="1065353216">My squad mates are all good.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095742" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do not have to trust them. Thanks to me, you can be sure they will die before betraying you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095744" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trust everyone I work with. Well, almost everyone. The point is, I'm not worried about them. You, on the other hand....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095744" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people are all loyal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095745" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will never need to fear. I watch them when you sleep.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have a more accurate count of how many people you've killed defending me? How bad has this gotten?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095747" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many is &quot;many&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095748" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is more than few, less than endless. It is many, understand?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095750" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you kept this quiet. Don't mention it to anyone else. There's no telling if these enemies have contacted other parties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095750" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thinking. I trust no one.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095751" id2="17" version="1065353216">I swear to stay silent and strike true.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not worry, Chief. I will protect you from all enemies, seen and unseen.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095755" id2="17" version="1065353216">More offers to betray you will come, and I will pretend to accept. The fools will die, I swear it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095756" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you're trying to help, but what you're doing is wrong. We only fight in self-defense--we never attack. I want you to stop.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095756" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, that is not the Jedi way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095757" id2="17" version="1065353216">To plot someone's death--even when you're protecting an ally--brings you closer to the dark side. You have to stop this and atone for those you've killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095757" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, we only fight to defend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095758" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're under my command, soldier--and I'm responsible for everything you do. I can't have you running black ops behind my back. I'm ordering you to stand down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095758" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, it's against regulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095759" id2="17" version="1065353216">No more, Treek. I don't want to have to bust you out of prison because you killed some corporate rep who thinks I ripped him off. Your &quot;hobby&quot; is over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095759" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, it's against the law.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095760" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are my chief, and I will obey--but life will be less fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095762" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care how stupid they are; sooner or later, one of them will figure out what you've been doing and set a trap for you. Stop before that happens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop before you get killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095763" id2="17" version="1065353216">You speak wisdom. I do not wish to die without you at my side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095765" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know I should be angry you did this behind my back, but honestly, I'm too amused by the whole thing. Keep up the good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095765" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's hilarious. Kill them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Chief. I will never disappoint you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095768" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will keep close watch on your other allies, just in case they turn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something's on your mind. What is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095773" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear your other allies talk of home with kindness. That is strange to me. I will never see my homeworld again.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095775" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have nothing in common with my tribe. They are quiet and soft people who fear me. I am not welcome in their village.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095776" id2="17" version="1065353216">It can't be easy to leave behind everyone you knew. Is there any chance you could return to them someday?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095776" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry to hear that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095777" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no reason for regret. I did not belong. We are all better off apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you do something to make your people be afraid?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why did they fear you?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095780" id2="17" version="1065353216">My strength and fearlessness confused them. My people think women's work is tending and gathering. We are not supposed to be fighters or explorers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095782" id2="17" version="1065353216">They probably kicked you out because they didn't want to be reminded of how pathetic they are compared to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095782" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're better than they are.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095783" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did not think of it that way before, but that makes sense! Thank you, Chief.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095785" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I left my tribe, the medicine man said I would find my best fate among the stars endless. He did not say how.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095787" id2="17" version="1065353216">I built good sky-gliders, but always crashed before reaching the clouds. Seasons many passed alone in failure, but the medicine man was right. I found my best fate here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095788" id2="17" version="1065353216">You never quit, do you? I guess that's why we get along so well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095788" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admire your resolve.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095789" id2="17" version="1065353216">You understand. Some challenges take longer to conquer than others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095791" id2="17" version="1065353216">What makes you think working as a mercenary is your best fate?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do you believe that?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095792" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mercenary is your word. I fight for my own legend, and you provide good enemies many.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095794" id2="17" version="1065353216">From what you've told me, that medicine man would've said anything to get you out of his village. He gave you an impossible task.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095794" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were manipulated.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095795" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are wrong. He would not mislead me. He was my father.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095797" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is good that the Empire does not care about my homeworld. My people could never stand against an invasion. They would just die.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095799" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire is much superior, but the Republic people fight as if they can still win. I respect that boldness. If the Republic falls, I will fight on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095800" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won't fight alone. Even if the Republic falls, the Jedi will never surrender to the dark side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095800" id2="17" version="1065353216">That makes two of us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes! We will make the enemy sorry it did not fail, Chief.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095803" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire will never win--not so long as there are Jedi and brave friends to stand against its tyranny.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095803" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's all any of us can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095804" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will do more than stand, Chief. We will trample!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095806" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic will pull through, Treek. Havoc Squad always finds a way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095806" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic won't fall.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095807" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are great warriors, Chief. We win, or we die. I like to win!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095809" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know about the Republic, but the Empire's never gonna take me down. We'll spend our lives making those Imps miserable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't count me out, either.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095810" id2="17" version="1065353216">I imagine no fate better than that, Chief. To our foes' misery!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095812" id2="17" version="1065353216">After all we've been through, what makes you so sure the Empire is stronger than us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095812" id2="17" version="1065353216">What makes the Empire better?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095813" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire fights with restraints none, like a rampaging gurreck. Very hard to kill--unless you are me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095815" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Republic falls, you'll wind up a stuffed animal in an Imperial museum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095815" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won't survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095816" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wear primed thermal detonators. When I die, boom! No museum for me. That is a fate worse than dying.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095818" id2="17" version="1065353216">One thing is certain: I live true to myself. The Empire will not take that away from me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there something you wanted to talk about?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095823" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could never dream my travels would bring me to worlds this far and many. The tribe would tremble to see me!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095825" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people told me to stay in the village--cook and raise children like the other women. I told them no. Instead, I walked our homeworld... all the way around!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi are expected to support others, but we're also taught to trust our intuition and follow where it leads. Choosing between those paths can be hard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095826" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a difficult choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095827" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew my place was not with the tribe. The horizon called, and I answered. It was simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095829" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only way to truly know who we are is by following our own path. You chose well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095829" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was a wise choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes! I had time alone, free from my tribe. I listened to no voices but mine and the Wisties in the trees.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095832" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't imagine you cooking meals and raising children. You were built for battle, Treek--no two ways about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095832" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a warrior, not a nanny.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095833" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew this, you know this, but my tribe did not. They called me rebel and troublemaker. I accepted those titles gladly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095835" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never been one for settling down, either. People like us need freedom to come and go whenever we want.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095835" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the spirit.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Life does not last. I will not spend it hunched over a cooking fire when there are stars endless waiting for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Were you on this long walk when you came across the starship that brought you to Republic space?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that how you got here?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095839" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was only my first walk around the homeworld. I did not find the starship until my third.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095841" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's true, a walk around your homeworld must be even shorter than you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095841" id2="17" version="1065353216">A small homeworld, then?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095842" id2="17" version="1065353216">My journey lasted seasons many. As my people say, &quot;short legs, long trip.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I saw my homeworld's wonders... the Desert of Simoom, Mount Thunderstone, the Sea of C'both. I defeated fire, ice, hunger, thirst... and worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095846" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Gorax tried to eat me. Terrible beast--taller than a rancor. I broke my leg in the duel, but it was the Gorax who fell into the lava lake!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095847" id2="17" version="1065353216">It sounds like you beat everything your homeworld could throw at you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095847" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're amazing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095848" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is why I had to leave. There were no challenges left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095850" id2="17" version="1065353216">You broke your leg next to a lava lake in the middle of nowhere? How did you make it back to safety?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095850" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you get home alive?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095851" id2="17" version="1065353216">I walked. The pain was my companion. Good friend--kept me alert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095853" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't get to claim a win just because some monster tripped over its own feet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095853" id2="17" version="1065353216">The creature probably slipped.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095854" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am here, and the Gorax is not. How else do you define victory?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095856" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I came to your space, I listened for the legends of your own great champions. But no one tells their tales.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095858" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people celebrate great lives with songs endless. Why do your people hide heroic deeds in libraries and museums? Are you ashamed of them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095859" id2="17" version="1065353216">My order remembers and celebrates its heroes, but Jedi stay focused on the present. It isn't what we've done, but who we are right now that truly matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi tend to be humble.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095860" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you know who you are if you do not remember who you were? It is confusing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095862" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't hide things in those places--we keep them safe. Some of those records and artifacts are older than the Republic itself. I'll show you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095862" id2="17" version="1065353216">I love libraries and museums.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095863" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have seen those places. They are cold and quiet. The caretakers discourage singing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095865" id2="17" version="1065353216">The statues on Coruscant aren't just for show. Every one of them represents a hero who deserves remembering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095865" id2="17" version="1065353216">We build monuments, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good! But where are the lore keepers telling stories? I see no bonfires and hear no ballads. This is wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you kidding? I tell my stories to anyone who'll listen. Sometimes I don't even charge them for the honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095868" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never hide my great deeds.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095869" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not think you understand what I mean--but you will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095871" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want to hear people telling you how great they are, just log into the HoloNet for ten minutes. You'll get an earful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Visit the HoloNet and see.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great legends must be celebrated by others, not the ones who performed the deeds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1095874" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I see you take down an Imperial cruiser all by yourself, I'll tell everyone about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1095874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Actions matter, not words.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095875" id2="17" version="1065353216">You set a challenge before me? I accept!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095877" id2="17" version="1065353216">I make this promise to you, Chief: If you die before I do, I will tell your legend to all who will hear it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095879" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galaxy will not forget you while I still breathe. We go!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095882" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope we visit your starship and speak soon, Chief.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095885" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will crush foes many today.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095886" id2="17" version="1065353216">I make songs of our journeys. One day, we will sing them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095887" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not ask for much in life--only challenges to conquer.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095888" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are a good chief. You lead me to greatness.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095889" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic has foes endless. I will never become restless.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095890" id2="17" version="1065353216">We go and become legends.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someday, they will sing our legends in loud voices endless.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Traveling light is a good policy. We do not slow down.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095893" id2="17" version="1065353216">People watch you when you pass them, Chief--and I watch back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your foes do not know how much trouble we have for them!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095895" id2="17" version="1065353216">I journey with my chief. Today is a good day.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095896" id2="17" version="1065353216">My homeworld offers no challenges greater than the ones we conquer.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095897" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wake each day and ask, &quot;What will I conquer?&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095898" id2="17" version="1065353216">When this war ends, none will sing the Empire's legends.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095899" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show me your foes, Chief. I will crush them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1095900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fighting droids does not make a good legend, but it is better than nothing.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
