<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>250</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/voss/world/imperial/deceit_and_diplomacy/darth_serevin.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553452" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak ship has been destroyed. They shall not reach the stars. You are the one from the vision.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553535" id2="17" version="1065353216">News of your victory preceded you. The entire city is talking of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get out of my sight. I have work to do, making up for your blunder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553537" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have served the Empire well. When Voss joins the Empire, I will see you recognized for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553539" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dark power has a name: Sel-Makor. I fought one of its servants, who claimed to have given Jokull his visions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553540" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fought a creature that claimed it was the source of Jokull's visions: a servant of a dark power called &quot;Sel-Makor.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553541" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is something the Voss should hear. They've been pestering me endlessly since you left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553545" id2="17" version="1065353216">My associates have returned as prophesied.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553547" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the Dark Heart, they defeated the creature that sent Jokull his visions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553549" id2="17" version="1065353216">My associate has returned at last, just as your Mystic said.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deep inside the Dark Heart, he fought a servant of darkness, which was the source of Jokull's visions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553553" id2="17" version="1065353216">She met the source of Jokull's power and defeated it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553555" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for defeating this creature, outsider. We await the wisdom the Mystic foretold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553557" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your learning will shape Voss's future among the stars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553559" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you've discovered something you can tell the Three. Something relevant to the Empire's negotiations, perhaps?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553560" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ancient Jedi conducted experiments on Gormak, and their tampering unleashed the power in the Dark Heart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553560" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi poisoned your world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553561" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such a crime is unthinkable. Why would the Jedi do us such harm?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this how the Gormak learned to construct monstrosities?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553565" id2="17" version="1065353216">We do not know yet that this claim is true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553567" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speak to your Mystics. Ask them to confirm what my colleague has said. The Jedi have greatly wronged you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553568" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should cast the Republic out of Voss-Ka. They've lied to you for too long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553568" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi are your enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your words require much consideration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talk to the Mystics. They must know something about this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen to Darth Serevin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553572" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a wise suggestion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553574" id2="17" version="1065353216">I only say what I learned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553575" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will ask the Mystics to meditate upon this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553577" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will halt all talks with the Republic until we know the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553579" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have done all that was asked, outsider. The vision is fulfilled.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553581" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss and the Gormak were once the same race. And now something in the Dark Heart feeds on your conflict.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553581" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss and Gormak are one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impossible! The Voss are not kin to those beasts!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm yourself, Gunta-Mer. Perhaps the outsider speaks metaphorically.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553586" id2="17" version="1065353216">No interpretation of such a claim can be true!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553588" id2="17" version="1065353216">My associate only meant that all life on Voss is connected. This is why you must have outsider allies to defeat the Dark Heart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553590" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553592" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will carry your words to the Mystics. They will guide us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553593" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you don't stop fighting the Gormak, the Nightmare Lands will spread.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553593" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you act on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553594" id2="17" version="1065353216">We follow the visions of the Mystics. If they say we must end the war, we will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553596" id2="17" version="1065353216">You accept that I'm telling you the truth?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you believe me, then?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553597" id2="17" version="1065353216">You gain nothing by telling us this tale. You have no reason to lie.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553599" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was worth the risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553600" id2="17" version="1065353216">You believe this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553602" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe the Mystics. The vision is fulfilled.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553604" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will speak again, Ambassador Serevin. The Mystics will consider what has been said here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done! Blaming the Jedi for the corruption at the Dark Heart was inspired.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553607" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't invent a word of it. The Jedi really are responsible for all the trouble here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553607" id2="17" version="1065353216">I told them the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553608" id2="17" version="1065353216">All the better for us, then! They will cast the Republic off Voss and run to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553610" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish I could be there when the Voss tell the Republic they're halting negotiations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553610" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi will be furious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553611" id2="17" version="1065353216">I may have someone from Intelligence sneak in to record the event. It's a moment worth savoring.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553614" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assure you, I will make your role in this known to those who matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553616" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have been awarded a rare honor. Even I have not spoken directly to the Three before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553618" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have served the Empire well. When I secure Voss, I will do so in your name. The Emperor will be pleased.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553619" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope that everything goes according to plan, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553619" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish you luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't practice your victory speech yet. Voss seems... unpredictable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553620" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt it will be so easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553621" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to have helped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did the Dark Heart erode your wits? You've thrown away any hope of an alliance with Voss, and for what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553624" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll be grateful to us for the truth once they've adjusted to the idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553624" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll come around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or perhaps the Voss will remain the obstinate, irrational nitwits they've always been.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553627" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the war ended, we can have both Voss Mystics and Gormak technicians join the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss is a bigger prize now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553628" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a rosy outcome, if I can smooth things over now that you've offended the Three.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553630" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had my reasons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553631" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've jeopardized our entire position on this planet. Don't think you've heard the end of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make yourself an obstacle if you want, Serevin. You won't be the first Sith Lord I've crushed underfoot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Try me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553633" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care if you're Sith; you get in my way, you're dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553633" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't want to cross me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553634" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did what was necessary. The needs of the Empire are greater than your petty ambition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Put a sock in it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553635" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm leaving Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553636" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've done what was best for Voss and the Empire. It's a pity you don't see that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553636" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry you feel that way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you been to see Gehn yet? The idiot Voss are pestering me for news of your progress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seek out Murbek Gehn on the edge of the Dark Heart. He may have answers for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553644" id2="17" version="1065353216">They say you took this so-called &quot;Gormak king&quot; captive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553646" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss are doubly impressed that you destroyed the ship and killed this &quot;Gormak king.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553648" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fools are entirely convinced you are the agent of their prophesy. Well done, indeed!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553649" id2="17" version="1065353216">So now we wait for the Voss to agree to join the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we just wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our victory is almost at hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553652" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sama-Ro said something about &quot;bringing new wisdom.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553652" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's more to the vision.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which could mean anything--it might even refer to Voss joining the Empire. It's nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553655" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sama-Ro has already asked for an audience with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553657" id2="17" version="1065353216">Emissary, my associates have returned. I believe you were anxious to see them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553659" id2="17" version="1065353216">The gentleman you wished to speak with has returned, emissary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553661" id2="17" version="1065353216">Emissary, the lady you wished to speak with has arrived. I wouldn't keep her waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553664" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Three have heard the report of your battle with Jokull. They are troubled. Gormak are not Mystics, they have no visions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553666" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the new wisdom the prophesy foretold. It lies in the Dark Heart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553667" id2="17" version="1065353216">You expect me to find out what gave him his power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553667" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want me to go there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553668" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is dangerous. But the Mystics have spoken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553670" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need more information on this place. Who or what is in there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553670" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is the Dark Heart?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553671" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most likely, yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553672" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dark Heart is an evil place deep within the Nightmare Lands. We are forbidden to go there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553674" id2="17" version="1065353216">We do not know what it holds. You must return to us with this knowledge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything for an ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553676" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll search the Dark Heart for answers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make me an offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553678" id2="17" version="1065353216">We understand this is the custom of outsiders. We will pay you for this service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553680" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have our gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done. One final move, and Voss will be ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553683" id2="17" version="1065353216">It won't be simple. Even the most powerful Sith have not made it far into the Dark Heart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553684" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's kept us from exploring it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why not?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553685" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll succeed with no trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553686" id2="17" version="1065353216">The power of the dark side is overwhelming there. Strong enough that it drives even Sith mad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553688" id2="17" version="1065353216">With so much riding on my success, I hope you have a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553688" id2="17" version="1065353216">How am I supposed to do this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dark Lord Murbek Gehn dwells on the edge of the Dark Heart, studying its power. He alone has managed to withstand the madness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553693" id2="17" version="1065353216">If anyone knows where to find the source of these visions, he does. Seek him out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seek him in the Nightmare Lands. He must know a way for you to defend yourself from the dark power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show the Voss that they are destined to join the Empire, and you will be well rewarded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553706" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've brought you something, my lord. Keln said this writing would prove that the Sith and Jedi had been to Voss before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's what Keln found in the ruins. He said this would prove that the ancient Voss fought the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553708" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi did find something in those ruins, my lord. Look. He said this writing spoke of an ancient war between the Sith and Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553709" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting. Very interesting. I assumed Keln's evidence would be recent. I'll send these to the Sith archive for study.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553712" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi found proof that the Voss once fought the Sith. No one will ever see it now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keln found stone tablets proving the Voss once fought the Sith--hard to read in little pieces, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553714" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Keln found tablets in the ruins that spoke of a Voss war against the ancient Sith. The tablets suffered a fatal accident.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553715" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith were here before? Our archaeologists have been lazy, it seems. This will be remedied.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553717" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have served the Empire well. I will personally make certain that nothing can be traced to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553718" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not every day you kill a Jedi Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553718" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would have liked the credit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553719" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you will distinguish yourself here on Voss enough that this one accomplishment won't be missed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553721" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happens now that Keln is out of the way?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553721" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was he your only threat?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Keln was the only one stupid enough to stand in our way. I think we will see some progress now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553724" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a relief.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553725" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should be proud; you have utterly crushed the Republic's hope of victory. They will not recover soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553727" id2="17" version="1065353216">I bring word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Emissary! I wasn't expecting you. Do come in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553731" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Mystic has had a vision concerning outsiders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553733" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those serving a red banner will keep the Gormak from the stars and bring new wisdom to Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553734" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think we're the outsiders your Mystic spoke of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553734" id2="17" version="1065353216">We fit that description.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553735" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed they are, emissary! The Empire brought them here knowing they were fated to serve Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553737" id2="17" version="1065353216">One who serves a great power will keep the Gormak from the stars and bring new wisdom to Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553738" id2="17" version="1065353216">One who has come seeking silence shall keep the Gormak from the stars and bring new wisdom to Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553739" id2="17" version="1065353216">One who hunts vengeance will keep the Gormak from the stars and bring new wisdom to Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553740" id2="17" version="1065353216">One seeking to illuminate those in the shadows will keep the Gormak from the stars and bring new wisdom to Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553741" id2="17" version="1065353216">One who stands at the right hand of the red man will keep the Gormak from the stars and bring new wisdom to Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553742" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I'm the outsider you're looking for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553742" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds like me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed she is, emissary! In fact, we brought her to Voss knowing that she had a destiny to fulfill for your people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed, emissary, the Empire has known for some time that he is destined to do great things for Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553747" id2="17" version="1065353216">What wisdom? And what's this about the stars?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553747" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does that mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553748" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's just gibberish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only interpreters can explain a vision. I may only say what I have been told.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553751" id2="17" version="1065353216">A wise course, emissary. Indeed, I believe my associates here are the ones described by the vision.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553753" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is fortunate you came here, emissary. I believe my associate here is the one described.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553755" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I must report to the Three. There is much to be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553757" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was well-played. You had that fool wrapped around your finger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553759" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is far better than I had anticipated. The gullible fools follow their Mystics without question.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their naivety can be made to serve us. Fulfill this vision, and it will surely lead them to ally with the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where should I start, my lord?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553762" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do I do that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553764" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. We have much to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553766" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553769" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is a Voss outpost on the edge of Gorma-Koss. Speak to the commander there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make a pilgrimage to the Shrine of Healing. It is a place these idiots revere greatly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553777" id2="17" version="1065353216">All outsider pilgrims must have Fadith-Ki's permission to enter. Seek him out and get his approval.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553781" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keln is in the Ruined City. Make sure he never leaves it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intercept Vesh. Leave no witnesses. The Empire is relying on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553783" id2="17" version="1065353216">Strange to see you here. I thought you were reporting to General Rosh at Fort Kodentha.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eliminate the Houk Syndicate. We cannot let them stand between us and victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553787" id2="17" version="1065353216">These charges are grave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553789" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am bringing the proof with me to Voss, emissary. When you see it, the Three will banish the Empire from the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553791" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid Jedi Master Keln is mistaken, Emissary Sama-Ro. No such evidence can possibly exist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553793" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am confident that the Three will find that an alliance with the Empire can only benefit your people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553795" id2="17" version="1065353216">I await this evidence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553797" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insufferable idiot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, you've arrived! It's about time. No doubt you heard some of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553800" id2="17" version="1065353216">I take it you have something for me to do, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553800" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sent for me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Things aren't going smoothly for the Empire here....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553801" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounded like trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553802" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could use more info on Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss must be brought into the Empire. Their obstinance was a problem before the Jedi began meddling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553805" id2="17" version="1065353216">We sense a great power here. Strong in the dark side. These people have powers of prophesy we have never seen before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553807" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire must have this world and its secrets, and we know from experience that it cannot be taken by force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553808" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're trying to woo the Voss into joining the Empire, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which only leaves diplomacy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553809" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is a delicate balance. We fawn over the arrogant Voss publicly and undercut the Republic's negotiations privately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553811" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you've already attempted force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553811" id2="17" version="1065353216">What experience?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553812" id2="17" version="1065353216">That incident has been smoothed over. We held enough executions to ensure that there are no further &quot;mishaps&quot; here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553814" id2="17" version="1065353216">And now this Jedi Master appears and thinks he can sabotage all we've done!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shall I get rid of this Jedi?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553815" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could kill him for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your enthusiasm will serve the Empire well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does he have specific claims against us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553818" id2="17" version="1065353216">What has he found?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553819" id2="17" version="1065353216">He remains vague, which he may be using to smoke out our secrets. We must act without detection.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553821" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a solution, my lord?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553822" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do I help &quot;acquire&quot; it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any evidence of misconduct must be erased before this Jedi arrives. Quietly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553825" id2="17" version="1065353216">A syndicate was hired to steal supplies from the city of Voss-Ka. We then generously offered aid to the people in need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553827" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the syndicate was made up of Houk: brutish idiots who turned from saboteurs into raiders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553828" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can see why you wouldn't want this traced back to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553828" id2="17" version="1065353216">That could be embarrassing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553831" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make them disappear for you, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553831" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want this syndicate gone?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. I knew you would not disappoint me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553834" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll pay for this betrayal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553835" id2="17" version="1065353216">The syndicate's lair is in a cave system. Silence these Houk. Report to General Rosh in Fort Kodentha afterward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553837" id2="17" version="1065353216">This prophesy is the opportunity we have been waiting for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553839" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm done running errands for you, Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely not. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553840" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will relate this to the Three.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553842" id2="17" version="1065353216">An unfortunate decision. We are poised on the edge of victory now. I hope you will reconsider.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not the one the Mystic spoke of. I'm not getting involved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't. [Refuse quest.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553845" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a waste of talent. Very well, speak to me if you decide you want to take part in the Empire's victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553847" id2="17" version="1065353216">No thanks. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553848" id2="17" version="1065353216">A pity. We could achieve great things together. Let me know if you reconsider.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you find anything else? I will compensate you for anything of value.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553854" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found this. I thought it might still be useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. [Hand over the relic]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, excellent! Our people have found nothing of this quality.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553857" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I found in there were Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553857" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, nothing. [Keep the relic]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very good. There is probably nothing left in there to trouble us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you find anything else that our incompetent researchers missed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553861" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ruins were full of Jedi, nothing more, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553861" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, I didn't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553862" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very good. There is likely nothing more to find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you think the Sith really came to Voss before?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you believe Keln's story?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553865" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have no records of such a thing in the Sith archives; still, it bears consideration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553867" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can take another look, if you think there's more to find, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="553867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should I go back and look?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="553868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't bother. I doubt there's anything to find.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
