<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>104</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/voss/world/imperial/deceit_and_diplomacy/general_rosh.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601060" id2="17" version="1065353216">I envy you, taking up arms against this Jedi Master. It must be nice to take action for a change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601061" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've missed something. Our spies report that Master Keln has already left Voss-Ka. He's headed into the Ruined City.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601062" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is the Empire involved in there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601062" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's in the Ruined City?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing at all. That is what worries me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601065" id2="17" version="1065353216">I took care of everything you told me about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601065" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't miss anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601066" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your work has been flawless. The Intelligence operatives responsible for monitoring Master Keln have been executed for this failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601068" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does that even mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your confusion is understandable. I, myself, don't understand what this means.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601071" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ruins were a city that the Voss abandoned in antiquity. We have archaeologists there, but nothing compromising.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing in that city should harm us, and yet that is where Master Keln has gone to retrieve his evidence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601074" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Jedi went to this Ruined City, I'm going after him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then that's where I'm going.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601075" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eliminate Master Keln and his evidence, and the Empire will be most grateful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601077" id2="17" version="1065353216">This may be a trap--or it's a distraction from wherever his real evidence is hidden.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601077" id2="17" version="1065353216">This must be a ruse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601078" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must be sure there's nothing in those ruins. This Jedi will not cost us an alliance now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601080" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do I stop him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601081" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire requires you to go to the ruins, find Master Keln and eliminate him and whatever evidence he has.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601083" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will craft a suitable excuse for his absence to the Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601085" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601088" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell Darth Serevin that Durik Vesh is no longer a problem, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601089" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent, my lord. Your timing is perfect; we've heard that Jedi Master Keln has just landed in Voss-Ka.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601091" id2="17" version="1065353216">The target's been eliminated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601092" id2="17" version="1065353216">You completed that mission just in time. Intelligence reports that Jedi Master Keln has arrived in Voss-Ka.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601094" id2="17" version="1065353216">Durik Vesh has been handled, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601095" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect. Darth Serevin will be pleased. We've received word that Jedi Master Keln just landed in Voss-Ka.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601097" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can report the good news to Darth Serevin. He asked to speak with you as soon as you returned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601099" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a great opportunity. We've wanted to eliminate Vesh for weeks. You should be proud to be chosen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601100" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am extremely pleased. The gullible Voss already talk of the heroic outsider who held back the Gormak abominations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601102" id2="17" version="1065353216">However, we've little time to savor this victory. An opportunity has presented itself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601103" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've had my fill of fighting surveillance equipment, beasts and thugs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601103" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not more cleanup, I hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me what needs to be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601105" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sort of opportunity?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601105" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601106" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is a place the locals call the &quot;Nightmare Lands.&quot; It is an area steeped in the power of the dark side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601108" id2="17" version="1065353216">A promising Sith named Durik Vesh led a group there to search for the source of the power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601110" id2="17" version="1065353216">But Vesh was weaker than we thought. Dark energy overpowered his mind. He went mad and was captured by the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601111" id2="17" version="1065353216">What good is a madman to the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601111" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do they want him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601112" id2="17" version="1065353216">They are almost certainly trying to pick his addled brains for information: about us and the Nightmare Lands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601114" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll use him against us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601115" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed. He's been kept out of sight. Locked in SIS maximum security. Until now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me who you want killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Skip the explanations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601118" id2="17" version="1065353216">Direct. I like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601120" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reports say Vesh is being moved. Under guard, naturally, but out in the open. We need him dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems highly convenient that the Republic is moving him now, just as we're trying to eliminate everything they have on us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601121" id2="17" version="1065353216">This sounds like a trap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601122" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would not trust this task to anyone less skilled than yourself. A failure here could cost the Empire Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601124" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why not just free him, or bring him back here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601124" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do you want him dead?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601125" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have too much at stake on this planet to coddle an insane fool who could not handle power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601127" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601128" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vesh and his escort will be leaving the SIS camp shortly. They will pass through a canyon nearby. Intercept them and leave no witnesses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601130" id2="17" version="1065353216">Plant this in the canyon before the convoy arrives. I wish you luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601134" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've all done extraordinary work. Our people had trouble spotting the towers' destruction, and they were watching for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601136" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, thank you for your aid. Our scouts reported the towers' destruction, and the Voss seem none the wiser.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601138" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do good work, hunter. The scouts watching your progress out there were positively gushing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601140" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should have known Intelligence would make quick work of the towers. Well done!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601142" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our own scouts barely spotted the destruction of those towers in all the confusion out there. Well played.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601144" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic must be squirming right now, wishing they could strike back at us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601145" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss told me you wanted to speak with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why did you send for me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601146" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd relish the chance to engage the Republic directly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let them try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601147" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not alone. I'd much prefer to end all this skulking about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601149" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd hate to be out of a job so soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suits me just fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601150" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very little danger of that. The Voss seem to delight in drawing out these negotiations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601152" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why can't they just go to the Voss and accuse us of destroying their property?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601152" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's stopping them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601153" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss would investigate, discover the Republic had built spy towers near Voss-Ka, and you can imagine how they would react.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601155" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume we're not done yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601156" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have more work to do before the arrival of this Jedi Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait. We have an incoming transmission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601160" id2="17" version="1065353216">If all goes well, you can destroy those Republic listening towers and earn us the gratitude of the Voss in a single blow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601161" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, perhaps, we can strike at the Republic. Albeit indirectly. Cursed diplomats and their games....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601162" id2="17" version="1065353216">You disagree with Darth Serevin's strategy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601162" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't sound happy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601163" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would simply prefer a more direct approach.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601165" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought we couldn't do anything that would upset the Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601165" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't be caught.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601166" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every step is mired in politics. My only consolation is that the Republic is equally stymied.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601168" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have my attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601169" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've detected Republic spy towers in our vicinity. If I sent men to destroy them, we would incur suspicion from the Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601171" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss post nearby, however, appears to have come under attack. We can aid them and destroy the towers at the same time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601172" id2="17" version="1065353216">What enemy am I supposed to help them fight?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who is attacking the Voss?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601173" id2="17" version="1065353216">My scouts can't determine who or what the attackers are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601175" id2="17" version="1065353216">Two birds with one stone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601176" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic won't take the loss of their listening towers lightly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="601176" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic will retaliate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601177" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this goads them to strike back at us openly, so much the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601179" id2="17" version="1065353216">The commander of the Voss post is Panthin-Dro. Seek him out, give him the Empire's full support.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601183" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Fort Kodentha. I'd only just received word you were coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601185" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, Fort Kodentha is honored by your presence. Darth Serevin mentioned you were coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601187" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am General Rosh. You must be the bounty hunter. Darth Serevin spoke highly of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601189" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, you must be the agent Darth Serevin told me to expect. Welcome to Fort Kodentha.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601191" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Fort Kodentha. I've been expecting this visit. Darth Serevin spoke very highly of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601193" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard what you did to the Houks. I must admit, I've wanted to exterminate those thugs for some time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="601195" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm busy at the moment. Another time.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
