<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>40</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/daily_area/kuat/imperial/admiral_ranken.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please excuse me; I'm overseeing several operations simultaneously.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123522" id2="17" version="1065353216">With your help, Kuat Drive Yards will be ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Kuat Drive Yards: the beating heart of the Republic Navy; a heart we're about to pierce.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123574" id2="17" version="1065353216">For centuries, Kuati ship production has afforded our enemy entire fleets, from the smallest fighters to Valor-class cruisers. We're about to turn that production in our favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123576" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is my own initiative from top to bottom, executed under the aegis of Darth Marr.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123606" id2="17" version="1065353216">The key to victory lies in a single space station. It's the defensive nerve center for the entire enterprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123613" id2="17" version="1065353216">The planet's economy revolves around Kuat Drive Yards. If we take that station, they'll have no choice but to work for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123615" id2="17" version="1065353216">This facility's never been taken before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before Admiral Ranken, no one was ever bold enough to try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123618" id2="17" version="1065353216">When we succeed, the Republic will crumble. The galaxy will finally fall in line with the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123618" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the Empire's moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123619" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd like to know who I'm supposed to be addressing here. You, or the admiral?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which of you is in charge?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123620" id2="17" version="1065353216">You make it sound so easy. Too easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123620" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're oversimplifying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123621" id2="17" version="1065353216">I serve at Admiral Ranken's pleasure. She's an unparalleled strategist, and I trust her with my life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123623" id2="17" version="1065353216">And, as I see it, any mission insight provided by Lord Krovos is the same as if spoken by me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wouldn't mind it if my wealthiest employer became all the wealthier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123624" id2="17" version="1065353216">A win for all of us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123625" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe we're at an accord. Lord Krovos?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, don't mistake me--I know how ambitious my plan is, and how difficult the road ahead will be. Lord Krovos?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123628" id2="17" version="1065353216">As we speak, a formidable Republic presence hinders our offensive at the station. We ask you to tilt the balance in our favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123630" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've also deployed starfighters to key points that will aid in the Republic's downfall, should you feel the need to avail yourself as a pilot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123634" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's day is close at hand. When that day arrives, it will be due to what we accomplish here and now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be strong, be merciless, and may the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125639" id2="17" version="1065353216">A number of our conscripts have been taken prisoner. I'd normally write them off as worthless, but we're in bit of a staffing pinch. Free them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125641" id2="17" version="1065353216">I grow tired of having my bridge shot at by that station. Secure those cannons!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125643" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our engineers want to get their hands on Kuat fighter assembly data. See what you can do about that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125645" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic must really fear our chances: they intend to sabotage the station's power core. Keep it safe, would you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125647" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've identified a major weapons cache the Republic could use to their advantage. Do us a favor and destroy it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125649" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we lose this hangar, we lose our way into the station. Defend it with your life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi: insufferable, aren't they? We have one mucking things up for us in there. Make sure this day is his last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125653" id2="17" version="1065353216">A single Republic trooper's been making short work of our forces. You know what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125655" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic can't fight their own battles, so they've sicced one of the corporate defense droids on us. Set it to scrap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125657" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic think they're so superior; you're showing them otherwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent work. Kuat Drive Yards will be ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125659" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a win for us--one we sorely needed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125660" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing that can stop you, is there? Good thing you're on our side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125661" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Krovos and I commend you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1125662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our position here grows ever stronger, thanks to you.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
