<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>77</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/trooper/chapter_2/event/major_donovan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634008" id2="17" version="1065353216">There you are! I've never seen anything so reckless and stupid in my entire career!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634010" id2="17" version="1065353216">And it worked! I've seen platoons fight for a month to hit the Imps that hard, and you did it on a whim!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634011" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just did my duty, nothing more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634011" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634012" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't call that &quot;nothing&quot; by a long shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634014" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's just how Havoc works.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634015" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got to be more than &quot;good&quot; to mess up the Imps like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634017" id2="17" version="1065353216">After that op, I was expecting a medal, not a rant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this the thanks I get?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634018" id2="17" version="1065353216">You get a medal in my book, Captain. That was some fancy fighting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain! Great work out there, great work!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634022" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made that op plan look easy. In and out, hit and run--the Imps never had a clue. Top-notch soldiering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634023" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just glad we got the Safecrackers out of there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634024" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and me both. Quesh definitely won't be making my list of the galaxy's most relaxing destinations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634026" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've had much tougher ops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634027" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd hate to see what you think is tough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone could've pulled that op--Havoc is needed elsewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634029" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was a waste of my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634030" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know anybody who could've sent the Imps running like you did. I've never seen anything like it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634032" id2="17" version="1065353216">You got me and my people out of a tight spot, and we won't forget it. Whatever and whenever you need, the Safecrackers are there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just keep fighting the Imps with everything you've got, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634033" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need for that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634034" id2="17" version="1065353216">That won't be a problem, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634036" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be glad to have your help, Lieutenant. General Garza already has plans for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Much appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634037" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I hear. It'll be a pleasure to work with you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your men sharp and ready for action, Lieutenant. You'll be called on very soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634039" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expect no less.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood. We'll stay limber.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634042" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, all right--we're not on vacation here, people. Coria, get your men settled and ready for transport.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, it's been a pleasure. Contact General Garza with the rundown before you take off. Dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Move out, soldier!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634047" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've dug in, Major, but the Imps are coming on strong, and I never much cared for playing defense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just hang in there, son. Havoc Squad just walked in--I'll get them briefed and in the field on the double!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634051" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just keep your heads down and your guns firing, son. Havoc Squad's CO is here now--we'll have you out of there in no time!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Copy that. I'm sure we'll find a way to keep busy. Coria out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634054" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the situation, Major?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634054" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reporting for duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634055" id2="17" version="1065353216">The situation is a mess, that's what it is!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634057" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just how bad off are we, Major?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634057" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds rough out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Things are grim, no doubt about it. If you hadn't turned up,..</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me a rundown so I can get moving, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's make this fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wrong attitude, Captain. If it takes a hundred years, we're getting those boys out of there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything went south while the Safecrackers were on a bunker raid. Intel was bad, alarms got tripped, and the Imps moved out in force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634065" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now Coria's people are surrounded, outnumbered and outgunned. We don't punch 'em a hole to run through, every man in that outfit is a goner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634066" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care how many Imps there are. We're getting our people out of there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634066" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let that happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get out there and bust some heads. What's the plan, Major?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed, Captain. Leaving our comrades to the Empire is never an option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634071" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic does not leave its heroes to suffer and die. Havoc Squad will do whatever it takes!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634073" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not big on rushing headfirst into enemy lines. Any other options?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="634075" id2="17" version="1065353216">No goal is unreachable, no feat unachievable. For every destination, there is a path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634077" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm all for rescuing our people, but we need a strategy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have a plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634078" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. We don't have the manpower to fight through the Imps head-on. We need to outmaneuver them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634080" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Imps outnumber a full platoon, they outnumber Havoc even more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634080" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you expect me to do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634081" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know how to do my job. I'm not going to throw you at the Imp lines and expect a miracle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Diversion is the key. Scouts found an Imperial command center, deep behind their lines. That's where you'll strike.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634085" id2="17" version="1065353216">Equipment, vehicles, personnel--anything with an Imperial logo gets holes in it. The Imps will rush back to stop you, and the Safecrackers will get the gap they need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just give me the coordinates, and I'll make some noise, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634086" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make it happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's give those scumbags a run for their money!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634089" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about air strikes or artillery? Couldn't we clear a path that way?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634089" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are other options.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634090" id2="17" version="1065353216">No-go on both. We'd have to drop more ordnance than we're likely to see in a year's worth of requisitions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634092" id2="17" version="1065353216">As soon as the Imps clear out, Coria will contact you so that you can all burn jets back here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634094" id2="17" version="1065353216">This plan just gets us pinned down instead of the Safecrackers. Who's going to get us out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634094" id2="17" version="1065353216">My team would be trapped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634095" id2="17" version="1065353216">It sounds like I'll just be trading places with Lieutenant Coria.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="634095" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd be trapped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634096" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can move a lot faster than the Safecrackers can. Coria will contact you as soon as the Imps pull out--you'll be long gone before they can close in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634098" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speeders are waiting for you. Get out there and give the Imps something to think about!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="634099" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got a speeder prepped and waiting. Get out there and make a mess, soldier!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
