<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>11</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/gui/backgrounddescriptions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="50" id2="194644" version="1065353216">By far the most common species in the galaxy, Humans are versatile and the norm against which other species are judged.

Social Ability: Rally - Rallies nearby allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="51" id2="194644" version="1065353216">Fiercely independent and identifiable by their horns and facial tattoos, Zabraks have two visually different cultural groups split almost perfectly between Republic and Imperial space.

Social Ability: Inspire Loyalty - Inspires loyalty from nearby allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="52" id2="194644" version="1065353216">Humans enhanced by cybernetic implants--some to compensate for injuries, others to enhance their combat abilities.

Social Ability: Scan Target - Scans the target with a critical cybernetic eye.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="53" id2="194644" version="1065353216">Descendants of the alien species that gave the name to the Sith Order and humans, Purebloods have a high percentage of Force sensitivity and sharp bone ridges.

Social Ability: Punish - Punishes your companion for his or her continued failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="54" id2="194644" version="1065353216">Instantly identifiable by their colorful skin and long head tails (called &quot;lekku&quot;), the Twi'lek people have long been oppressed, with only the rare group escaping slavery.

Social Ability: Parlor Dance - Performs a unique cultural dance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="55" id2="194644" version="1065353216">Born and bred in a culture of war, Rattataki tattoo harsh, deep black symbols across their white skin and never walk away from a fight.

Social Ability: Shadowbox - Performs a series of mock blows, blocks and counters, warming up for the fights to come.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="56" id2="194644" version="1065353216">A secretive, mysterious people, the blue-skinned Chiss are the only official allies of the Sith Empire, making them a subject of interest to everyone else.

Social Ability: Mission Review - Review your current mission while catching your breath.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="57" id2="194644" version="1065353216">The deeply spiritual Mirialan people have a religion built around a basic concept of the Force and tattoo geometric designs onto their faces to celebrate life achievements.

Social Ability: Focusing Ritual - Undergo a Focusing Ritual to rest and recuperate the spirit.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="58" id2="194644" version="1065353216">Born without eyes, the near-human Miraluka possess the unusual ability to see with the Force, viewing all the galaxy by how the Force moves through it.

Social Ability: Sense Force Alignment - Senses the target's alignment with the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="194644" version="1065353216">The feline Cathar take great pride in their cultural heritage of loyalty and honor, though they have struggled to find their place in the galaxy since the devastation of their homeworld centuries ago.

Social Ability: Pride of the Cathar - Intimidates those around you with a bestial roar.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="194644" version="1065353216">A tribal species originating from an ancient planet, the Togruta are mainly distinguished by their colorful montrals and distinctive facial patterns.

Social Ability: Tribal Storytelling - Tells a traditional Togruta story.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
