<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>24</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/gui/charcreatestory.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="480729" version="1065353216">An unstoppable force of darkness, the Sith Warrior is entrusted with the task of destroying the Empire's enemies and enforcing Sith domination across the galaxy. The Warrior channels the destructive emotions of fear, anger and hatred to purge weakness from body and mind and become a being of pure, brutal efficiency.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Destined to eradicate the incompetent chaos created by the Jedi, the Sith seek to rule the galaxy through power and intimidation. The armies of the Sith Empire are trained to accomplish this task, but they require the leadership of bold Sith Warriors--loyal and mighty overlords--who will drive them to conquest and victory.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These cold-blooded conquerors waste no time with cunning manipulations and carefully crafted plans. Sith Warriors crush their opponents and stride toward their goals with dreadful determination, leaving ruin and annihilation in their wake. Emanating awe and terror at every step, they accept nothing but absolute obedience from their followers. In turn, Sith Warriors can serve as loyal subjects to their own dark masters, often surprising enemies and allies with their rigorous honor and perfect discipline.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether they align their ambitions with those of the Dark Council or become renegades in pursuit of their own goals, they are never far from the action. Their fierce hatred of the Jedi keeps Sith Warriors at the forefront of any conflict with the Republic. The passion to eradicate the Jedi Order fuels many of their actions, but that does not make them single-minded fools. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ultimately, the destiny of any Sith Warrior is his own to choose... and woe to those who would stand in his way. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working with Others&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Natural leaders in any context, Sith Warriors inspire both fear and undying loyalty into their followers and allies. Though they rarely exercise patience for incompetence or indecisiveness, Warriors have realized the importance of strength in numbers in their war with the Jedi and have learned to accept and sometimes even encourage their comrades, whether they are like-minded Sith, ruthless Bounty Hunters or others who embrace the darkness.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="480729" version="1065353216">The history of the Sith Empire is fraught with scheming politics and dark secrets--the lifeblood of the Sith Inquisitor. Treachery hides around every corner in the Empire's dark corridors, and survival depends on an individual's natural cunning and the will to manipulate and defeat their enemies and allies alike. The Inquisitor experiments with forbidden powers to not only survive in this cutthroat environment, but to excel and seize authority.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regardless of potential, few acolytes succeed in facing the rigorous trials to become Sith Inquisitors. Only the most determined acolytes attain such an achievement, but these Sith are often the ones to watch. Due to their manipulative genius, Inquisitors are skilled at exploiting both their enemies and their allies to further their own personal agendas. Channeling this Force energy, Inquisitors are capable of draining the life from their enemies and using it to feed themselves and their allies. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though their skills are varied and many, Sith Inquisitors are most feared for their ability to channel the energy of the Force, making them a spectacle to behold on the battlefield. Seething sparks of lightning explode from the Inquisitors' fingertips and wrap their enemies in tendrils of pure Force energy. Because Inquisitors can twist the Force into lightning to stun, subdue or destroy their foes, it has become their signature. Those who have experienced the sensation of the Inquisitor's Force Lightning and survived forever recoil from the crackling sound of electricity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mastering the Dark Side&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To reach the highest echelons of power, the Inquisitor needs more than Force Lightning and a razor-sharp mind. The most formidable Inquisitors dare to explore unorthodox practices by investigating the enigmas of the past and by unlocking new powers for themselves. The Force is a source of unlimited potential--a wellspring Inquisitors tap and bend to their will. Such intensity allows Sith Inquisitors to become architects of the Empire's future... or simply the architects of their own destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="3" id2="480729" version="1065353216">Countless enemies stand in the way of the Sith Empire's drive for domination. The Empire spares no expense eliminating these threats, offering massive bounties to employ the galaxy's most lethal hunters. Earning a death mark from the Empire means a life spent in fear, constantly looking over one's shoulder. It's never a question if a Bounty Hunter will find you... only when.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both infamous and anonymous at the same time, Bounty Hunters are far more than mercenaries for hire--they're heirs to a professional legacy, an ancient brotherhood with a glorious history. Tracking elusive targets across multiple star systems requires expertise, especially when the targets can be prominent, powerful and often prepared for confrontation. Thrill seekers from all walks of life set out to become Bounty Hunters, but only the most hard-boiled survive in this competitive and deadly business. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bounty Hunter's path lies along the edge--the stakes are always high--and the path only leads two places: to a life of infamous glory... or to a quick and ignominious death. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imperial Relations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though the Empire disapproves of the Bounty Hunters' fierce independence, exceptions are made for those who get results. Few individuals in the galaxy have the gall and the stomach to deliver on the delicate and grim tasks in which Bounty Hunters excel. Nonetheless, no one is irreplaceable in the Empire, and even the most proficient must repeatedly prove their worth. In the bounty business, one's name is everything, and with each mark a Bounty Hunter takes down, his reputation grows, as does his price. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliations and Loyalties&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bounty Hunters are far from a homogeneous lot; they come from all races and affiliations and each pursues his quarry in his own unique way. Some Bounty Hunters adhere to the rugged Mandalorian code of honor while others answer only to their own moral compass. Some work only on behalf of organizations they agree with, while others have no sense of loyalty. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite being kindred spirits, fellow Bounty Hunters cannot always be trusted; among the profession's most notorious members, competition turns colleagues into the most ruthless of enemies. Even the Bounty Hunters' employers harbor hidden agendas; the tables are turned quickly when complications arise... and they always do. Shifting allegiances, unbeatable odds and deadly showdowns are common occurrences in the life of a Bounty Hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="4" id2="480729" version="1065353216">The Empire dominates scores of star systems across the galaxy, but not through the power of the dark side alone. Behind the scenes, the cunning Agents of Imperial Intelligence track down and eliminate the Empire's enemies--from intractable Republic Senators to traitorous Imperial Moffs to bloodthirsty rebels with Republic ties. Imperial Agents must master the arts of infiltration, seduction and assassination to advance the Empire's causes; they face the opposition of a terrified galaxy and the capriciousness of their own Sith overlords.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imperial Intelligence cultivates a notoriously vast and efficient network of informants, enabling the Agent to navigate the galaxy's political landscape with effortless suave. Naturally, the Agent's allegiance to the Empire is without question, but great latitude exists for those so closely attuned to the Empire's secret agendas; Agents often harbor their own mysterious motivations as well. Having pierced countless layers of intrigue, these spies know of conspiracies within conspiracies. Even close contacts find it hard to predict what an Imperial Agent will do until it's done.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most elite operative within Imperial Intelligence is the &quot;Cipher&quot; Agent, recruited and trained to carry out the most dangerous and sensitive assignments the Empire has to offer. Whether working undercover or carrying out assignments in broad daylight, the Cipher races along the razor's edge of disaster, using carefully orchestrated tactics that leave little room for error--the smallest slipup can be catastrophic. Each successful mission, however, shifts the galactic landscape in the Empire's favor, and the Agent plays a supremely critical role in securing Imperial domination.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relations with the Sith&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The upper echelons of Imperial society are reserved for the Force-sensitive Sith alone, but theirs is a world apart. The heart of the Empire consists of millions of subjects, descendants of the original exiles who settled Dromund Kaas. For these loyal citizens, the Imperial Agent is the exemplar of the highest level of achievement one might aspire to. These are the people the Agent risks everything to protect. Though there are few idealists in Imperial Intelligence, the art of professional perfection is held in deep reverence, and the Agent embodies the Imperial ideal in this respect.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="5" id2="480729" version="1065353216">A symbol of hope in dark times, the Jedi Knight stands for the legacy of the Jedi Order--more than 20,000 years of protecting the Republic and keeping the peace across the galaxy. Though Jedi Knights have served as generals, guerrilla fighters and warriors for generations, their legendary combat prowess faces its greatest test during this age.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Through years of disciplined training and meditation, the Jedi Knight hones body and mind into perfect harmony. Combining the foresight of the Force with unrivaled reflexes and practiced physical precision, the Knight turns combat into an art form, gracefully executing acrobatic feats in tandem with elegant lightsaber tactics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A source of inspiration to allies and intimidation to adversaries, the Jedi Knight's presence is welcome in any confrontation. The order's long history of fighting for justice has earned the trust of countless friends and the hate of innumerable enemies. Few, though, are foolish enough to challenge a seasoned Jedi Knight unless they have the skills and technology to even the odds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing the Dark Side&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jedi's dark counterparts scored many victories during the war, expanding their Empire and putting the Republic on the defensive. Since the Treaty of Coruscant, the Sith have consolidated their military might, even while the Jedi have withdrawn to Tython, a move that's been looked at with suspicion by many of the Republic's politicians. Nonetheless, the war is far from over, and the Jedi Knight's resolve remains firm. With unwavering allegiance to the Republic and the light side of the Force, the Jedi Knight fights with valiant determination, wading into the thick of any battle to protect freedom and democracy and to hold fast against those who oppose it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No matter how dire circumstances may become, the Jedi Knight trusts the Force and keeps a cool head. Knowledge and self-control are the critical components of wise decisions, and emotional and mental clarity are an absolute necessity. Maintaining focus allows the Knight to rely on intuition; a right mind leads to right action.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many, the Jedi Knight is the guardian of a precious dream; a dream of peace, a dream of justice, a dream of a brighter future. The fate of the galaxy depends upon the Knight's ability to keep this dream alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="6" id2="480729" version="1065353216">For more than 20,000 years, the Jedi Order has worked to promote peace and balance in the Galactic Republic, but each new day brings with it a new threat, promising to rip the Jedi and the entire galaxy apart. If the Republic is to survive, it needs leaders and visionaries--it needs the Jedi Consular.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jedi Consulars channel the power of the Force for strength in combat and wisdom in diplomacy. Years of arduous training and meditation have sharpened Consulars' minds to cut to the truth as cleanly as their lightsabers cut through their foes. Whether unlocking long forgotten mysteries of the Jedi, raising armies to fight for the Republic or engaging in mortal combat with Dark Lords of the Sith, the Consulars' deep attunement to the Force gives them all the power they need to rise to the occasion with poise and balance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intimate attunement with the deepest Force mysteries gives Jedi Consulars the insight and empathy to deftly handle charged conflicts that confound even the most cunning Senators and governors--but Consulars know when it's time to talk and when it's time to fight. When negotiations turn aggressive, Consulars demonstrate their gifts of foresight, anticipating and deflecting enemy attacks with fluid strikes from their dual-bladed lightsaber.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing the Darkness Within&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jedi Consulars always seek to grow their knowledge of the galaxy, in understanding of themselves, and in comprehension of the Force that binds it all together. The commitment to this pursuit gives Consulars an unrivaled capacity for clarity in situations otherwise shrouded in darkness. However, this same dedication can also prove to be extremely perilous--inviting Consulars to explore paths that are better left untraveled. Some of the Jedi Order's greatest minds have been seduced to the dark side through purely academic inquiries. The Consular knows the pain of this temptation as a battle-hardened warrior knows the throbbing of an old wound.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before they can dispel the darkness in the galaxy, Jedi Consulars know they must first come to terms with the darkness within. There's no avoiding the temptation to take shortcuts or even to use their knowledge for personal power; Consulars must constantly check their own motives. When tempted to step onto the path leading to darkness, Consulars must remember the tormented fate of the Jedi who have passed that way before. This is the only way they can unite the Jedi Order and the Republic and rally the troops to rescue the galaxy from the menacing darkness.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="7" id2="480729" version="1065353216">Sometimes luck is more important than skill, but it never hurts to have both.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawlessness has become common in the wake of the devastating war between the Republic and Empire. Shifting political allegiances and marauding pirates have made independent space travel a dangerous enterprise. Cut off from traditional supply routes, entire star systems waver on the verge of collapse. An adventurous spirit who's not afraid to break a few rules can make a handsome profit hauling cargo to these hotspots, but it requires fast reflexes, fast wits and a fast draw with a blaster. Even then, the life of a Smuggler is always a gamble.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stacking up enemies as fast as they stack up credits, Smugglers only survive in this galaxy by being slick, sneaky and street-smart. Whether sweet-talking an attractive alien or bargaining with a hardened criminal contact, the Smuggler's charm is a notorious asset, and often the ticket to turning around a deteriorating situation. If circumstances get too complicated, though, count on a Smuggler to always have an escape plan. Experienced in flying under the radar, Smugglers are amazingly elusive. Yet when backed into a corner, they quickly become cunning and often deadly combatants.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Above all else, Smugglers make their own destinies. Despite their affinity for credits, Smugglers have been known to turn down lucrative opportunities when the clients have demanded too much control. Some Smugglers are even more discriminating--refusing to work with slavers and representatives of the Sith Empire. It's a business where one is always looking for trustworthy allies, but they are often few and far between. Whether running an Imperial blockade or shooting down a double-crossing gangster, Smugglers are always flying by the seat of their pants. Every deal carries the chance for wealth beyond their wildest dreams... or an anonymous death in the harsh void of space.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relations with the Republic&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Faced with choosing an allegiance in these uncertain times, Smugglers have been forced to consider the implications of trying to operate under the tight controls imposed by the Sith Empire. Though never the most patriotic members of Republic society, many Smugglers have decided that siding with the Republic is siding with freedom, and of course, freedom is everything.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republic has never indulged a systematic prejudice against Smugglers. Generally speaking, they have more commonly tangled with laws and law enforcement measures from specific star systems, not the greater Republic. Thus, it has not been overly difficult for the Jedi and the Republic military to accept Smugglers as allies in resisting the growing dominance of the Sith Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="8" id2="480729" version="1065353216">Not all heroes carry lightsabers. Some just have the will to fight.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades, the armed forces of the Galactic Republic defended their civilization against the seemingly unstoppable Sith Empire. Despite countless setbacks, the men and women of the Republic military never backed down until the Senate ordered them to do so. These brave souls remain ready and willing to lay their lives on the line today.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of the Treaty of Coruscant, the Republic military has begun recruiting from within its own ranks, creating cutting-edge Special Forces squads for the inevitable day when the war with the Sith Empire begins anew. These advanced strike teams are comprised of only the most talented and disciplined soldiers--a new breed of elite Republic Troopers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These Troopers are the embodiment of the Republic military's highest aspirations--the most advanced fighting force in the galaxy. They are equipped to face any foe in any environment, but it's not their gear that makes them tough--it's their guts. The Troopers' greatest weapons are their indomitable spirit, their unwavering sense of duty and their undying loyalty to each other and to the ideals that the Republic represents. In this age, the stakes have never been higher. The Republic must win or face extinction. The fate of the galaxy rests upon ordinary men becoming extraordinary heroes. This is the path of the Republic Trooper.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relations with the Jedi&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Knights of the Jedi Order have defended the Republic for generations, but they have not fought alone. A host of unsung heroes have marched at the Jedi's side--common men courageous enough to enlist and face the same risks as their Jedi comrades despite not having access to the Jedi powers of protection. These heroes have not gone unappreciated by the Jedi. The men and women of the Republic military are accorded complete respect and admiration by the order and by the Republic's political leaders.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the years since the Treaty of Coruscant, the Jedi have withdrawn in significant numbers to their homeworld of Tython. Their presence in the Republic military, though still significant, is not what it was during the war. In many ways, the Republic's newly trained elite Troopers have stepped up to take charge of the Republic's defenses. When Troopers are partnered with the Jedi, they are a force to be reckoned with on any battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="100" id2="480729" version="1065353216">An unstoppable force of darkness, the Sith Warrior is entrusted with the task of destroying the Empire's enemies and enforcing Sith domination across the galaxy. The Warrior channels the destructive emotions of fear, anger and hatred to purge weakness from body and mind and become a being of pure, brutal efficiency.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Destined to eradicate the incompetent chaos created by the Jedi, the Sith seek to rule the galaxy through power and intimidation. The armies of the Sith Empire are trained to accomplish this task, but they require the leadership of bold Sith Warriors--loyal and mighty overlords--who will drive them to conquest and victory.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These cold-blooded conquerors waste no time with cunning manipulations and carefully crafted plans. Sith Warriors crush their opponents and stride toward their goals with dreadful determination, leaving ruin and annihilation in their wake. Emanating awe and terror at every step, they accept nothing but absolute obedience from their followers. In turn, Sith Warriors can serve as loyal subjects to their own dark masters, often surprising enemies and allies with their rigorous honor and perfect discipline.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether they align their ambitions with those of the Dark Council or become renegades in pursuit of their own goals, they are never far from the action. Their fierce hatred of the Jedi keeps Sith Warriors at the forefront of any conflict with the Republic. The passion to eradicate the Jedi Order fuels many of their actions, but that does not make them single-minded fools. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ultimately, the destiny of any Sith Warrior is his own to choose... and woe to those who would stand in his way. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working with Others&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Natural leaders in any context, Sith Warriors inspire both fear and undying loyalty into their followers and allies. Though they rarely exercise patience for incompetence or indecisiveness, Warriors have realized the importance of strength in numbers in their war with the Jedi and have learned to accept and sometimes even encourage their comrades, whether they are like-minded Sith, ruthless Bounty Hunters or others who embrace the darkness.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="101" id2="480729" version="1065353216">An unstoppable force of darkness, the Sith Warrior is entrusted with the task of destroying the Empire's enemies and enforcing Sith domination across the galaxy. The Warrior channels the destructive emotions of fear, anger and hatred to purge weakness from body and mind and become a being of pure, brutal efficiency.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Destined to eradicate the incompetent chaos created by the Jedi, the Sith seek to rule the galaxy through power and intimidation. The armies of the Sith Empire are trained to accomplish this task, but they require the leadership of bold Sith Warriors--loyal and mighty overlords--who will drive them to conquest and victory.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These cold-blooded conquerors waste no time with cunning manipulations and carefully crafted plans. Sith Warriors crush their opponents and stride toward their goals with dreadful determination, leaving ruin and annihilation in their wake. Emanating awe and terror at every step, they accept nothing but absolute obedience from their followers. In turn, Sith Warriors can serve as loyal subjects to their own dark masters, often surprising enemies and allies with their rigorous honor and perfect discipline.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether they align their ambitions with those of the Dark Council or become renegades in pursuit of their own goals, they are never far from the action. Their fierce hatred of the Jedi keeps Sith Warriors at the forefront of any conflict with the Republic. The passion to eradicate the Jedi Order fuels many of their actions, but that does not make them single-minded fools. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ultimately, the destiny of any Sith Warrior is his own to choose... and woe to those who would stand in his way. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working with Others&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Natural leaders in any context, Sith Warriors inspire both fear and undying loyalty into their followers and allies. Though they rarely exercise patience for incompetence or indecisiveness, Warriors have realized the importance of strength in numbers in their war with the Jedi and have learned to accept and sometimes even encourage their comrades, whether they are like-minded Sith, ruthless Bounty Hunters or others who embrace the darkness.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="200" id2="480729" version="1065353216">The history of the Sith Empire is fraught with scheming politics and dark secrets--the lifeblood of the Sith Inquisitor. Treachery hides around every corner in the Empire's dark corridors, and survival depends on an individual's natural cunning and the will to manipulate and defeat their enemies and allies alike. The Inquisitor experiments with forbidden powers to not only survive in this cutthroat environment, but to excel and seize authority.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regardless of potential, few acolytes succeed in facing the rigorous trials to become Sith Inquisitors. Only the most determined acolytes attain such an achievement, but these Sith are often the ones to watch. Due to their manipulative genius, Inquisitors are skilled at exploiting both their enemies and their allies to further their own personal agendas. Channeling this Force energy, Inquisitors are capable of draining the life from their enemies and using it to feed themselves and their allies. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though their skills are varied and many, Sith Inquisitors are most feared for their ability to channel the energy of the Force, making them a spectacle to behold on the battlefield. Seething sparks of lightning explode from the Inquisitors' fingertips and wrap their enemies in tendrils of pure Force energy. Because Inquisitors can twist the Force into lightning to stun, subdue or destroy their foes, it has become their signature. Those who have experienced the sensation of the Inquisitor's Force Lightning and survived forever recoil from the crackling sound of electricity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mastering the Dark Side&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To reach the highest echelons of power, the Inquisitor needs more than Force Lightning and a razor-sharp mind. The most formidable Inquisitors dare to explore unorthodox practices by investigating the enigmas of the past and by unlocking new powers for themselves. The Force is a source of unlimited potential--a wellspring Inquisitors tap and bend to their will. Such intensity allows Sith Inquisitors to become architects of the Empire's future... or simply the architects of their own destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="201" id2="480729" version="1065353216">The history of the Sith Empire is fraught with scheming politics and dark secrets--the lifeblood of the Sith Inquisitor. Treachery hides around every corner in the Empire's dark corridors, and survival depends on an individual's natural cunning and the will to manipulate and defeat their enemies and allies alike. The Inquisitor experiments with forbidden powers to not only survive in this cutthroat environment, but to excel and seize authority.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regardless of potential, few acolytes succeed in facing the rigorous trials to become Sith Inquisitors. Only the most determined acolytes attain such an achievement, but these Sith are often the ones to watch. Due to their manipulative genius, Inquisitors are skilled at exploiting both their enemies and their allies to further their own personal agendas. Channeling this Force energy, Inquisitors are capable of draining the life from their enemies and using it to feed themselves and their allies. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though their skills are varied and many, Sith Inquisitors are most feared for their ability to channel the energy of the Force, making them a spectacle to behold on the battlefield. Seething sparks of lightning explode from the Inquisitors' fingertips and wrap their enemies in tendrils of pure Force energy. Because Inquisitors can twist the Force into lightning to stun, subdue or destroy their foes, it has become their signature. Those who have experienced the sensation of the Inquisitor's Force Lightning and survived forever recoil from the crackling sound of electricity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mastering the Dark Side&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To reach the highest echelons of power, the Inquisitor needs more than Force Lightning and a razor-sharp mind. The most formidable Inquisitors dare to explore unorthodox practices by investigating the enigmas of the past and by unlocking new powers for themselves. The Force is a source of unlimited potential--a wellspring Inquisitors tap and bend to their will. Such intensity allows Sith Inquisitors to become architects of the Empire's future... or simply the architects of their own destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="480729" version="1065353216">Countless enemies stand in the way of the Sith Empire's drive for domination. The Empire spares no expense eliminating these threats, offering massive bounties to employ the galaxy's most lethal hunters. Earning a death mark from the Empire means a life spent in fear, constantly looking over one's shoulder. It's never a question if a Bounty Hunter will find you... only when.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both infamous and anonymous at the same time, Bounty Hunters are far more than mercenaries for hire--they're heirs to a professional legacy, an ancient brotherhood with a glorious history. Tracking elusive targets across multiple star systems requires expertise, especially when the targets can be prominent, powerful and often prepared for confrontation. Thrill seekers from all walks of life set out to become Bounty Hunters, but only the most hard-boiled survive in this competitive and deadly business. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bounty Hunter's path lies along the edge--the stakes are always high--and the path only leads two places: to a life of infamous glory... or to a quick and ignominious death. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imperial Relations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though the Empire disapproves of the Bounty Hunters' fierce independence, exceptions are made for those who get results. Few individuals in the galaxy have the gall and the stomach to deliver on the delicate and grim tasks in which Bounty Hunters excel. Nonetheless, no one is irreplaceable in the Empire, and even the most proficient must repeatedly prove their worth. In the bounty business, one's name is everything, and with each mark a Bounty Hunter takes down, his reputation grows, as does his price. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliations and Loyalties&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bounty Hunters are far from a homogeneous lot; they come from all races and affiliations and each pursues his quarry in his own unique way. Some Bounty Hunters adhere to the rugged Mandalorian code of honor while others answer only to their own moral compass. Some work only on behalf of organizations they agree with, while others have no sense of loyalty. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite being kindred spirits, fellow Bounty Hunters cannot always be trusted; among the profession's most notorious members, competition turns colleagues into the most ruthless of enemies. Even the Bounty Hunters' employers harbor hidden agendas; the tables are turned quickly when complications arise... and they always do. Shifting allegiances, unbeatable odds and deadly showdowns are common occurrences in the life of a Bounty Hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="480729" version="1065353216">Countless enemies stand in the way of the Sith Empire's drive for domination. The Empire spares no expense eliminating these threats, offering massive bounties to employ the galaxy's most lethal hunters. Earning a death mark from the Empire means a life spent in fear, constantly looking over one's shoulder. It's never a question if a Bounty Hunter will find you... only when.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both infamous and anonymous at the same time, Bounty Hunters are far more than mercenaries for hire--they're heirs to a professional legacy, an ancient brotherhood with a glorious history. Tracking elusive targets across multiple star systems requires expertise, especially when the targets can be prominent, powerful and often prepared for confrontation. Thrill seekers from all walks of life set out to become Bounty Hunters, but only the most hard-boiled survive in this competitive and deadly business. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bounty Hunter's path lies along the edge--the stakes are always high--and the path only leads two places: to a life of infamous glory... or to a quick and ignominious death. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imperial Relations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though the Empire disapproves of the Bounty Hunters' fierce independence, exceptions are made for those who get results. Few individuals in the galaxy have the gall and the stomach to deliver on the delicate and grim tasks in which Bounty Hunters excel. Nonetheless, no one is irreplaceable in the Empire, and even the most proficient must repeatedly prove their worth. In the bounty business, one's name is everything, and with each mark a Bounty Hunter takes down, his reputation grows, as does his price. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affiliations and Loyalties&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bounty Hunters are far from a homogeneous lot; they come from all races and affiliations and each pursues his quarry in his own unique way. Some Bounty Hunters adhere to the rugged Mandalorian code of honor while others answer only to their own moral compass. Some work only on behalf of organizations they agree with, while others have no sense of loyalty. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite being kindred spirits, fellow Bounty Hunters cannot always be trusted; among the profession's most notorious members, competition turns colleagues into the most ruthless of enemies. Even the Bounty Hunters' employers harbor hidden agendas; the tables are turned quickly when complications arise... and they always do. Shifting allegiances, unbeatable odds and deadly showdowns are common occurrences in the life of a Bounty Hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="400" id2="480729" version="1065353216">The Empire dominates scores of star systems across the galaxy, but not through the power of the dark side alone. Behind the scenes, the cunning Agents of Imperial Intelligence track down and eliminate the Empire's enemies--from intractable Republic Senators to traitorous Imperial Moffs to bloodthirsty rebels with Republic ties. Imperial Agents must master the arts of infiltration, seduction and assassination to advance the Empire's causes; they face the opposition of a terrified galaxy and the capriciousness of their own Sith overlords.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imperial Intelligence cultivates a notoriously vast and efficient network of informants, enabling the Agent to navigate the galaxy's political landscape with effortless suave. Naturally, the Agent's allegiance to the Empire is without question, but great latitude exists for those so closely attuned to the Empire's secret agendas; Agents often harbor their own mysterious motivations as well. Having pierced countless layers of intrigue, these spies know of conspiracies within conspiracies. Even close contacts find it hard to predict what an Imperial Agent will do until it's done.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most elite operative within Imperial Intelligence is the &quot;Cipher&quot; Agent, recruited and trained to carry out the most dangerous and sensitive assignments the Empire has to offer. Whether working undercover or carrying out assignments in broad daylight, the Cipher races along the razor's edge of disaster, using carefully orchestrated tactics that leave little room for error--the smallest slipup can be catastrophic. Each successful mission, however, shifts the galactic landscape in the Empire's favor, and the Agent plays a supremely critical role in securing Imperial domination.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relations with the Sith&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The upper echelons of Imperial society are reserved for the Force-sensitive Sith alone, but theirs is a world apart. The heart of the Empire consists of millions of subjects, descendants of the original exiles who settled Dromund Kaas. For these loyal citizens, the Imperial Agent is the exemplar of the highest level of achievement one might aspire to. These are the people the Agent risks everything to protect. Though there are few idealists in Imperial Intelligence, the art of professional perfection is held in deep reverence, and the Agent embodies the Imperial ideal in this respect.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="401" id2="480729" version="1065353216">The Empire dominates scores of star systems across the galaxy, but not through the power of the dark side alone. Behind the scenes, the cunning Agents of Imperial Intelligence track down and eliminate the Empire's enemies--from intractable Republic Senators to traitorous Imperial Moffs to bloodthirsty rebels with Republic ties. Imperial Agents must master the arts of infiltration, seduction and assassination to advance the Empire's causes; they face the opposition of a terrified galaxy and the capriciousness of their own Sith overlords.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imperial Intelligence cultivates a notoriously vast and efficient network of informants, enabling the Agent to navigate the galaxy's political landscape with effortless suave. Naturally, the Agent's allegiance to the Empire is without question, but great latitude exists for those so closely attuned to the Empire's secret agendas; Agents often harbor their own mysterious motivations as well. Having pierced countless layers of intrigue, these spies know of conspiracies within conspiracies. Even close contacts find it hard to predict what an Imperial Agent will do until it's done.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most elite operative within Imperial Intelligence is the &quot;Cipher&quot; Agent, recruited and trained to carry out the most dangerous and sensitive assignments the Empire has to offer. Whether working undercover or carrying out assignments in broad daylight, the Cipher races along the razor's edge of disaster, using carefully orchestrated tactics that leave little room for error--the smallest slipup can be catastrophic. Each successful mission, however, shifts the galactic landscape in the Empire's favor, and the Agent plays a supremely critical role in securing Imperial domination.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relations with the Sith&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The upper echelons of Imperial society are reserved for the Force-sensitive Sith alone, but theirs is a world apart. The heart of the Empire consists of millions of subjects, descendants of the original exiles who settled Dromund Kaas. For these loyal citizens, the Imperial Agent is the exemplar of the highest level of achievement one might aspire to. These are the people the Agent risks everything to protect. Though there are few idealists in Imperial Intelligence, the art of professional perfection is held in deep reverence, and the Agent embodies the Imperial ideal in this respect.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="500" id2="480729" version="1065353216">A symbol of hope in dark times, the Jedi Knight stands for the legacy of the Jedi Order--more than 20,000 years of protecting the Republic and keeping the peace across the galaxy. Though Jedi Knights have served as generals, guerrilla fighters and warriors for generations, their legendary combat prowess faces its greatest test during this age.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Through years of disciplined training and meditation, the Jedi Knight hones body and mind into perfect harmony. Combining the foresight of the Force with unrivaled reflexes and practiced physical precision, the Knight turns combat into an art form, gracefully executing acrobatic feats in tandem with elegant lightsaber tactics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A source of inspiration to allies and intimidation to adversaries, the Jedi Knight's presence is welcome in any confrontation. The order's long history of fighting for justice has earned the trust of countless friends and the hate of innumerable enemies. Few, though, are foolish enough to challenge a seasoned Jedi Knight unless they have the skills and technology to even the odds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing the Dark Side&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jedi's dark counterparts scored many victories during the war, expanding their Empire and putting the Republic on the defensive. Since the Treaty of Coruscant, the Sith have consolidated their military might, even while the Jedi have withdrawn to Tython, a move that's been looked at with suspicion by many of the Republic's politicians. Nonetheless, the war is far from over, and the Jedi Knight's resolve remains firm. With unwavering allegiance to the Republic and the light side of the Force, the Jedi Knight fights with valiant determination, wading into the thick of any battle to protect freedom and democracy and to hold fast against those who oppose it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No matter how dire circumstances may become, the Jedi Knight trusts the Force and keeps a cool head. Knowledge and self-control are the critical components of wise decisions, and emotional and mental clarity are an absolute necessity. Maintaining focus allows the Knight to rely on intuition; a right mind leads to right action.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many, the Jedi Knight is the guardian of a precious dream; a dream of peace, a dream of justice, a dream of a brighter future. The fate of the galaxy depends upon the Knight's ability to keep this dream alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="501" id2="480729" version="1065353216">A symbol of hope in dark times, the Jedi Knight stands for the legacy of the Jedi Order--more than 20,000 years of protecting the Republic and keeping the peace across the galaxy. Though Jedi Knights have served as generals, guerrilla fighters and warriors for generations, their legendary combat prowess faces its greatest test during this age.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Through years of disciplined training and meditation, the Jedi Knight hones body and mind into perfect harmony. Combining the foresight of the Force with unrivaled reflexes and practiced physical precision, the Knight turns combat into an art form, gracefully executing acrobatic feats in tandem with elegant lightsaber tactics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A source of inspiration to allies and intimidation to adversaries, the Jedi Knight's presence is welcome in any confrontation. The order's long history of fighting for justice has earned the trust of countless friends and the hate of innumerable enemies. Few, though, are foolish enough to challenge a seasoned Jedi Knight unless they have the skills and technology to even the odds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing the Dark Side&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jedi's dark counterparts scored many victories during the war, expanding their Empire and putting the Republic on the defensive. Since the Treaty of Coruscant, the Sith have consolidated their military might, even while the Jedi have withdrawn to Tython, a move that's been looked at with suspicion by many of the Republic's politicians. Nonetheless, the war is far from over, and the Jedi Knight's resolve remains firm. With unwavering allegiance to the Republic and the light side of the Force, the Jedi Knight fights with valiant determination, wading into the thick of any battle to protect freedom and democracy and to hold fast against those who oppose it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No matter how dire circumstances may become, the Jedi Knight trusts the Force and keeps a cool head. Knowledge and self-control are the critical components of wise decisions, and emotional and mental clarity are an absolute necessity. Maintaining focus allows the Knight to rely on intuition; a right mind leads to right action.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many, the Jedi Knight is the guardian of a precious dream; a dream of peace, a dream of justice, a dream of a brighter future. The fate of the galaxy depends upon the Knight's ability to keep this dream alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="600" id2="480729" version="1065353216">For more than 20,000 years, the Jedi Order has worked to promote peace and balance in the Galactic Republic, but each new day brings with it a new threat, promising to rip the Jedi and the entire galaxy apart. If the Republic is to survive, it needs leaders and visionaries--it needs the Jedi Consular.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jedi Consulars channel the power of the Force for strength in combat and wisdom in diplomacy. Years of arduous training and meditation have sharpened Consulars' minds to cut to the truth as cleanly as their lightsabers cut through their foes. Whether unlocking long forgotten mysteries of the Jedi, raising armies to fight for the Republic or engaging in mortal combat with Dark Lords of the Sith, the Consulars' deep attunement to the Force gives them all the power they need to rise to the occasion with poise and balance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intimate attunement with the deepest Force mysteries gives Jedi Consulars the insight and empathy to deftly handle charged conflicts that confound even the most cunning Senators and governors--but Consulars know when it's time to talk and when it's time to fight. When negotiations turn aggressive, Consulars demonstrate their gifts of foresight, anticipating and deflecting enemy attacks with fluid strikes from their dual-bladed lightsaber.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing the Darkness Within&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jedi Consulars always seek to grow their knowledge of the galaxy, in understanding of themselves, and in comprehension of the Force that binds it all together. The commitment to this pursuit gives Consulars an unrivaled capacity for clarity in situations otherwise shrouded in darkness. However, this same dedication can also prove to be extremely perilous--inviting Consulars to explore paths that are better left untraveled. Some of the Jedi Order's greatest minds have been seduced to the dark side through purely academic inquiries. The Consular knows the pain of this temptation as a battle-hardened warrior knows the throbbing of an old wound.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before they can dispel the darkness in the galaxy, Jedi Consulars know they must first come to terms with the darkness within. There's no avoiding the temptation to take shortcuts or even to use their knowledge for personal power; Consulars must constantly check their own motives. When tempted to step onto the path leading to darkness, Consulars must remember the tormented fate of the Jedi who have passed that way before. This is the only way they can unite the Jedi Order and the Republic and rally the troops to rescue the galaxy from the menacing darkness.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="601" id2="480729" version="1065353216">For more than 20,000 years, the Jedi Order has worked to promote peace and balance in the Galactic Republic, but each new day brings with it a new threat, promising to rip the Jedi and the entire galaxy apart. If the Republic is to survive, it needs leaders and visionaries--it needs the Jedi Consular.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jedi Consulars channel the power of the Force for strength in combat and wisdom in diplomacy. Years of arduous training and meditation have sharpened Consulars' minds to cut to the truth as cleanly as their lightsabers cut through their foes. Whether unlocking long forgotten mysteries of the Jedi, raising armies to fight for the Republic or engaging in mortal combat with Dark Lords of the Sith, the Consulars' deep attunement to the Force gives them all the power they need to rise to the occasion with poise and balance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intimate attunement with the deepest Force mysteries gives Jedi Consulars the insight and empathy to deftly handle charged conflicts that confound even the most cunning Senators and governors--but Consulars know when it's time to talk and when it's time to fight. When negotiations turn aggressive, Consulars demonstrate their gifts of foresight, anticipating and deflecting enemy attacks with fluid strikes from their dual-bladed lightsaber.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing the Darkness Within&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jedi Consulars always seek to grow their knowledge of the galaxy, in understanding of themselves, and in comprehension of the Force that binds it all together. The commitment to this pursuit gives Consulars an unrivaled capacity for clarity in situations otherwise shrouded in darkness. However, this same dedication can also prove to be extremely perilous--inviting Consulars to explore paths that are better left untraveled. Some of the Jedi Order's greatest minds have been seduced to the dark side through purely academic inquiries. The Consular knows the pain of this temptation as a battle-hardened warrior knows the throbbing of an old wound.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before they can dispel the darkness in the galaxy, Jedi Consulars know they must first come to terms with the darkness within. There's no avoiding the temptation to take shortcuts or even to use their knowledge for personal power; Consulars must constantly check their own motives. When tempted to step onto the path leading to darkness, Consulars must remember the tormented fate of the Jedi who have passed that way before. This is the only way they can unite the Jedi Order and the Republic and rally the troops to rescue the galaxy from the menacing darkness.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="700" id2="480729" version="1065353216">Sometimes luck is more important than skill, but it never hurts to have both.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawlessness has become common in the wake of the devastating war between the Republic and Empire. Shifting political allegiances and marauding pirates have made independent space travel a dangerous enterprise. Cut off from traditional supply routes, entire star systems waver on the verge of collapse. An adventurous spirit who's not afraid to break a few rules can make a handsome profit hauling cargo to these hotspots, but it requires fast reflexes, fast wits and a fast draw with a blaster. Even then, the life of a Smuggler is always a gamble.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stacking up enemies as fast as they stack up credits, Smugglers only survive in this galaxy by being slick, sneaky and street-smart. Whether sweet-talking an attractive alien or bargaining with a hardened criminal contact, the Smuggler's charm is a notorious asset, and often the ticket to turning around a deteriorating situation. If circumstances get too complicated, though, count on a Smuggler to always have an escape plan. Experienced in flying under the radar, Smugglers are amazingly elusive. Yet when backed into a corner, they quickly become cunning and often deadly combatants.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Above all else, Smugglers make their own destinies. Despite their affinity for credits, Smugglers have been known to turn down lucrative opportunities when the clients have demanded too much control. Some Smugglers are even more discriminating--refusing to work with slavers and representatives of the Sith Empire. It's a business where one is always looking for trustworthy allies, but they are often few and far between. Whether running an Imperial blockade or shooting down a double-crossing gangster, Smugglers are always flying by the seat of their pants. Every deal carries the chance for wealth beyond their wildest dreams... or an anonymous death in the harsh void of space.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relations with the Republic&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Faced with choosing an allegiance in these uncertain times, Smugglers have been forced to consider the implications of trying to operate under the tight controls imposed by the Sith Empire. Though never the most patriotic members of Republic society, many Smugglers have decided that siding with the Republic is siding with freedom, and of course, freedom is everything.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republic has never indulged a systematic prejudice against Smugglers. Generally speaking, they have more commonly tangled with laws and law enforcement measures from specific star systems, not the greater Republic. Thus, it has not been overly difficult for the Jedi and the Republic military to accept Smugglers as allies in resisting the growing dominance of the Sith Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="701" id2="480729" version="1065353216">Sometimes luck is more important than skill, but it never hurts to have both.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawlessness has become common in the wake of the devastating war between the Republic and Empire. Shifting political allegiances and marauding pirates have made independent space travel a dangerous enterprise. Cut off from traditional supply routes, entire star systems waver on the verge of collapse. An adventurous spirit who's not afraid to break a few rules can make a handsome profit hauling cargo to these hotspots, but it requires fast reflexes, fast wits and a fast draw with a blaster. Even then, the life of a Smuggler is always a gamble.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stacking up enemies as fast as they stack up credits, Smugglers only survive in this galaxy by being slick, sneaky and street-smart. Whether sweet-talking an attractive alien or bargaining with a hardened criminal contact, the Smuggler's charm is a notorious asset, and often the ticket to turning around a deteriorating situation. If circumstances get too complicated, though, count on a Smuggler to always have an escape plan. Experienced in flying under the radar, Smugglers are amazingly elusive. Yet when backed into a corner, they quickly become cunning and often deadly combatants.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Above all else, Smugglers make their own destinies. Despite their affinity for credits, Smugglers have been known to turn down lucrative opportunities when the clients have demanded too much control. Some Smugglers are even more discriminating--refusing to work with slavers and representatives of the Sith Empire. It's a business where one is always looking for trustworthy allies, but they are often few and far between. Whether running an Imperial blockade or shooting down a double-crossing gangster, Smugglers are always flying by the seat of their pants. Every deal carries the chance for wealth beyond their wildest dreams... or an anonymous death in the harsh void of space.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relations with the Republic&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Faced with choosing an allegiance in these uncertain times, Smugglers have been forced to consider the implications of trying to operate under the tight controls imposed by the Sith Empire. Though never the most patriotic members of Republic society, many Smugglers have decided that siding with the Republic is siding with freedom, and of course, freedom is everything.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republic has never indulged a systematic prejudice against Smugglers. Generally speaking, they have more commonly tangled with laws and law enforcement measures from specific star systems, not the greater Republic. Thus, it has not been overly difficult for the Jedi and the Republic military to accept Smugglers as allies in resisting the growing dominance of the Sith Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="800" id2="480729" version="1065353216">Not all heroes carry lightsabers. Some just have the will to fight.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades, the armed forces of the Galactic Republic defended their civilization against the seemingly unstoppable Sith Empire. Despite countless setbacks, the men and women of the Republic military never backed down until the Senate ordered them to do so. These brave souls remain ready and willing to lay their lives on the line today.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of the Treaty of Coruscant, the Republic military has begun recruiting from within its own ranks, creating cutting-edge Special Forces squads for the inevitable day when the war with the Sith Empire begins anew. These advanced strike teams are comprised of only the most talented and disciplined soldiers--a new breed of elite Republic Troopers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These Troopers are the embodiment of the Republic military's highest aspirations--the most advanced fighting force in the galaxy. They are equipped to face any foe in any environment, but it's not their gear that makes them tough--it's their guts. The Troopers' greatest weapons are their indomitable spirit, their unwavering sense of duty and their undying loyalty to each other and to the ideals that the Republic represents. In this age, the stakes have never been higher. The Republic must win or face extinction. The fate of the galaxy rests upon ordinary men becoming extraordinary heroes. This is the path of the Republic Trooper.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relations with the Jedi&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Knights of the Jedi Order have defended the Republic for generations, but they have not fought alone. A host of unsung heroes have marched at the Jedi's side--common men courageous enough to enlist and face the same risks as their Jedi comrades despite not having access to the Jedi powers of protection. These heroes have not gone unappreciated by the Jedi. The men and women of the Republic military are accorded complete respect and admiration by the order and by the Republic's political leaders.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the years since the Treaty of Coruscant, the Jedi have withdrawn in significant numbers to their homeworld of Tython. Their presence in the Republic military, though still significant, is not what it was during the war. In many ways, the Republic's newly trained elite Troopers have stepped up to take charge of the Republic's defenses. When Troopers are partnered with the Jedi, they are a force to be reckoned with on any battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="801" id2="480729" version="1065353216">Not all heroes carry lightsabers. Some just have the will to fight.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades, the armed forces of the Galactic Republic defended their civilization against the seemingly unstoppable Sith Empire. Despite countless setbacks, the men and women of the Republic military never backed down until the Senate ordered them to do so. These brave souls remain ready and willing to lay their lives on the line today.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of the Treaty of Coruscant, the Republic military has begun recruiting from within its own ranks, creating cutting-edge Special Forces squads for the inevitable day when the war with the Sith Empire begins anew. These advanced strike teams are comprised of only the most talented and disciplined soldiers--a new breed of elite Republic Troopers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These Troopers are the embodiment of the Republic military's highest aspirations--the most advanced fighting force in the galaxy. They are equipped to face any foe in any environment, but it's not their gear that makes them tough--it's their guts. The Troopers' greatest weapons are their indomitable spirit, their unwavering sense of duty and their undying loyalty to each other and to the ideals that the Republic represents. In this age, the stakes have never been higher. The Republic must win or face extinction. The fate of the galaxy rests upon ordinary men becoming extraordinary heroes. This is the path of the Republic Trooper.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relations with the Jedi&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Knights of the Jedi Order have defended the Republic for generations, but they have not fought alone. A host of unsung heroes have marched at the Jedi's side--common men courageous enough to enlist and face the same risks as their Jedi comrades despite not having access to the Jedi powers of protection. These heroes have not gone unappreciated by the Jedi. The men and women of the Republic military are accorded complete respect and admiration by the order and by the Republic's political leaders.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the years since the Treaty of Coruscant, the Jedi have withdrawn in significant numbers to their homeworld of Tython. Their presence in the Republic military, though still significant, is not what it was during the war. In many ways, the Republic's newly trained elite Troopers have stepped up to take charge of the Republic's defenses. When Troopers are partnered with the Jedi, they are a force to be reckoned with on any battlefield.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
