<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>24</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/gui/charcreatecombatrole.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="482853" version="1065353216">A Sith Warrior's skills with a lightsaber are unrivaled. Driving at their enemies with strong, crushing blows, Warriors quickly beat their foes into submission or death. Though the lightsaber is their primary method of attack, Warriors also use their dark command of the Force to paralyze, terrify and kill. Protected by heavy armor and their powers of intimidation, Warriors wade into the thick of the fight and unleash pure hatred and fury to eliminate all who would stand against them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Whether facing a traitorous fellow Sith or a crowd of Republic soldiers, the Inquisitor fights with unlimited fury to create a storm of destruction. Expertise in conducting Force energies further allows Inquisitors to draw upon the life essence of themselves and others. This energy can be channeled to bolster their powers, harm their foes, and even to reinvigorate their allies. An Inquisitor's skills with a lightsaber are equally impressive. Often wielding a double-bladed lightsaber, Inquisitors use quick, guileful and lethal maneuvers to strike their enemies down with astonishing speed.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="3" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Whether working for credits or principle, the Bounty Hunter pursues targets with dogged determination and methodical precision. Bounty Hunters are renowned for their versatility on the battlefield and their ability to go toe-to-toe with Force users. Their legendary abilities in this arena have earned them the nickname &quot;Jedi Killers.&quot; Whoever they must face, however, the Bounty Hunter comes armed with the most-advanced weaponry on the black market, packing heavy firepower but always keeping a variety of tricks and gadgets ready to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="4" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Relying on range, surprise and an arsenal of state-of-the-art gadgets and weaponry, the Imperial Agent enters battle with a confident strategy. Though striking from a distance or from the shadows plays to the Agent's strengths, well-equipped operatives are more than capable of evading their enemies when necessary or moving in close to quietly slide a blade between an opponent's ribs. Whether on a solo mission or working in conjunction with a strike team, this operative keeps a finger on the right button for almost any situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="5" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Whether defending allies by deflecting a barrage of blaster fire or charging in to challenge a Sith Lord, the Knight's role is crucial in any conflict. The Jedi Knight enjoys the benefit of ancient teachings that have been passed down through hundreds of generations. Combining these time-tested maneuvers with the natural guidance of the Force, the Knight is capable of achieving extraordinary feats.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="6" id2="482853" version="1065353216">The Consular's powers go far beyond meditation and mediation, and nothing illustrates this as vividly as their graceful movements in battle. Whether beset by an army of assassin droids or caught in the middle of soured negotiations, the Jedi Consular fights with an open conduit for the Force; manipulating massive forces to disable, or even destroy, their enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="7" id2="482853" version="1065353216">The Smuggler's approach to fighting is guileful and improvisational. Preferring to tip the odds in their favor from the start, Smugglers often rely on the element of surprise, using stealth and trickery to catch opponents off guard. Despite the sly tactics, they are more than capable of holding their own in a fair fight. Fast on the draw and a crack shot with a blaster, Smugglers tend to shoot first and be the last ones standing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="8" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Whether fighting as part of a small strike squad or at the forefront of a larger force, Troopers can unleash unrivaled firepower against their enemies. A rifle is a Trooper's best friend, and the military is constantly challenged to design faster, more powerful and more reliable blaster rifles every year. Wielding such rifles and wearing protective battle armor designed by the Republic's top engineers, the Trooper will not hesitate to step right into the cross fire. Whether storming a base or a battlefield, the Trooper charges into the fight, blaster-rifle blazing, to clear a path for freedom and justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="100" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Dark energies feed the insatiable rage of the Marauders, letting them dominate foes with unflinching savagery. Agile aggression is the Marauder's hallmark as they carve through opposition with unrivaled speed. The Marauder can also destroy targets slowly, prolonging their suffering with ruptured, burning wounds.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="101" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Juggernauts' tenacity is only matched by their unshakable attunement with the dark side of the Force. Capable of tearing through enemies with single swipes of their lightsabers, they shatter and slam their prey across the fields of war. When the enemy attempts to flee, the Juggernaut can chase them down with terrifying speed. Embracing the dark side of the Force, Juggernauts rise to near-invincibility to defend their allies and secure the ambitions of the Sith Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="200" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Assassins know no equal in double-bladed lightsaber combat, calling upon dark Force energies to wrack and wither their prey. They can use mysterious Force wards to grant themselves unnatural fortitude and draw the ire of their enemies. Disappearing to strike from the shadows, Assassins excel as lethal executioners. Surprise slashes tear through foes, letting the Assassin stage the next attack as they weave through enemy lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="201" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Conduits of the dark side of the Force, Sorcerers unleash corruption and ruin on their enemies without hesitation. The Sorcerer can raze entire enemy battalions with tempests of Force lightning and mind-flaying terror. Supporting their comrades, the Sorcerer wards off death itself by twisting latent Force energy into corrupted sources of revivification.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Only the bold and the foolish get between Mercenaries and their marks. Salvos of rocket fire and blaster bolts drop single opponents while combustible munitions vanquish entire groups of ill-fated prey. When Mercenaries need to give the blasters some time to cool off, they can assist their comrades with medical support to keep the crew focused and efficient through the end of the mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="482853" version="1065353216">When credits are on the line, Powertechs will wade into any scenario to subdue their prey and finish the job. They push past friend and foe alike to assault single targets or groups of enemies with uncompromising force. Impenetrable shielding lets the Powertech support their comrades by soaking up enemy fire and taunting targets to control the field and seize victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="400" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Snipers' expertise stems from honed tactical-assessment skills and the knowledge that their target will never see the shot coming. Snipers can execute single targets by tearing through defenses with unrelenting fire from long range. &quot;Safety in numbers&quot; doesn't apply to victims in the Sniper's scope. If an onslaught of assault probes and corrosive ordnances doesn't finish the job, the Sniper need only whisper their targets' coordinates to summon an overwhelming orbital strike.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="401" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Tasked with furthering the clandestine will of the Empire, Operatives are versatile tactical agents. As the tech-affluent lifeline of a strike team, Operatives wield state-of-the-art medical technology to maintain allies' health. Operatives acting in the shadows debilitate and eviscerate targets by approaching unnoticed for a sudden lethal assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="500" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Defiant foes and perilous circumstances await Guardians at every turn, requiring them to display the full range of combat acumen. When defending their allies from blaster fire, Guardians can tap into the Force to weaken the impact of incoming attacks and bolster their own protection. Following an unwavering defense, Guardians can shift to a hammering offense that leaves foes battered and dazed. A focused mind and limitless determination make Guardians key defenders at the forefront of any battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="501" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Following the teachings from generations of Jedi Battlemasters, Sentinels have become an unmatched force on the battlefield. Wielding two lightsabers with expert precision, the Sentinel can overpower the enemy with unrelenting strikes that dismantle the stoutest defenses and bring the fiercest foes to their knees. The Sentinel's expertise makes equally quick work of a single target or a group of foes.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="600" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Sages' powers are as boundless and comprehensive as their knowledge of the Force. Standing beyond the heat of the fray, the Sage offers healing and respite to allies. When engaged directly, they unleash volleys of telekinetic energy and Force power to keep foes at a distance or fling them across the battlefield. As an offensive warden, the Sage can assail multiple enemies with Force attacks that diminish and absorb the opponents' vitality.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="601" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Fit to engage opponents head on or with subtlety, the Shadow is a master of martial dexterity. Kinetic wards and defensive skills let the Shadow survive astonishing odds or protect their allies in the heart of the fray. When dealing with a single hazardous target, Shadows may veil themselves in the Force to execute opportune strikes that swiftly rend defenses and restore their own vitality.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="700" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Gunslingers assail their opponents from a distance with blaster bolts that rattle and ravage the competition. A fist full of combustible charges evens the score with radial explosives that leave entire rooms empty. If time isn't of the essence, the Gunslinger can mock foes with shots that debilitate and maim, allowing the scuffle to last just long enough to leave a lasting impression.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="701" id2="482853" version="1065353216">It's a ruthless galaxy out there, and the Scoundrel is just the person to tackle it with a smile and a whip of their scattergun. When &quot;clean-up&quot; is necessary after a deal goes sour, Scoundrels can pummel their way out of any opposition. If the fist doesn't finish the job, a quick blast of the scattergun will. Healing is no trouble for the Scoundrel, as their skill in back-alley medicine lets them mend friends in a scrap to keep the momentum alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="800" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Providing artillery support to tactical operations and assault squads, Commandos dominate their foes through relentless firepower. Assault-cannon sieges rapidly dismantle single targets, and when an enemy station requires comprehensive destruction, the Commando can cause pandemonium with a salvo of incendiary projectiles. Following Republic military regulations, Commandos can perform impromptu medical assistance in hazardous environments to keep squads fit and primed.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="801" id2="482853" version="1065353216">Leading the charge into any encounter, Vanguards hit the front line with the force of a heavy artillery round. Vanguards go toe-to-toe with their foes, assaulting them with rifle fire, energy bursts and a well-placed vibroblade to the gut. When enemy forces cluster in a final defense, the Vanguard razes their numbers with a shower of plasma at point-blank range. Top-of-the-line shielding lets Vanguards protect their allies and storm through all opposition as an unyielding bulwark of freedom.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
