<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>24</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/gui/charcreateequipment.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="480731" version="1065353216">Despite their reliance on their strength in the Force, Warriors have no compunction about donning heavy and intimidating suits and armors. Unthreatened by the use of technology for biological augmentation, Warriors' vestments often make use of dangerous and experimental components that imbue the wearer with immense strength and fortitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="480731" version="1065353216">Asserting power and authority is one of the highest priorities for the Sith Inquisitors. Their choice of attire reflects this strategy, as they often prefer dark, high-contrast robes to express their sophisticated tastes and ambitions for political control. Nonetheless, despite regal appearances, great attention is given to ensure all their attire allows the flexibility for stunning acrobatics in lightsaber combat. Of course, some Inquisitor outfits take expression to the highest extreme--designed to inspire sheer terror in those the Inquisitor comes into contact with.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="3" id2="480731" version="1065353216">Preparation is the Bounty Hunter's best defense, and cutting-edge protective gear is standard equipment for most Bounty Hunters. Artisans spend months and even years handcrafting the Bounty Hunters' heavy armor to ensure it offers superior resistance to all manner of weaponry, and that each suit will still allow maximum flexibility and versatility. Offense is just as critical as defense, however, and powerful weaponry is necessary for Bounty Hunters who might have to shoot their way out of a messy situation. It's not unheard of for a Bounty Hunter to spend as many credits on an advanced blaster as others might spend to purchase an entire starship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="4" id2="480731" version="1065353216">The Empire risks everything on the Imperial Agent's performance and spares no expense to make sure Agents' gear is as smart as they are. State-of-the-art attire with high-grade armor mesh provides protection and ease of movement. Many of the Agent's outfits are augmented with advanced communications technology and attachments to facilitate interfacing with varied computer networks and security systems.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="5" id2="480731" version="1065353216">The galaxy has been plagued by war for decades, and despite the Treaty of Coruscant, the Jedi have no delusions about the constant danger. Though traditional Jedi robes range from light cloth to thick leathers, many Jedi Knights also wear parts or entire suits of heavy armor when going into battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="6" id2="480731" version="1065353216">Preferring to stay as nimble on the battlefield as they are in negotiations, Jedi Consulars avoid the heavy battle armor worn by many Jedi Knights. Dense polymers and cortosis armors would weigh them down; light cloaks and ornamented robes suit their strengths better, and the efforts they most often find themselves engaged in. No matter where they go, however, Consulars are never without the lightsaber that marks their initiation into the Jedi Order.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="7" id2="480731" version="1065353216">They don't wear fancy armor or carry high-powered blaster rifles, but Smugglers are outfitted for action nonetheless. Wearing comfortable, flexible clothing with some custom modifications, Smugglers are able to stay light on their feet and quick on the draw. Usually carrying a fast-firing blaster or two, Smugglers have everything they need to shoot their way out of trouble. Though style is rarely their intent, it seems to come naturally to Smugglers, and their dashing duds generally complement their roguish charm.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="8" id2="480731" version="1065353216">The Republic's experiments with a new generation of heavy blaster rifles have proven successful, sparking a galaxy-wide trend towards larger, more powerful and more versatile armaments. It takes a great deal of strength and training, however, to wield these war machines, so they're rarely used outside the military. Republic engineers have also worked overtime fashioning new defensive gear for the Republic's most elite soldiers, armor suits that provide maximum protection and flexibility in multiple environments.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="100" id2="480731" version="1065353216">Flexible armors and adrenal enhancers propel Marauders across the battlefield while imbedded cybernetic fortifiers grant them unmatched speed and response. Wielding two lightsabers to both intimidate and eviscerate anyone they face, the Marauder cleaves through foes of any size or number with absolute efficiency.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="101" id2="480731" version="1065353216">While rage and resilience drive the boundless fortitude of the Juggernaut, brawny suits of durasteel and augmented plate let them shrug off injuries received in their onslaughts. Imperial engineering has supplied experimental components and metabolic enhancers that infuse the Juggernaut's lightsaber blows with sinister might and unparalleled power.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="200" id2="480731" version="1065353216">One with the shadows, Assassins don obscuring cloaks and malice-imbued vestments. The double-bladed lightsaber-the Assassin's ultimate tool of execution-is quick to ignite within their hands, striking down any who block their ambitions. Using a dark side Force focus, Assassins amplify their aggression, becoming an unstoppable wraith of death.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="201" id2="480731" version="1065353216">Sith Sorcerers select robes to supplement their sophisticated tastes and fear-inducing visages. Dark foci collected from the tombs of forgotten Sith Lords offer unnatural sources of power. While Sorcerers relies on malign manipulations of Force energy, their lightsabers remain at their side as instruments of dark channeling and Sith status.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="480731" version="1065353216">When a mark hides behind fortified defenses or a trigger-happy guard, the Mercenary relies on cutting-edge weapons and armor to pound them into submission. Dual pistols charged with high-powered rounds complement Mercenaries' volleys of missiles and incendiary ordnances. Heavy armors augmented with sophisticated energy shielding and kolto dispersion systems ensure the Mercenary survives to get paid for a job well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="480731" version="1065353216">To tread into perilous environments and unknown hazards in search of their mark, the Powertech become a mobile fortress of destruction. Well-earned credits go into outfitting Powertechs with augmented durasteel plate and impregnable shield technologies. With only a single blaster visible at all times, the Powertech masks the full array of their combustion and immolation tech until they are on top of their quarry.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="400" id2="480731" version="1065353216">Top-grade tactical suits and coats lined with armor mesh protect Snipers from wounds that would otherwise jeopardize the success of the Empire's most sensitive schemes. Rifles equipped with state-of-the-art telescopic technology and armor-piercing rounds allow Snipers to dispatch sensitive targets with the utmost accuracy and efficiency.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="401" id2="480731" version="1065353216">Discretion and secretive stratagems require precise toolsets and attire to guarantee the success of Imperial Intelligence's top Operatives. Flexible leathers and lightweight field armor reinforced with climate-regulating tech grant unhindered movement during covert operations. When an assignment requires subtlety, Operatives turn to their deadly vibroknives to silence their targets.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="500" id2="480731" version="1065353216">The Jedi Guardian must always be prepared to defend the people of the Republic with lightsaber in hand. Guardians complement the traditional heavy cloth and sturdy leather robes of their Order with parts or entire suits of heavy armor. These armors are specially designed to ward off blaster fire and lightsaber strikes while still offering enhanced mobility.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="501" id2="480731" version="1065353216">To weave through the battlefield with minimal hindrance, the Jedi Sentinel forgoes full suits of armor for tough leathers and heavy robes. Where one lightsaber suffices for many Jedi Knights, Sentinels have mastered the efficiency of dual lightsaber combat. Unrestricted attire and nimble movement make them peerless duelists.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="600" id2="480731" version="1065353216">Sages require attire that permits unwavering focus in diplomatic and combat scenarios alike. Light cloaks and ornamented robes grant effortless movement and an unrestricted connection to the Force. Jedi Sages proudly display their lightsabers at their sides, reminding them of their virtuous purpose and place in the Jedi Order.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="601" id2="480731" version="1065353216">To move unseen through hostile territory, the Jedi Shadow requires equipment that embodies both balance and subtlety. Light cloth and concealing robes give Jedi Shadows their hallmark agility and unparalleled stealth. With honed finesse in double-bladed lightsaber combat, Shadows are prepared to end any engagement before wandering eyes find them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="700" id2="480731" version="1065353216">Gunslingers don't need fancy armor or high-caliber armaments to whittle down their foes in an old-fashioned firefight. Donning flexible vests or dashing dusters, Gunslingers always aim to stay light on their feet and quick on the draw. They wield two blasters to give them a definite edge while displaying their undeniable roguish charm.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="701" id2="480731" version="1065353216">The encumbrances of heavy armor and bulky weaponry are the last thing a Scoundrel wants in a shower of blaster fire. Comfortably fitting clothing with face-concealing masks and stealth-enhancing modifications are all they need to slide past wary guards or an automated defense grid. When their trusty pistol falls short, Scoundrels are quick to reach for their scatterguns to even the odds with a point-blank punch of searing shrapnel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="800" id2="480731" version="1065353216">To face down the enemies of peace and freedom, the Republic's Commandos require ordnances that rival the power of its most sophisticated ground assault vehicles. Outfitted with next-generation heavy armor for maximum protection with unhindered mobility, Commandos are ready to wade into any firefight. With an assault cannon and a bandolier of demolitions at the ready, Commandos prove no foe can withstand the fury of their arsenal.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="801" id2="480731" version="1065353216">Vanguards call for state-of-the-art armaments and protection to face down the enemies of justice. The brilliant minds of Republic engineering have fashioned revolutionary plate armors and on-board shield generators capable of withstanding punishment in the field. Blaster rifles armed with plasma and ion discharge capacitors let the Vanguard turn a steadfast defensive into an unstoppable offense at a moment's notice to guarantee victory.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
