<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>24</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/gui/charcreateabilities.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="480730" version="1065353216">The Sith Warrior is a fearsome melee combatant skilled with both single and dual lightsabers.  The Sith Warrior uses Dark Force powers in addition to his close range saber attacks, though not as many as the Sith Inquisitor.  

Warriors who become Sith Juggernauts continue to specialize in single saber combat, and may learn defensive lightsaber forms to help shield themselves and allies from incoming attacks.  

Warriors who become Sith Marauders become versed in combat with two lightsabers, and learn powerful attacks that utilize both weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="480730" version="1065353216">The Sith Inquisitor is deadly due to his skill with single and double-bladed lightsabers, as well as his ability to fire powerful bursts of Force Lightning from his fingertips.  

Inquisitors who pursue the Sith Sorcerer path learn to master Force Lightning and other dark Force attacks, inspiring fear and dread in their enemies, siphoning the life out of them, or using the powers of the Force to restore life to their allies.   

Those pursuing the Sith Assassin path learn to cloak themselves in shadows, sneaking up behind enemies with their double-bladed lightsaber and unleashing saber and lightning attacks at close range.  Some Sith Assassins specialize in defensive abilities, allowing them to shield themselves and their allies from harm.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="3" id2="480730" version="1065353216">The Bounty Hunter is a heavily armored fighter who specializes in the use of a number of heavy weapons.  All Bounty Hunters are skilled in the use of blaster pistols, as well as missile attacks and close-range flamethrower barrages.  Their blasters can be loaded with different gas cylinders, allowing them to change the functionality of their blasters for the needs of any battle.  

Bounty Hunters who become Powertechs power up their close range attacks, learning new flamethrower attacks, attacks using retractable bladed weapons, and new explosive attacks.  

Bounty Hunters who become Mercenaries learn to use a second blaster,  and learn many new ranged attacks, including specialized tracer and heatseeking missiles, new dual-blaster barrages, and new explosive attacks.  Some Mercenaries may specialize in combat medicine and become effective medics.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="4" id2="480730" version="1065353216">The Imperial Agent is an unparalleled marksman with a rifle, but can also utilize a number of high-tech weapons to assist in combat.  Agents use several types of grenades, poisons and acids, offensive and defensive probe droids, energy blades, and may even call in help from Imperial forces orbiting the planet to destroy tough enemies.  

Agents who specialize as Snipers upgrade to the longer range Sniper Rifle, and will utilize both environmental cover and their portable cover generator to avoid enemy fire.  

Agents who become Operatives learn to better utilize their close-range energy blade, and use their personal stealth generator to sneak behind enemies and gut them with blade attacks.  Some Operatives may use Imperial medical technology to keep their allies healed.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="5" id2="480730" version="1065353216">The Jedi Knight is a master of lightsaber combat.  The Knight's abilities focus on the use of single and dual lightsabers both as devastating offensive weapons, and powerful protective implements.  The Knight occasionally uses Force powers in addition to his close range saber attacks, though not as much as the Jedi Consular.  

Knights who become Jedi Guardians will continue to specialize in single saber combat, and may learn defensive lightsaber forms to help shield themselves and allies from incoming attacks. 

Knights who become Jedi Sentinels become versed in combat with two lightsabers, and learn powerful attacks that utilize both weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="6" id2="480730" version="1065353216">The Jedi Consular is versed in both powerful Force attacks and close-range combat with the double-bladed lightsaber.  

Consulars who pursue the Jedi Sage path will find themselves masters of telekinetic attacks, using the Force to knock enemies around and hurl objects at them.  Some Sages may also learn restorative abilities that use the Force to heal their allies. 

Those that pursue the path of the Shadow are able to use the Force to sneak close to enemies without being seen,  then using the element of surprise to best enemies in melee combat with their double-bladed lightsaber.  Some Jedi Shadows specialize in defensive abilities, allowing them to shield themselves and their allies from harm.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="7" id2="480730" version="1065353216">While the Smuggler is primarily skilled in the use of blaster pistols, he can also use an arsenal of gadgets and tech to help him gain the upper hand in combat.  Smugglers use many types of grenades, as well as flashbombs, scramblers, smoke bombs, shield generators, and weapon modifications.  

Smugglers who become Gunslingers learn to use two pistols, and will utilize both environmental cover and their portable cover generator to avoid enemy fire.  

Smugglers who become Scoundrels will use their personal stealth generator to sneak up behind enemies and blast them from behind with a powerful scattergun.  Some Scoundrels may learn medical techniques to help keep their allies healed.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="8" id2="480730" version="1065353216">The Trooper is a heavy weapons expert.   All Troopers are skilled in the use of blaster rifles, as well as powerful grenade launchers capable of firing explosive rounds and volleys of incendiary mortars.  Their rifles can be loaded with many types of ammunition, allowing the Trooper to tailor his gun's performance for the needs of any battle.  

Troopers who become Vanguards continue using blaster rifles, but also carry powerful shield generators that help them survive tough fights.  

Troopers who become Commandos learn to use assault cannons, massive underslung weapons capable of firing powerful incendiary rounds and other heavy ammunition.  Some Commandos may specialize in battlefield medicine and become effective combat medics.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="100" id2="480730" version="1065353216">As the personified rage of the Sith Empire, Marauders cut through legions in a flash of sparks and fury. Carnage Marauders swiftly carve through opponents with a storm of lightsaber strikes and debilitating attacks. Annihilation Marauders prefer to enact prolonged suffering, rupturing their prey with strikes that cause lasting pain and searing wounds. With the dark side sustaining their rage, Fury Marauders crush their victims in a blitz of lightsaber and Force attacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="101" id2="480730" version="1065353216">Juggernauts are the embodiment of the brawn and fortitude of the Sith Empire. Rage Juggernauts are torrents of destruction on the battlefield who wield their ferocity to obliterate all who stand against them. Vengeance Juggernauts tap into the dark side of the Force to impale their foes and shatter their resolve with menacing tenacity. Imbued with dark Force energies, Immortal Juggernauts tear through legions of foes with crushing blows that rend their opponents' defenses while bolstering their own.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="200" id2="480730" version="1065353216">Assassins harness the powers of subterfuge and the dark side to tear their foes asunder. Deception Assassins hide in the shadows, preparing assaults that ravage their quarry in a blaze of lightning-infused lightsaber strikes. Hatred Assassins employ leeching strikes that drain the life from their foes. Darkness Assassins raise shadowy wards to defend themselves and drain their opponents as they savage the enemies of the Sith Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="201" id2="480730" version="1065353216">Sorcerers are fonts of dark energy from the forbidden depths of the Force. Lightning Sorcerers master the Sith art of Force Lightning, summoning torrents of energy to overwhelm foes from a distance. Madness Sorcerers thread their fingers through their foes' minds, damaging their sanity and leeching their life essence. Aiming to conquer death itself, Corruption Sorcerers twist the Force around their allies to revivify and sustain them in their continued service to the Sith Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="480730" version="1065353216">Mercenaries are versatile weapon specialists with exceptional skill in taking out targets from a distance. Ordnance Mercenaries welcome chaos in their contracts, besieging with explosive and piercing munitions for lasting damage to anyone who survive the initial assault. Arsenal Mercenaries decimate their foes with heat-seeking missiles, blaster fire and tracer missiles that mark their quarry for ongoing destruction. Bodyguard Mercenaries employ recuperative scans and kolto technology to keep their allies safe in even the deadliest warzone.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="480730" version="1065353216">Investments in revolutionary shielding and weapons technology make the Powertech a lone war machine against any number of foes. Advanced Prototype Powertechs use retractable blades and magnetized melee-suppression technology to subdue their quarry with minimal resistance. Pyrotechs unleash steams of fire and incendiary ordinances to quell their mark with an overwhelming inferno. Shield Techs charge into the fray with infallible defenses to spray their opponents with a variety of debilitating and damaging tech-based attacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="400" id2="480730" version="1065353216">Snipers are Imperial Intelligence's elite executioners who have mastered the art of eliminating targets at a distance. Marksmanship Snipers understand lining up a perfect shot, keeping to cover as they tear through enemies with penetrating blasts and calculated ambushes. Engineering Snipers employ an array of combat probes to rain plasma, shrapnel and electricity upon victims. Virulence Snipers appreciate the prolonged agony and debilitating effects of lethal toxins, maintaining a safe distance as they barrage foes with acid grenades and noxious weapon effects.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="401" id2="480730" version="1065353216">Operatives are Imperial Intelligence's premier agents of stealth and subterfuge. Concealment Operatives leap from the shadows to lacerate and cripple their prey with a series of vibroknife strikes. Lethality Operatives believe that no martial skill can match a good toxin, choosing to unleash corrosive assaults and toxic blasts that turn enemies into withered husks. Medicine Operatives use their extensive survival knowledge to mend allies with kolto and recuperative nanotechnology.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="500" id2="480730" version="1065353216">Jedi Guardians are icons of hope and justice across the galaxy. Disciplined in protective Force techniques, Defense Guardians don an aegis of willpower to batter opponents and persevere against all odds. Vigilance Guardians employ a dominant offense, plunging into the thick of combat as a maelstrom of lightsaber strikes and Force attacks. Focus Guardians manipulate the Force around them to exhaust enemies beneath a constant bombardment of Force and lightsaber blows.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="501" id2="480730" version="1065353216">Focus and a calculated approach mark Sentinels as the paramount warriors of the Jedi Order. Using deft lightsaber slashes to overwhelm their opponents, Combat Sentinels subdue oppressors with precision strikes and unparalleled swordsmanship. Watchman Sentinels rely on calculated blows that dismantle their foes overtime, melting defenses and weakening resolve over the course of combat. Melding their minds with the flow of Force, Concentration Sentinels batter their enemies with bursts of Force power and focused strikes that exhaust even the toughest opponents over the course of a melee.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="600" id2="480730" version="1065353216">Renowned for their wisdom and meditative prowess, Sages are viewed as avatars of the Force among the Jedi Order. Seer Sages reach into their innermost selves to cure and rejuvenate their allies. Telekinetic Sages hone their connection to the world around them, summoning gales of raw Force power to scatter their foes. Balance Sages tap directly into the Force to revitalize their own reserves and simultaneously dismantle large groups of opponents.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="601" id2="480730" version="1065353216">Shadows embrace a balance between melee combat and Force techniques to subtly dispatch any foes they are forced to face. Serenity Shadows follow the ebb and flow of the Force around them, weaving a series of blows that sap the target's vitality while replenishing their own. Focusing on opportune strikes and a stealthy approach, Infiltration Shadows cut through enemies with a crescendo of strikes that they never see coming. Kinetic Combat Sages use Force-based techniques that block enemy attacks while employing defensive strategies to control the flow of battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="700" id2="480730" version="1065353216">Masters of long-range combat and evasive maneuvers, Gunslingers provide the sly firepower to pull off any job. The Sharpshooter is a twin-blaster ace who uses trick shots and penetrating fire to rapidly resolve any hostilities. Saboteurs specialize in dispatching foes with a rain of incendiary grenades and sabotage charges, adding flair to any skirmish. When the occasion calls for a more sinister approach, the Dirty Fighting Gunslinger unleashes canny tricks that engulf enemies in blaster fire and shrapnel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="701" id2="480730" version="1065353216">Moving in and out of combat to confuse their opponents, Scoundrels are tactical rogues prepared for any scenario. The Scrapper flies into the fray to pummel foes beneath a barrage of crippling blows and blasts to weaken their resolve. Ruffians are dedicated opportunists who incite chaos with shrapnel bombs and maiming shots before moving in to finish the job at immediate range. Sawbones Scoundrels provide the necessary boosts from underworld medicine to keep their allies alive and aware in even the direst circumstances.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="800" id2="480730" version="1065353216">The Commando is a ground-assault specialist proficient in demolitions operations and strike-team deployments. Gunnery Commandos overpower foes with barrages of assault-cannon fire and gravity-manipulating munitions. Assault Specialist Commandos tear through enemy lines with a hail of incendiary rounds and demolitions. Combat Medics tend to wounded comrades with kolto boosts and medical probes to see the mission through.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="801" id2="480730" version="1065353216">As the first line of defense in the Republic military, Vanguards meet their foes with brute force and unwavering willpower. Plasmatech Vanguards wield unrivaled incendiary armaments as a mobile force of destructive power. Tactics Vanguards charge into the fray to suppress the enemy with a torrent of vibroblade slashes and energy burns. Shield Specialists storm into battle with sophisticated ion shielding and defensive tech to conquer any aggressor.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
