<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>24</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/gui/classdescriptions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="194653" version="1065353216">No one inspires more fear than a Sith Warrior. Born for battle, few opponents can withstand the rage-fueled blows from a Warrior's lightsaber or penetrate a Warrior's armor. If dual-wielded lightsabers can't finish the job, there is always Force Choke to bring an opponent to his knees.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="194653" version="1065353216">Where a Sith Warrior is rage, an Inquisitor is cunning. A master of Force Lightning and arcane secrets, the Inquisitor can hold one enemy in the air and stun another all the while attacking with lightsaber moves designed for maximum pain.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="3" id2="194653" version="1065353216">A thorough professional, the Bounty Hunter trains mind and body for every possible job. Blasters, flamethrowers, missiles, energy shields, jetpack and the best armor money can buy--the name of the game is preparation and versatility.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="4" id2="194653" version="1065353216">Behind every Imperial surprise attack, each sabotage, all the great betrayals, was an Imperial Agent. Armed for stealth and assassination, Agents do the jobs nobody else can and as such are trained to use everything from sleeping darts to sniper rifles, stealth belts and knives to advanced probe droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="5" id2="194653" version="1065353216">Leaders and warriors, heroes and champions, the Jedi Knights have stood at the forefront of every battle. They are masters of the lightsaber arts, kicking, jumping and flashing through the air and using the Force to clear the way in front of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="6" id2="194653" version="1065353216">A master of the secrets of the Force, the Jedi Consular is both fighter and healer, teacher and student. The Force can be used to cloud the minds of the weak, restore strength to the fallen and hurl both opponents and objects through the air.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="7" id2="194653" version="1065353216">Living life by their own rules, Smugglers are the galaxy's most unpredictable characters. They dress for ease of movement--with a healthy dose of style--carry one or dual blasters and are always ready to shoot first, stealth up and sneak away after.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="8" id2="194653" version="1065353216">Across the galaxy, the Republic's elite Special Forces drop into the harshest conflicts ready to do maximum damage. Outfitted with advanced armor, huge weaponry and the best training possible, Troopers combine leadership with suppression fire, a variety of explosives and incendiary weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="100" id2="194653" version="1065353216">Entrusted with the task of destroying the Empire's enemies, the dual-wielding Marauder embodies the teachings of Naga Sadow. Never hesitating, never faltering, there is no swifter bringer of pain in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="101" id2="194653" version="1065353216">A stalwart defender of the Sith Empire, the Juggernaut embodies the teachings of Marka Ragnos, charging into enemies with heavy armor and pure rage.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="200" id2="194653" version="1065353216">Assassins leap from the shadows, channeling Force Lightning through their double-bladed lightsabers to disable and drain their enemies. They are masters of subterfuge, feared by even the most terrible opponents.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="201" id2="194653" version="1065353216">The Sith Sorcerer draws energy from the forbidden depths of the Force, mastering techniques that sap and drain enemies as they invigorate allies--or simply wreak utter devastation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="194653" version="1065353216">A pair of blasters, deadly heat-seeking missiles and heavy armor make the Mercenary a mobile weapons platform. There's no problem extra firepower can't solve, and no one with sense gets between a Mercenary and their target.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="194653" version="1065353216">The best in shielding, defensive tactics and high-powered flamethrowers combine to make the Powertech an impenetrable one-man blockade, getting up close and personal to take down enemies of all sizes.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="400" id2="194653" version="1065353216">Identified as the most elite sharpshooters in the galaxy, Snipers use their extensive training to eliminate sensitive targets and turn the tide of the battle in the Empire's favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="401" id2="194653" version="1065353216">Whether ambushing enemies from stealth or using advanced medical technology to keep colleagues in the fight, the Operative will do whatever it takes to advance the agenda of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="500" id2="194653" version="1065353216">A wall between the good people of the Republic and their enemies, the Guardian stands firm in the face of overwhelming odds and dares opponents to attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="501" id2="194653" version="1065353216">Control and focus are the hallmarks of the Sentinel. Through years of training, the Sentinel learns the art of using two lightsabers simultaneously to create an intricate web of damage that is almost impossible to evade.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="600" id2="194653" version="1065353216">Sages are famed for their wisdom as much as for their powerful healing and defensive skills. In troubled times, a Sage brings together the insight of the past with raw power to change the flow of galactic events.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="601" id2="194653" version="1065353216">Wielding double-bladed lightsabers, Shadows embrace the synergy between melee and Force combat, enabling them to strike down enemies of the order with deadly efficiency.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="700" id2="194653" version="1065353216">Master of the trick shot and willing to take advantage of every opportunity, the Gunslinger learns how to fire two blasters at once, specializing in long-range combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="701" id2="194653" version="1065353216">In addition to a trusty blaster, Scoundrels pack a stealth belt, a scattergun and a medpac--everything they need to get in, knock the enemy for a loop and get out alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="800" id2="194653" version="1065353216">Trained in advanced assault tactics and weaponry, Commandos charge into battle with massive assault cannons, overwhelming their enemies with brute firepower.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="801" id2="194653" version="1065353216">Unstoppable and utterly fearless, Vanguards are the first and best line of defense in the Republic military.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
