<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>48</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/gui/disciplines.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="785481" version="1065353216">The Seer Sage is the rejuvenation master of Consulars, assisting with an array of Force healing powers that grant allies the strength to continue though even the harshest of encounters. Separated from the heart of the fray, the Seer can be an unfailing warden to those in need.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="785481" version="1065353216">There is serenity in balance, and no one knows this better than the Balance Sage. Able to assail multiple targets at once while at the same time absorbing their vitality, the Balance Sage is a formidable presence in long-range engagements.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="785481" version="1065353216">At one with the environment, the Telekinetic Sage manipulates the essence of the surrounding elements with the power of the Force to mount powerful distance attacks. Waves of turbulence and torrential gusts of telekinetic energy make for a potent combination that can pummel even the toughest adversaries into submission.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Launching into the fray with a jetpack-propelled attack and able to withstand powerful offenses, the Powertech trained in the Shield Tech specification takes the brunt of the assault while employing a wide range of tech-based attacks to scorch and trip up even the most formidable adversaries.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Need a light? The Pyrotech-style Powertech adds fuel to any firefight with an abundance of vivid, searing flame attacks. From fistfuls of fire to missiles loaded with highly combustible compounds, the Pyrotech's arsenal allows them to never back down while making sure their enemy burns out in a blaze of destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="785481" version="1065353216">When stalking dangerous prey, a selection of powerful, high-tech armaments can be a hunter's best friend. The Advanced Prototype Powertech's thermal detonators, gauntlet blades and magnetized bracers devastate their intended target while ensuring the Powertech remains on the bleeding edge of any engagement.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Storming to the front line with a powerful charge, the Shield Specialist Vanguard can withstand any incoming offensive. The Shield Specialist boldly takes the brunt of the attack while employing a wide range of tech-based attacks to gas, blast and jolt their enemies into oblivion.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Vanguards adamant on burning their way through hostile forces can do so effectively with the latest in weaponized plasma technology. The Plasmatech Vanguard stands their own, striking their enemy with waves and rounds of raw incendiary power that persist in their searing destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="785481" version="1065353216">The Tactics Vanguard is a pro at executing a focused line of attack on a hostile target with great efficiency. From up-close vibroblades in the gut to deadly charges of explosive plastique thrown from a distance, all manner of effective strategies for eliminating enemies are at the Tactics Vanguard's disposal.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="785481" version="1065353216">The Bodyguard Mercenary specializes in personal-security services, positioning themselves as the best protection credits can buy. A varied array of kolto dispersement instruments provide the Bodyguard's targets with protective shells and time-release infusions, offering safe haven in even the most hostile environments.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="785481" version="1065353216">The Arsenal Mercenary specializes in distance attacks, employing long-range weapons to demolish anyone unlucky enough to be in their sights. Devastating missile-fire combinations and relentless blaster volleys generate a spectacle of explosive brilliance and transform the Bounty Hunter into a virtual artillery platform.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Taking advantage of chaos they've created is what the Innovative Ordnance Mercenary is all about. With an arsenal of explosive and piercing munitions, the I.O. Merc's barrages of missiles, grenades and weapon blasts cause lasting, destructive damage to all their enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="785481" version="1065353216">The dark side of the Force provides many benefits, including the ability to ward off death itself. By conjuring a series of arcane Force abilities from out of harm's way, the Corruption Sorcerer can sustain injured allies, allowing them to fight on with the power of the dark side's twisted gift.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Of all the dark arts of the Sith, little can match the spectacle and devastation of Force lightning. Summoning intense discharges of pure Force energy, the Lightning Sorcerer overwhelms enemies with punishing damage from a distance, leaving them shaken and vulnerable--if not dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="785481" version="1065353216">As a Smuggler who finds nothing honorable about losing in a scrap, the Dirty Fighting Gunslinger doesn't pull punches. Lobbed bombs and cheap shots are just a sampling of the Dirty Fighting Gunslinger's bag of cruel tricks that can cause their target untold continuous suffering while the Gunslinger stands back with a satisfied smile.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Just behind the front line, the Combat Medic Commando uses medical know-how and an array of tools to keep their allies in pristine fighting shape. Damage monitoring equipment and advanced kolto delivery systems allow the Combat Medic to maintain the offense's forward momentum.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="785481" version="1065353216">The Gunnery Commando specializes in ranged cannon attacks, employing long-range weapons to demolish anyone unlucky enough to be in their sights. Devastating blaster round combinations and relentless assault cannon volleys generate a spectacle of explosive brilliance and transform the Commando into a virtual blaster storm.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Using the chaos of the battlefield to their advantage is the Assault Specialist Commando's forte. Loaded to the brim with incendiary ordnance and perforating bolts, the Assault Specialist's volleys and explosions add to the pandemonium--causing massive damage to their enemies all the while.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="785481" version="1065353216">In darkness, there is protection. A Darkness Assassin acts in defense of their allies, using the dark side of the Force to ward off attacks and launch powerful channels of Force lightning while standing their ground against even the most formidable enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="785481" version="1065353216">From the murky depths of the dark side, the Deception Assassin emerges with a calculated plan. As the Assassin presses the attack, Force lightning accumulates within their double-bladed lightsaber and culminates in a massive discharge that can ravage the Assassin's opponent before they even know what hit them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Hate fuels the dark side of the Force, and no one knows this better than the Hatred Assassin. Able to command dark Force powers that assault many targets at once or sap an enemy's very essence from a distance, the Hatred Assassin can also stand face-to-face against any foe.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Some Agents prefer a less direct method of eliminating a target, such as administering poison. Lethal toxins and all-consuming microbes are the domain of the walking biohazard known as the Virulence Sniper, who inflicts lethal shots and lobs corrosive grenades from a safe distance where they can witness the results of their handiwork.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="785481" version="1065353216">One of the perks of being a Smuggler is access to all the latest tools of any trade--including the many high-tech charges and grenades in the Saboteur Gunslinger's arsenal. Able to wreak havoc on their intended target from a safe distance, the Saboteur is a crafty, resourceful and incendiary master of mayhem.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="785481" version="1065353216">One perfect shot has the potential to change everything, and no one is more precise than the Marksmanship Sniper. From the safety of cover, the Marksmanship Sniper ambushes the enemy and follows up with an encore of penetrating blasts that make extra sure the Sniper's job is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="785481" version="1065353216">As the toughest of the Warriors, the Immortal Juggernaut can withstand even the most brutal assaults. Using the Force to turn nearly invincible for short bursts of time and to deliver crushing blows to the enemy, this Juggernaut is capable of taking a beating and giving one, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="785481" version="1065353216">When embracing the dark side of the Force, vengeance can be a powerful ally. With sustained and ruthless lightsaber thrusts delivered in the lithe Shien Form, the Vengeance Juggernaut increases damage without sacrificing defense--an ideal combination of tenacity and viciousness.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Fuelled by extreme rage, a Sith Warrior can reach new heights of destructive power. Furiously striking at one or more foes with bursts of hate and anger, the Rage Juggernaut forges ahead, the dark side of the Force providing ever more opportunities to crush and obliterate the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Annihilation doesn't have to be instantaneous--and that's how the Annihilation Marauder likes it. With lightsaber and Force attacks designed to bleed their foe and increasing their potency with an aggressive combat form, the Annihilation Marauder causes deep, rupturing wounds that add up until it's too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Agile and swift, the Carnage Marauder wins the day by way of sheer volume. As a devastating flurry of dual lightsaber strikes and Force attacks overwhelm their foe, each successful blow can serve to embolden the Carnage Marauder in their assault, making them all the more deadly.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="785481" version="1065353216">The dark side can be a powerful ally when one channels their inner fury, and no one knows this better than the Fury Marauder. Faced with one opponent or many, the Fury Marauder strikes with raging bursts of power while maintaining a balanced stance that offers protection against the enemy's attempts at obliteration.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="785481" version="1065353216">The great protector among Jedi Knights, the Defense Guardian is able to withstand even the most brutal assaults, and can give as good as they take. Even while dealing powerful blows, the Defense Guardian can  reduce the impact of any attacks that come their way, making them key participants at the front line of any battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Operating through a disciplined state of enlightened focus, the Vigilance Guardian defends by providing would-be attackers with a torrential offense. The Vigilance Guardian enters the fray nimble and alert, unleashing a whirlwind of lightsaber and Force attacks that leaves any adversaries wondering what just happened--if they're still conscious.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="785481" version="1065353216">The ways of the Force can reveal themselves to a Jedi Knight through intense concentration and, most importantly, focus. The Focus Guardian uses debilitating bursts of lightsaber strikes and Force powers to exhaust their foes, crushing any hopes they had of mounting an effective offense.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Some try to take down their opponent with a single blow, but the Watchman Sentinel chooses to utilize  calculated strikes that continue to dismantle their foe over time. An aggressive stance and merciless offense help to keep the Watchman's foe from comprehending the toll they've taken until it's too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="785481" version="1065353216">A lively flurry of dual lightsabers and Force abilities, the Combat Sentinel is a Jedi Knight who specializes in unrelenting volume. Rushing into battle with skilled precision, the barrage of overwhelming strikes increase the Combat Sentinel's vigor until their enemy is little more than a memory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Absolute awareness in the moment brings the Force to bear--a fact the Concentration Sentinel knows well. However many opponents they may face, the Concentration Sentinel leaps into battle with focused bursts of power while maintaining a balanced stance that offers protection against the enemy's attempts at exhausting them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Armed with the steely fortitude required to set up the perfect shot, the Sharpshooter is the Gunslinger at its most devious. Aiming from distant cover, the Sharpshooter goes for a devastating opening salvo, following up with vicious trick shots and penetrating rounds, putting a definitive end to the fight they started.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Delving ever deeper into the dark side of the Force can lead to madness, but it can also lead to immense power. Attacking multiple enemies simultaneously and instilling terror in their hearts, all while sapping their very life essence from afar, the Madness Sorcerer is a dark threat unlike any other.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Technology--and its application in deploying advanced weaponry--sets the Engineering Sniper apart from the rest. A variety of probes at their disposal allows the Engineering Sniper to attack from a distance with explosions, electrical jolts and waves of destructive plasma designed to eliminate any target.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="785481" version="1065353216">As an accomplished practitioner of the medical arts, the Medicine Operative serves as the preservative backbone of any combat team. Deploying a full complement of sophisticated gadgets to dispense healing kolto and reparative nanotech clouds to one or more targets, the Medicine Operative ensures their allies remain fit for fighting.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Striking from the shadows, the Concealment Operative surprises the enemy with a flurry of calculated attacks designed to stun and debilitate. Then, before the fight gets out of hand, the Concealment Operative can return to a position of stealth, biding their time until the time to strike reveals itself again.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="785481" version="1065353216">The Lethality Operative firmly believes the one true gift that keeps on giving is poison. Dispensing potent toxins using a variety of methods, the Lethality Operative's attacks take a toll over time, corroding the enemy from within until all that's left is a whithered husk that only thinks it still has a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="785481" version="1065353216">As an Underworld figure armed with the latest advances in medical technology, the Sawbones Scoundrel is a crucial ally. From healing a single target to many at once, distributing emergency medpacs and clouds of healing kolto, the Sawbones ensures that their crew will endure throughout the heat of battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Holding no punches, the Scrapper Scoundrel never backs down from a fight--so long as said fight is on their terms. Able to hide from the fray, the Scrapper can sucker punch and bludgeon their adversary, ducking back out before things get too hairy and biding their time until the moment is right to scrap once more.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Never shy about taking advantage of any opportunity, the Ruffian is a rough-and-tumble Scoundrel able to handle any fight, big or small. Inciting chaos with a shrapnel bomb and then coming in close for a shot at point-plank range, the Ruffian Scoundrel makes devious moves that keep their enemies reeling.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="785481" version="1065353216">A powerful connection to the Force allows the Kinetic Combat Shadow to draw the opposition's attention while also warding off their attacks. Add to that a formidable Force-based offense, and it becomes clear that the Kinetic Combat Shadow can serve as an effective bulwark against any foe.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="785481" version="1065353216">Planning a coordinated attack from a position of stealth and striking at the most opportune of times, the Infiltration Shadow is a master of surprise. By adopting special Force techniques, the Shadow's attacks can become even more effective, building to a powerful crescendo that the opposition won't even see coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="785481" version="1065353216">The Serenity Shadow is ever mindful that the Force ebbs and flows, and uses this knowledge to great advantage. Able to wield the Force against multiple targets while wresting vitality from the enemy, the Serenity Shadow can even stand up to opponents in close combat.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
