<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>232</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/gui/galaxymap.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Core</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="2" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Inner Empire Space</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="3" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Wild Space</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="4" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Northern Outer Rim</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="5" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Eastern Outer Rim</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="6" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Southern Outer Rim</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="7" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Western Outer Rim</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="8" id2="194665" version="1065353216">A cruel planet of rocky red deserts and crumbling ruins, Korriban was the homeworld of the ancient Sith. Reclaimed by the Empire in recent decades, it is now the site of the Sith Academy, where the Dark Council oversees the training of new acolytes. Only Sith may come and go freely from the Academy, and for a non-Sith to visit Korriban is a great privilege.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surrounding the Academy are the tombs of the first Dark Lords. Used as testing grounds by the Academy overseers, the tombs remain filled with traps, monstrosities and relics, even millennia after their construction--along with the bodies of a generation of failed acolytes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="9" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Adopted homeworld of the notorious Hutt Cartel, Hutta is a planet of semi-toxic swampland broken up by industrial facilities and urban centers. Hutt-aligned gangs control the civilized regions, forever warring over territory and resources. In the swamps, the native Evocii struggle against their Hutt rulers with limited success.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hutts are officially neutral in the conflict between Empire and Republic, and welcome visitors. Pirates, slavers and spice dealers are all common sights in Hutt palaces, while corporations often establish themselves on Hutta's moon, Nar Shaddaa. Newly arriving shuttles on Hutta are directed to the town of Jiguuna.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="10" id2="194665" version="1065353216">A longstanding member of the Galactic Republic, Ord Mantell is a world of deep seas, tall mountains and lush islands. Traders and merchants from across the galaxy ply their wares in Mantellian ports, along with black marketeers and other underworld forces.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent years, Ord Mantell has become embroiled in civil war, as anti-government separatists encourage Mantellian independence in the face of a brutally corrupt government with ties to organized crime. The Republic is responding with military force, and the fighting has resulted in high numbers of civilian casualties. Shuttle traffic is currently directed to the island of Avilatan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="11" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The mysterious Deep Core world of Tython is the birthplace of the Jedi Order. Millennia ago, Tythonian warriors and scholars developed a unique mystic and martial philosophy while studying the Force. Today, their Jedi descendants excavate ancient Tythonian ruins and relearn what was lost.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the recent destruction of the Jedi Temple on Coruscant, the Jedi made their new home on Tython. The mountainous planet remains mostly unexplored, and the violent natives pose a constant threat. The order remains committed to rebuilding here, however, and is now training a new generation of Padawans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="12" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Dromund Kaas is the capital of the Sith Empire, founded a millennium ago in the aftermath of the Great Hyperspace War. Since then, the sleek metropolis of Kaas City has grown into a symbol of Imperial power, towering over the surrounding jungle and looming dark against the stormy skies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The military and the Sith have authority here, under the eye of the Emperor himself. Aside from the wildlife, the greatest threats are internal--slave revolts, feuding Sith Lords and the like. Planetary defenses are formidable, as the Empire still remembers its defeat and exile long ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="13" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The proud capital of the Republic, Coruscant is the largest, the oldest and the most diverse city-world in the galaxy. Kilometer-tall buildings cover virtually all of the planet's surface, with the wealthy and powerful living at the top and the poorest and the most desperate dwelling near the foundations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coruscant is only now recovering from the attack by the Empire that led to the eventual cease-fire. Many buildings were reduced to rubble; a few still burn, the fires fueled by chemicals and uncontrolled reactors. During the Empire's attacks, the criminal underworld increased its power base as well, and remains a formidable threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="14" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Once an independent corporate and manufacturing world, Balmorra was defended by the Republic and conquered by the Empire during the war. Now the corporations have mostly fled, local collaborators have been rewarded with positions in the Imperial puppet government, and an entrenched and well-armed resistance opposes the Empire's rule.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite brutal retaliation by the Imperial military against military and civilian targets, the battle to eliminate the resistance drags on. Droid factories and industrial waste sites have become battlegrounds. The main Balmorran spaceport is in the city of Sobrik, an Imperial military stronghold heavily fortified against resistance attacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="15" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Once an independent corporate and manufacturing world, Balmorra was defended by the Republic and conquered by the Empire during the war. Now the corporations have mostly fled, local collaborators have been rewarded with positions in the Empire's puppet government, and an entrenched resistance opposes Imperial rule.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a prolonged absence, the Republic has returned to Balmorra to aid the resistance movement. Droid factories and industrial waste sites have become battlegrounds, and the Imperial military is responding with a buildup of its own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="16" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Taris was once a city-world like Coruscant. Three centuries ago, however, it was bombarded by the Sith Lord Darth Malak and left a toxic ruin. The years since have not been kind to Taris, as vegetation and animal life struggle to gain a foothold in the shattered skeleton of a planetary metropolis.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republic began to recolonize Taris less than a decade ago, and has suffered innumerable setbacks--everything from pirate attacks to the strange &quot;rakghoul plague.&quot; Nonetheless, the reconstruction effort continues, its proponents determined to prove that the Empire can never truly destroy greatness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="17" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Taris was once a city-world, home to a planetary metropolis. Three centuries ago, however, it was bombarded by the great Darth Malak and left a toxic ruin. The years since have not been kind to Taris, as vegetation and animal life struggle to gain a foothold in shattered skyscrapers and habitats.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republic began to recolonize Taris less than a decade ago, aiming to make it into a symbol of Republic hope and steadfastness. In response, the Empire is mobilizing troops and beginning a full-scale assault. Early reports speak of fierce resistance from the Republic, as well as natural hazards in the form of wildlife and the mysterious &quot;rakghoul plague.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="18" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The so-called &quot;Smuggler's Moon&quot; is best known for one thing: anything can be bought here if the price is right. Nar Shaddaa orbits Hutta, homeworld of the Hutt Cartel, but exists as a power in its own right. Criminal organizations and legitimate enterprises operate side-by-side, regulated only by the Hutts' whims. Gleaming skyscrapers house corporations, casinos, technology shops, spice houses and every other type of business imaginable.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although no other world offers Nar Shaddaa's unique services, the city has a notorious murder and disappearance rate. Gangsters, pirates, slavers and worse crowd the streets, and Republic and Imperial representatives compete for influence with the local powers. Strangers should be extremely cautious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="19" id2="194665" version="1065353216">A harsh desert planet off all the major trade routes, Tatooine is known for its heat, its sand, its dangerous wildlife--and little else. Only a few settlements dot Tatooine's endless wastes, inhabited by handfuls of traders and moisture farmers. Tatooine's obscurity has also attracted a small but significant criminal population, here to hide from galactic authorities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tatooine lacks any central government or allegiance to Republic or Empire. There are rumors of an Imperial occupation taking place in one of the frontier settlements, but nothing has been confirmed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="20" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Alderaan is a mountainous world of lush forests and grasslands, ruled by an assembly of noble houses and an enlightened and advanced citizenry. A founding member of the Republic, Alderaan has been traditionally admired for its wealth, its art and its thinkers, while the deadly intrigues and politics of the nobility have been downplayed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recently, those intrigues erupted into civil war, and Alderaan--now officially withdrawn from the Republic--sees conflict it hasn't known in ages. The Republic is backing House Organa's quest for the crown, whereas the Empire backs the former House Thul exiles. Palaces and fields have become pockmarked by cannon fire, and house armies clash on the battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="21" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Once a lush tropical swamp, Quesh's atmosphere became toxic after a series of quakes released dangerous chemicals contained below the planet surface. Most of the native wildlife died off, and Quesh became poisonous to virtually all higher species.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quesh's toxicity is also its source of value--the chemicals that poisoned the atmosphere are usable in the most powerful adrenals and stimulants. The Republic, with the aid of the Hutt Cartel, has staked a claim to Quesh and is attempting to establish chemical mines. Upon learning of Quesh's existence, the Empire quickly established a presence of its own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="22" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Few life-forms can survive on the ice planet Hoth. Between its subzero surface temperatures, sheering winds and frequent whiteouts, the environment should be considered extremely hostile even to properly outfitted individuals; mechanical equipment and communications technology are prone to freeze and malfunction as well, making any minor setback potentially lethal.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the war between Republic and Empire, the Hoth system was the site of a major fleet battle. This resulted in a large number of starships falling into Hoth's gravity well and crashing on the planet surface. These derelict ships have become the base of operations for a large group of pirates, as well as a center of dispute between Republic and Imperial forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="23" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Officially, Belsavis is a sparsely populated Republic world dominated by arctic plains. Its only notable feature is the rare tropical rifts that break up the expanses of ice, heated by natural geothermal vents and home to a surprising diversity of plant life.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In truth, Belsavis is an ultrasecure prison colony established by the Republic. Until recently, the prison's existence was top secret, but its discovery by the Empire has resulted in rumors spreading throughout the galactic underworld. The prison is now in a state of lockdown, and both Republic and Imperial militaries have a presence on the scene.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="24" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Voss was first discovered only a few years ago, and the rocky, lightly forested planet remains absent from many star charts. Two distinct cultures inhabit the world, both at a pre-spaceflight stage of development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first culture, known as the Gormak, is a xenophobic and violent species that dominates most of the planet surface. The second culture, known as the Voss, has been amenable to contact with outsiders and welcomes visitors to the mountain city of Voss-Ka. The Voss have a highly ritualistic society and are notable for their unusual aptitude with the Force. The Republic and the Empire have sent representatives to Voss-Ka to explore the possibility of an alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="25" id2="194665" version="1065353216">One of the founding worlds of the Galactic Republic, Corellia nonetheless prides itself on its independence. Some of the finest starships in the galaxy are made on Corellia, along with their daring pilots--men and women looking to explore, to trade or just stay ahead of the law. The cities, like the people, are distinctly Corellian, incorporating the natural landscape into their design despite a heavy manufacturing base.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Corellian government recently agreed to turn over power to the Sith Empire. This has resulted in riots in the streets and open revolution despite Imperial claims of legitimacy, and the capital of Coronet City has become a battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="26" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The mountainous ice planet Ilum is home to one of the Jedi Order's most distant outposts. Nestled between snow-covered crags is an enclave used by the Jedi for generations, a shelter from the cold and a launching point for journeys into Ilum's exotic crystal caves. These caves produce some of the most rare and powerful lightsaber crystals in the galaxy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ilum hosts no indigenous population, although a number of larger animals survive in its environment. Its temperatures fail to reach the extremes of Hoth, but it has never been a target for colonization or occupation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="27" id2="194665" version="1065353216">RETURN TO THE GALAXY</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="28" id2="194665" version="1065353216">RETURN TO THE &lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="29" id2="194665" version="1065353216">You are traveling to &lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="30" id2="194665" version="1065353216">You do not have enough credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="31" id2="194665" version="1065353216">You don't have permission to use the galaxy map!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="32" id2="194665" version="1065353216">You don't own this ship; you don't have permission to fly it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="33" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Error, data not found.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="34" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Error, attempted to fly to an invalid destination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="35" id2="194665" version="1065353216">THE GALAXY</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="36" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Unknown Regions</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="37" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Seat of the Empire</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="38" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Coreward Worlds</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="39" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Hutt Space</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="40" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Distant Outer Rim</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="41" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Contested Space</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="42" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Imperial Space</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="43" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Neutral Space</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="44" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Republic Space</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="61" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Polith Minefield</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="62" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Javaal Fleet Action</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="63" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Sarapin Assault</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="64" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Balosar Outpost</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="65" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Kovor Ice Field</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="66" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Sullust Interception</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="67" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Drexel Sweep</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="68" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Llanic Station Strike</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="69" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Ezran Outpost</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="70" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Mugaar Ice Field</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="71" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Kalee Fortification</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="72" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Clouds of Vondoru</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="73" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The Impossible Sector</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="74" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Aeten Defense</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="75" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Ascendancy Barrier</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="76" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Skaross Fortification</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="77" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Nez Peron Sweep</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="78" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Hydian Way Blockade</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="79" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Makem Te Assault</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="80" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Pakuuni Defense</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="81" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Saleucami Fleet Action</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="82" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Archenar Interception</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="83" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Cartel Listening Station</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="84" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Zosha Advance</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Taspan Ambush</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="86" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Fondor Escort</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="87" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Jabiim Escort</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="88" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Syvris Evacuation</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="89" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The Justice is a fully armed Imperial capital ship with all combat systems charged and ready. You have been cleared to land in the primary docking bay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="90" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The Aurora is one of the Republic's fearsome planetary assault cruisers, capable of punching through an interdicting fleet and delivering its massive payload of troops and armor to a planet's surface. Aboard it, Master Kellian Jarro and a battalion of Republic special forces await.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="91" id2="194665" version="1065353216">This asteroid field once hosted a thriving ore-processing industry, but Czerka Corporation withdrew when profits dwindled. The company abandoned a small mining facility here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="92" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Long-range scanners have identified an Imperial dreadnaught in orbit around the Artus Five gas giant. Further information is unavailable at this distance; the cloaking device will engage automatically when within range of the Artus system.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="93" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Uphrades is one of the Republic's primary agriworlds: a lush planet with a temperate atmosphere and especially rich soil due to significant volcanic activity over twenty millennia ago. Nearly half of the Republic capital's food supply is grown and harvested on Uphrades, earning it the nickname &quot;Coruscant's Granary.&quot; Sixteen million farmers and food technologists oversee the sustainable agricultural production across the planet's five continents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="95" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The Carida is a standard Republic capital ship equipped for long-range patrols. The ship appears to have life support and power, but she is adrift and is not responding to communications.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="96" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The starship Celestial Crow is a standard light freighter. The vessel's engines appear to be non-functional, leaving the ship drifting into the sun of an otherwise uninhabited star system.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="97" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Commander Tavus's ship is at a full stop with all systems active. Jamming prevents any detailed scans of the ship's interior.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="98" id2="194665" version="1065353216">A starship built for speed, Jaesa Willsaam's starship waits at the appointed coordinates, ready to be docked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="99" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Master Yuon Par's coordinates lead to a huge starship lingering in a distant sector. The ship appears Imperial, but scanners detect many upgrades and strange power fluctuations. Master Yuon's code should lower its defenses long enough for you to board.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="100" id2="194665" version="1065353216">This unaffiliated space station doesn't appear on scanners. Sophisticated tech covers every inch, leaving no room for defenses. It clearly relies on invisibility to keep it safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="101" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The Long Shadow is a lifeless region of space at the furthest edge of the galaxy. The only thing of note here is an unmarked derelict starship slowly drifting into a black hole.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="102" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Port Raga is a backwater trading and refueling station that caters to all business, legal or otherwise. Ship traffic appears to be much lighter than usual.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="103" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The Oppressor is Darth Angral's battle cruiser. It has been upgraded with advanced technology and a planet-destroying superweapon, which is now aimed at Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="104" id2="194665" version="1065353216">This door is locked! Try using an escape pod.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="105" id2="194665" version="1065353216">You will travel immediately, do you want to continue?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="106" id2="194665" version="1065353216">YES</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="107" id2="194665" version="1065353216">CANCEL</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="108" id2="194665" version="1065353216">SHIP</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="109" id2="194665" version="1065353216">TRAVEL NOW</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="110" id2="194665" version="1065353216">TRAVEL COST</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="111" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Parsecs</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="112" id2="194665" version="1065353216">System Overview</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="113" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Currently on</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="114" id2="194665" version="1065353216">This space station is a popular hub for shipping and passenger vessels traveling through Republic space. Traffic from Tython and Ord Mantell often stops at this outpost before continuing on to Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="115" id2="194665" version="1065353216">This Imperial space station routes ship traffic and monitors activity throughout its designated sector. Travelers arriving from Korriban and Hutt space and destined for Dromund Kaas typically pass through this outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="116" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The Telos is a Republic heavy dreadnaught, and the First Expeditionary Fleet's flagship. The Telos leads a battle group of more than fifty vessels, including six heavy cruisers and over two dozen rapid-attack frigates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="117" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The flagship of Moff Phennir, the White Nova is an Imperial dreadnaught designed to command and coordinate a fleet of capital ships. Thirty Terminus-class destroyers are in formation around the Nova, along with an undetermined number of smaller vessels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="118" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Active Missions:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Hyperspace</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="120" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 3 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pirate fleet has set ambushes and laid an extensive minefield in the Polith system to disrupt Imperial convoys passing through the region. Enemy vessels must be destroyed and the mines cleared to reopen crucial supply lines.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Disable a bay on the minelayer&lt;br&gt;- Cripple minelayer engines&lt;br&gt;- Destroy mines&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 3 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Any.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Republic patrol group has been illegally ambushed by Imperial ships in orbit high above the planet Javaal. The Imperial task force is led by a notorious Intelligence agent, and the patrol needs backup urgently if it's going to have any hope of surviving the Empire's attack.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Bring down the X-70B Phantom&lt;br&gt;- Shoot down Mark VII interceptors</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="122" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 1 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Damaged during a failed incursion into Imperial space, the Republic warship Enkindle is attempting to hide in the upper atmosphere of the planet Sarapin Four. Any available forces should move quickly to cripple the Enkindle before Republic reinforcements arrive.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Obliterate the capital ship's shield generators&lt;br&gt;- Decimate the capital ship's turrets&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 1 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="123" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Any.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Empire has constructed an illegal hidden space station in the Balosar system to act as a staging point for covert assaults on Republic territories. All available ships have been dispatched to destroy the station, but additional forces will be necessary to breach the Imperial defenses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Destroy station turrets&lt;br&gt;- Destroy station shield generators&lt;br&gt;- Destroy station hangars&lt;br&gt;- Destroy station antennae</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="124" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 3 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Imperial fleet led by Captain Tervor &quot;Riptide&quot; Jheran has illegally engaged a Republic patrol surveying the orbital ice rings of the planet Kovor. Without immediate reinforcements, the overmatched patrol cannot hope to survive against the ace Imperial starfighter or his forces.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Defeat a Fury-class Imperial intercepter&lt;br&gt;- Shoot down ace Mark VII interceptors&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 3 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="125" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 5 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Traitors aboard a space station orbiting Aeten Two have compromised the installation's defenses. The traitors have been neutralized, but the station is defenseless and under attack by a Republic fleet. All available vessels are ordered to engage the enemy forces to protect the station.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Intercept ace Raven bombers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 5 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="126" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 5 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crew aboard the Imperial space station on the outskirts of Kalee was secretly preparing to defect to the Republic. The Empire discovered their plan and sent a fleet to destroy the station. All available vessels must engage the enemy forces while the station's crew and intel files are extracted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Shoot down ace extinction bombers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 5 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="127" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 1 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An illegal Imperial chemical weapons program has been traced to a space station in the remote Llanic system. Republic forces have been dispatched, but additional ships are requested to ensure that the Empire's deadly creations are completely destroyed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Destroy station turrets&lt;br&gt;- Destroy station shield generators&lt;br&gt;- Destroy station hangars&lt;br&gt;- Destroy station antennae&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 1 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="128" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 1 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A space station used by Republic-aligned smugglers has been identified in the Ezran system. All available Imperial vessels should converge on the Ezran system to purge the galaxy of these illegal and amoral pirates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Destroy station turrets&lt;br&gt;- Destroy station shield generators&lt;br&gt;- Destroy station hangars&lt;br&gt;- Destroy station antennae&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 1 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="129" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 3 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imperial ships have lured a Republic border patrol into the orbital ice rings of the planet Mugaar. Communications are being jammed, and the Republic patrol can now be discreetly eliminated. Be aware that a Jedi Master is in command of the enemy forces.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Eliminate the Corellian defender&lt;br&gt;- Destroy ace Red Talon fighters&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 3 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="130" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 3 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An elite Imperial fighter squadron has been launching devastating hit-and-run attacks on Republic convoys. The squadron has been tracked to an asteroid field in the Drexel system. Eliminating these Imperial fighters is vital to the Republic war effort.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Neutralize ace Mark VII interceptors&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 3 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="131" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 5 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Imperial fleet ambushed and damaged the Intercessor, a Republic capital ship, in the skies above Vondoru. Republic reinforcements have joined the battle; it is imperative that Imperial vessels in the area converge to bring the Intercessor down.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Obliterate the capital ship's shield generators&lt;br&gt;- Decimate the capital ship's turrets&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 5 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="132" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 5 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mandalorian forces have erected a minefield along a popular smuggling route traversing the region known as the Impossible Sector. The mines must be removed to clear a path for Republic-commissioned privateers supporting the war effort; expect heavy resistance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Disable a bay on the minelayer&lt;br&gt;- Destroy minelayer engines&lt;br&gt;- Destroy mines&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 5 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="133" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 3 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An elite Republic fighter squadron has been launching devastating hit-and-run attacks on Imperial installations in the Sullust system. The squadron has been tracked to a nearby asteroid field. Eliminating these Republic fighters is vital to the Imperial war effort.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Exterminate ace Red Talon fighters&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 3 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="134" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 5 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alien forces sympathetic to the Republic have blockaded a primary route to the Chiss regions in an effort to cut off their support of the Empire. For the sake of our war effort, the enemy ships must be destroyed and the minefield blockade neutralized immediately.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Disable a bay on the minelayer&lt;br&gt;- Cripple minelayer engines&lt;br&gt;- Destroy mines&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 5 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="135" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 3 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key Imperial weapons manufacturing station in the Skaross system is under assault from Republic bombers. Reinforcements are desperately needed to ensure the station's survival.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Intercept Raven bombers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 3 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="136" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 1 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Republic fighter wing has established a position over the Imperial-aligned agricultural planet of Nez Peron. Reinforcements are needed to eliminate the Republic vessels so Nez Peron's resources can be secured for the Empire.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Exterminate Talon fighters&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 1 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="137" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 3 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mandalorian mercenaries working for the Empire have laid an extensive minefield in order to blockade the Hydian Way trade route and funnel Republic convoys into a deadly ambush. The mines must be cleared to reopen crucial supply lines.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Disable a bay on the minelayer&lt;br&gt;- Blast minelayer engines&lt;br&gt;- Punch through mines&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 3 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="138" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 1 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Separated from its escorts after a failed illegal assault, Imperial warship Overlord is badly damaged and attempting to hide in the upper atmosphere of the planet Makem Te. Any available forces should move quickly to cripple the Overlord before Imperial reinforcements arrive.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Neutralize the capital ship's shield generators&lt;br&gt;- Take out the capital ship's turrets&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 1 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="139" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 3 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Empire is plotting to blame the Republic for the destruction of a neutral space station in the Pakuuni system. An Imperial fleet is sending bomber squadrons to destroy the station and everyone on board. Republic vessels have been dispatched, but they will need assistance to ensure the station's survival.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Shoot down extinction bombers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 3 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="140" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Any.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Imperial infiltration squadron has been ambushed by Republic forces near the planet Saleucami. The enemy is led by legendary pilot Nezhel &quot;Sunspot&quot; Othren. The squadron needs backup if it's going to survive the battle in the planet's low-orbit asteroid field, but more importantly, this is an opportunity to eliminate the deadly Republic ace.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Eliminate the BT-7 Thunderclap&lt;br&gt;- Destroy Red Talon fighters</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="141" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 1 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enemy fighters have been detected attempting to slip through the Archenar asteroid field in order to attack nearby shipping lanes. These fighters must be intercepted before they can wreak havoc on Republic supply lines.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Neutralize Mark VI interceptors&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 1 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="142" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Any.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cartel has allowed the Republic to set up a hidden space station in Hutt Space to intercept dispatches from nearby Imperial operations. All available ships have been dispatched to destroy the station, but additional forces will be necessary to breach the Republic defenses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Destroy Station Turrets&lt;br&gt;- Destroy Station Shield Generators&lt;br&gt;- Destroy station hangars&lt;br&gt;- Destroy station antennae</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="143" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 5 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patrols intercepted the Imperial destroyer Scream of Ragnos and its frigate escort deep inside Republic territory. A battle rages above the uninhabited world of Zosha; casualties are high on both sides. Reinforcements are needed to bring the Scream down and prevent it from returning to Imperial space.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objectives:&lt;br&gt;(Remember to save your missiles for these objectives!)&lt;br&gt;- Neutralize the capital ship's shield generators&lt;br&gt;- Take out the capital ship's turrets&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 5 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="144" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 1 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key Republic military officer has agreed to defect to the Empire. He is attempting to rendezvous with Imperial forces, but Republic ships have intercepted his shuttle. Immediate assistance is requested in securing the defector before he is captured or destroyed by the enemy assault.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objective:&lt;br&gt;- Escort defector shuttle to safety&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 1 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="145" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Any.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An urgent distress signal has been detected in the Fondor system. Republic soldiers and colonists kidnapped by the Empire have escaped confinement and taken flight in a shuttle. All available vessels are requested to defend the escapees and ensure that some proof of the Empire's aggression is preserved.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objective:&lt;br&gt;- Escort the shuttle to safety</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="146" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Any.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imperial Intelligence spies carrying vital information on Republic plans are attempting to escape enemy territory in a stolen shuttle. Republic forces are in pursuit, however, and have trapped the shuttle in a tractor beam. Reinforcements are needed to defend the shuttle and ensure the stolen data arrives intact.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objective:&lt;br&gt;- Escort the shuttle to safety</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="147" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 1 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Republic SIS listening post in the Syvris system has been compromised by Imperial forces. Immediate assistance is requested in evacuating critical intelligence, personnel and a captured Imperial vessel before they are destroyed by the enemy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Objective:&lt;br&gt;- Escort defector shuttle to safety&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: This mission will be difficult if you do not have Grade 1 Upgrades or higher.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="148" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Space Battle - &quot;&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="149" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Engage in Space Mission: &lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="150" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The dreadnaught Spirit of Vengeance acts as Mandalore's mobile command center while he is away from his stronghold on Geonosis. Its intimidating silhouette and countless weapons emplacements leave no doubt that the vessel lives up to its name.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="151" id2="194665" version="1065353216">A Republic capital ship normally assigned to the Core Worlds, the Fortitude was involved in the breaking of the Hydian Way blockade. The Supreme Chancellor hopes that having the Fortitude host the Rift Alliance will be seen as a gesture of respect by its members.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="152" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Waypoint Station Three is one of several Republic facilities created during the war, originally intended to quickly restock and refuel military ships. After the war ended, they became convenient safe ports, often used by Republic allies or small trading vessels.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="153" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The Emperor's private fortress is a millennium-old construct orbiting the Imperial capital planet Dromund Kaas. A powerful cloaking device hides this ancient, virtually impregnable space station even from visual scanners.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="154" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The infamous Port Nowhere is a converted Azalus-class Hutt dreadnaught retrofitted with over a hundred additional docking bays. This &quot;flying space station&quot; traverses neutral space near the Core Worlds, providing safe haven for less-than-legitimate business.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="155" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The Imperial treasury cruiser, the King's Ransom, is a high-security space-faring vault that contains a sizable portion of the Empire's monetary assets. The King's Ransom is cruising in contested Hutt Space while the Empire's diplomats negotiate favors from the Cartel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="156" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Final testing of the Empire's deadly superweapon is being conducted in a secured research zone far from any charted sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="157" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The massive Imperial dreadnaught hangs in space above the planet Quesh, smoking from a recent attack. Systems are online but the ship's been crippled. Republic fighters are swarming into the docking bay, laying siege.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="158" id2="194665" version="1065353216">This Imperial destroyer is broadcasting standard (albeit high-security) identification codes, but the military database contains no crew or mission records for a ship called &quot;Tenebrous.&quot; Either the records have been eliminated or this is not a military vessel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="159" id2="194665" version="1065353216">An orbital docking station where a stolen Republic transport is being prepped to board the Supreme Chancellor's flagship: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unassuming vessel at first glance, more suited to ceremonies and entertaining dignitaries than naval battles, the Founder is more than capable of defending itself from determined assault and is manned by the most loyal and dedicated soldiers in the Republic's armed forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="160" id2="194665" version="1065353216">A full-sized Imperial battle cruiser leads an armada of smaller vessels in a planetary assault on the world of Rabaan.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="161" id2="194665" version="1065353216">A full-sized Imperial battle cruiser leads an armada of smaller vessels in a planetary assault on the world of Rabaan.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="162" id2="194665" version="1065353216">An Imperial dreadnaught of astonishing power, the Javelin is on a direct course for Corellia, escorting a large number of troop carriers. The Javelin is armed with several heavy turbolaser batteries and is capable of devastating a planet from orbit.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="163" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The flagship of the infamous Voidwolf, the Regnant strikes terror in the hearts of those unfortunate enough to witness its arrival in their system. The Regnant operates outside the Imperial command structure, making it almost impossible to track using normal methods. However, a rare opportunity to infiltrate the vessel has presented itself in the skies above Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="164" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Warren Sedoru has captured the Valiant, the Republic flagship of Admiral Darbin. Exploiting the captured admiral's knowledge of Republic tactics, the fallen Jedi has turned the Valiant into an unstoppable weapon capable of crippling the Republic fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="165" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The Euphony is an unregistered, privately owned vessel with minimal armaments and shields. There is no response to communications.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="166" id2="194665" version="1065353216">This remote military prison carries a fearsome reputation among Republic soldiers. Until now, its location has been a secret known only to the highest Imperial officials.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="167" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Acting on rumors that several important Sith Lords were gathering at Korriban's Flame, Jedi Knight Jomar Chul tried to infiltrate the heavily fortified station, only to be captured. Jomar disappeared, but if the rumors are true, the meeting on the station could offer some clue to the Emperor's plan to wipe out all life in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="168" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Dromund Kaas is the Empire's capital world, home to its vast military and legions of Sith. Beneath its storm-wracked skies, the sleek metropolis of Kaas City towers above a deadly predator-infested jungle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The planet's formidable defenses include orbital battle stations, ground-to-space artillery and the First Defense Fleet. Enemy landing parties that reach the surface will confront a world where military service is mandatory and virtually every citizen is armed for war.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="169" id2="194665" version="1065353216">This is an Imperial flagship, where three very prominent Moffs are meeting to see the demonstration of an amazing new superweapon. It is in range of both a Republic fleet and a separate Imperial fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="170" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Isen Four is an asteroid satellite in orbit around the Isen gas giant. Too small to hold a breathable atmosphere, it nonetheless hosts a small Republic mining colony; tunnels honeycomb the inside of the asteroid, along with all the machines needed to support life.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The colony is not broadcasting standard landing protocols. Long-range scans indicate no blaster scarring or signs of battle, and Isen Four's minimal external defenses do not appear to be active.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="171" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, approaching this space station undetected requires that no sensor sweeps be made en route. Records describe it as an independently owned fueling and supply station.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="172" id2="194665" version="1065353216">This Imperial warship is on course to Corellia. According to Quinn, it's using a special transponder signal emitter in order to verify its identity and pass through the Imperial fleet; such an emitter could be removed and repurposed for your own ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="173" id2="194665" version="1065353216">This space station is located deep in the Null Zone--an empty region of space devoid of stars, planets and any known life. Ships traveling through the Null Zone are few, and high-intensity scans are rare; there's nothing to find beyond a few drifting wrecks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The station deflects all scans and probes and emits almost no energy. It is impossible to tell whether the upgrades to your ship aboard the Tenebrous will allow you to approach undetected.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="174" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Tytun Four is the fourth moon of a gas giant in the Gacerian system. The surface and much of the interior have been largely replaced by databanks, power generators, maintenance tunnels and self-repair facilities--in effect, turning Tytun Four into a gigantic computer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In orbit around the moon are rings of derelict starships converted into additional databanks--added capacity for the moon. Archive node 803-A is a battle-scarred Imperial transport.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alongside the derelict starships are several sleek, heavily armed corvettes, likely used by the mercenaries paid to defend against intruders.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="175" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The venerable Carrick Station is currently designated as the Republic Navy's primary rally point. Once merely a hub for civilian traffic within Republic borders, it has become increasingly strategically important since the return of the Sith Empire. Targeted for assault and sabotage numerous times, Carrick Station has proven to be as hardy as the Republic hero it was named for.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="176" id2="194665" version="1065353216">The bulk of the Imperial fleet is currently massed at Vaiken Spacedock, an enormous installation capable of acting as a central hub for both military actions and civilian transport. It is the heart of the Imperial war effort and a fitting tribute to its namesake, Grand Moff Vaiken, the founder of the modern Imperial military.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="177" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Space Mission Available</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="178" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Space Missions Available</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="179" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Levels &lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt; - &lt;&lt;2&gt;&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="180" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Level &lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Close Galaxy Map</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="194665" version="1065353216">&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt; to &lt;&lt;2&gt;&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="194665" version="1065353216">This derilect Czerka research vessel was recently discovered by a passing salvage ship. It is unclear why the ship was abandoned, but sensor data suggests that it has been unused for several decades at least.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="194665" version="1065353216">You have &lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt; Space Missions avaliable. You are allowed &lt;&lt;2&gt;&gt; free Space Missions weekly as a Free-to-Play Player.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="194665" version="1065353216">You have unlimited access to Space Missions for &lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="194665" version="1065353216">An error has occurred. Please try that action again.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 7 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Short-range Republic ships have been tracked to the Far Cradle, a refueling station in the Unknown Regions. Imperial fighter squadrons are needed to launch a surprise offensive and devastate the Republic station's defenses. Expect additional resistance from refueling destroyers.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Far Cradle Strike</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Regnant Station Assault</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 7 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Imperial refueling outpost Regnant Station gives the enemy a vital foothold in the Unknown Regions. To drive the Empire back, the Republic's top fighter groups must launch a surprise attack against the outpost and cripple Regnant Station's defenses. Be wary of refueling Imperial destroyers.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Kabal Station Defense</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 7 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republic fleet has launched a devastating attack against Kabal Station, a key Imperial outpost in the Distant Outer Rim. Any available ships must destroy the enemy fleet and save Kabal Station from destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Ardis Outpost Fortification</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 7 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Imperial fleet has emerged from hyperspace to ambush Ardis Outpost, a Republic space station in the Unknown Regions. Reinforcements are needed to aid our frigates in eliminating the Imperial fleet before the outpost is lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Kanz Minefield</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 7 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Republic fleet is laying mines in the Bimmiel asteroid field to divide Imperial forces in the Kanz sector. To aid the Imperial war effort, all ships are needed to destroy the mine controller satellites and clear Republic fighters from the asteroid field.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="194665" version="1065353216">New Cov Ice Field</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 7 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imperial fighters are hiding in the New Cov ice field and fortifying their position with prototype mines, controlled remotely by satellites. For the sake of the Republic war effort, we must destroy these satellites and the Imperial ships that are deploying the mines.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Duma Strike</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 7 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Captain Duma is rallying the Republic fleet to ambush the Empire's top pilots: your name is at the top of his list. To disrupt his ambush, the Empire must bring down Captain Duma and every last Republic vessel under his command.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Baros Ambush</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 7 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Darth Ordrem is amassing his fleet near Baros to ambush the Republic's most elite pilots: you will be his first target. To save our ships from his wrath, the Republic must launch a preemptive strike against Darth Ordrem and his Imperial fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Lorta Escort</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 7 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The maiden voyage of the D-1Z prototype bomber is underway. The Empire has invested a fortune in the ship's development, and the Republic now rallies its forces to destroy it. Reinforcements are needed over the planet Lorta to escort the bomber and shield it from the Republic onslaught.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Hypori Escort</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 7 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republic's prototype bomber--the &quot;Gilded Meteor&quot;--has begun its test flight in the Ferra sector, and the Empire has deployed a dreadnaught to sabotage its maiden voyage. The Republic fleet requests backup over the planet Hypori to provide air support and protect the bomber.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Cha Raaba Assault</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 7 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mandalorians have stolen construction plans for the Sovereign Forge, the Empire's ultimate mining station and shipyard. The Mandalorian warlord Varek Tarn plots to sell the plans to the Republic at a minefield in the Cha Rabaa system. To save the Sovereign Forge, the shuttle carrying the plans must be destroyed before delivery to the Republic buyers; Varek Tarn himself will be escorting the shuttle and should be treated as a high-priority target.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Thanium Disruption</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="194665" version="1065353216">(Recommended Level of Ship Upgrades: Grade 7 and higher.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Mandalorian warlord has captured the construction plans for the Void Anvil, the Republic's top-secret mining station and shipyard. Warlord Rimark will soon sell the plans to the Empire at a minefield in the Thanium sector. Republic vessels must rally to bring down the shuttle carrying the plans and erase evidence of the Void Anvil at all costs. Warlord Rimark will be in the area and should be considered extremely dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Located off major hyperspace routes, Makeb went unnoticed until the Mandalorian Wars, when a damaged transport ship carrying Republic refugees--including wealthy businessmen fleeing raiders--crash-landed there. Led by magnate Semako Thalien, the survivors built settlements and re-established contact with the galaxy. Rich mineral deposits in Makeb's mesas, combined with the settlers' credits and influence, made it an immensely profitable world within fifty years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the war between the Empire and the Republic, Makeb stubbornly retained its independence, attracting corporate leaders, rich tourists and banking enterprises. Rumors claim that a remarkably vast deposit of minerals was discovered soon after the Treaty of Coruscant, but details are surprisingly scarce.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Through the years, the Sith Empire has accumulated many artifacts, devices and specimens deemed too powerful to destroy, yet far too dangerous for anything but the most careful, contained research. The Arcanum was built for precisely this reason. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commissioned in secret by the Emperor himself and operated under the aegis of Darth Acina of the Dark Council, the Arcanum is a vast storehouse, featuring first-rate security measures as well as the Empire's most cutting-edge research laboratories. Aside from its staff of hardened security officers and brilliant theoretical scientists, very few have been allowed a glimpse into the mysteries within.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="194665" version="1065353216">During its heyday, Czerka Corporation bought up all the land it could manage, including entire moons. While some of these moons were purchased to exploit their abundant mineral deposits, most were turned into massive warehouses for excess manufacturing parts and inventory. One such storage facility was designated CZ-198.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks in part to its remote locale, CZ-198 was transformed by an ambitious executive into a major profit center for Czerka, developing and manufacturing cutting-edge droids and weapons. With Czerka having fallen on hard times of late, the ownership of the moon--and the fate of its manufactories, laboratories and experimental biodomes--is entirely up in the air.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="194665" version="1065353216">At first blush, there is nothing at all remarkable about the remote, rocky sphere called Oricon. However, anyone with an affinity for the Force can sense that the Outer Rim moon is immeasurably strong with the dark side. Fitting, then, that the rogue Sith lords known as the Dread Masters have claimed Oricon as their home.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The once-lifeless moon now brims with creatures from across the galaxy that have been experimented on, corrupted with dark energy and driven to frenzy by the Dread Masters. It is also a starship graveyard, its surface littered with Republic and Imperial ships torn apart by dark waves of madness and fear. There can be no doubt: Oricon has become one of the most hazardous destinations in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Few planets have been as important to both sides of the war as Manaan. But with its surface covered completely by water, and with its native Selkath population having adopted an isolationist stance, access to the planet can be difficult to come by. The Selkath economy's reliance on the export of kolto to the Republic and the Empire does provide opportunities to visit, but guests are typically limited to the world's few trading platforms--the only surface structures not affected by the Empire's bombardment of the planet during the Great Galactic War.

Millennia of Rakatan dominion over the planet and a predominantly unexplored ocean floor evoke strong temptations to probe Manaan's crushing depths. However, due to the strategic importance of its kolto reserves, Manaan will have to largely remain a mystery for now.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="194665" version="1065353216">More than two dozen moons orbit the Outer Rim gas giant Yavin. Of those moons, the one designated Yavin 4 is by far the most habitable, supporting a vast array of flora and fauna within its lush and endless jungles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yavin 4 also holds a great deal of interest to the Jedi and the Sith. For well over a thousand years now, the dark side of the Force has flowed through Yavin 4 in an ever-increasing magnitude. But those who visit the moon's deadly rainforests and swamps in search of an explanation for the phenomenon rarely return, and never with any answers.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="194665" version="1065353216">For a very long time, Rishi remained ignored and untouched on the fringes of the Outer Rim. Its dominant species--the intelligent, avian Rishii--lived a simple and mostly serene existence on the island-flecked world. But when a pirate craft crash-landed on Rishi more than a hundred years ago, all that changed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With its plentiful fossil fuel reserves and close proximity to a largely unexplored dwarf galaxy, this tropical pearl of a planet has since become a favorite hub for underworld types in search of riches, refuge from authorities or just a good time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="194665" version="1065353216">UNKNOWN</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Situated in the heart of Imperial Space, Ziost has long played a vital role in the intricate history of the Sith. For thousands of years, in fact, the craggy, arid world served as the ancient Sith Empire's capital until infighting splintered its leadership.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today, Ziost remains an important commercial, political and population center of the Empire--this in spite of its shift from a warm climate with dense forests to a bitterly cold tundra. Whether this environmental turnabout is due to geological reasons or eons of dark side influence remains a subject of scholarly consideration.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Home to the Eternal Throne and defended by the Eternal Fleet, Zakuul has become the new superpower in the galaxy. An old civilization reshaped by Emperor Valkorion, Zakuul is technologically advanced, relying mainly on droid labor, with seemingly unlimited resources. All roads lead to the Spire, a sprawling metropolis built on the Endless Swamp. Valkorion's &quot;golden city&quot; symbolizes his victory over the Old Ways of Zakuul. A vertical labyrinth, the Spire is filled with countless neighborhoods, each with its own unique personality. The populace is primarily human, but as the Eternal Empire continues to grow, more aliens are welcomed into the fold.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Odessen is a remote, unsettled planet in Wild Space with a strong connection to the Force. Realizing that Asylum couldn't support a permanent base of operations for the Alliance, Lana Beniko began searching for a more appropriate location. Odessen pulled at her through the Force. Unlike with Tython, Korriban or Yavin 4, Odessen's affinity with the Force is balanced, making it the perfect spot for a coalition of Sith and Jedi. Covered in lush wilderness and mountains, the planet is a hidden oasis with a mild climate and a variety of wildlife.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="194665" version="1065353216">In the five centuries since its discovery by spice smugglers, the planet Darvannis has existed purely as a navigational footnote on most galactic star charts. Located in the Calaron sector of Hutt Space, the planet lacks any profitable resources or unusual native species. A dense asteroid field makes any approach to the planet a risky venture, so most navigators avoid Darvannis entirely.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Levels &lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;-&lt;&lt;2&gt;&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="194665" version="1065353216">CONTROLLED BY:</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="194665" version="1065353216">TRAVEL NOW</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="194665" version="1065353216">&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt; to &lt;&lt;2&gt;&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="194665" version="1065353216">&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt; PARSECS</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="194665" version="1065353216">SPACE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Current Location</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Can not afford travel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="194665" version="1065353216">EXIT MAP</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="194665" version="1065353216">GALAXY MAP</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="194665" version="1065353216">GALAXY VIEW</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Quick travel is forbidden in your current location.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="194665" version="1065353216">You cannot travel while in combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="194665" version="1065353216">You cannot travel while dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="194665" version="1065353216">You are not able to travel while BitRaider is active.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Space</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Level &lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="194665" version="1065353216">You do not have a ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Open location on Galaxy Map.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Travel to your personal ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Purchase the Legacy Perk: Priority Transport: Personal Starship.  This perk will allow you to quickly shuttle to your personal Starship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="194665" version="1065353216">TRACKED MISSIONS:</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="194665" version="1065353216">PARTY MEMBERS:</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Traveling directly to this location is prohibited.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="194665" version="1065353216">CURRENT LOCATION:</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="194665" version="1065353216">&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt; KILOMETERS</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="194665" version="1065353216">Devastated by the Sith centuries ago, the planet Ossus has largely been forgotten by the greater galaxy. Enshrouded in the nebular material of the Cron Drift, the planet is difficult to even reach, with those who survive the journey discovering only hazardous wastelands and abandoned ruins on its surface.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
