<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>819</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/gui/tutorials.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="532678" version="1065353216">TIPS</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Close</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Toggle Off The Tutorial Window</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Toggle On The Tutorial Window</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;/&lt;&lt;2&gt;&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Welcome</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Welcome to Star Wars: The Old Republic. Your epic story in the Star Wars universe has just begun. These tutorials will help guide you. May the Force be with you!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Movement</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can move your character by pressing the A, S, W and D keys. To look around, hold the left mouse button and move the mouse.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Missions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have a mission. In order to find the objective of your mission, open your map. A flashing icon should show you where you need to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Mission Log</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can keep track of your mission objectives through the mission log accessed through the mission icon at the top of your screen. Your missions are also tracked on the right-hand side of the screen.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Class Story Areas (Solo)</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="532678" version="1065353216">These areas are where many important events in your class story take place. A Class Story area can be identified by moving the mouse over its entrance. If the entrance barrier is green, you can enter the story area. If the entrance barrier is red, you cannot enter the story area.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Group Story Areas</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="532678" version="1065353216">A Group Story area can be identified by moving the mouse over its entrance. If the entrance barrier is green, you can enter the story area. If the entrance barrier is red, you cannot enter the story area.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Class Story Areas (Multiplayer)</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can allow group members of your same class into your Class Story area by changing a preference. This preference, called Allow access to same-class story areas, is in the Social tab of the Preference window.

Note: Group members of your same class may be able to enter your Class Story area; however, their missions will not progress while they are in your Class Story area.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Group Story Areas (Multiplayer)</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="532678" version="1065353216">A Group Story area can be identified by moving the mouse over its entrance. If the entrance barrier is green, your group can enter the story area. If the entrance barrier is red, your group cannot enter the story area.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Attacking Enemies</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To engage enemies in battle, left-click on them to target them. Move into attack range. You will know you are in attack range when one or more of the abilities on your Quickbar lights up. Then left-click an ability on the Quickbar. The Quickbar is located at the bottom of your screen.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Using Abilities</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Any time you want to view your abilities, left-click on the Abilities button in the upper part of your screen to open your Abilities panel. To move the ability to your Quickbar, left-click and drag the ability to a location on the Quickbar.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Player and Enemy Status</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your health bar is the red bar located in the lower left part of your screen. When your health reaches zero, you will be defeated. Your ability resource bar is below your health bar. Enemies also have health bars located in the lower right part of your screen.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Looting</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="532678" version="1065353216">When you defeat an enemy, its defeated body will glow if it has loot. Right-click your enemy's defeated body to open its Loot window. Then, right-click on any items in the Loot window to add them to your inventory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Opening Your Inventory</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have picked up an item. It is now in your inventory. You can left-click on the Inventory button in the upper part of your screen to open the Inventory panel. Move the mouse over the acquired item to learn more about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Equipping Items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To equip an item, right-click or double left-click on the item in your inventory. To view your equipped item, click on the Character Sheet button in the upper part of your screen to open the Character Sheet panel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Using Items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can use some of the items in your inventory. Right-click on an item to use it. You can also drag these items to your Quickbar and use them without opening your inventory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Experience Points (XP)</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Experience Points (or XP) are acquired by defeating enemies and completing missions. When you have acquired enough XP, you will gain another level.

Leveling up allows you to become more powerful, acquire more abilities and take on greater challenges. You must find a trainer to learn new abilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Leveling Up</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Congratulations! You have reached a new level! Your health and some of your core attributes have been increased, and you should have an easier time fighting higher level enemies. Also, you should seek out a class trainer to learn new abilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Mission Completed</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Congratulations! You have completed a mission. Mission givers will reward you with experience and often will give you credits and items as well. Right-click on mission givers to interact with them and claim your reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Unavailable Missions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="532678" version="1065353216">If a mission giver has a gray mission offer symbol over its head that means it offers a mission too high for your current level. Return to this mission giver once you have reached a higher level.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Vendors</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have items to sell. In order to sell your items you must find a vendor. Vendors are represented by a credit icon on your map.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Inventory Almost Full</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your inventory is almost full. To free up inventory space, you can sell items you have acquired. Locate a vendor and right-click on him. Then, right-click on any items in your inventory you would like to sell.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Inventory Full</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your inventory is full. You can either sell items to vendors, or you can pay credits to expand your Inventory Module by left-clicking the Expand Inventory Module button located in the center of your Inventory panel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Chatting</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To chat, press the ENTER key, type your text, and your text will appear in the chat box in the top left of your screen. Press ENTER again to display your text. For more chat options, click the chat button to the left of the Chat window.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Players and Grouping</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To group, all you need to do is to right-click on another player. You will be given the option to send them a group invite. If they accept, you will be able to chat with them using Group chat. To find players to group with, mark yourself as Looking For Group using the Who panel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Quick Travel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Quick Travel allows you to transport from your current location to a quick travel point. You can unlock a quick travel point by right-clicking on a Quick Travel Point terminal.

You automatically unlock a quick travel point when you enter a new planet. Also, there's a cooldown for using the Quick Travel ability.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Appraising Enemy Difficulty</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have targeted a challenging enemy. Challenge ratings range from weakest to strongest: Weak, Standard, Strong, Elite and Boss.

More challenging enemies may require you to group with others to defeat them. Mousing over enemies is a quick way to appraise them in a hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Defeated</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have been defeated. You can be revived by either activating a medical probe or by returning to the nearest medical center. Nearby players can also revive your character if they are not in combat mode.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Class Trainers</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can learn new abilities from your class trainer. Right-click on your class trainer to interact with them. Note: Training is expensive. Be sure to save some credits for training when you level up!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Specialty Goods</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have acquired a data crystal. These crystals contain data of lost knowledge. They can be traded to Data Crystal and Specialty vendors for specialty goods.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Companions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have gained a companion! These characters complement your strengths and weaknesses and provide company for the epic journey you will inevitably undertake. Companions have combat abilities that can be toggled on and off by right-clicking on an ability next to their portrait in the lower left corner of the screen.

Left-click on the + sign to the far right of their portrait to display the Companion Quickbar located below your Quickbars.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Advanced Class Training</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Now that you've reached level 10, you can choose an Advanced Class. Advanced Classes are specialized careers that will not only make you more distinct and powerful, but will also help further define your role. Left-click on the Disciplines button in the upper part of your screen to open the Disciplines panel and make your selection between two options based on your character's current class.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Disciplines</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Disciplines provide access to various special abilities (such as the ability to dual-wield lightsabers, wear heavy armor) and allows you to customize how your character plays during combat. At certain levels during your progression you will get new abilities and skills that grant special bonuses to exisitng abilities you are already using within your Discipline. In addition, you can select Utility Skills from a pool of possible choices, allowing your character to play exactly how you want it while keeping your main role strength intact. 

Left-click on the Disciplines button in the upper part of your screen to open the Disciplines panel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Crew Skill Trainers</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Crew Skills allow you to assign your crew of companions to gather resources, craft useful and valuable items, and even undertake their own missions, bringing you a variety of benefits and rewards. The world map and minimap will show you where nearby Crew Skill trainers are located.

Right-clicking on a Crew Skill trainer will grant you a Codex entry that tells you more about the Crew Skill available to train. To manage your crew of companions, left-click on the Crew Window button in the upper part of your screen.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="532678" version="1065353216">PvP Warzone Queue</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="328" id2="532678" version="1065353216">At level 10, you can participate in player versus player Warzones. Left-click the PvP Warzone button located in the lower right part of the screen and select the Warzones Icon. Then select to Queue Solo or Queue Group to be added to the warzone queue.

Once enough players are queued up, you will receive a popup allowing you to enter the battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Gathering Resources</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You are near a gathering resource node, which you can harvest if you have the proper skill. You can instruct your companion to gather the node by holding down the SHIFT key and right-clicking on the node, or you can gather the resource node yourself by right-clicking on it. Nearby gathering resource nodes are also visible on the world map and minimap.

You can also gather resources by sending your companions on missions. Note: Mission costs can be expensive. Be sure to save some credits!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Crafting Exceptional Items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have crafted an item! There is a chance that when you craft an item it will be of exceptional quality. Exceptional quality items will be labeled with a special prefix and will possess an Augment slot. Augments make crafted items more powerful and can be acquired by sending your companions on Slicing missions. Note: You can queue up to 5 crafting tasks for a companion.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Crafting Droids and Workstations</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have learned a crafting skill. Once you acquire a ship, you will be granted access to a Crafting Droid companion and a crafting workstation (required for higher level crafting). Your ship's cargo hold can also be used to store crafting materials. If your inventory lacks the required materials to craft an item, companions can use the stored materials from the ship's cargo hold.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Reverse Engineering Crafted Items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can reverse engineer most items that you craft and some items that you find in the world. Reverse engineering will return you some of the materials needed to craft that item, as well as offer a chance to make a better version of that item.

To reverse engineer an item, open your Inventory panel, left-click on the Reverse Engineering button and then right-click on the item.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Galaxy Map</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have acquired your starship! You may travel to other worlds by right-clicking on the Galaxy Map object in your ship's cockpit and selecting your destination. Make sure you have credits for the fuel cost.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Piloting Speeders</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have acquired a Speeder bike! Left-click on the Abilities button in the upper part of your screen to open your Abilities panel. Then left-click on the Vehicles tab. You can also left-click and drag your Speeder bike to move it to your Quickbar.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Space Combat Movement</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="532678" version="1065353216">As you move your mouse around the screen, your ship will fly toward your cursor. Press the SPACEBAR to barrel roll.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="343" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Space Combat Blasters</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="344" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can fire your starship blasters at the target under your cursor by left-clicking. Hold down the left mouse button to fire continuously.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="345" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Space Combat Missiles</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="346" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Hold down the right mouse button and select 1 to 4 targets by dragging the mouse over them. When you release the right mouse button, a missile will be fired at each target.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="347" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Influence</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="348" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Making decisions in a conversation can modify your companion's influence for you. Make decisions they agree with, and their opinion of you will increase. Note that companions rarely think in terms of &quot;Dark Side&quot; and &quot;Light Side,&quot; but instead value concepts like honor, avarice or mischief.

Read your companions' Codex entries to see what exactly they might value. Note: Influence improves a companion's mission and crafting results as well as reduces the amount of time required for them to perform crew skill tasks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="349" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Gifts</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="350" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Some items will increase your currently selected companion's influence when you use them. Better gifts give greater rewards. Note that different companions value different kinds of gifts, so be sure to pay attention to their reactions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="351" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Taking Cover</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="352" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can take cover from enemy blaster fire by moving behind a solid object and using the Cover ability (default key: F) on your quickbar.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="353" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Respecialization</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="354" id2="532678" version="1065353216">If you make a mistake choosing a Discipline, you can choose to abandon it by interacting with the Skill Mentor. You can find the Skill Mentor aboard your Fleet's space station. Abandoning your Discipline will allow you to choose a new one from the three your Advanced Class has available. Note that the cost of doing so increases each time you do so.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="355" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Damaged Items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="356" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You may have noticed an indicator on your screen denoting that one of your items is very damaged and nearly destroyed. Items take damage from wear and tear in combat and are damaged greatly when you are defeated in combat.

Items that are fully destroyed offer no benefit to the character, so you should find a vendor to repair these items as soon as it is convenient.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="357" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Destroyed Items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="358" id2="532678" version="1065353216">One of your items has been destroyed, and you can no longer gain the benefits of equipping that item. It is recommended you find a vendor and repair it as quickly as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="359" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Light Side/Dark Side</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="360" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Some conversation responses will reward the player with Light Side or Dark Side points. Your conversation choices can change your Light Side/Dark Side levels. You can check your Light Side/Dark Side level by opening the Character Sheet panel.

Some items you find in the world have level requirements (such as Light Side III) before they can be used. These items can often be purchased at vendors throughout the game.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="361" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Equipping Your Companion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="362" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can equip gear onto your companion! Do so by selecting the Companion tab on your Character Sheet, and then equipping gear as usual. Note that your companions' skills may limit which gear they can equip.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="363" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Social Points</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="364" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can earn social points by joining missions and conversations with other players. You can win more social points by winning (and even losing) conversation rolls. You can view your social score on your Character Sheet.

Some items you find in the world have level requirements (such as Social II) before they can be used. These items can often be purchased at vendors throughout the game.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="365" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Holocalls</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="366" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have to use your holocommunicator to complete your current mission. Find a safe location, then click on the Holocall button below to initiate that conversation. Holocalls are usually better answered sooner rather than later.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="367" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Mission Items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="368" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have a mission that requires you to use an item in your inventory to progress.  All mission items can be found in the Mission Items tab of your Inventory panel.

To use a mission item, select a target and right-click the item in your inventory. You can also drag the item to your Quickbar and click the icon or use the hotkey.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="369" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Item Modifications</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="370" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have acquired an item modification. You can use this to improve one of your existing items; however, item modifications can only fit into compatible slots. If an item is modifiable, you can CTRL + right-click on it to open its Modification window.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="371" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Speaking with Companions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="372" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your companion wants to speak to you in private. Sometimes, he or she will be satisfied talking with you in a cantina, but more frequently, you will need the privacy of your own ship. Mouse over the icon on your companion's portrait for more information.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="373" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Selling Junk</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="374" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your inventory is full. However, your companion can help you with that. Right-click on his or her portrait and choose Sell Junk, and your companion will go off and sell all gray-quality items in your inventory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="375" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Start Saving!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="376" id2="532678" version="1065353216">When you reach level 25, you will be able to learn how to pilot Speeder bikes and other ground vehicles. You might want to start saving your credits now--the cost to learn vehicle piloting is expensive.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="377" id2="532678" version="1065353216">PvP Warzone Ready</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="378" id2="532678" version="1065353216">A warzone is now ready for you. Left-click ENTER Now to be transported to the battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="379" id2="532678" version="1065353216">PvP Warzones</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="380" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have entered a player versus player warzone! Warzones are instanced battles between teams of players. Watch the Warzone UI at the upper right part of the screen to see the status of your objectives.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="381" id2="532678" version="1065353216">PvP Valor Ranks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="382" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have gained a valor rank! Valor ranks display your experience in PvP combat and unlock special rewards based on your progress. You can view your current valor rank from the Character Sheet panel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="383" id2="532678" version="1065353216">PvP Flag</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="384" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You are flagged for PvP! You can now attack and be attacked by other players who are also flagged for PvP. Your PvP flag will wear off after 5 minutes in PvP-safe areas.

If you are defeated by another player, you will become immune to PvP and unable to reactivate your PvP flag for 10 minutes.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="385" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Open World PvP</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="386" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have entered a player versus player area! This area contains objectives for both factions to achieve. Fight against opposing faction players and accomplish your faction's objectives while preventing the enemy from accomplishing theirs.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="387" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Datacrons</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="388" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Many datacrons remain hidden throughout the known worlds. These ancient artifacts enhance those who activate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="389" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Taxis</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="390" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Taxis allow you to quickly travel between locations. Use a taxi by right-clicking a Transport Service droid and selecting your destination. Make sure you have enough credits for the fare.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="391" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Elevators</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="392" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Some elevators will require you to right-click a nearby console to use it. Other elevators are always moving, pausing only for a few seconds to let you onto its lift platform.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="393" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Dangerous Environments</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="394" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Blazing infernos, toxic lakes, blistering sand dunes, freezing tundras and falling long distances can harm you if you're not careful. When faced with such hazards, the safest thing to do is back up the way you came until you are out of danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="395" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Fleet Commendations</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="396" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Ships can be improved with upgrades purchased from Starship Sales and Service vendors. These ship upgrades can only be purchased with fleet commendations and cannot be purchased with credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="397" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Starship Sales and Service Vendors</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="398" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Starship Sales and Service vendors can be found among large groups of vendors, typically near each planet's entry point. Use fleet commendations to buy upgrades and improve your ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="399" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Ship Upgrades</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="400" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To add an upgrade to your ship, open your Character Sheet panel and left-click the Ship tab. Then open your Inventory panel and drag the upgrade into the appropriate upgrade location in the Ship tab.

If your upgrades have special abilities, they can be used by clicking their icons in your ship's Quickbar on the lower left corner of your screen.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="401" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Fleet Command Console</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="402" id2="532678" version="1065353216">While in your ship's cockpit, right-click on the Fleet Command Console to learn if your contact has more space missions for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="403" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Locating Space Missions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="404" id2="532678" version="1065353216">While in your ship's cockpit, use the galaxy map to locate any available space missions. While viewing a mission's objectives, you can choose to start the mission by left-clicking the Travel Now button.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="405" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Proton Torpedoes</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="406" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To fire a proton torpedo, target a critical point on an enemy and hold down the right mouse button for a few seconds. Once the proton torpedo has locked on, release the mouse button to launch it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="407" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Bonus Objectives</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="408" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Bonus objectives are often given while doing a mission. You do not have to complete a bonus objective in order to complete your primary goals, but it's a great way to get additional experience.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="409" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Heroic Missions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="410" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Heroic missions can be more challenging than one player can handle alone. For many heroic missions, you'll need to call in a friend or two to help. Some heroic missions will need a full group of four players in order to succeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="411" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Maps</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="412" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can track current mission objectives on your world map. Access your world map from the planet icon on your minimap. Your mission objectives will appear on the map as animating icons. Icons for services (such as vendors and trainers) can be toggled on and off using the filter controls.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="413" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Security Chests</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="414" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Security Chests are hidden throughout various planets. They can contain valuable items and supplies.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="415" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Codex</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="416" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have received a Codex entry in your mission log. Codex entries are acquired by meeting persons of note, training Crew Skills, receiving titles, exploring planets and defeating powerful enemies.

To view your Codex entries, left-click on the Mission Log button in the upper part of your screen then left-click the Codex tab.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="417" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Mail</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="418" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have clicked on a mailbox. Mailboxes allow players to send and receive in-game mail and items. You can also send mail to one of your other characters. However, you cannot send or receive in-game mail or items to player characters of opposite factions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="419" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Galactic Market Kiosks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="420" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have clicked on a galactic market kiosk. These kiosks allow you to buy and sell items to and from other players.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="421" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Flashpoint Missions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="422" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Flashpoints are action-packed, story-driven adventures that test a group of players to their limits, putting them up against difficult foes in volatile situations.

Flashpoint missions take place in private story areas and most are balanced for a full group of four players.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="423" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Flashpoint Instances</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="424" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Flashpoint instances will last for as long as the group remains inside. If all players leave the flashpoint, they can return for one hour without losing progress; after an hour, all progress through the flashpoint will be lost. You may leave a Flashpoint at any time by left-clicking the Exit Area button above your minimap.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="425" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Instance Ownership</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="426" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Instances are always owned by the current group leader. Kicking any players from the group will remove them from the instance after 30 seconds.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="427" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Leaving a Flashpoint</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="428" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You may leave a Flashpoint at any time by left-clicking the Exit Area button above your minimap.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="429" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Operations</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="430" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Operations are instanced, large-scale multiplayer challenges. Assemble a full ops group of either 8 or 16 players before embarking on an operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="431" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Leading an Ops Group</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="432" id2="532678" version="1065353216">As leader of an ops group, you may promote assistant leads or rearrange players within the ops group. To rearrange the group, open the Operations window, left-click a player's name and drag it to the desired position.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="433" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Ops Groups</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="434" id2="532678" version="1065353216">An ops group is a force of either 8 or 16 players banded together for large-scale multiplayer challenges, such as operations or warzones.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="435" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Lockouts</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="436" id2="532678" version="1065353216">When your group defeats a powerful enemy or defeats a challenge in an operation, you will be locked out of that content temporarily. Check the Lockouts tab in your mission log for more information.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="437" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Difficulty Modes</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="438" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can change the difficulty mode for flashpoints and operations by changing the Difficulty Mode setting on your player portrait.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="439" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Ilum PvP Region</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="440" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have entered Western Ice Shelf. Search for the supply crates and collect munitions to destroy the turrets defending the enemy base. Take out enemy players carrying supplies before they are able to use them to destroy the turrets at your base.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="441" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Ilum PvP Supplies</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="442" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You found a supply crate! These crates contain weaponry capable of damaging the defensive turrets around the enemy base. Carry the supplies to the enemy base and attack their turrets.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="443" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Ilum PvP Turrets</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="444" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You are using an anti-personnel turret! These turrets fire a limited number of shots effective against enemy troops. Defend the power generators to keep enemy players from disabling your turrets.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="445" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Ilum PvP Base Destruction</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="446" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have damaged an enemy turret! Once the turrets are destroyed, allied bombers will be called in to destroy the enemy base. But beware, enemy players are also trying to destroy your base, so be prepared to defend your base at all costs.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="447" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Ilum PvP Victory</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="448" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have destroyed the enemy base and secured the area for you and your allies! The battle is done for now, but soon the enemy will repair their base and the conflict will begin again.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="449" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Ilum PvP Defeat</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="450" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Enemy players have destroyed your base! Repairs to your base's turrets will be completed soon. In the meantime, secure the munitions supplies before your enemies do and prepare to begin the battle again.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="452" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Fog of War</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="453" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have surveyed your first map. Accessible exterior (and some interior) areas are indicated by light-colored hexes on your map. Walk into the center of a hex to explore the surrounding area and earn experience points. Explore all areas to survey an entire map; complete all maps to survey an entire planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="454" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Energy</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="455" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your energy regenerates faster at higher energy levels. As your energy decreases, so does the rate at which it recovers. To maintain a high amount of energy, use Rifle Shot regularly to allow your energy to recover.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="456" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Energy</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="457" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your energy regenerates faster at higher energy levels. As your energy decreases, so does the rate at which it recovers. To maintain a high amount of energy, use Flurry of Bolts regularly to allow your energy to recover.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="458" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Heat</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="459" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your heat dissipates faster at lower heat levels. As your heat builds, so does the time it takes to dissipate that heat. To maintain a low heat level, use Rapid Shots regularly to allow your heat to dissipate.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="460" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Energy Cells</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="461" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your energy cells regenerate faster at higher energy levels. As your energy cells deplete, so does the rate at which they regenerate. To maintain a high level of energy cells, use Hammer Shot regularly to allow your energy cells to regenerate.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="462" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Titles</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="463" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have unlocked a title! You can choose to display that title by clicking the icon next to your name on your character sheet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="464" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Operations</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="465" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have unlocked Operations! Band together with 16 players to take on the greatest threats in the galaxy. Ops start on the fleet. To enter one, you must be in an Ops Group. Right-click on your character portrait to convert your group to an Ops Group.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="466" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Flashpoint Veteran Mode</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="467" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have unlocked Flashpoint Veteran Mode! Locate Flashpoint Veteran Mode access missions near the flashpoint entrances to conquer greater challenges and reap greater rewards.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="468" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Ilum Territorial Control PvP</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="469" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have unlocked Ilum Territorial Control PvP! Participate in the planet's ongoing PvP conflict by competing for the five battle points on the western side of Ilum. Win all five, win control for your side and reap PvP rewards.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="470" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Leaving an Operation</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="471" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You may leave an Operation at any time by left-clicking the Exit Area button above your minimap.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="472" id2="532678" version="1065353216">New Tutorial Entries:</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="473" id2="532678" version="1065353216">New</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="474" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Read</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="475" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Show read articles</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="476" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Show new articles</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="477" id2="532678" version="1065353216">TUTORIAL INDEX</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="478" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Show Tutorial Alerts</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="479" id2="532678" version="1065353216">OPEN INDEX</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="480" id2="532678" version="1065353216">TUTORIAL</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="481" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Show next article:</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="482" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Show previous article:</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="483" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;/&lt;&lt;2&gt;&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="484" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Summary text</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="485" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/en-us/tutorial.leveling_character1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;
Your health &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;and some of your core&lt;/font&gt; attributes have been increased, making it easier to fight more powerful enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="486" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Panel 2 text</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="487" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Panel 3 text</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="488" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Category</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="489" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Coming Soon 1 title</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="490" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Coming Soon 2 title</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="491" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Coming Soon 3 title</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="492" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Legacy title</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="493" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Activity Finder title</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="494" id2="532678" version="1065353216">EmergencyFleetPass Title</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="495" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;u&gt;Current filter settings are preventing you from seeing tutorials. Click here to remove filters.&lt;/u&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="591" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Getting Around</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="592" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Missions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="593" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Combat</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="594" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Items and Inventory</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="595" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Character Advancement</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="596" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Teaming Up</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="597" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Companions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="598" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Crew Skills</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="599" id2="532678" version="1065353216">The Journey Ahead</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="600" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Movement</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="601" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Basic movement skills help you explore your environment.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="602" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.movement1a.dds' width='324' height='248'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To move forward, press the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;W&lt;/font&gt; key. To move backward, press &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;S&lt;/font&gt;. To turn to the left, press &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;A&lt;/font&gt;. To turn to the right, press &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;D&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.movement1b.dds' width='324' height='96'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="603" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.movement2b.dds' width='324' height='96'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To jump, press the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;spacebar&lt;/font&gt;. To overcome some obstacles, you may need to jump &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;while moving&lt;/font&gt;. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.movement2a.dds' width='324' height='260'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="604" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To rotate the camera, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;hold down one of the mouse buttons&lt;/font&gt; while moving the mouse.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.movement3a.dds' width='324' height='152'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Holding down the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;left mouse button&lt;/font&gt; while moving the mouse rotates only the camera.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.movement3b.dds' width='324' height='112'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Holding down the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right mouse button&lt;/font&gt; while moving the mouse turns your character with the camera.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="605" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Missions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="606" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Completing missions advances your character's development and progresses your story.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="607" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.flashpoints2.dds' width='324' height='272'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;triangle icon&lt;/font&gt; over a character's head means that he or she has a mission available for you. &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Right-click&lt;/font&gt; on the character to start a conversation and learn more about the mission.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some missions may require content access to be purchased before accepting the mission; these triangle icons will display the Cartel Coin symbol.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="608" id2="532678" version="1065353216">The are four different types of &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;mission icon&lt;/font&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.missions_4_0_icons.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Story Missions&lt;/font&gt; are the core content of Star Wars: The Old Republic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Mission Offers&lt;/font&gt; are additional, non-critical missions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Exploration Missions&lt;/font&gt; are optional and can be enabled at the top right of your Map Screen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.missions_exploration.dds' width='324' height='44'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any mission can be &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Repeatable.&lt;/font&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="609" id2="532678" version="1065353216">The same icons &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;on your minimap&lt;/font&gt; mark the location of a character with an available mission. &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.missions2.dds' width='324' height='272'&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accepted missions appear in the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;mission tracker&lt;/font&gt; in the upper-right corner of the screen. The light-blue text tells you what to do next in the mission.&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.missions3.dds' width='324' height='100'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="610" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Class Story and Group Areas</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="611" id2="532678" version="1065353216">These areas are dedicated to critical moments in specific class story and group missions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="612" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.story_group_areas1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Class Story and Group areas are identified by a red or green entrance barrier. If the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;barrier is green, you can enter&lt;/font&gt; the area. If it's red, you can't enter.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="613" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Hover your cursor over the entrance barrier to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;bring up a tooltip&lt;/font&gt; with details on what the area is reserved for.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.story_group_areas2.dds' width='324' height='272'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Class Story areas for group members are blue. You can enter these areas &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;unless you share the same class.&lt;/font&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="614" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.story_group_areas3.dds' width='324' height='272'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can allow group members of your class into your Class Story areas by selecting that setting on the Social tab of the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Preferences menu&lt;/font&gt;. However, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;their class stories will not progress&lt;/font&gt; while they are in your Class Story area.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="615" id2="532678" version="1065353216">World Map</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="616" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can track mission objectives and locate points of interest on your world map.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="617" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.world_map1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To open the world map, click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;planet icon&lt;/font&gt; next to your minimap.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="618" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Mission objectives&lt;/font&gt; and directions to objectives in other areas are marked with specific icons. &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.world_map2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="619" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.world_map3.dds' width='324' height='280'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Green arrows&lt;/font&gt; point to area transition points and taxis to mission objectives that aren't on the current map.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="620" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Taxis</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="621" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Travel quickly between locations by using the taxi transport service.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="622" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.taxis1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taxi locations are indicated by the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;double-sided arrow icon&lt;/font&gt; over a transport service droid's head or on your map.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="623" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To use a taxi, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right-click&lt;/font&gt; on the transport service droid to bring up the destination map.  &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.taxis2.dds' width='324' height='188'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To select a destination, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;left-click&lt;/font&gt; on the icon for the location you want to travel to. Each travel route charges a fee.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="624" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.taxis3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taxi stations that lead to mission objectives are &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;highlighted in green&lt;/font&gt; on the destination map.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="625" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Basic Combat</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="626" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Hostile enemies will attack you as you approach them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="627" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.basic_combat1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Select an enemy you want to attack by &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;left-clicking&lt;/font&gt; on it.  When you do, you should see his nameplate and health bar.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="628" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Use your abilities to attack the enemy. Abilities appear as &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;icons in the quickslot bar&lt;/font&gt; at the bottom of your screen. &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.basic_combat2a.dds' width='324' height='128'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To activate an ability, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;left-click&lt;/font&gt; on the icon or press the corresponding number key. &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.basic_combat2b.dds' width='324' height='96'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="629" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Some abilities do not work if you are &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;out of range&lt;/font&gt;. Melee-based abilities can only be used up close, and even ranged abilities have limitations. &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.basic_combat3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As you deal damage, the health bar over the enemy's head drains. When the health bar is empty, the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;enemy is defeated&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="630" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Cover</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="631" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your class can take cover to gain a defensive advantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="632" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.cover1.dds' width='324' height='256'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where cover is available, you will see a green silhouette. By default, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;press the F key&lt;/font&gt; to roll into cover.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="633" id2="532678" version="1065353216">While in cover, you have strong defensive bonuses and access to additional abilities that appear in the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cover Bar of your quickslots&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.cover2.dds' width='324' height='152'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As you learn new cover abilities, you may want to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;add them&lt;/font&gt; to the Cover Bar.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="634" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.cover3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can disable the Cover Bar on the User Interface tab of the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Preferences menu&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="635" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Loot</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="636" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Acquire new items by looting defeated enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="637" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.loot1.dds' width='324' height='400'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A beam of light shining from a downed enemy means that they have loot. &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Right-click&lt;/font&gt; on the body to open the loot window.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="638" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can right-click each item in the loot window to take it. However, in most cases, it's easier to click on &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Take All&lt;/font&gt; to grab all of the items in the window.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.loot2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="639" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Different-colored beams and item names correspond to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;item quality&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.loot3.dds' width='324' height='272'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you see a green beam, be sure to get the loot! Even if it's not useful to you, it's probably &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;valuable&lt;/font&gt; and worth taking to sell later.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="640" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Inventory and Equipment</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="641" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Newly acquired items are stored in your inventory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="642" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.inventory_equipment1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To open the Inventory panel, left-click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;person icon&lt;/font&gt; on the Menu Bar and then left-click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;box icon&lt;/font&gt; or press the I key.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="643" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To see an item's details, hover your mouse cursor over it. To equip an item, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right-click&lt;/font&gt; on it.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.inventory_equipment2.dds' width='324' height='300'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some items might require a Free-to-Play Player to have the correct &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Authorization&lt;/font&gt; to use it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="644" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.inventory_equipment3.dds' width='324' height='348'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To see your character's equipped items, open the Character Sheet panel by clicking on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;person icon&lt;/font&gt; on the Menu Bar or pressing C.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="645" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Chatting with Other Players</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="646" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Communicate with other players in the area using the Chat panel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="647" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To type a message, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;press the Enter key&lt;/font&gt; to open the Chat panel.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.chatting_others1.dds' width='324' height='96'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Press &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Enter&lt;/font&gt; again to send the message.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="648" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To access chat options, click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;chat button&lt;/font&gt; in the left corner of the Chat panel or use slash commands.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.chatting_others2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="649" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can type &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;/say&lt;/font&gt; before your message to speak only with nearby players or &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;/yell&lt;/font&gt; to shout across a wide area.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.chatting_others3.dds' width='324' height='300'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;/general&lt;/font&gt;, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;/trade&lt;/font&gt;, and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;/pvp&lt;/font&gt; channels cover the entire planet and are limited to the Origin Worlds for Free-to-Play Players until level 10.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="650" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Grouping with Other Players</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="651" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Playing in a group is a great way to take on more challenging content.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="652" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.grouping_players1.dds' width='324' height='300'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To form a group, left-click on another player to target them and then left-click on the purple &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Invite to Group button&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="653" id2="532678" version="1065353216">If the other player accepts, you can chat with them on a group channel (&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;/group&lt;/font&gt;). Their portrait is also added to your screen.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.grouping_players2.dds' width='324' height='256'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Group members and mission markers appear as &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;purple icons&lt;/font&gt; on your map and minimap.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="654" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.grouping_players3.dds' width='324' height='288'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Take advantage of groups! Grouping with other players can help you complete difficult missions, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;gain more experience&lt;/font&gt; and defeat difficult enemies more quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="655" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Light Side/Dark Side</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="656" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your conversation choices determine your path toward the Light Side or Dark Side.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="657" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.light_dark_level1.dds' width='324' height='300'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Making certain &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;choices in conversation&lt;/font&gt; reward you with either Light Side or Dark Side points.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="658" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can check your alignment status on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Character Sheet panel&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.light_dark_level2.dds' width='324' height='344'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hover your cursor over the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Alignment bar&lt;/font&gt; to see your Light Side and Dark Side levels as well as your total alignment value.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="659" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Some items have alignment &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;level requirements&lt;/font&gt; (such as Dark II or Light IV) that you must meet before you can use them.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.light_dark_level3.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;vendors&lt;/font&gt; also offer items with these requirements.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="660" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Leveling Your Character</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="661" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Congratulations! You've gained a level!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="662" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.leveling_character1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your health and some of your core attributes have &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;increased&lt;/font&gt;, making it easier to fight more powerful enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="663" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Find a class trainer when you level up. A &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;green + symbol&lt;/font&gt; under the trainer's icon indicates new abilities you can learn. &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.leveling_character2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="664" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Right-click&lt;/font&gt; on the class trainer to bring up your Abilities panel and then &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;left-click&lt;/font&gt; on new abilities to train them for a fee.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.leveling_character3.dds' width='324' height='296'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly trained abilities are added to your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Quickbar&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="665" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Vendors</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="666" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Buy and sell items at a vendor.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="667" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.vendors1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Selling items you have no use for is a good way to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;earn extra credits&lt;/font&gt; and free up space in your inventory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="668" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Vendors appear as &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;credit icons&lt;/font&gt; on your map and minimap.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.vendors2.dds' width='324' height='368'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Free-to-Play Players will see increased vendor prices compared to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Subscribers&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="669" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To open a vendor's shop, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right-click on the vendor&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.vendors3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To buy an item, right-click on it in the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;shop inventory&lt;/font&gt;. To sell one of your items, right-click on it in &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;your inventory&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="670" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Understanding Enemy Difficulty</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="671" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Some enemies are more challenging than others.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="672" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Insignias attached to the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;portraits&lt;/font&gt; of enemies show their relative difficulty.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.enemy_difficulty1.dds' width='324' height='116'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;More complex insignias indicate &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;more difficult opponents&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="673" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To get a brief description of enemies, hover your cursor over them. &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Targeting the enemy&lt;/font&gt; reveals their full details.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.enemy_difficulty2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="674" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.enemy_difficulty3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To defeat more challenging enemies such as Champions, Elites, and Bosses, you may need to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;group&lt;/font&gt; with other players.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="675" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Defeated</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="676" id2="532678" version="1065353216">After you're defeated, you need to be revived.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="677" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Call a medical probe to be revived at your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;current location&lt;/font&gt; or return to the nearest medcenter.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.defeated1.dds' width='324' height='176'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The time it takes to call a medical probe &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;increases&lt;/font&gt; if you're defeated more than once in a short period of time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Free-to-Play Players are initially limited to 5 Medical Probes. Additional Medical Probes can be found in the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Market&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="678" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Nearby players&lt;/font&gt; can also revive you if they're not in combat. &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.defeated2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you're defeated, your equipment's durability &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;decreases&lt;/font&gt; significantly. When an item's durability is depleted, it will be unusable until it's repaired.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="679" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.defeated3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Returning to the nearest medcenter &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;resets&lt;/font&gt; the medical probe's cooldown time and gives you a chance to repair items or purchase consumable items.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="680" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Unavailable Missions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="681" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Some missions are not immediately available.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="682" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.unavailable_missions1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;gray mission icon&lt;/font&gt; over a character's head usually indicates a mission that will become available at a higher level.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="683" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To begin the mission, return to this character when you've reached a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;higher level&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.unavailable_missions2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="684" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.unavailable_missions3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daily and Weekly repeatable missions use a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;triangle icon with arrows&lt;/font&gt;. Once you've completed the mission, the icon turns gray. If you return on another day, the mission will be available again.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="685" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Managing Your Inventory</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="686" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your inventory is almost full.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="687" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.managing_inventory1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If your inventory gets full, you will be unable to acquire new items. To free up space, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;sell items to a vendor&lt;/font&gt; or purchase more inventory space.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="688" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To purchase more inventory space, click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Expand Inventory Module button&lt;/font&gt; in the Inventory panel.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.managing_inventory2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can purchase up to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;5&lt;/font&gt; additional inventory modules; the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;credits&lt;/font&gt; cost increases each time you add more space but the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Coins&lt;/font&gt; cost remains the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="689" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.managing_inventory3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If your inventory gets full while you're in the field, you can &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;discard less valuable items&lt;/font&gt; by dragging them out of the Inventory panel and confirming that you want to destroy them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="690" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Data Crystals</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="691" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Data Crystals let you purchase specialty goods.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="692" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.commendations1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To see your data crystals, open your Inventory panel and then click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Currency tab&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="693" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Mission rewards, defeated enemies, space combat and PvP Warzones are some of the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;many sources&lt;/font&gt; for data crystals.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.commendations2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="694" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.commendations3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trade data crystals to data crystal and specialty goods &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;vendors&lt;/font&gt; to get high-quality equipment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Free-to-Play Players will find higher prices for items from these vendors compared to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Subscribers&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="695" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Quick Travel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="696" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Activating Quick Travel terminals lets you shuttle between locations you've discovered.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="697" id2="532678" version="1065353216">As you explore each planet, you'll find &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Quick Travel terminals&lt;/font&gt; at special locations. &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.quick_travel1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most terminals will unlock as you reveal the map areas they reside in, otherwise to unlock a terminal, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right-click&lt;/font&gt; on it. It is now available on your map.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="698" id2="532678" version="1065353216">When you arrive on a new planet, you unlock a terminal there &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;automatically&lt;/font&gt;. &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.quick_travel2.dds' width='324' height='240'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To activate Quick Travel, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;left-click on the ability&lt;/font&gt; in your Quickbar to open the Quick Travel destination map.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="699" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Left-click&lt;/font&gt; on your destination's icon, and a shuttle is dispatched to transport you there immediately. &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.quick_travel3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subscribers can use Quick Travel &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;once every 6 minutes&lt;/font&gt;. Free-to-Play Players have a 30 minute cooldown. You can reduce Quick Travel cooldown with &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Legacy Unlocks&lt;/font&gt; from the Legacy Panel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="700" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Social Points</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="701" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Earn social points by grouping with other players.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="702" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.social_points1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You'll be awarded social points for participating in &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;group conversations&lt;/font&gt;. The larger the group, the more social points you'll earn.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="703" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To see your social level, open the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Character Sheet panel&lt;/font&gt;. Each level gives you access to a new tier of social items. &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.social_points2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="704" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.social_points3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social items are available from &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;social vendors&lt;/font&gt; on all of the major planets.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="705" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Companions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="706" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Companion characters will join in your adventures and support you in combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="707" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.companions1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your companion's portrait, health bar, and abilities are located in the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;lower-left corner&lt;/font&gt; of the screen.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="708" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Right-click&lt;/font&gt; your companion's portrait to select their combat role: &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Heal, Tank, or Damage.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.companions2.dds' width='324' height='132'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To set which of your companion's abilities you want them to use, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right-click&lt;/font&gt; on an ability to toggle it on or off.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="709" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.companions3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To manage your companion's equipment, select the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Companion tab&lt;/font&gt; on the Character Sheet panel.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companions equipment is purely cosmetic and does not affect their combat effectiveness.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="710" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Influence</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="711" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Conversation choices can change the way your companion feels about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="712" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You will gain influence based on decisions you make in and out of conversation.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.affection1.dds' width='324' height='128'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companions generally don't view your actions in terms of Light Side or Dark Side. Instead, they &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;value concepts&lt;/font&gt; such as honesty, avarice or mischief.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="713" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Read your companion's &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Codex entry&lt;/font&gt; to get a better understanding of the principles he or she values.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.affection2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="714" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.affection3.dds' width='324' height='148'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Higher influence &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;improves&lt;/font&gt; your Companion's combat effectiveness as well as their speed and quality in performing crew skills.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="715" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Damaged and Destroyed Items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="716" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Repair your equipment regularly to keep it in good condition.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="717" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.damaged_items1.dds' width='324' height='184'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;armor icon&lt;/font&gt; over your character's portrait indicates that one of your equipped items is damaged or destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="718" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Items lose a small amount of durability from general wear and tear, and a larger amount of durability when you are &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;defeated&lt;/font&gt;. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.damaged_items2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="719" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.damaged_items3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When an item's durability drops to 0, the item is no longer usable or provides no benefit when equipped. &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Replace or repair it&lt;/font&gt; at a vendor as soon as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="720" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Mission Items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="721" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Some missions require you to use an item from your inventory to progress.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="722" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Mission items can be activated directly from the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;mission tracker&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.mission_items1.dds' width='324' height='172'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may need to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;select a target&lt;/font&gt; before you can activate the item.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="723" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You may need to use a mission item in a tight spot, such as &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;during combat&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.mission_items2.dds' width='324' height='156'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drag the item to your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Quickbar&lt;/font&gt; and use it just as if it were an ability.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="724" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.mission_items3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can also use mission items from the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Mission Items tab&lt;/font&gt; of your Inventory panel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="725" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Bonus Objectives</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="726" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Some missions offer bonus objectives.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="727" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.bonus_objectives1.dds' width='324' height='172'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bonus objectives appear under the corresponding mission in the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;mission tracker&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You must complete bonus objectives before finishing the mission they are associated with.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="728" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You don't have to complete bonus objectives, but they reward you with &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;extra experience&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.bonus_objectives2.dds' width='324' height='292'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You also earn experience for any bonus objectives a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;group member&lt;/font&gt; completes.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="729" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Some bonus objectives have &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;multiple stages&lt;/font&gt; that lead up to a difficult battle.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.bonus_objectives3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the battle, you may have to go to a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;mission drop box&lt;/font&gt; to complete the bonus objective.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="730" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Dangerous Environments</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="731" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Be careful when traveling through hazardous environments.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="732" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.dangerous_environments1.dds' width='324' height='280'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Environmental factors can &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;pose risks&lt;/font&gt; to the unsuspecting.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="733" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Blazing infernos, toxic lakes, blistering sand dunes, freezing tundra and long falls will &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;harm your character&lt;/font&gt;. &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.dangerous_environments2.dds' width='324' height='268'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="734" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.dangerous_environments3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you encounter such hazards, the safest thing to do is &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;back up the way you came&lt;/font&gt; until you are out of danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="735" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Item Modifications</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="736" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can enhance some items by adding modifications.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="737" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Use item modifications to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;improve equipment&lt;/font&gt; at the Custom (orange) grade or above.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.item_modifications1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Item modifications fit only in &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;compatible slots&lt;/font&gt;; for example, a color crystal requires a color-crystal slot.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="738" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To open the modification panel, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right-click&lt;/font&gt; on the item while holding down the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Ctrl key&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.item_modifications2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can then right-click on appropriate modifications from your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;inventory&lt;/font&gt; or drag them into the corresponding slots.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="739" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To remove a modification, drag it from the item in the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;modification panel&lt;/font&gt; to your inventory.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.item_modifications3.dds' width='324' height='168'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After you accept the extraction cost, you can &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;reuse&lt;/font&gt; the modification.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Modification extraction has a cost in Credits. Subscribers pay a reduced price compared to Free-to-Play Players.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="740" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Titles</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="741" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Titles proclaim your feats and accomplishments.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="742" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.titles1.dds' width='324' height='192'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earn titles by reaching certain &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;social or alignment levels&lt;/font&gt; or milestones in your class story. Some heroic missions and group mission series also grant titles.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="743" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To choose which title (if any) you want to display to other players, open the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Character Sheet panel&lt;/font&gt;. &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.inventory_equipment3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="744" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.titles3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Click the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;medal icon&lt;/font&gt; next to your character's name and select the title you want from a list of all of the titles you've earned.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Subscribers&lt;/font&gt; can freely display their Titles; Free-to-Play Players can purchase the ability to display their Title with Cartel Coins.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="745" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Speaking with Companions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="746" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Companions will let you know when they want to speak with you in private.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="747" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.speaking_companions1.dds' width='324' height='124'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;speech icon&lt;/font&gt; appears on your companion's portrait when he or she wants to talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="748" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Look for an opportunity to speak with your companion on your ship. Sometimes a cantina will also suffice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.speaking_companions2.dds' width='324' height='124'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="749" id2="532678" version="1065353216">When your companion is comfortable talking, the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;mission icon&lt;/font&gt; appears over his or her head.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.speaking_companions3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Right-click&lt;/font&gt; on your companion to start the conversation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="750" id2="532678" version="1065353216">PvP Warzone Queue</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="751" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Participating in PvP Warzones earns you experience, valor points, and access to other benefits.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="752" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.pvp_queue1.dds' width='324' height='300'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To queue for a Warzone, left-click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;faction icon&lt;/font&gt; next to your minimap. Select Queue Group if you're in a group and want to join the battle together.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Subscribers&lt;/font&gt; have unlimited access to Warzones. Free-to-Play Players have a weekly alottment of Warzones, but can purchase a weekly pass from the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Market&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="753" id2="532678" version="1065353216">When enough players have queued, you're &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;prompted&lt;/font&gt; to enter the battle.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.pvp_queue2.dds' width='324' height='116'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You will be transported from your current location directly into the Warzone and returned to the&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt; same location&lt;/font&gt; when the battle is over.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="754" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.pvp_queue3.dds' width='320' height='312'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To compete as a group against other players at your skill level, select the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Ranked Warzone Arenas&lt;/font&gt; icon. You can examine your personal statistics by clicking the small &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Show PvP Stats&lt;/font&gt; button on the lower left side of the window. Ranked Warzone Arenas are only available to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Subscribers&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="755" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Advanced Class Training</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="756" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Advanced classes let you further specialize your combat style.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="757" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.advanced_class_training1.dds' width='324' height='216'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Choosing your advanced class gives you access to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;new skill sets&lt;/font&gt; and helps define the roles you can play in group combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="758" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Use the Combat Proficiencies screen to select your Advanced Class or find your advanced class trainer on a capital world or aboard your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;fleet's space station&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.advanced_class_training2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="759" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.advanced_class_training3.dds' width='324' height='288'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whenever you gain a level, make sure to check the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;advanced class abilities&lt;/font&gt; available from your class trainer.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="760" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Crew Skill Trainers</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="761" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your companions can learn crew skills to earn extra credits and give you access to special items.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="762" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.crew_skill_trainers3.dds' width='324' height='312'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visit crew skill trainers to learn about the various &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;crew skills&lt;/font&gt; and choose the ones you want to train. To locate the trainers, check your map.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Subscribers&lt;/font&gt; can have a three crew skills simultaneously; Free-to-Play Players are limited to one crew skill but can purchase additional slots.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="763" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To manage your companions' crew skill activities, click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;gem icon&lt;/font&gt; on the Menu Bar or press the B key to open the Crew Management panel.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.crew_skill_trainers1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="764" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.crew_skill_trainers2.dds' width='324' height='312'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crew skills let you assign your companions to gather resources, craft useful and valuable items and even undertake their own missions for &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;benefits and rewards&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="765" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Combat Proficiencies</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="766" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Access your Combat Proficiencies to choose specific bonuses and abilities available to your advanced class.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="767" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.skill_trees2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To open the Combat Proficiences, left-click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;person icon&lt;/font&gt; on the Menu Bar and then left-click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;triangle in a circle icon&lt;/font&gt; or press the K key.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="768" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Every time you gain a level, you increase along your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;discipline path&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.skill_trees1.dds' width='324' height='256'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once you gain a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;utility point&lt;/font&gt; select one from the utility selection pane on the right side of the window. Doing so will increase your combat prowess.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="769" id2="532678" version="1065353216">If you want to change the Discipline you've selected, find a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;skill mentor&lt;/font&gt; on your fleet's space station and reset your Discipline.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.skill_trees3.dds' width='324' height='272'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subscribers can reset their Discipline free of charge while Free-to-Play Players have to pay a cost in Credits. The cost to reset &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;increases&lt;/font&gt; with each reset for Free-to-Play Players, but resets weekly.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="770" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Flashpoints</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="771" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Flashpoints are action-packed special adventures designed to challenge your group.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="772" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.flashpoints1.dds' width='324' height='288'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flashpoints involve complex or multiple missions that your group must &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;work together&lt;/font&gt; to complete.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Subscribers&lt;/font&gt; have unlimited access to Flashpoints. Free-to-Play Players have a weekly limit on loot from Flashpoint final bosses, but can purchase a weekly pass from the  &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Market&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="773" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Flashpoint missions usually begin on your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;fleet&lt;/font&gt;, often near the entrance to the respective flashpoint.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.flashpoints2.dds' width='324' height='272'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entering a flashpoint creates a special &quot;instance&quot; for your group. To leave the instance at any time, click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Exit Area&lt;/font&gt; button above your minimap.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="774" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.flashpoints3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If all players in the group leave the flashpoint before it's completed, the instance will close after &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;an hour&lt;/font&gt;, and you will lose all progress.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="775" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Crafting Items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="776" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Crafting skills let you create special items by combining resources.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="777" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.crafting_items1.dds' width='324' height='184'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To open the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Crafting panel&lt;/font&gt;, left-click on the skill in the Crew Management panel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="778" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Browse and sort your available &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;crafting schematics&lt;/font&gt; on the left and see the required &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;components&lt;/font&gt; on the right.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.crafting_items2.dds' width='324' height='232'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After you've gathered the components, click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Craft button&lt;/font&gt; to add it to your companion's queue.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="779" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.crafting_items3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy new crafting schematics from a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;crew skill trainer&lt;/font&gt; or on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Galactic Trade Network&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="780" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Gathering Resources</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="781" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can gather resources if you've trained the appropriate crew skill.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="782" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.gathering_resources1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To have your companion harvest a resource node, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right-click&lt;/font&gt; on it. To harvest it yourself, right-click on it while holding down the Shift key.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="783" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Nearby resource nodes are marked on both the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;world map&lt;/font&gt; and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;minimap&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.gathering_resources2.dds' width='324' height='316'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="784" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can also send your companion on gathering missions from the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Crew Management panel&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.gathering_resources3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These missions can be &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;expensive&lt;/font&gt;, so make sure you can afford them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="785" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Crafting Augmented Items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="786" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Augments make crafted items more powerful.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="787" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.crafting_exceptional_items1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you craft an item, there is a chance that it will have an &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;augmentation slot&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subscribers have a greater chance to create an &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;augmentation slot&lt;/font&gt; than Free-to-Play Players.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="788" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Augment kits can be made through various &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;crew skills&lt;/font&gt; or purchased from the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Galactic Trade Network&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.crafting_exceptional_items3.dds' width='324' height='220'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Augment Kit schematics can be acquired through Slicing missions. Augment Kits can be crafted through Armormech, Synthweaving and Armstech.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="789" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.crafting_exceptional_items3.dds' width='324' height='220'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone can use &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Augment Kits&lt;/font&gt; at a workbench to add or upgrade an augment slot.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Subscribers&lt;/font&gt; pay a reduced fee when adding an Augment Kit to an item.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="790" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Reverse Engineering</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="791" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Reverse-engineer crafted items to recover resource components.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="792" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.reverse_engineering1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can reverse-engineer most items you &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;craft&lt;/font&gt; and some items you find in the world.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="793" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Reverse-engineering an item returns some &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;components&lt;/font&gt; and could give you a schematic for a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;higher-quality&lt;/font&gt; item.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.reverse_engineering2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tooltip indicates if an &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;upgraded schematic&lt;/font&gt; is available to research.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subscribers have a higher chance of schematic discovery than Free-to-Play Players.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="794" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.reverse_engineering3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To reverse-engineer an item in your inventory, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;left-click&lt;/font&gt; on the Reverse Engineering button and then &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right-click&lt;/font&gt; on the item.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="795" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Gifts</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="796" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Gifts help earn influence with your companions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="797" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.gifts1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Better gifts will earn &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;more influence&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="798" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Different companions value different &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;types&lt;/font&gt; of gifts.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.gifts2.dds' width='324' height='292'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check your companions' profiles in the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Codex&lt;/font&gt; to learn their preferences.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="799" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You can acquire gifts from &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;crew skills missions&lt;/font&gt;, and some are available for purchase from vendors.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.gifts3.dds' width='324' height='296'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The curator on the fleet offers some of the best gifts. These gifts require you to combine &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;gift fragments&lt;/font&gt; from crew skills missions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="800" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Selling Trash Items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="801" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your companion can help you free up space in your inventory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="802" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.selling_trash1.dds' width='324' height='268'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If your inventory is full, your companion can &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;sell the trash items&lt;/font&gt; for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="803" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To send your companion to sell trash items, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right-click&lt;/font&gt; on his or her portrait and select the option from the menu.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.selling_trash2.dds' width='324' height='152'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your companion leaves to sell all the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;gray-quality items&lt;/font&gt; in your inventory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="804" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.selling_trash3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Selling trash items should free up some space in your inventory, and your companion will return soon with the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;credits&lt;/font&gt; from the sale.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="805" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your Cargo Hold</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="806" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Use your cargo hold to store items you don't need right away.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="807" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.junk_and_cargo1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To find Cargo Hold Access terminals, look for the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;key icon&lt;/font&gt; on your map and minimap.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subscribers have free access to the cargo hold. Free-to-Play players gain the Cargo Hold after aquiring Preferred Player Status with their first purchase of &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Coins&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="808" id2="532678" version="1065353216">When your cargo hold starts to fill up, you can &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;buy additional cargo bays&lt;/font&gt; directly from the top of the Cargo Hold window.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.junk_and_cargo2.dds' width='324' height='280'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;credits&lt;/font&gt;  cost to purchase an additional bay increases each time, while the Cartel Coin cost is always the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="809" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.junk_and_cargo3.dds' width='324' height='316'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your cargo hold is also a good place to store &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;crafting materials&lt;/font&gt;. Companions can access these components automatically while crafting.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="810" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Galaxy Map</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="811" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Explore the many worlds of the Old Republic in your newly acquired starship!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="812" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.galaxy_map_01.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once you have acquired your personal starship you can travel to other worlds by right clicking on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;galaxy map&lt;/font&gt; in your ship's cockpit or choosing the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;galaxy map&lt;/font&gt; option from the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;menu bar&lt;/font&gt; (shortcut Shift+M)</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="813" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.galaxy_map_02.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Use the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;mouse wheel&lt;/font&gt; to zoom in and out or &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;left click&lt;/font&gt; with the cursor to zoom in to view a particular region.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your location is shown with a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;green icon&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="814" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.galaxy_map_03.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Select a destination and then click on &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Travel Now&lt;/font&gt;. Make sure you have enough credits for fuel costs!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some destinations may also require you have the content purchased. Check the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Market&lt;/font&gt; for new destinations to visit!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="815" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Space Combat</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="816" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Engage in space combat missions to earn experience and rewards.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="817" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.space_combat1a.dds' width='324' height='220'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To pilot your starship, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;move your cursor&lt;/font&gt; around the screen. You can also use the W, A, S, and D keys to move and the spacebar to do a barrel roll.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.space_combat1b.dds' width='324' height='136'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="818" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Hover your cursor over a target and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;left-click&lt;/font&gt; to fire your ship's blasters. Hold down the left mouse button to fire continuously.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.space_combat2a.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt; &lt;br&gt;Continuous fire can clear out enemies quickly, but it prevents your shields from &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;recharging&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.space_combat2b.dds' width='324' height='136'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="819" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.space_combat3a.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To fire missiles, hold down the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right mouse button&lt;/font&gt; and drag your cursor over up to four targets. Releasing the right mouse button fires the missiles. &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.space_combat3b.dds' width='324' height='136'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="820" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Saving for a Speeder</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="821" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Start saving now to purchase your Speeder.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="822" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.saving_for_speeder1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Subscriber&lt;/font&gt;, when you reach level 10 you can &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;learn how to pilot&lt;/font&gt; speeder bikes and other ground vehicles. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Free-to-Play Players can learn to pilot speeders beginning at level 20.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="823" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Before you can pilot a speeder, you have to acquire the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Speeder Piloting ability&lt;/font&gt; from your class trainer.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.saving_for_speeder2.dds' width='324' height='172'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier access to the Speeder Piloting ability can be purchased in the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Legacy Panel&lt;/font&gt; under Global Unlocks for Credits or Cartel Coins.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="824" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.saving_for_speeder3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speeders and other vehicles are &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;expensive&lt;/font&gt;, so you should start saving credits now or you can click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Market&lt;/font&gt; icon next to the menu bar on the top of your screen and purchase one using Cartel Coins.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="825" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Piloting Speeders</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="826" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Travel across planets more quickly with your new Speeder.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="827" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.piloting_speeders1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To activate your Speeder ability, open your Abilities panel, click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Vehicles tab&lt;/font&gt; and select your Speeder.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="828" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To summon your Speeder, click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;speeder icon&lt;/font&gt;. To put it away, click on the icon again.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.piloting_speeders2.dds' width='324' height='256'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To place your Speeder icon in your quickslots, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;drag the icon&lt;/font&gt; from your Abilities panel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="829" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.piloting_speeders3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most interior spaces &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;prohibit Speeders&lt;/font&gt; and, after a brief warning period, will automatically force you to dismount.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="830" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Operations</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="831" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Battle the greatest threats in the galaxy in groups of 8 or 16 players</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="832" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Operations start on your fleet, but you can't enter unless you are in an &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;ops group&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.operations1.dds' width='324' height='120'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To create an ops group, create a group, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right-click&lt;/font&gt; on your portrait and select Convert to an Ops Group.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Subscribers&lt;/font&gt; get free access to Operations. Free-to-Play Players can purchase weekly access using Cartel Coins.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="833" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Assistant Leads can help you manage the operation. To promote Assistant Leads in the ops group, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right-click&lt;/font&gt; on their name and select Promote to Assistant Lead.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.operations2.dds' width='324' height='228'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To rearrange players in the group, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;left-click&lt;/font&gt; on their names and drag their boxes to the desired location.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="834" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.operations3.dds' width='324' height='264'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When your ops group defeats a significant challenge in an operation, you will be temporarily &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;locked out&lt;/font&gt; of that content. Check the Lockouts tab of your mission log for a breakdown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="835" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Difficulty Modes</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="836" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Take on Veteran Mode missions for greater challenges and greater rewards.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="837" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.difficulty_modes1.dds' width='324' height='272'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Veteran Mode flashpoints, locate the missions &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;near the entrances&lt;/font&gt; to the flashpoints.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="838" id2="532678" version="1065353216">For Veteran Mode operations, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right-click&lt;/font&gt; on your portrait and select Phase.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.difficulty_modes2.dds' width='324' height='128'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="839" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.difficulty_modes3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Operations have &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;three difficulty modes:&lt;/font&gt; Story, Veteran and Master. Each mode can be played by either eight or sixteen players.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="840" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your Saga Begins</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="841" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You have taken your first steps into a massive galaxy. Epic adventure awaits!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="842" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.the_adventure_begins1.dds' width='324' height='424'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companions will soon begin &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;joining you&lt;/font&gt; on your journeys, fighting at your side as well as providing friendship and, in some cases, romance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="843" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You'll learn more &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;advanced combat styles&lt;/font&gt;. Choose your discipline and begin honing your skills. &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.the_adventure_begins2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="844" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.the_adventure_begins3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You'll also be able to battle other players in &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Warzones&lt;/font&gt;, a series of fiercely competitive scenarios where your team fights for glory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="845" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Explore the Galaxy</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="846" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You will soon undertake an epic journey and visit many worlds in your personal starship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="847" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.the_galaxy_awaits1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You'll have the chance to take the helm of &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;your own ship&lt;/font&gt; and embrace the freedom to travel wherever you choose.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="848" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Engaging in &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;daring space missions&lt;/font&gt;! Blast your enemies with laser fire and missiles, and earn powerful upgrades for your ship.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.the_galaxy_awaits2.dds' width='324' height='312'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="849" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.the_galaxy_awaits3.dds' width='324' height='288'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Join friends&lt;/font&gt; for flashpoints that put you into volatile and deadly situations. The choices are difficult, and the battles require smart tactics and teamwork.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="850" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Fulfill Your Destiny</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="851" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You've proven yourself a hero, but the greatest experiences and challenges are still ahead.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="852" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.fulfill_your_destiny1.dds' width='324' height='260'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Upon reaching level 10, you'll create your own &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Star Wars Legacy&lt;/font&gt; and bind your characters together as family and friends to unlock new skills and opportunities.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="853" id2="532678" version="1065353216">At level 50 and beyond, confront the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;most powerful threats&lt;/font&gt; in the galaxy in large-scale multi-group operations.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.fulfill_your_destiny2.dds' width='324' height='284'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="854" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.fulfill_your_destiny3.dds' width='324' height='284'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long-hidden mysteries, untold dangers and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;new challenges&lt;/font&gt; lie waiting for you in every corner of the galaxy!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="855" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Fleet Pass</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="856" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Quickly travel back to your fleet with the Fleet Pass item or ability.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="857" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.fleet_pass1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Subscribers&lt;/font&gt; gain the Emergency Fleet Pass ability. It lets you transport back to your fleet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Free-to-Play Players&lt;/font&gt; do not have access to the Emergency Fleet Pass ability, but can purchase single-use items from the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Market&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="858" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To activate the Fleet Pass, open the Abilities panel and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;left-click&lt;/font&gt; on Emergency Fleet Pass on the General tab.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.fleet_pass2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Free-to-Play Players&lt;/font&gt; will not have this ability listed.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="859" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.fleet_pass3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Purchase single-use Fleet Pass items from the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;security key vendor&lt;/font&gt; on your fleet or from the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Market&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="860" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Legacy</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="861" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Bind your characters together to unlock new perks and abilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="862" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.legacy1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To create your Legacy, enter a Legacy surname and click &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Create&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To show off your legacy name, become a subscriber today! Legacy surname display can also be unlocked with Cartel Coins.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="863" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To build out your family tree, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;drag a character&lt;/font&gt; from the character pool onto the larger tree menu.&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.legacy2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To bring up the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;relationship menu&lt;/font&gt;, drag the character onto another character in the family tree. This radial menu lets you select the relationship the two characters have with each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="864" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.legacy3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Global Unlocks tab&lt;/font&gt; contains different features that may be unlocked via a combination of Legacy level, credits, Cartel Coins or other accomplishments.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="865" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Activity Finder</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="866" id2="532678" version="1065353216">The Activity Finder can help you join up with other players for multiplayer experiences or find a solo mission thats just right.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="867" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.group_finder1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To open the Activity Finder panel, click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;group icon&lt;/font&gt; next to your minimap.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="868" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Select a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;combat role&lt;/font&gt; from the top of the panel. &lt;br&gt; &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.group_finder2.dds' width='324' height='36'&gt; &lt;br&gt;You may notice a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Role In Need&lt;/font&gt; for a particular activity. Playing as the listed role will provide you with  &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;additional rewards&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="869" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.grouping_players3.dds' width='324' height='288'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the left portion of the panel, choose the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;mission type&lt;/font&gt; you want to queue for.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To finalize your selection and enter the queue, click on &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Join Queue&lt;/font&gt;. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remember, queuing &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;randomly&lt;/font&gt; within a category will provide a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;daily reward bonus&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="870" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;u&gt;Click here to continue...&lt;/u&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="871" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Show/Hide Tutorial Notifications</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="872" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Cartel Market</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="873" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Sample from the Hutt Cartel's expansive collection of goods.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="874" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.cartelmarket1.dds' width='320' height='156'&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Market&lt;/font&gt; offers many unique and interesting items to the galaxy's adventurers. Items in the Cartel Market can be acquired for a modest amount of &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Coins&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="875" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Access the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Market&lt;/font&gt;  from the main screen. To visit the Market, simply click on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Coin&lt;/font&gt; icon on your screen. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.cartelmarket2.dds' width='320' height='64'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Items in the Cartel Market can't be found anywhere else and require &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Coins&lt;/font&gt; to purchase. &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Subscribers&lt;/font&gt; receive a monthly allotment of &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Coins&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="876" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.cartelmarket3.dds' width='260' height='224'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Cartel Coins can be purchased from the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Add Coins&lt;/font&gt; button.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="877" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Shopping with the Cartel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="878" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Purchasing from the Market</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="879" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Claiming your purchase</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="880" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Browse the Cartel's exclusive selection to find the best deals this side of Hutt Space!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="881" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Collect your purchases into your inventory to use or gift to friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="882" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.mtxpurchaseflow1.dds' width='324' height='272'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Select one of the helpful categories to see what the Cartel Market offers.The &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;FEATURED&lt;/font&gt; category will often update to show the galaxy's best deals!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Items in a category load to the right and display with their price, a helpful image as well as &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Sale&lt;/font&gt; and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;New Item&lt;/font&gt; indicators.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="883" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Select any item in the Market to see the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Item Details&lt;/font&gt;. The Item Details displays a description, bullet point details and any restrictions to the item.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.mtxpurchaseflow2.dds' width='324' height='260'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Click &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Show Items&lt;/font&gt; to display the in-game item. From here, you can preview armor, weapons and even mounts directly on your character!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="884" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.mtxpurchaseflow3.dds' width='324' height='220'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Click on &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;BUY NOW&lt;/font&gt; and your purchase is transferred to Unclaimed Items.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Coins&lt;/font&gt; will be adjusted immediately to reflect your new balance. You can continue shopping and add more items to Unclaimed Items.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="885" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Purchases at the Cartel Market are placed into your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Unclaimed Items&lt;/font&gt;. Unclaimed Items is a convenient space to collect all of your purchase while at the Market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.mtxclaimandreturnflow1.dds' width='324' height='148'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unclaimed Items is accessed from the Cartel Market and holds purchases &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;for as long as you need&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="886" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.mtxclaimandreturnflow2.dds' width='324' height='224'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Purchases in your Unclaimed Items can be &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;transferred&lt;/font&gt; into your inventory or &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;returned&lt;/font&gt; for a full refund.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are buttons to claim and return items individually. There is also an option to claim all items at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="887" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Some items will have &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;warning icons&lt;/font&gt; to indicate restrictions for an item. Take the time to read any restrictions on an item you have purchased in case you need to return it!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.mtxclaimandreturnflow3.dds' width='324' height='224'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most items in the Market (including unlocks!) can be sent to other players as &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;gifts&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="888" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Achievements</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="889" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Achievements are badges that recognize major accomplishments.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="890" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.achievements1.dds' width='324' height='344'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To view your achievements, open your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Legacy panel&lt;/font&gt;.  Achievement categories are listed on the left side of the panel.  Click a category to view specific achievements.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="891" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.achievements3.dds' width='324' height='220'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Achievements&lt;/font&gt; can be awarded for defeating enemies, completing missions, and many other activities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.achievements2.dds' width='324' height='120'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Click on an &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;achievement icon&lt;/font&gt; to see what is required to unlock it, as well as what rewards it grants.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="892" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.achievements4.dds' width='320' height='56'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every achievement awards &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Prestige Points&lt;/font&gt;.  Your total &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Prestige Score&lt;/font&gt; is the sum of all unlocked achievements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.achievements5.dds' width='324' height='128'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some achievements may award items, titles or Cartel coins in addition to Prestige points.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="893" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Rise of the Hutt Cartel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="894" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.macrobinoculars1.dds' width='324' height='160'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Macrobinoculars&lt;/font&gt; are used to identify and scan distant targets of interest.  &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Right click&lt;/font&gt; the macrobinoculars item in your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;mission items&lt;/font&gt; inventory to activate it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="895" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.macrobinoculars2.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Objects that can be scanned by the macrobinoculars will &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;highlight orange&lt;/font&gt; when you mouse over them. &lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.macrobinoculars3.dds' width='324' height='196'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Left click&lt;/font&gt; on highlighted objects to zoom in and positively identify them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="896" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.macrobinoculars4.dds' width='320' height='252'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only certain targets can be &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;identified&lt;/font&gt; with the macrobinoculars.  Identifying targets may advance missions, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;unlock achievements&lt;/font&gt;, or trigger other events for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="897" id2="532678" version="1065353216">The Seeker Droid can be used in specially designated areas to find hidden items. &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Right click&lt;/font&gt; the Seeker Droid in your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;mission items inventory&lt;/font&gt; to activate it.  After activating the Seeker Droid, use the targeting reticule to select an area to search in.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.seekerdroid2.dds' width='320' height='304'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="898" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.seekerdroid1.dds' width='320' height='376'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the Seeker Droid finds something in the search area, the searched area will &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;highlight green&lt;/font&gt;, and the droid will bring the item to you and put it directly in your inventory.  If the droid does not find anything, the area will &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;highlight red&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="899" id2="532678" version="1065353216">If the droid finds nothing, or does not find the item you are looking for, try searching in &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;different locations&lt;/font&gt;.  You will not find what you seek by searching the same spot many times.  &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Be warned&lt;/font&gt;; you may find things other than items as you search new areas! &lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.seekerdroid3.dds' width='320' height='312'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="900" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Macrobinoculars</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="901" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Perform discreet reconnaissance with EV2 Macrobinoculars</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="902" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Seeker Droid</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="903" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Find hidden artifacts with the Subterranean Seeker Droid</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="904" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Level 50! Now continue your saga with Rise of the Hutt Cartel!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="905" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Purchase the Digital Expansion: &lt;hl lid=&quot;BFBO&quot; &gt; and click on your ship's holoterminal to start your new adventures!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="906" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.rothc.rothc_splash_makeb.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Discover the new world of Makeb!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;A paradise planet that was once home to the galaxy's most wealthy, Makeb has been conquered by the ruthless Hutt Cartel, whose brutal actions have left the planet teetering on the brink of destruction! Now, you and your friends can travel to Makeb, fight back against the Hutt Cartel and decide the fate of the planet and its people!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Purchase &lt;hl lid=&quot;BFBO&quot; &gt; and click on your ship's holoterminal to start your new adventures!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="907" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.rothc.rothc_splash_macrobinoculars.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Explore the galaxy with Macrobinoculars &amp; Seeker Droids!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the Macrobinocular and Seeker Droid missions, return to your favorite worlds armed with these new devices, tracking down elusive adversaries and finding exciting treasures, rare items and other discoveries!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Purchase &lt;hl lid=&quot;BFBO&quot; &gt; and click on your ship's holoterminal to start your new adventures!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="908" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.rothc.rothc_splash_level55.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Acquire new skills, abilities and gear as you advance to Level 55!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience dangerous new areas, challenging missions and formidable opponents as your heroes continue their adventures to level 55!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Purchase &lt;hl lid=&quot;BFBO&quot; &gt; and click on your ship's holoterminal to start your new adventures!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="909" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Pre-purchase Rise of the Hutt Cartel to continue your saga past level 50!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="910" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.rothc.rothc_levelcap_kaon.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Epic adventures await you at level 55! &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Flashpoints and Operations&lt;/font&gt; are challenging, group-oriented missions that will test your skill and coordination. For more information, visit our &lt;hl lid=&quot;BFBQ&quot; &gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="911" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.rothc.rothc_levelcap_darvannis.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Looking for a group&lt;/font&gt; to tackle these challenges? Click the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Activity Finder&lt;/font&gt; icon above your minimap to queue for &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Flashpoints, Operations, Uprisings, Warzones and Starfighter!&lt;/font&gt; You will be matched with a balanced group and transported to your destination.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="912" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.rothc.rothc_levelcap_ancienthypergate.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looking for some &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;quick action&lt;/font&gt;? Join the fight to win the Galactic War in &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;PvP Warzones&lt;/font&gt;! Click the icon at the bottom of your minimap to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;queue&lt;/font&gt; for a Warzone. You will be &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;bolstered in power&lt;/font&gt; to ensure that you are competitive with enemy forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="913" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Welcome to Level 55!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="914" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You've unlocked a new tier of adventure!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="915" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Congratulations on reaching level 17! Pre-purchase Rise of the Hutt Cartel to continue your saga beyond level 50!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="916" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Congratulations on reaching level 50! Extend your saga to level 55 with Rise of the Hutt Cartel today!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="917" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.rothc.rothc_splash_makeb.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Discover the new world of Makeb!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;A paradise planet that was once home to the galaxy's most wealthy, Makeb has been conquered by the ruthless Hutt Cartel, whose brutal actions have left the planet teetering on the brink of destruction! Now, you and your friends can travel to Makeb, fight back against the Hutt Cartel and decide the fate of the planet and its people!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once you're level 50, click on your ship's holoterminal to begin the Digital Expansion: Rise of the Hutt Cartel adventures!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="918" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.rothc.rothc_splash_macrobinoculars.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Explore the galaxy with Macrobinoculars &amp; Seeker Droids!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the Macrobinocular and Seeker Droid missions, return to your favorite worlds armed with these new devices, tracking down elusive adversaries and finding exciting treasures, rare items, and other discoveries!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="919" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.rothc.rothc_splash_level55.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Acquire new skills, abilities and gear as you advance to Level 55!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience dangerous new areas, challenging missions, and formidable opponents as your heroes continue their adventures to level 55!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="920" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Extend your legacy in Star Wars: The Old Republic. Click on your ship's holoterminal to start your new adventures!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="921" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Introducing Collections</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="922" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Introducing Collections: Basic Navigation</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="923" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Collections provide a convenient means for tracking many items you have obtained including those from the Cartel Market, Market Packs, Collector's Edition, and more. &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Items are logged in your Collections upon binding&lt;/font&gt;, allowing you to track which items you have collected, which ones you have not yet acquired, and to retrieve duplicate copies later.&lt;br&gt;Your Collections can be accessed from the Inventory window via the button in the lower left, or from the Cartel Market window via the button in the upper right.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.collections1a.dds' width='324' height='444'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="924" id2="532678" version="1065353216">The left pane of the Collections window is an index of Categories which can be expanded into subcategories.  Items are organized under these categories by the source of the item.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.collections1b.dds' width='324' height='268'&gt;&lt;br&gt;Items can be browsed by clicking through the category tree or by clicking on the elements in the right pane.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="925" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.collections1c.dds' width='324' height='272'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Within a given category, there may be multiple pages of items.  If so, buttons will be displayed along the bottom of the pane, allowing you to quickly move between pages.&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Items are unlocked in your Collections by binding them to your character.&lt;/font&gt; Once the item is unlocked in your Collections, its icon will appear at full brightness.  Note that all items in an Armor Set must be bound to become unlocked.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="926" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Credit Escrow</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="927" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Transferring Credits from your Escrow.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="928" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.escrow_1.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Free-to-Play and Preferred players have a lower cap on their Credits than Subscribers. &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt; Credits earned beyond this cap are stored in Escrow.&lt;/font&gt;  Your stored Credit Escrow can be viewed from the Currency tab of your Inventory.&lt;br&gt;You may transfer credits from your Escrow to your available balance via the Access Escrow button.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="929" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Accessing your Escrow allows you to transfer Credits to your available balance at the cost of Cartel Coins.&lt;/font&gt;  There are multiple options for Credit amounts to transfer.  Transferred Credits can exceed the Credits cap.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.escrow_2.dds' width='324' height='160'&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 50,000 Credit transfer may always be done regardless of your stored Escrow, and will transfer all available credits in escrow if you have fewer than the full 50,000.  The larger Credit transfers may only be performed if you have at least that many Credits in Escrow.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="930" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.escrow_3.dds' width='324' height='172'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition to transfering Credits via the Escrow panel, you may purchase single-use Escrow Transfer items from the Cartel Market.  These items are available in various Credit amounts.&lt;br&gt;Use of these items transfers the specified Credits amount from your Escrow to your current balance.  &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;You must have at least the specified Credits available in your Escrow to use these items.&lt;/font&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="931" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Dye Modules</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="932" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Change the color of gear to suit your tastes.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="933" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.dye_modules_1.dds' width='324' height='244'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most pieces of gear have an enhancement slot for Dye Modules.  Dye Modules allow you to alter the color scheme of such gear, and are available from Artifice and Packs in the Cartel Market, as well as some exclusive vendors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Each piece of gear has areas that will take a primary hue, and most (but not all) have areas that will take a secondary hue.&lt;/font&gt;  Dye Modules are available as dual-color modules, providing both a primary and secondary hue, as well as single-color modules, providing either a primary hue or a secondary hue, but not both.  In all cases, only one Dye Module can be applied to a given piece of gear.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="934" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You may choose to dye each piece of your gear individually, or you can use the Unify Colors option to allow your other gear to match a dye applied to the equipment in your chest slot.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.dye_modules_2.dds' width='324' height='400'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Dye modules can be previewed without adding them to gear by pressing CTRL+Left Click on the dye module itself.&lt;/font&gt;  This will open a preview window displaying the effects of applying this dye module to all currently-worn gear.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="935" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.dye_modules_3.dds' width='324' height='296'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can add a Dye Module to gear using the same methods as adding any other enhancement. Press CTRL+Right Click to access the field modification menu, or select the item when using an Item Modification table.&lt;br&gt;Adding a Dye Module to gear that already has a Dye Module applied will replace the existing Dye Module with the new one, and destroy the original.&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Dye Modules can be removed.  Doing so will restore the equipment to its original colorscheme, but will destroy the Dye Module in the process.&lt;/font&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="936" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Appearance Designer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="937" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Creating a whole new you!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="938" id2="532678" version="1065353216">The Appearance Designer offers the ability to change a character's facial features, body type and species.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.appearance_designer_1.dds' width='324' height='272'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Appearance Designer Kiosks&lt;/font&gt; are located on the Republic and Imperial Fleets as well as on Coruscant and Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="939" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Basic &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt; customization options&lt;/font&gt; are shared with Character Creation and always available. Some options are unlocked with Cartel Coins and will be displayed in purple. Options that are available because of Legacy are gold.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.appearance_designer_2.dds' width='324' height='240'&gt;&lt;br&gt;If a selection is made that not currently unlocked an icon will appear showing how many Cartel Coins are required to unlock it.
A locked option can be purchased from the Cartel Market or directly in Appearance Designer. Purchased &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt; customization options&lt;/font&gt; are unlocked for your account.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="940" id2="532678" version="1065353216">When a Legacy Species is unlocked, that species and its Appearance options will become available in Appearance Designer. Species may be unlocked directly in Appearance Designer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.appearance_designer_3.dds' width='324' height='240'&gt;&lt;br&gt;After making your desired selections, use the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt; &quot;Change Appearance&quot;&lt;/font&gt; button to change your character and complete the transaction. Note that slider changes are free of charge when changing your Species.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="941" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Tracking Collections</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="942" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Tracking Collections, Inspecting Items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="943" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.collections2a.dds' width='324' height='268'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each Collection category or subcategory tracks the items you have unlocked.  Your completion progress for sets of items is shown in both the category pane and in the right items pane.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="944" id2="532678" version="1065353216">If an item in your Collections is currently available on the Cartel Market, the &quot;Open Cartel Market&quot; button in the lower left of its icon to take you directly to that item on the Cartel Market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.collections2b.dds' width='324' height='464'&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may see additional information on the items in your Collection by clicking on them.  From here, items can be previewed and information about any restrictions and stats are visible.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="945" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.collections2c.dds' width='324' height='464'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Inspecting an item, Collections items that represent a set of items will have a &quot;Show Items&quot; button.  Pressing this button will display the individual items in the set, allowing you to preview their appearance and statistics. You may also simply CTRL+Left Click the item to preview it.&lt;br&gt;While in this mode, the &quot;Show Items&quot; button will become a &quot;Show Details&quot; button, allowing you to return to the previous view.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="946" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Retrieving From Collections</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="947" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Unlocking and Retrieving Items from Your Collection</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="948" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.collections3a.dds' width='324' height='428'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To unlock an item in your Collections, it must be Bound to you.  Merely possessing the item will not unlock it. Note that all items in an Armor Set must be bound to unlock it.&lt;br&gt;Once unlocked, a duplicate copy of that Collection item can be retrieved at any time from your Collections.  Retrieved items will be Bound to the character, and cannot be traded.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="949" id2="532678" version="1065353216">To retrieve a copy of an unlocked item from your Collections, press the Transfer button.  This will transfer a Bound copy of the item (or all items in the set, if appropriate) to your character's inventory.  You must have enough space in your inventory to accommodate the transfer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.collections3b.dds' width='324' height='168'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="950" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.collections3c.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlocking an item in your Collections makes that item available for retrieval for the character that originally bound the item.  This character is able to retrieve the item for free at any time.&lt;br&gt;Other characters on your account may also purchase the ability to retrieve the item for a small one-time purchase with Cartel Coins.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1023" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Galactic Starfighter</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1024" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Hangar - Overview</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1025" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn the major features of the Galactic Starfighter hangar.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1026" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Overview&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Galactic Starfighter hangar is broken up into several easy to navigate elements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Account Info and Requisition:&lt;/font&gt; (The currency of Galactic Starfighter) info can be found along the top of the hangar.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Tabs:&lt;/font&gt; Just below this you will find tabs that provide access to every section of the hangar.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Panes:&lt;/font&gt; Each tab is separated into panes that will allow you to make selections, observe changes, and access details about your ships and their various components.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1027" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Tabs&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting with &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Ships&lt;/font&gt; and moving all the way through &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Launch&lt;/font&gt;, the tabs along the top of the hangar will step you through the process of readying a ship.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.hangar_overview_pane2.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each tab represents another aspect of your ship's &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;loadout&lt;/font&gt;. Click on the tabs individually to access their content.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1028" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Panes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;The contents of each tab in the hangar are broken into three separate panes of information.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;left pane&lt;/font&gt; will allow you to select various options.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;center pane&lt;/font&gt; will display the choices you've made and how they affect your ship.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right pane&lt;/font&gt; contains details about your ship, selected component, cosmetics, or crew member. This is also where you can manage component upgrades and paint jobs.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1029" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Hangar - Launch Tab</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1030" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn how to ready your ships and launch into battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1031" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Overview&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the Launch Tab you can review and ready ships to queue for battle or toggle back to other tabs to adjust your equipment &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;loadouts&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.hangar_launch_loadouts.dds' width='324' height='64'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the bottom of the tab you'll find your readied ships bar, indicating which ships you've chosen to take into battle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Getting into the action is as simple as choosing which ships you want to ready and pressing one of the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Queue&lt;/font&gt; buttons.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1032" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Readied Ships&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;To ready a ship, simply click on an empty slot and select a ship from the selection menu that appears. To swap an already filled slot with a different ship, click on the slot and press the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Select Your Ship&lt;/font&gt; button to bring up the selection menu. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can rearrange readied ships by dragging icons from one position on the bar to another. Drag an icon off of the bar completely to remove it from the bar.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Details about a selected loadout will show up in the right pane.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1033" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Queuing&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;The queue buttons appear at the bottom of the right pane on the Launch Tab and allow you to either queue for &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Battle&lt;/font&gt; or  &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Group Battle&lt;/font&gt;. Both queue options will put you in line for the next battle once enough other players are queued as well.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are currently part of a group, use the Group Battle button to queue your entire group for battle so that when you enter combat, you'll all be on the same team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flying into battle as part of a group is a great way to facilitate  more focused communication during combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1034" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Hangar - Ships Tab</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1035" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn about creating loadouts and choosing ships.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1036" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Ship Roles&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ships in Galactic Starfighter are organized by &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;roles&lt;/font&gt;. Roles are overarching categories that define a ship's basic functionality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Within each role there may be many different ships, each with its own unique spin on the role.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By default, all pilots begin with one &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Scout&lt;/font&gt; role ship and one &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Strike Fighter&lt;/font&gt; role ship unlocked. By spending fleet requisition gained by completing battles, you can purchase new ships for these and future roles from the left pane of the Ships Tab.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1037" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Choosing a Ship&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clicking on a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;ship role&lt;/font&gt; will reveal a selection of ships you currently own for that role.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mouse over a ship in the list to see its &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;stats&lt;/font&gt;. Choosing components and crew in the other tabs will modify these stats.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clicking on a ship from the list will allow you to see it in the center pane and display its technical details in the right pane.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1038" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Details&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detailed technical information about your selected ship can be seen in the right pane. From here you can make decisions about which ship you want to fly based on stats such as:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Blaster&lt;/font&gt;, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Shield&lt;/font&gt;, and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Engine&lt;/font&gt; power pools &amp; regen rates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Hull&lt;/font&gt; health &amp; damage reduction&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Engine&lt;/font&gt; speed, turn rate, evasion, and boosting.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Sensor&lt;/font&gt; and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Communications&lt;/font&gt; range &amp; dampening.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1039" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Hangar - Components Tab</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1040" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn how to equip and upgrade your ship's components.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1041" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Overview&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Components are your ship's weapons, engines, systems, and defenses. Every ship comes equipped with a default set of components allowing you to get into action quickly. As you become a more skilled pilot you can purchase your own complement of components to suit your piloting style.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Major components&lt;/font&gt; are self-contained ship systems such as blasters and engines&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Minor components&lt;/font&gt; are sytems that can passively alter the effectiveness of multiple other systems.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1042" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Components&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Components are broken into categories in the left pane. Clicking on a category will show you all the components you currently own and can equip as well as those you can purchase.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clicking on a component will show you any physical changes it will make to your ship in the center pane while also bringing up details and upgrade info in the right pane.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clicking on an &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;owned&lt;/font&gt; component in the list immediately equips it to your ship and adds it to the current loadout. Unowned, but &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;purchasable&lt;/font&gt; components will be grayed out and have a purchase button alongside them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1043" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Upgrades&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every component has a set of upgrades that can be purchased using &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Requisition&lt;/font&gt;, a type of currency gained by participating in Galactic Starfighter battles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.hangar_components_upgrades.dds' width='324' height='240'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Upgrades enhance various aspects of a component's functionality such as making blasters stronger and engines faster.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1044" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Hangar - Cosmetics Tab</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1045" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn about cosmetic modifications for your ships.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1046" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cosmetics&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cosmetics are visual modifications to your ship such as &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;paint jobs&lt;/font&gt;, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;blaster colors&lt;/font&gt;, and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;engine trails&lt;/font&gt;. Such customizations have no effect on your ship's performance in battle, but allow you to further personalize your starfighter.&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Every ship has access to a number of cosmetic options that can be purchased to customize its appearance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cosmetic modifications are listed within the left pane.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1047" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Purchase and Preview&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clicking on an owned modification in the left pane will automatically apply it to the current ship (paint jobs) or component (blasters and engine trails).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Purchasable cosmetic modifications will be grayed out and can be boughtd by pressing the currency icon next to their name.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.hangar_cosmetics_preview.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both locked and unlocked cosmetics will &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;preview&lt;/font&gt; on your ship in the center pane when selected.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1048" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Customization&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.hangar_cosmetics_colors.dds' width='324' height='148'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some cosmetics (like paint jobs) will have additional customization options. These options will appear in the right pane of the hangar when a cosmetic has been selected and allow you to further customize the look and feel by purchasing additional options or by selecting one of the defaults.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1049" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Hangar - Crew Tab</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1050" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn about choosing and assigning crew members.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1051" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Crew Members&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crew members are characters that can be assigned to various positions on your ship and that confer bonuses and additional combat abilities. There are two types of crew member:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Support Crew:&lt;/font&gt; Provides your ship with passive bonuses related to their position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Copilot:&lt;/font&gt; Provides an additional active ability that can be used in combat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a crew member is selected, detailed information about that crew member and their bonuses will be shown in the right pane.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crew members can be purchased from within the hangar by pressing the currency icon next to their name, but you can also &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;unlock&lt;/font&gt; your class' companions as crew members as you encounter them on the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1052" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Support Crew&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.hangar_crew_hk.dds' width='324' height='180'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are four support crew &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;positions&lt;/font&gt;. Each crew member has a specific position they are allowed to fill.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the left pane on the Crew tab is a list of each position. Clicking on a position will open a list of crew members that can be assigned to that position. Clicking on an &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;unlocked&lt;/font&gt; crew member will assign them to that position. &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Locked&lt;/font&gt; crew members will be grayed out and have a purchase button alongside them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As with components, each ship may have a different complement of crew.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1053" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Copilots&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your copilot is chosen from among your currently assigned support crew.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clicking on the copilot position will open a list with only those &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;currently assigned&lt;/font&gt; support crew members in it. Clicking on a crew member from this list will assign them as your copilot.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition to the passive abilities they apply as a member of your support crew, your copilots all have &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;active abilities&lt;/font&gt; that you can use during battle. These abilities will appear along with your systems, shields, and engine abilities on screen during combat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your copilot is also the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;voice&lt;/font&gt; of your ship and will bark comments during battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1054" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Welcome to Galactic Starfighter! Click on the Galactic Starfighter icon on the left-side of the minimap or press &quot;H&quot; to access your Hangar and launch into battle!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1055" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Combat HUD</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1056" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn about the Heads Up Display for Galactic Starfighter combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1057" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Combat:&lt;/font&gt; Most information you need will be displayed in the center of the screen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_cbt_hud_pane2.dds' width='324' height='112'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Targeting Reticle:&lt;/font&gt; Your cursor position, where your ship is pointed and where your weapons will fire.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Firing Arc:&lt;/font&gt; A circle representing the area within which a weapon may fire.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Enemy and Objective Indicators:&lt;/font&gt; Icons indicating the direction of enemies and objectives not currently on the screen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_cbt_hud_pane1_2.dds' width='324' height='72'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These appear around your firing arcs.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1058" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Other:&lt;/font&gt; Two on-screen elements that will be very useful during combat are the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Scorecard&lt;/font&gt; and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Map&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_cbt_hud_score.dds' width='324' height='88'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scorecard shows the current progress of the battle with team scores, objective status indicators, and time remaining.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_cbt_hud_pane3_1.dds' width='324' height='100'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The map is a top down view of the battle area as a whole. On the map you will be able to see the positions and movement of your allies, enemies, and objectives within sensor range.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1059" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Power&lt;/font&gt;: Your ship has three power pools that you can manage during combat: &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Blaster Power&lt;/font&gt;, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Shield Power&lt;/font&gt;, and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Engine Power&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_cbt_hud_pane1.dds' width='324' height='144'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blasters, Shields, and Engines each have their own on-screen indicators showing how much power is left in their pools. Regen of these pools can be managed using the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;F1-F4 keys&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1060" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Flight Controls</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1061" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn about the Flight Controls for Galactic Starfighter</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1062" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Direction and Movement:&lt;/font&gt; Direction is controlled by moving your mouse. Moving your mouse forwards and backwards will &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;pitch&lt;/font&gt; your ship up and down. Moving your mouse left and right will &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;yaw&lt;/font&gt; your ship from side to side.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_flight_ctrl_pane1.dds' width='324' height='144'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spatial movement is handled using the W, A, S, and D keys on the keyboard. &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;W and S&lt;/font&gt; control your forward movement, by increasing and decreasing the throttle respectively. &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;A and D&lt;/font&gt; will roll your ship left and right.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1063" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Throttle:&lt;/font&gt; All ships have a default speed that they will move at regardless of whether the pilot adjusts the throttle or not.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pressing &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;W&lt;/font&gt; will increase the ship's throttle to full. Pressing &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;S&lt;/font&gt; will slow the ship below the default speed, but not stop it completely. Pressing &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;X&lt;/font&gt; will stop the ship completely until the throttle is again engaged.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visual representation of your ship's current speed is shown on the throttle gauge on the right side of your screen. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By holding &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;SPACE&lt;/font&gt; to engage boosters, a ship can move faster than its top speed for as long as it has engine power to spend.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1064" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Engine Power:&lt;/font&gt; Using boosters and certain special abilities will expend engine power. Engine power is measured by a bar along the right hand side of your screen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_flight_ctrl_pane3.dds' width='324' height='184'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Engine power will regenerate slowly while not being actively drained.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1065" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Combat Controls</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1066" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn about the Combat Controls for Galactic Starfighter.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1067" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Targeting:&lt;/font&gt; In order to effectively destroy an enemy, you first need to target them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;TAB:&lt;/font&gt; Targets the enemy closest to you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;R:&lt;/font&gt; Targets the enemy who most recently damaged you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;E:&lt;/font&gt; Targets the enemy currently under your reticule.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you have an enemy targeted you'll see two reticules for them. The first will always be centered on their ship, turning red when they're in range. The second is the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;lead indicator&lt;/font&gt;, which shows you where you will need to fire in order to hit your target.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1068" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Attacking:&lt;/font&gt; Each ship has primary and secondary weapons, fired by the left and right mouse buttons respectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Primary Weapons:&lt;/font&gt; Most primary weapons are blasters that only require you to aim at the enemy's &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;lead indicator&lt;/font&gt; and fire to attack.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Secondary Weapons:&lt;/font&gt; Most secondary weapons require you to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;lock-on&lt;/font&gt; before firing. To lock-on, hold down your right mouse button while a target is in range and within your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;firing arc&lt;/font&gt;. Let go of the button once the target is locked to fire.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Railguns:&lt;/font&gt; Railguns are a type of secondary weapon only available to gunships. Pressing the right mouse button enters &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;sniping mode&lt;/font&gt; and the left button &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;charges&lt;/font&gt; up your railgun to fire. The more charge, the more damage done.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1069" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Using Abilities:&lt;/font&gt; Your choice of Systems, Shields, Engines, and Copilot will all give you additional abilities that can be used in combat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In combat, abilities will show up in component-specific slots on your screen and can be fired using the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;number keys&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_cbt_ctrl_pane3.dds' width='324' height='72'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some abilities may require you to have a target in order to be used.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Icons for &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;negative&lt;/font&gt; and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;positive&lt;/font&gt; effects from abilities that are currently applied to you will appear over your shield indicator.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1070" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Battle Type - Domination</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1071" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn about the Domination battle type for Galactic Starfighter.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1072" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;DEFEAT ALL ENEMIES&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_domination_pane1.dds' width='324' height='184'&gt;If the lights on a satellite are &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;red&lt;/font&gt; then it is controlled by the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;enemy team&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking control of satellites is the best way to score during  the domination game mode and defeating nearby enemies is the first step in this process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enemies include not just players on the opposing team, but also the defense turrets that appear near captured objectives.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1073" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;STAY CLOSE / KEEP ENEMIES AWAY&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_domination_pane2.dds' width='324' height='152'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the lights on a satellite are &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;white&lt;/font&gt; it is &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;neutral&lt;/font&gt; and whichever team approaches it first can try to capture it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As long as there are no enemies within the capture radius of a satellite it can be taken over for your team. If an enemy comes near however, the capture process will halt.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As you capture the satellite you will see its lights change color. When all the lights are green, the satellite has been captured for your team.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1074" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;DEFEND YOUR SATELLITE&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_domination_pane3.dds' width='324' height='136'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;your team&lt;/font&gt; controls a satellite, the lights are &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;green&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Captured satellites generate points for your team. Over time defense turrets will also appear, up to three in total. If there are enemies within the satellite's capture radius however, no new turrets will appear.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition to generating points for your team, owning a satellite will also create a new respawn location nearby to help you defend it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1075" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Welcome to Galactic Starfighter</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1076" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Take your battle to space!  Get ready for PvP Dogfighting adventures as you fight for your faction.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1077" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_welcome_pane1.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;BATTLE!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The struggle between the Empire and the Republic has escalated and extended the conflict to space.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The call for pilots resounds across the galaxy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Choose your side and take your battle to space!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1078" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_welcome_pane2.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;DOMINATE!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Jump in and choose your side as you join intense 12v12 battles with your allies in new battle zones set in space.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Choose one of three unique gameplay roles as you take on PvP challenges.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Test your skills in battle with the Scout, Strike Fighter, or Gunship!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1079" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_welcome_pane3.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;CUSTOMIZE!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Discover over 14 ships and customize your ship with paint jobs, components, blaster/engine colors and more!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Bring your Companions from the ground game with you into space and leverage their unique abilities to your advantage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Earn new Companions as you progress to build your crew!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1086" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Welcome to the Galactic Starfighter Hangar. Tutorials for each Hangar section will be made available as you navigate through them. You can find all your tutorials by opening the SW:TOR Game Menu or enabling tutorial alerts in your Preferences.

For a brief solo lesson in flying your starfighter, press the tutorial button in the top-right corner of the Hangar.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1087" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Battle Type - Team Deathmatch</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1088" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn about the Team Deathmatch battle type for Galactic Starfighter.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1089" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;RACK UP THE MOST KILLS&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_tdm_outshoot.dds' width='324' height='184'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Team Deathmatch&lt;/font&gt; pits two teams of players against each other in deadly PvP combat to determine which side can rack up the most kills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each battle area will have a number of &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;power-ups&lt;/font&gt; scattered throughout the map. Flying through these powerups will give your ship a powerful bonus to engines, blasters, shields, or overall damage!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1090" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;GRAB THE POWER-UPS&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_tdm_outmanuever.dds' width='324' height='184'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Engine Overcharge (purple):&lt;/font&gt; Refills engine power. Increases your engine power regen, movement speed, and evasion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Weapon Overcharge (yellow):&lt;/font&gt; Refills blaster power and ammo. Increases your blaster power regen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Shield Overcharge (blue):&lt;/font&gt; Refills shield power. Increases your shield power regen and allows regen in combat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Damage Overcharge (red):&lt;/font&gt; Significantly increases your damage with primary and secondary weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1091" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;DEFEAT THE ENEMY&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.starfighter_tdm_outlast.dds' width='324' height='184'&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your goal in a Team Deathmatch battle is to ensure that your team reaches the score limit before the other team or before time runs out. Points in Team Deathmatch battles are gained in one way only:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Defeating enemy Starfighters!&lt;/font&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1092" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Galactic Strongholds</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1093" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Galactic Strongholds: Getting Started</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1094" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Start building your home in Star Wars: The Old Republic by purchasing a stronghold today!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1095" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.strongholds_management_page1.dds' width='324' height='180'&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;purchase a stronghold&lt;/font&gt; at the appropriate &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Stronghold Directory&lt;/font&gt;. Directories may be found on the Fleet, as well as on the various worlds where strongholds are located, including Nar Shaddaa and Tatooine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strongholds are &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;shared across your Legacy&lt;/font&gt;, and you can have a maximum of four. Some strongholds, such as the Kaas City and Coruscant Apartments, have a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;faction alignment&lt;/font&gt;. You may travel to these strongholds with any character in your Legacy, but characters aligned with the enemy faction will need to pay a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;smuggler's fee&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1096" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.strongholds_management_page2.dds' width='324' height='180'&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once you've purchased a Stronghold, you can travel to it by opening the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Stronghold Management Window&lt;/font&gt; from your Menu Bar and clicking the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Travel&lt;/font&gt; button.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;exit your Stronghold&lt;/font&gt; by clicking the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Exit Area&lt;/font&gt; button above your minimap. You will have the option to return to the coordinates you traveled from, as well as an option to exit to the planet your stronghold is located on. If you are a subscriber, you will also have the option to return to the Fleet or to your personal starship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1097" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.strongholds_management_page3.dds' width='324' height='180'&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;initial purchase of a stronghold&lt;/font&gt; will grant you access to the entry area and a handful of rooms. You may &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;expand your stronghold&lt;/font&gt; further by clicking on locked doors and making additional purchases with credits or Cartel Coins.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;expansion&lt;/font&gt; you purchase will grant you access to the associated room, increase the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;maximum number of decorations&lt;/font&gt; you can place, and increase your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;maximum player occupancy&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1098" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Galactic Strongholds: Customizing and Decorating</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1099" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Editing layouts and placing decorations. Start expanding and customizing your stronghold right away!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1100" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.strongholds_customization_page1.dds' width='324' height='140'&gt;&lt;br&gt;To start placing decorations, click the button on your toolbar to enter &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;EDIT MODE&lt;/font&gt;. While you are in Edit Mode, you can &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right-click&lt;/font&gt; a hook layout to pop up the hook editor.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hook editor window will display a complete &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;list of decorations&lt;/font&gt; that will fit into the hook you've selected. You can filter this list by &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;category&lt;/font&gt; and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;subcategory&lt;/font&gt;. Decorations will often fit into multiple hook types. Eligible hooks are displayed in the decoration's tooltip.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1101" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.strongholds_customization_page2.dds' width='324' height='180'&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once you've selected the decoration you want, click the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;PLACE&lt;/font&gt; button to insert it into the hook. You can then &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;nudge and rotate&lt;/font&gt; the decoration within the hook using the sliders that appear.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you aren't happy with your decorating options for a certain hook, you can usually modify it by clicking the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;LAYOUTS&lt;/font&gt; button and selecting a different set of hooks. You can preview different layouts by selecting them. Clicking &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;APPLY LAYOUT&lt;/font&gt; will confirm the change and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;automatically pick up&lt;/font&gt; any decorations placed in the associated hooks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1102" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.strongholds_customization_page3.dds' width='324' height='180'&gt;&lt;br&gt;You will earn &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;prestige&lt;/font&gt; for your Legacy with each new decoration you unlock in your personal collection. As you place decorations, your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;stronghold completion percentage&lt;/font&gt; will increase. Your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;stronghold's prestige&lt;/font&gt; value is determined by its completion percentage multiplied by your Legacy's prestige. Prestige is used to rank strongholds on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Public Listings&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can also unlock &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;stronghold labels&lt;/font&gt;, which allow you to set a different name for your stronghold in the Stronghold Management Window. You can also select a different character in your Legacy to be the official owner.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1103" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Collecting Decorations &amp; Crafting Prefabs</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1104" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn where to collect decorations and how to craft them with Fabricator Droids!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1105" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.strongholds_decorations_page1.dds' width='324' height='180'&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are many ways to collect new decorations for your stronghold. Some can be purchased from vendors for &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;credits or data crystals&lt;/font&gt;. Many decorations &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;drop as loot in Flashpoints and Operations&lt;/font&gt;, and special wall decorations called &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;trophies&lt;/font&gt; can be unlocked by completing certain achievements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Decorations can also be obtained on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Market&lt;/font&gt;. You can browse all available decorations by clicking on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;PERSONAL&lt;/font&gt; button in your Stronghold Management window.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1106" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.strongholds_decorations_page2.dds' width='324' height='180'&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can build decorations for your stronghold by crafting &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;prefabs&lt;/font&gt;, which can be exchanged for decorations at a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Fabricator Droid&lt;/font&gt; on the Fleet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armstechs, Armormechs, and Cybertechs can craft &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Industrial Prefabs&lt;/font&gt;, whereas Artificers, Biochems, and Synthweavers can craft &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Synthetic Prefabs&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All crafting professions can train the first tier of schematics for these prefabs starting at a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;skill level of 150&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1107" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.strongholds_decorations_page3.dds' width='324' height='180'&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each prefab type is divided into three tiers: &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;MK-1, MK-2, and MK-3&lt;/font&gt;. You can learn the schematics from your crew skill trainer, but &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;higher tier prefab schematics&lt;/font&gt; require a higher skill level.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the most impressive and useful decorations can be obtained with &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Universal Prefabs&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crafting a Universal Prefab requires combining a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Synthetic Prefab&lt;/font&gt; with an &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Industrial Prefab&lt;/font&gt;, along with a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Fabricator Design&lt;/font&gt; and a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Fabricator Crystal&lt;/font&gt;. This may require the cooperation of multiple crafters.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1108" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Planetary Conquests</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1109" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn how you can support the war effort and earn rewards - or join a guild and conquer planets!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1110" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.rothc.rothc_splash_level55.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the war effort evolves, &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Conquest Events&lt;/font&gt; provide you with a new set of shifting objectives every week. The current conquest event can be viewed by opening your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Mission Log&lt;/font&gt; and clicking on the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;CONQUEST&lt;/font&gt; tab.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Complete &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;objectives&lt;/font&gt; to earn &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;conquest points&lt;/font&gt; and meet your personal point target before the end of the event to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;rewards&lt;/font&gt;. Your conquests points are &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;reset each week&lt;/font&gt; so pay close attention to the countdown timer!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1111" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.strongholds_conquest_page2.dds' width='324' height='180'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;You don't need to be in a guild&lt;/font&gt; to participate in conquest events, but it's a good idea to join one.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;During each conquest event, several planets will be &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;contested&lt;/font&gt;. If your guild owns a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;flagship&lt;/font&gt;, you may choose to &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;invade a planet&lt;/font&gt;, which provides &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;additional benefits&lt;/font&gt; and pits your guild against others on that planet's leaderboard for the duration of the event.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whichever guild places first on the leaderboard &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;takes control of the planet&lt;/font&gt; when the next event begins!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1112" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.strongholds_conquest_page3.dds' width='324' height='180'&gt;&lt;br&gt;If your guild completes its conquest point target, every guild member who met his or her &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;personal contribution&lt;/font&gt; will be granted special &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;guild rewards&lt;/font&gt;. Each guild member's contribution can be viewed in the guild window. If you join or leave a guild, your contribution will be reset.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Conquering planets&lt;/font&gt; unlocks special privileges, including temporary access to the special &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Command Walker&lt;/font&gt; mount, increased potency of &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;flagship orbital support&lt;/font&gt;, achievements, and more!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1113" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Perks of Stronghold Ownership</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1114" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Unlock Legacy Stronghold Storage, gathering decorations, and more!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1115" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.strongholds_ownership_page1' width='324' height='180'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Legacy Stronghold Storage&lt;/font&gt; is a new way to store your items and share them between characters in your Legacy. You can obtain access to this new feature by unlocking the Legacy Stronghold Storage &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;utility decoration&lt;/font&gt;. Once you've unlocked the decoration, simply &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;place it in your stronghold&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your Stronghold Storage will start with one bay containing 80 item slots. You can purchase &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;additional storage bays&lt;/font&gt; for your Legacy with credits or Cartel Coins. Crew Skills will &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;automatically use materials&lt;/font&gt; from your Stronghold Storage if your personal inventory and Cargo Hold are exhausted.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1116" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.strongholds_ownership_page2' width='324' height='180'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Gathering node decorations&lt;/font&gt; can be earned by completing &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Conquest Events&lt;/font&gt;. These decorations can be harvested for &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;crafting materials&lt;/font&gt; simply by interacting with them in your stronghold!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvesting from one of these decorations has a chance to cause &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;resource exhaustion&lt;/font&gt;, which prevents your character from gathering inside strongholds for a while. Any player with a &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;silver key&lt;/font&gt; to your stronghold will be able to use these decorations.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1117" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.strongholds_ownership_page3.dds' width='324' height='180'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Completing your stronghold&lt;/font&gt; establishes a power base for your Legacy that improves your influence throughout the galaxy and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;increases your Conquest point gain&lt;/font&gt;. As the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;completion percentages&lt;/font&gt; for your strongholds increase, your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Conquest stronghold bonus&lt;/font&gt; also increases, which helps you &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;earn rewards faster&lt;/font&gt; and makes you a better contributor to your guild's conquest score.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;all four strongholds fully completed&lt;/font&gt;, you'll earn &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;+100% Conquest points&lt;/font&gt;!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1118" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Welcome to Galactic Strongholds! Visit a Stronghold Directory on the Fleet to get started customizing your very own bastion of military might and personal luxury.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1119" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Welcome to Game Update 3.0: Shadow of Revan! Click here for more information.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1120" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Shadow of Revan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1121" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn about the all-new story and features in the Shadow of Revan Digital Expansion!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1122" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.SoR_Revan.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;New Epic Storyline!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Experience the epic new storyline at level 55! Travel to your ship and pick up the mission &quot;Shadow of Revan: Prelude&quot; to begin.

Your mission starts with the explosive Forged Alliances story arc.  You'll pick up where you left off in the story, with a new option to play through these Flashpoints in SOLO MODE with the help of a combat support droid.

Completing this prelude will prepare you for the challenge ahead by providing a powerful set of level 55 gear.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1123" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.SoR_Yavin.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Explore New Planets!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Adventure beckons on the remote world of Rishi, a tropical paradise that's become a lawless hideaway for pirates, smugglers, and anyone else who wishes to remain hidden from the eyes of the greater galaxy.

Then continue the story on Yavin 4, a primeval moon steeped in ancient mysteries of the Force-and overrun by vicious beasts and ruthless Massassi warriors.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1124" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.SoR_Level_60' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Level up to 60!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The new Discipline system gives you a clear role in combat. Choose your path, and customize your play style by selecting from a variety of utility powers!

Level up to 60 to unlock new powers and unleash your full potential in new OPERATIONS and FLASHPOINTS! Or queue for Warzones to rejoin the frontlines and earn powerful new PvP gear.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1125" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Welcome to Game Update 3.0: Shadow of Revan!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1127" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Welcome to Outfit Designer! Open your Character Sheet or press the C key to get started!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1128" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Welcome to Outfit Designer!  Click here for more information.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1129" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Outfit Designer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1130" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Access your Outfit Designer to create custom appearances for your character!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1131" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/Tutorial.Outfitter.Tabs.dds' width='324' height='284'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;

To access the Outfit Designer, select the Character Sheet icon from your Menu Bar or press C.

The window opens on your currently equipped gear. Click any of the numbered tabs on the right to change the view to the Outfit Designer.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1132" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/Tutorial.Outfitter.Stamping.dds' width='324' height='280'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;

Select the Inventory icon from your Menu Bar or press I to access your inventory. Right-click or drag and drop an item from your inventory to &quot;stamp&quot; that item to the appropriate slot for your selected outfit. Stamping an item assigns the appearance of that item to the slot. It does not consume the item, and you can stamp the same item into multiple outfits.

Note that stamping and committing an item to your outfit will bind that item to your character.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1133" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/Tutorial.Outfitter.Receipt.dds' width='324' height='300'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;

Once you are satisfied with your new look, select the Commit Changes button at the bottom of the window to save it. You will be presented with a confirmation window informing you of the total outfit build cost in credits, as well as any items that will become bound. Select OK to save your outfit, withdraw the necessary funds, bind any unbound items, and activate the outfit for your character.

To unlock additional outfit slots, simply select the plus (+) tab and choose whether you want to purchase the slot with credits or Cartel Coins. Switching between numbered tabs allows you to preview your outfits. Select the Apply button over any previewed outfit to show off your new look!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1134" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Knights of the Fallen Empire</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1135" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Knights of the Fallen Empire is divided into exciting player-focused chapters.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1136" id2="532678" version="1065353216">New Max Level Player Tutorial</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1137" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Chapter I includes the new player tutorial experience.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1138" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.episodic_content_1.dds' width='324' height='165'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chapter&lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Play Button&lt;/font&gt; will allow you to quickly jump into the active chapter at any time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1139" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.episodic_content_2.dds' width='324' height='220'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each chapter has a series of &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;checkpoints&lt;/font&gt; that save your progress and returning location. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clicking the &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Play Button&lt;/font&gt; will bring you right back to the current checkpoint and allow you to continue the chapter.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1140" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.episodic_content_3.dds' width='324' height='152'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your friends can join you on your adventure. Form a group and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right-click&lt;/font&gt; on your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;portrait icon&lt;/font&gt; to invite your group mates into your story.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1141" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.new_60_1.dds' width='324' height='224'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a new player, you are starting with a subset of your offensive abilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1142" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.new_60_2.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As you progress through chapter I you will unlock more of your &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;class discipline's&lt;/font&gt; abilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1143" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.new_60_3.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once you have finished with the tutorial and &lt;font color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Chapter I&lt;/font&gt;, you will have access to all of your class's abilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1144" id2="532678" version="1065353216">The new-player tutorial has been enabled. You will gain new abilities at key moments as you play through the first chapter. The tutorial can be disabled and re-enabled at any time in the preferences menu.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1145" id2="532678" version="1065353216">A new-player tutorial is available, would you like to enable it? You can disable it again at any time by hitting ESC and left-clicking on the &quot;Disable Tutorial&quot; button on the menu.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1146" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Welcome to Knights of the Fallen Empire! Click here for more information.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1147" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn about the all-new story and features in the Knights of the Fallen Empire!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1148" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Alliance</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1149" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn how to gain Influence and rewards by building a galactic Alliance!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1150" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.alliance_pane1.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;CONTINUE THE EPIC STORY&lt;/font&gt;

The battle against the Eternal Empire continues on the planet Odessen!

Forge your &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Alliance&lt;/font&gt; and continue your personal Star Wars: The Old Republic 
saga through &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Classic Conversations&lt;/font&gt;, presenting you more dialog options and personal interactions as you rally your Alliance camp leaders.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1151" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.alliance_pane2.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;STRENGTHEN YOUR ALLIANCE&lt;/font&gt;

By increasing your &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Influence Rank&lt;/font&gt; with each of the Alliance camp leaders you will strengthen your Alliance, giving you new story choices and avenues of adventure!

Increase your influence by completing &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Alliance Alert Missions&lt;/font&gt; for specialist contacts or turning in &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Supply Crates&lt;/font&gt; obtainable from &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Planetary Heroic Missions&lt;/font&gt;, the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Star Fortress flashpoint&lt;/font&gt;, and more!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1152" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.alliance_pane3.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;REAP THE REWARDS&lt;/font&gt;

For each &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Supply Crate&lt;/font&gt; you turn in your contact will give you back a cut as a reward. As your &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Influence&lt;/font&gt; grows watch each Alliance camp evolve into bustling centers of activity bent toward defeating the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1153" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Companions &amp; Contacts</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1154" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn how to summon Followers, travel to Contacts, and manage Alerts.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1155" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.companionscontacts_pane1.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;FOLLOWERS&lt;/font&gt;

Followers are Companions and Alliance members that you can summon to fight by your side in battle using the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Summon This Crew Member&lt;/font&gt; button.

Followers' &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Combat Roles&lt;/font&gt; can be changed via the drop down next to their name on the right side of the window.

Increasing your &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Influence&lt;/font&gt; with Followers will make them more proficient at combat and &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Crew Skills.&lt;/font&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1156" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.KOTFE_Social_03.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;CONTACTS&lt;/font&gt;

Contacts become available during the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Knights of the Fallen Empire&lt;/font&gt; storyline and are Alliance members, potential &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Followers&lt;/font&gt;, and other important persons.

You can increase your &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Influence&lt;/font&gt; with Contacts by performing &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Alliance Alert Missions&lt;/font&gt; or turning in &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Supply Crates.&lt;/font&gt;

You can &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Quick Travel&lt;/font&gt; to a Contact using the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Travel Button&lt;/font&gt; next to their name on the right side of the window.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1157" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.companionscontacts_pane3.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;ALERTS&lt;/font&gt;

Beginning with the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Knights of the Fallen Empire&lt;/font&gt; storyline you will occasionaly 
receive Alerts from your &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Contacts&lt;/font&gt; and &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Followers.&lt;/font&gt; This indicates that they have a mission for you to undertake.

Selecting an Alert from the list will allow you to view the contact (if they are known to you) and &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Travel to Alert Location.&lt;/font&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1158" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.KOTFE_Social_01.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;New Epic Storyline!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience the epic new storyline at level 60! Travel to your ship and pick up the mission&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt; &quot;Chapter I: The Hunt&quot;&lt;/font&gt; to begin.
Your mission starts with the explosive first chapter in the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Knights of the Fallen Empire&lt;/font&gt; story arc. You'll pick up where the story left off after Ziost, delivered in all new episodic story &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Chapters&lt;/font&gt;. Each chapter can be completed solo or with a group of friends. There are a total of 9 chapters at launch and more chapters will be released in the following months.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1159" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.KOTFE_Social_02.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Explore New Planets!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;The planet &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Zakuul&lt;/font&gt; has become the new seat of power in the galaxy. Its skyscrapers reach toward the stars while its lowest levels brim with danger and crime, all surrounded by a vast and savage swamp. Those who wish to evade Zakuul's power hide out on &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Asylum&lt;/font&gt;, a smuggling den floating among the clouds where freedom and anarchy reign. The shadowy forest world of &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Odessen&lt;/font&gt; holds many mysteries; its remote location is a secret known only to a select few....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1160" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.KOTFE_Social_03.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Level Up To 65!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;New abilities and powers await you as you progress to level 65. All &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Operations&lt;/font&gt; have been raised to level 65 and have all new gear and rewards waiting for you. All your favorite &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Flashpoints&lt;/font&gt; have had solo modes added with all new rewards.
&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Redesigned Core Game Experience&lt;/font&gt;
The core leveling experience from 1 - 60 has been redesigned with a streamlined quest progression that keeps you fully focused on your character's personal story.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1161" id2="532678" version="1065353216">The Eternal Championship</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1162" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Fight for fame, fortune, and glory in Zakuul's Arena Grand!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.eternal_championship1.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Enter the Arena Grand&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enter the Eternal Championship by using the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Arena Terminal&lt;/font&gt; in the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Platform 6 Cantina&lt;/font&gt; on Zakuul. From there you can acquire the [Daily] mission to enter the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Mayhem&lt;/font&gt; event.&lt;br&gt;
You can also acquire the [Weekly] missions to defeat the bosses of specific rounds from this terminal.&lt;br&gt;
When you're ready to enter the event head down the nearby elevator and enter the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Arena Grand&lt;/font&gt; flashpoint instance gate.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1164" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.eternal_championship2.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Compete for the Eternal Championship&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each round of Mayhem at the Arena Grand begins with an introduction by &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Rokka Rey&lt;/font&gt;, after which your battle with that round's boss will begin.&lt;br&gt;
Between rounds you will go into an intermission period. Use the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Intermission Terminal&lt;/font&gt; to choose whether you want to continue or leave the competition.&lt;br&gt;
If you are defeated in any round, you will be sent back to intermission, but incur no other penalties.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1165" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.eternal_championship3.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Reap the Rewards&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rewards for Mayhem accumulate as you progress, so the more rounds you win each day the more rewards you get. To claim your rewards you have to win every round of the competition &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;or&lt;/font&gt; chose to leave during intermission.&lt;br&gt;
Retrieve your [Daily] Mission rewards from the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Arena Winnings Terminal&lt;/font&gt; in the Platform 6 Cantina. [Weekly] missions for the Eternal Championship will reward you immediately upon completion.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1166" id2="532678" version="1065353216">PvP</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1167" id2="532678" version="1065353216">PvP Focus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your PvP focus will determine if you are placed into a PvE instance or a PvP instance when you transition areas.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn about changing your PvP Focus! Click here for more information.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1170" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.focus_switching1.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;

Players now have a new option: PvE or PvP Focus. By setting your Focus, you will be placed in an appropriate instance. PvE instances will play like the game does normally. While in a PvP instance you will be flagged for player-vs-player combat. This will allow opposing faction players to attack you, and you them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.focus_switching2.dds' width='324' height='252'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;

You can change your focus at any time by clicking on the drop-down located below your minimap. Changing your focus will, in most cases, immediately transfer you to the appropriate instance. Doing so will apply the normal instance changing cooldowns. Changing your instance to a PvP instance will automatically move you to the med center closest to your current location.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1172" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.focus_switching3.dds' width='324' height='220'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;

PvP Missions are now located under the PvP category. These missions are colored differently than other missions both in your Mission Log and on the world map. PvP Mission targets can only be found in PvP instances.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1173" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Odessen Proving Grounds</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1174" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Compete in the Odessen Proving Grounds to prove your prowess against other players.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.proving_grounds1.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

There are &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;7 rounds&lt;/font&gt;, each lasting &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;90 seconds&lt;/font&gt;.  2 or 3 control sectors become active each round.  Control sectors are captured by standing inside a marked area.  Control sectors cannot be captured if enemies are within the area.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1176" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.proving_grounds2.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

A control sector is held by remaining within its area. &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;One point&lt;/font&gt; is earned for &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;every second&lt;/font&gt; a control sector is held. Leaving the sector will result in losing the control sector. Stealthed players do not count towards capturing a control sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1177" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.proving_grounds3.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Battle mods&lt;/font&gt; spawn throughout the map. Use them to impact control sectors:
&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Multiply (Blue)&lt;/font&gt; - Increases the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;points gained&lt;/font&gt; from a control sector.
&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Activate (Green)&lt;/font&gt; - Turns &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;on&lt;/font&gt; an inactive control sector.
&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Deactivate (Red)&lt;/font&gt; - Turns &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;off&lt;/font&gt; an active control sector.
&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Speed  (Orange)&lt;/font&gt; - &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Speeds up the rate&lt;/font&gt; at which a control sector rewards points.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1178" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Welcome to the Odessen Proving Grounds!  Click here for more information.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Dark vs. Light Event</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1181" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Embark on a new Star Wars: The Old Republic journey and determine the fate of the galaxy!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.dark_v_light1.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Choose Your Side&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Take part in the Dark vs. Light event by creating a &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;new character&lt;/font&gt;. Characters created during the Dark vs. Light event will automatically have their Dark and Light &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;story choices&lt;/font&gt; tallied as they play, contributing to their &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;server's alignment.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Choose your side and help determine the fate of the galaxy. Stay tuned to &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;swtor.com&lt;/font&gt; throughout the event to see your server's alignment update.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1183" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.dark_v_light2.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Achieve Greatness&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dark vs. Light event features 8 categories of &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;all new Achievements&lt;/font&gt; that unlock as you complete story and repeatable content &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;beginning at level 1&lt;/font&gt; and reaching across the entire Star Wars: The Old Republic experience.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.dark_v_light3.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Reap the Rewards&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With each new achievement category you complete, &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;you will be rewarded&lt;/font&gt; with lockboxes containing exclusive Force-Bound Dark vs. Light packs that will allow you to roll for &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;valuable loot!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The more you &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;play&lt;/font&gt;, the more you &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;achieve&lt;/font&gt;, the more you &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;win!&lt;/font&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185" id2="532678" version="1065353216">The Dark vs. Light Event has begun! Which side will you choose? Click here for more information.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1186" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Events</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187" id2="532678" version="1065353216">The Cartel Market Item Stash</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Discover wonderous goods from the Cartel Market.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1189" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.packviewer_1.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;The Finest Goods from Around the Galaxy&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cartel Market Packs are an assortment of various exciting Cartel Market items. The &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Market Pack Viewer&lt;/font&gt; is an effective way to view the contents of these packs and safely store items in the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Market Item Stash. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1190" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.packviewer_2.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Simplicity is Key&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Right-Clicking a pack in your inventory you'll be presented with the pack viewer. Opening the pack will reveal the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;valuable contents&lt;/font&gt; that await inside. &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Each Item&lt;/font&gt; will be stored in your &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Cartel Market Stash&lt;/font&gt;. All items will be stackable while located in the stash!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1191" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.packviewer_3.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Convenience&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clicking the Cartel Market Stash Icon on your UI will display a list of unclaimed pack items. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Claim&lt;/font&gt; items you wish to use or sell by clicking the claim button. These will be sent to your&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt; Current Characters'&lt;/font&gt; inventory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Dark vs Light</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1193" id2="532678" version="1065353216">The balance of the Force is in your hands!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1194" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.dark_v_light1.dds' width='324' height='72'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The struggle between the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Dark&lt;/font&gt; and the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Light&lt;/font&gt; sides of the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Force&lt;/font&gt; continues!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Through your actions&lt;/font&gt; and the actions of others in the galaxy, the balance of the Force can be swayed one way or the other, with &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;fantastic rewards&lt;/font&gt; and &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;new challenges&lt;/font&gt; waiting for both sides.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1195" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.dark_v_light02.dds' width='324' height='128'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Participating in the struggle&lt;/font&gt; between the Dark and Light sides of the Force is as easy as flipping a switch and playing the game.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Toggle your allegiance&lt;/font&gt; using the buttons on the main game screen and your actions will begin contributing toward your own alignment shift and that of &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;the entire galaxy.&lt;/font&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1196" id2="532678" version="1065353216">When one side wins the struggle, players of that alignment will receive bonus &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Command Experience Points&lt;/font&gt; as well as &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Dark or Light side tokens&lt;/font&gt; that can be spent with vendors on the Imperial and Republic fleets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even though the winners' influence will be felt throughout the galaxy, &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;there is hope&lt;/font&gt; for the losing side. &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;New challenges, creatures, and opponents&lt;/font&gt; will surface that if defeated will provide Dark or Light side tokens and help them to &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;upset the balance&lt;/font&gt; of the Force once again!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1197" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Difficulty Modes</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1198" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Choose your difficulty and reap the rewards!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1199" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Difficulty modes&lt;/font&gt; allow you to repeat content at higher or lower difficulties and with variable rewards. The three difficulty modes are:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Story&lt;/font&gt; - suitable for groups comprised of players in any combination of roles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Veteran&lt;/font&gt; - designed for groups of well-equipped players with a balanced group composition containing the appropriate number of healers and tanks for the group size.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Master&lt;/font&gt; - the most challenging experiences in the galaxy, requiring a balanced group of players with extremely high quality gear.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1200" id2="532678" version="1065353216">In addition to &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Flashpoints&lt;/font&gt; and &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Operations&lt;/font&gt;, difficulty modes have been added to new content like &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Uprisings&lt;/font&gt; and existing content like &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Chapters&lt;/font&gt; in order to give you additional challenges and rewards.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can lower difficulty without penalty by right-clicking on your character portrait at any time. Raising difficulty however will require you to start your mission over.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.difficulty_modes02.dds' width='324' height='208'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1201" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Chapters&lt;/font&gt; (beginning with Chapter I of Knights of the Fallen Empire) will now be repeatable on different difficulties.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Access Chapter difficulties through the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Galactic Command&lt;/font&gt; window or by pressing &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Shift-E&lt;/font&gt; on your keyboard.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In order to repeat a Chapter, you must have already completed it once. Decisions you make when repeating a Chapter will not carry over past the Chapter's end.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1202" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Uprisings</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1203" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Your enemies are many, but the Force is with you!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1204" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.uprisings1.dds' width='324' height='208'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;The Alliance&lt;/font&gt; is strong, but so are its enemies and the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Eternal Fleet&lt;/font&gt; is not the only threat you face. &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Uprisings&lt;/font&gt; by groups opposed to your Alliance have begun sprouting up throughout the galaxy and &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;it's up to you&lt;/font&gt; to put together a team and restore order.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1205" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.uprisings2.dds' width='324' height='208'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Uprisings&lt;/font&gt; are fast-paced, high-action, repeatable group missions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Access Uprisings through the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Galactic Command&lt;/font&gt; window (Ctrl+G) or from &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;terminals&lt;/font&gt; on the Imperial and Republic Fleets.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1206" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.uprisings3.dds' width='324' height='208'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Uprisings&lt;/font&gt; are designed for group play and feature multiple difficulty settings for those seeking bigger challenges and rewards.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gather your party and squash the Uprisings!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1207" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Command Crates</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1208" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Acquire and manage the rewards of Galactic Command.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1209" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.command_pack1.dds' width='324' height='52'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With each &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Command Rank&lt;/font&gt; gained, you will receive a &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Command Crate&lt;/font&gt; containing valuable items and powerful gear.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opening and managing your crates is easily handled via the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Command Stash&lt;/font&gt; window, accessible by pressing the button next to your Command Rank in the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Galactic Command&lt;/font&gt; window or by pressing &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Ctrl+I&lt;/font&gt; on your keyboard.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1210" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.command_pack2.dds' width='324' height='208'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;left side&lt;/font&gt; of the Command Stash are the Command Crates that you have yet to open. Click the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Open&lt;/font&gt; button on a crate in order to see what's inside.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;right side&lt;/font&gt; of the Command Stash will show you all the items in your stash from opened crates. Items will remain in your stash until you &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Disintegrate&lt;/font&gt; or &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Claim&lt;/font&gt; them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1211" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.command_pack3.dds' width='324' height='208'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can select one or multiple items in the right pane of the Command Stash by clicking on them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;move the items from your stash to your inventory&lt;/font&gt;, press the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Claim&lt;/font&gt; button. Claimed items cannot be moved back into the Stash.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;destroy items in your stash&lt;/font&gt;, press the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Disintegrate&lt;/font&gt; button. This will remove the item entirely and give you &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Command Experience Points&lt;/font&gt; in return.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1212" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Galactic Command</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1213" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Forge your destiny as the Alliance Commander!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1214" id2="532678" version="1065353216">As the Alliance Commander, &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Galactic Command&lt;/font&gt; is not just your quickest way to access a galaxy's worth of Star Wars: The Old Republic content, it's also your means to acquire &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;the most powerful gear in the game&lt;/font&gt; by increasing your Command Rank.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participating in Galactic Command and increasing your Command Rank is as easy as playing the game!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To begin, press &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Ctrl+G&lt;/font&gt; on your keyboard to access the new Galactic Command window.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1215" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Upon reaching your character's maximum level, every activity you do in Star Wars: The Old Republic will confer &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Command Experience Points.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gain enough Command Experience Points and you will earn a &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Command Rank&lt;/font&gt; and receive a &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Command Crate&lt;/font&gt; with powerful gear and rewards.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The higher your Command Rank the more &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;powerful&lt;/font&gt; the gear you'll get from each Command Crate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.galactic_command2.dds' width='324' height='208'&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1216" id2="532678" version="1065353216">The &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Galactic Command&lt;/font&gt; window not only lets you monitor your &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Command Rank&lt;/font&gt; progress, claim &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Command Crates&lt;/font&gt;, and view the current &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Dark vs Light&lt;/font&gt; alignment of the galaxy, but it also gives you quick access to hundreds of hours of repeatable content in the form of &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Daily&lt;/font&gt; and &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Heroic&lt;/font&gt; Missions, &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Chapter&lt;/font&gt; content, &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Flashpoints, Operations, Warzones, Starfighter&lt;/font&gt;, and &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Uprisings.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Keep an eye on the Galactic Command window to see which activities are &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;currently highlighted&lt;/font&gt;, giving greater Command Experience Point rewards on completion.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1217" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Knights of the Eternal Throne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1218" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Learn more about the all-new story and features in Knights of the Eternal Throne!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1219" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.kotet_welcome1.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Your Epic Saga Continues!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Command your Alliance in battle against Empress Vaylin and the overwhelming power of the Eternal Throne across nine epic story chapters!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1220" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.kotet_welcome2.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Play The Newest Chapters - Or Repeat Your Favorites!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can use the Chapters menu to begin the Knights of the Eternal Throne storyline as soon as your character reaches Level 65. You can also use this menu to repeat previously-released story chapters on multiple difficulty levels.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1221" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.kotet_welcome3.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Level Up To 70 For Galactic Command!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New abilities and features await you as you progress to level 70, including the new Galactic Command system! Use Galactic Command to advance your character's power and earn the best gear at max level by participating in any activity in the game, including new Uprisings for groups of four players.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1222" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Welcome to Knights of the Eternal Throne! Click here for more information.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1223" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.masters_datacron_1.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the wisdom contained within the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Master's Datacron&lt;/font&gt;, you have reached max level! Be sure to select your &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Discipline&lt;/font&gt; if you haven't already (default: K).</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1224" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.masters_datacron_2.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have also been granted &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Eternal Commander Equipment &lt;/font&gt;appropriate to your Class and Discipline. Plus, you now have access to a &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;personal droid companion&lt;/font&gt; to aid you in your journeys (if you didn't have one already).</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1225" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.masters_datacron_3.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that you've attained &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;max level&lt;/font&gt;, an entire galaxy of adventure awaits. Use your &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;personal starship or galaxy map&lt;/font&gt; (default: Shift+ M) to start exploring!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1226" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Master's Datacron</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1227" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Master's Datacron</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1228" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Explore the world of Star Wars: The Old Republic at maximum level!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1229" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Stronghold Group Free-For-All PVP</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1230" id2="532678" version="1065353216">You choose how to play!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1231" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Game Modes</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1232" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/codex/cdx.stronghold_ffa_pvp_volumes_3.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stronghold Group Free-For-All PVP areas allow you to engage in group &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;player vs. player &lt;/font&gt;combat in your stronghold!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;While in these designated areas anyone outside of your group is hostile to you.  You can do anything from challenging another player to a one on one duel to organizing a large scale 16 on 16 raid group battle!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Customize your own combat spaces by placing decorations!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1233" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/codex/cdx.stronghold_ffa_pvp_volumes_2.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Groups can simply jump into these areas and face off against each other or&lt;/font&gt; they can &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;choose a game mode&lt;/font&gt; to play!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Use a console to pick either &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Team Death Match&lt;/font&gt; or &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Huttball Simulation&lt;/font&gt; as your game mode!  Then your group can pick &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Rotworm&lt;/font&gt; or &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Frogdog&lt;/font&gt; to define where they respawn during the match!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1234" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/codex/cdx.stronghold_ffa_pvp_volumes_1.dds' width='324' height='204'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Team Death Match:&lt;/font&gt; First team to 30 kills wins the match! As your team scores kills the score boards update to mark your progress. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Huttball Simulation:&lt;/font&gt; Carry or throw the huttball into the defined endzones to score the Huttball!  First team to 10 points wins! Just don't kick it!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1235" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Guilds</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1236" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Guild Levels</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1237" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Guild Levels track your guild's progress</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1238" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.guildlevels1' width='324' height='100'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Levels&lt;/font&gt; are gained by members of your guild doing conquests, which gain &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Conquest Points&lt;/font&gt; that will go towards &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Level Experience&lt;/font&gt;. Guild level experience is gained after completing &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Invasions&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1239" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.guildlevels2' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can check your guild level by opening the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Window&lt;/font&gt; using the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;G Key&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1240" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.guildlevels3' width='324' height='160'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gaining levels as a guild unlocks bonuses for the entire guild, such as increased reputation, &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Commendations&lt;/font&gt; and the ability to use &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Perks&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Play together as a team and achieve greatness together!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1241" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Guild Perks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1242" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Guild Perks are purchased by your guild, benefiting every guild member for a limited duration!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1243" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.guildperks' width='324' height='152'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Perks&lt;/font&gt; are temporary bonuses purchased from the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Window&lt;/font&gt;, costing credits and &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Commendations&lt;/font&gt; from your &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Bank&lt;/font&gt;. Each perk lasts a certain amount of time, and affects every member of your guild. Whenever a guild perk is purchased it is automatically equipped to that &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Flagship&lt;/font&gt; room slot.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Set Bonuses&lt;/font&gt; are earned by equipping four of the same type of &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Perks&lt;/font&gt; and appear in the lower left of the &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Perk Window&lt;/font&gt;. Set Bonuses give every member of your guild even more benefits!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1244" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.guildperks1' width='324' height='172'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Perks&lt;/font&gt; are unlocked by leveling up your guild and purchasing new rooms for your &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Flagship&lt;/font&gt;. The rooms are listed in your &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Perk Window&lt;/font&gt;. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hover over a locked perk to find out the additional requirements for purchasing it! &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Remember, you need a Guild Bank and a Guild Flagship to use Guild Perks.&lt;/font&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1245" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://&lt;&lt;grammar::locpath&gt;&gt;/tutorials/tutorial.guildperks2' width='324' height='160'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The types of &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Perks&lt;/font&gt; that are available to purchase cycle every two weeks, so try to be on top of purchasing perks to enhance your guild. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remember, only guild members with appropriate permissions can purchase and equip &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;Guild Perks&lt;/font&gt;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1246" id2="532678" version="1065353216">PvP Challenge</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1247" id2="532678" version="1065353216">Group together to challenge other groups to PvP combat!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1248" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.rothc.rothc_splash_level55.dds' width='324' height='200'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;PvP Challenge&lt;/font&gt; is a feature that allows you and a group to come together and challenge another group to selected PvP content. &lt;br&gt;To start off, you need a group, a group leader, and another group you wish to challenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1249" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.grouping_players3.dds' width='324' height='288'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find the group you wish to challenge, and either right click on a group member and select &lt;font style='bold' color='#&lt;&lt;1&gt;&gt;'&gt;PvP Challenge&lt;/font&gt; or open the challenge window and type in the group leader's name. Fill out the rest of the details specific to the game. Once initialized, the challenged group will have to accept the challenge and the details of the game.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1250" id2="532678" version="1065353216">&lt;img src='img://gfx/tutorials/tutorial.the_adventure_begins3.dds' width='324' height='324'&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once both groups agree to the challenge, you will both be loaded into a PvP instance and the battle will commence! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Note that PvP achievements cannot be earned in PvP challenges. and PvP Missions will not be completed.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
