<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>12</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/bronze/republic/blinding_the_rist/captain_alethios.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for all your help. I'll send someone to collect my aunt before she volunteers for another mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maelrich Alde wanted me to inform you that I'd destroyed the Rist transceiver, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318316" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm honored by your assistance, Master Jedi. I hope my aunt was not too much trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318318" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you Captain Alethios? I destroyed House Rist's transceiver at your aunt's request.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318319" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thank you, Master Jedi. I can't even imagine how you found my aunt, let alone how she convinced you to do this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318321" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, your aunt says I should tell you the Rist transceiver has been taken out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soldier, I don't know if I'm more shocked to hear that you've destroyed a Rist spy network, or that my aunt is alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318324" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Alethios? Your aunt told me to let you know when I'd destroyed the Rist transceiver.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318325" id2="17" version="1065353216">I beg your pardon? You did what, exactly? Wait--my aunt is alive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318327" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've had men trying to find her for days. If she had fallen into enemy hands....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318329" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have struck a blow at our enemies' communications and protected the integrity of the Organa intelligence network. We owe you greatly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318330" id2="17" version="1065353216">I beg your pardon. I can't speak at present. I'm coordinating a search for a missing person.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
