<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>61</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_2/old_feuds/mayor_erkens.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1013808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can this wait? We're a little busy here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1013810" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the galaxy coming to? Hutts invading, planets cracking in half, and now that... that... whatever it was! Somebody tell me what that was!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1013823" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get these people out of here. Sounds like you need to be heading for Shalim's new camp site. Thanks for saving us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014977" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're under attack in the central square! Help us! Hurr--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever you're doing out there, it's working like a charm. The Hutts aren't landing reinforcements. Keep it up!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014979" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got our wounded stabilized. We're prepping everyone for evacuation at the central square. Keep those Hutt forces off us!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014981" id2="17" version="1065353216">It appeared to be a droid, Mayor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here I was thinking it was a shiny Wookiee on stilts wearing turbolasers for a hat! &quot;A droid,&quot; indeed! Now... who the blazes are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014984" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a Jedi Knight, here to protect you on behalf of Shalim Avesta and the Galactic Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014984" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm someone who can help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014985" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thought as much, what with the lightsaber and all. Good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014987" id2="17" version="1065353216">I represent the Jedi. I was sent by Shalim Avesta to defend you from this attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014987" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014988" id2="17" version="1065353216">In that case, welcome to Tarlam.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Special Forces Infantry Unit 326. My team's evacuating everyone off Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014990" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Havoc Squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not everyone, hopefully. Hutts can stay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014993" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm one of the Republic's top experts on Hutt-smashing, or whatever. My point is, I'm the best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, I'm your expert help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014994" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a relief. Thanks for gracing us with your presence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take a deep breath and relax. You don't need to yell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm down, please.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014997" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, what? I can't hear over that ringing in my ears! You know, from all the screaming and explosions!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1014999" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm the person in charge here--effective immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1014999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your replacement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015000" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want the shortest term as mayor in town history? Take it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015002" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are the reinforcements Shalim Avesta told us to expect. They're here to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015004" id2="17" version="1065353216">This mesa's already collapsing. Now I've got wounded people everywhere, and all the working shuttle pads are outside town.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015005" id2="17" version="1065353216">You obviously can't stay. What will it take to get your people out of here safely?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1015005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me how to assist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015006" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not a question of resources--we're racing disaster here. No telling when this mesa will fall apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shalim can get more shuttles for the evacuation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1015008" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can call for support.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015009" id2="17" version="1065353216">What we really need is the one thing those Hutts won't give us--time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless you can evacuate people with your mouth, I suggest closing it and getting to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1015011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop whining and act!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for the advice!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mayor, we're getting emergency alerts. The Hutts are landing reinforcements--mercenaries and more of those droids!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lovely! I'm the one-legged woman at the droid-kicking contest!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015018" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're holding the shuttle pads. We'll never get off the mesa unless someone drives the enemy off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave the Hutt forces to me. I'll open the routes out of here--you be ready to move your people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1015019" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll clear you a path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015022" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a big mesa. Surely there's another way off it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1015022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't you go around?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those droids are fast, and their weapons have enough kick to take us out from a distance. If you can't handle them, we're dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015025" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take on those Hutt forces, but you'll never get everyone moving. Decide now who gets left behind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1015025" id2="17" version="1065353216">Abandon the wounded and run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015026" id2="17" version="1065353216">I promised my people I'd get them to safety--all of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1015028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just clearing off the pads isn't enough, though. We need to stop the Hutts from landing more reinforcements until we've all evacuated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020390" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could erect energy shields, Mayor. Cover the pads so they can only be used for flying out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020392" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soler, you're actually useful! If we got you some energy shields, could you set them up at each landing pad?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020393" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on me--complicated missions are my specialty. I'll clear the shuttle pads and make sure they won't work for the Hutts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020394" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't you just run for it once the shuttle pads are clear?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020394" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is getting complicated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our wounded move too slowly. You've got to buy us more time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop wasting time with stupid questions and give me what I need to secure those pads!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just hand over the stuff!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020398" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate your enthusiasm!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gather the wounded! Prep for evacuation on the double! We are leaving!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020402" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take these energy shields; activate them at the landing pads. Good luck!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
