<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>117</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/excavation/roth/imperial/darth_acina.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104951" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep the seeker droid as a memento, until we meet again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104956" id2="17" version="1065353216">You return to me empty-handed. Why? Whatever your little game is, I am not amused.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104958" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are withholding property of the Dark Council--of the Emperor himself. Where are the Seeds?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104959" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were too dangerous. I made sure we'll never have to hunt down those devices again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104959" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] I destroyed them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104960" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was not your decision to make. The Seeds were entrusted to me by the Emperor. He will know of this insult.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep the seeker droid. I doubt it will let you dig your way back into our good graces, but anything's possible. Best of luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104963" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Emperor wants his machines back so badly, give him my holo-frequency. I want him to know who really got them back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104963" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell the Emperor to call me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104964" id2="17" version="1065353216">So it is to be that way. Very well. Remember this moment when you require my favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104966" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wouldn't be the first Sith to let others do your dirty work and then stab them in the back. The Seeds are safe as long as I am. Understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104966" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] I kept them as insurance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104967" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have overplayed your hand with me. This will not be forgotten.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since you're of a mood to keep things that aren't yours, retain the seeker droid. You'll need a digging device more than me. Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104975" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Seeds. Well done. Their dark side power... so warm to the senses. What a pity the machines must be locked away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arcanum facility is compromised, but I found a suitable new hiding place for the Seeds on Ziost. I depart immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your travels to yourself. The Seeds' hiding place is your secret. I never want to see those things again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep them safe and inactive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Being responsible for power I can never use has always provided a unique challenge. I don't know how you walk away with such ease.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't rush off. I know good places to eat around here. Quiet, private... we could deepen our alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104981" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Join me for dinner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104982" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one has spoken to me so boldly in years. How refreshing. I regret we must continue this another time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104984" id2="17" version="1065353216">Weapons shouldn't be locked up when you're in the middle of a war. We should be burying the Seeds all over Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1104984" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Seeds should be used.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104985" id2="17" version="1065353216">For what it's worth, I agree--but it's not our place to question the Emperor's plans, is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104987" id2="17" version="1065353216">When my servants evacuated all remaining technology from Arcanum, they discovered something you might appreciate. Keep it and the seeker droid with my compliments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104989" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you speak of me, I trust you'll be kind. Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive. One Seed recovered, many more to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104998" id2="17" version="1065353216">You found a Seed. Excellent. Fascinating little machines, aren't they?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1104999" id2="17" version="1065353216">You caught that Seed just in time. They're programmed to evade capture.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105000" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're making this look easy. Put the Seed somewhere safe and find the others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another Seed found. That seeker droid has turned out to be as good an investment as you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait a moment... incoming transmission... those mad fools! The Dread Masters have sent an army to raid the Arcanum facility. They're stealing everything, this time!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105005" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm alerting the Ninth Fleet, but you're my best hope of stopping this outrage. Fly to Arcanum and destroy the Dread Masters' forces. Hurry!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Arcanum. Please do not touch the exhibits. The Dread Masters' thieves murdered my staff, so you're welcome to kill anything that moves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105011" id2="17" version="1065353216">I recognize that one! He's the leader--kill him now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105012" id2="17" version="1065353216">So much for the would-be thieves. It does not appear they escaped with any of the Emperor's possessions. You've saved us both pain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105014" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Ninth Fleet has arrived to guard Arcanum. Boarding parties are en route. I need you back out hunting the remaining Seeds of Rage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our traitor has graciously provided fresh coordinates. I'm passing them along now. Happy hunting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105021" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very good work. I almost wish we could let the Seeds run, and see what happens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done! One must credit Lord Fulminiss with his brilliant design. It's no wonder the Dread Masters wanted the Seeds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105023" id2="17" version="1065353216">You found another Seed--good. It's a shame we're depriving the Republic of their influence, but oh well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105024" id2="17" version="1065353216">You found it. The Dread Masters have gotten more clever about their hiding places.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105025" id2="17" version="1065353216">You found another one. At this rate, we'll have recovered all the Seeds before they've inflicted any lasting damage. Pity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105026" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done it. Those were all the Seeds we had coordinates to find. Don't worry, the fun isn't over yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105028" id2="17" version="1065353216">The traitor has finally revealed the location of the base where the Dread Masters' forces planned their theft on Arcanum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105030" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll transmit the coordinates. Won't the thieves be surprised when you come to pay your respects?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105035" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're entering the thieves' base. Try to keep one alive for questioning, just in case. My traitor is beginning to wear out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105036" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should have known they'd never let you take them alive. How disappointing. No sign of the leader, or the last Seeds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105038" id2="17" version="1065353216">This presents a problem, as my traitor just expired under an especially intense round of interrogation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps the thieves' databanks have information you can use. Search them, and follow whatever leads you find. I'll do some digging on my end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105045" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the last of the Seeds. Your thoroughness has been most admirable. Please bring them all to me right away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use the seeker droid at the coordinates I've provided. As my traitor succumbs to further interrogation, I will transmit updated target lists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105049" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're finally here--good. The situation is growing more dangerous with each passing moment. Do try to keep up with my briefing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105051" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I joined the Dark Council, the Emperor personally selected me to oversee his most treasured storehouse of technology. The facility is called &quot;Arcanum&quot;.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105052" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought I knew all the secrets worth knowing in the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105052" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't heard of this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only a select few have ever learned of Arcanum's existence--and most of them are dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105055" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've taken good care of yourself, for a Dark Council member. I expected another dried-up old Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105055" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] You're beautiful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105056" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a pity that more don't follow my example. Recruitment would be much simpler.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105058" id2="17" version="1065353216">I serve the Emperor, too. His Hand never mentioned your name or this facility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105058" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Wrath is not impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105059" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Wrath receives knowledge on a &quot;need-to-know&quot; basis. Did the Hand not mention that when they snatched you from death?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's assume all that nonsense earned my respect. Get to the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop trying to impress me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105062" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not abide rudeness. Save your posturing for the Grand Moff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105064" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters helped build Arcanum before their imprisonment. Now that they've escaped, they seem to think the facility's contents are theirs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105066" id2="17" version="1065353216">They corrupted one of Arcanum's most important guards, who helped them steal Sith technology known as &quot;the Seeds of Rage&quot;.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105067" id2="17" version="1065353216">What makes these devices so special?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the Seeds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105068" id2="17" version="1065353216">They are the only surviving work of the Empire's greatest Sith alchemist, Lord Fulminiss. A Jedi knight on Voss deprived us of his genius.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105070" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's all they wanted? It sounds like they could have stolen everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105070" id2="17" version="1065353216">And they took nothing else?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105071" id2="17" version="1065353216">A larger raid would have triggered alarms--and we should be grateful they only took the Seeds. Those devices are dangerous enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105073" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are accountable for that facility and everything inside it. Give me one good reason you should live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105073" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have failed the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your energy would be better spent on the threat the Dread Masters have unleashed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105076" id2="17" version="1065353216">You had one job to do. What's the matter, were you busy getting your hair done?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105076" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really blew it, lady.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105077" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't owe you any explanations, hunter. The point is, a terrible danger has been unleashed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105079" id2="17" version="1065353216">When placed near living beings, the Seeds transmit signals that arouse irrational and violent impulses. The effect is slow, insidious and irreversible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105081" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters' agents are burying Seeds across the galaxy, where they will drive entire populations mad. We must recover those devices.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105082" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Seeds are weapons of the Empire. If anyone uses them to sow chaos, it should be us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. They belong to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it done, Acina. You want them in one piece, or lots?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine by me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105084" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bring them back intact. Do not destroy or disassemble them. The Emperor would be most angry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105086" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't take back what you can't find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recover them how?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105087" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've already acquired a means of locating them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105089" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems to me the Empire only benefits if there's more madness and violence in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105089" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the point? Let them go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105090" id2="17" version="1065353216">If left unchecked, the Seeds could inflict untold damage to Imperial interests. I will not permit that on my watch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105092" id2="17" version="1065353216">I captured the traitor who allowed the Dread Masters into Arcanum. My interrogators are slowly encouraging him to reveal the targeted worlds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105094" id2="17" version="1065353216">These specially-modified seeker droids can tunnel through soil, find and extract the Seeds. I would expect to encounter violent resistance from afflicted natives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105095" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone foolish enough to attack the Emperor's Wrath deserves elimination. I will return with the Seeds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105095" id2="17" version="1065353216">They will be swept aside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105096" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's probably best if you don't leave any survivors. The devices' long-term effects remain unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105098" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expect a Dark Council member to understand that nothing in life is free. This is no simple business contract.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105098" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're going to owe me favors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105099" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you succeed, this will mark the beginning of a long and beneficial partnership.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105101" id2="17" version="1065353216">My objectives are the seeds, not pointless combat with madmen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105101" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll never see me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105102" id2="17" version="1065353216">The possibility exists that servants of the Dread Masters may be near the burial sites. If so, I hope you'll announce yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure I'd even take this job if my weapons wouldn't get a workout.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105104" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm counting on a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105105" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you should encounter any servants of the Dread Masters, pass along my regards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to hear I won't need a shovel. How will the droids know when they've found a Seed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105107" id2="17" version="1065353216">The seekers are that good?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105108" id2="17" version="1065353216">The science is... inexact. The droid will dig down, search for unusual objects in the soil and bring up whatever it finds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105110" id2="17" version="1065353216">How powerful are the Seeds? Do I need to take special precautions to avoid being affected by them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1105110" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will the Seeds affect me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105111" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Seeds can be deactivated once they're found. I certainly wouldn't leave them running.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105113" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will receive a seeker and all the coordinates we've extracted from the traitor. I'll remain in contact via transmissions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105115" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find the Seeds and bring them back to me. For the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1105118" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't remember requesting your presence.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
