<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>51</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/bronze/hunting_mandalorians/technician.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296683" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for your help. It's nice to know the Republic and resistance can work together after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296687" id2="17" version="1065353216">The long-range scanners are functioning again. Next time the Imperials try to launch a sneak attack, they'll be in for a shock!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296691" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate to admit it, but the resistance could never have done this alone. Our families are safe for another day because of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296692" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't change the past, but going forward, we have to work together to defeat the true enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296692" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is on your side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296693" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sense you hold resentment for the Republic in your heart. Let it go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296693" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember this in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296694" id2="17" version="1065353216">You Jedi are pretty perceptive. I've got a lot of bitterness stored up. It's not going to disappear overnight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296696" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the Republic abandoned you before, but we're all on the same side now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296696" id2="17" version="1065353216">See? We can work together.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296697" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right. This doesn't come easy for me. A lot of hard feelings and bad memories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296699" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need the Republic, and they need you. Keep clinging to the past, and it'll only drag you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296699" id2="17" version="1065353216">See? We can all play nice.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296700" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's good advice. I can't promise things will change overnight--old habits are hard to break.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't mention it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296703" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't spend gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296704" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess you deserve something for your efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296706" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be sure to tell everyone how the Republic stepped up when it counted. Good luck out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296712" id2="17" version="1065353216">You got those scanners repaired yet?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296718" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surprised to see a Jedi down here. Figured your type was always busy with bigger, more important things.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, well. The captain of Havoc Squad. If you're looking for the last of the Imps, you're in the right place.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296722" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must be that Republic hire I've been hearing about. Some kind of special agent problem solver, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296724" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fighting the Imps is bad enough, but dealing with Mandalorians too? I don't know how much more of this I can take.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296725" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know things are tough, but you can't give up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296725" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hang in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296726" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no quitter. I'm just tired. The resistance was battling the Empire long before you got here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296728" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm tired of everyone on Balmorra moaning about how hard you've had it. Things are tough all over!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quit whining.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody had it as bad as us! When the Republic left Balmorra, the resistance kept fighting the Empire without any support!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296731" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me the details.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296732" id2="17" version="1065353216">For years, we've given the Imperials all they could handle, and now they want payback-- only it's our families paying the price.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296734" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Mandalorians disabled several of our long-range scanners. Without them, we have no warning of incoming Imperial attacks!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296735" id2="17" version="1065353216">How badly are the scanners damaged?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296735" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can they be repaired?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296736" id2="17" version="1065353216">The problem isn't repairing them--it's getting past the Mandalorians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="296738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fighting the Mandalorians isn't like fighting the Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296738" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're in over your head.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296739" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296741" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't need my help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Easier said than done. We can handle the Imperials. But these Mandos are something else....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296744" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're still camped out near the sensors. They ambush anyone who tries to repair them. I've lost two teams to them already.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those long-range scanners are the only thing keeping us ahead of the Empire. They need to be fixed, Mandalorians or not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296747" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Mandos won't be a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296748" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess I can help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296749" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate it. I know I'm a little rough on you Republic types, but this is something the resistance just can't do.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come back to me after you repair all the scanners. And watch out for the Mandos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="296753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Figured as much. We'll figure out a way to handle this on our own... as usual.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="296758" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not in the mood to chat.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="771630" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imps are doing more than enough damage on their own, but they went the extra mile and hired Mandalorian mercenaries too.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="771632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rond Berrin, Balmorran resistance. Soon-to-be dead man too, if the Empire and their goons keep pounding us like this.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
