<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/class/sith_warrior/darth_baras.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671507" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, I am docked at the space station above Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very good. Now that Admiral Monk and the War Trust have fallen to your might, all that remains is Jedi Knight Xerender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Xerender has dedicated himself to the Republic like no other, he's led our enemies to many cunning victories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671512" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not only is he a symbol of inspiration for the Republic, he's been a thorn in my side for a long time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671513" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will bury him in the snow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="671513" id2="17" version="1065353216">He won't leave alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know what he's trying to achieve here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="671514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is he on Hoth?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is he a legitimate target for Plan Zero, or is this just a vendetta?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="671515" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is personal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why can't it be both? The satisfaction will be compounded when he is no more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671518" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Chiss traitor you spared confirmed Xerender's presence and has since informed me that the Jedi is seeking a secret superweapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intelligence reports suggest that he has brought his troop of elite special ops to seek a secret superweapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671522" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can uncover no information about this weapon, only that it was lost in the wreckage of one of the crashed star ships from the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once I stop Xerender, whatever he's after will be inconsequential.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="671523" id2="17" version="1065353216">The weapon doesn't matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Xerender isn't one to waste time on anything less than a critical mission. His death is the primary goal, but I want to know what he seeks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe we can use the Republic's toy against them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="671526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should I get the weapon?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps. If Xerender wants it, it must be very powerful. His death is the goal, but if the weapon can be salvaged, all the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671529" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's very little to go on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="671529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not much help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Xerender is a shrewd target--we're fortunate to have this much insight. Killing him is paramount--if you discover the superweapon, all the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your contact on the surface is Commander Lanklyn. He's been tracking Xerender and should be ready to meet you at the Imperial Base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671534" id2="17" version="1065353216">The commander occasionally bites off more than he can chew. But he's been warned that this mission cannot afford anything less than perfection.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Xerender is the last of your targets. Report to me when you know the nature of the superweapon he seeks. Get this right, apprentice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hoth. Back in the day, I managed to escape assignment here. It chills my bones just to be in orbit above this frigid planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uhm, yeah, you should (cough) leave me on the ship. I'm (cough)... I think I'm fighting off a cold (cough-cough).</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget those cowards, my lord. A little snow won't stop me. I'm ready for action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671544" id2="17" version="1065353216">I too would gladly accompany you on this mission, my lord. I wish to see all the galaxy has to offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671545" id2="17" version="1065353216">The soldier mirrors my attitude, master. I want to consume every experience I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671552" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will continue to search for Admiral Monk. Report back when you have learned the nature of the superweapon Xerender seeks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671554" id2="17" version="1065353216">And why is that? I specifically directed you to stop the siege of Darth Vengean's flagship and kill Admiral Monk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Monk has come out of his hole. This will be our only opportunity to destroy him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671558" id2="17" version="1065353216">Head to the conflict in space immediately!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671560" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very good. My efforts to locate Admiral Monk, the missing Republic leader, are ongoing. Your target on this planet is Jedi Knight Xerender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671568" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, I wish to see all the galaxy has to offer. I will happily join you on Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="671569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cold won't stop me. Let them sit on their hands here on the ship. I'm hungry for any experience I can get.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
