<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>36</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/bronze/trouble_in_deed/luran_gonthor.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689388" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to your troubles, Gonthor Industries will reopen... just as soon as those Justicars cool off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689390" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sure had the deed locked up tight. Here it is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fantastic! Now I get a lawyer, embarrass the Senate if I have to, and Gonthor Industries will be back up in no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once business kicks in, I'll do everything I can to help the Republic clean this place up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689397" id2="17" version="1065353216">The deed's locked up. If you're looking for an access code to reach it, check that security card I gave ya.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689400" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi. Thank the Force. Hope I can convince you to help an old man out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689402" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, Lieutenant. No one enforces justice like the Republic's finest, am I right? 'Course I am.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689404" id2="17" version="1065353216">You look strong, armed for a fight. Maybe I can interest you in restoring some law and order down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Name's Luran Gonthor, president of Gonthor Industries. Finest custom metalwork on Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689408" id2="17" version="1065353216">Least we used to be before the Sacking. Once the attack began, I went off the grid, lost my connection to the upper levels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Took elbow grease to stay afloat. Did well until those Justicars arrived. They took over my shop and kicked me into the street!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689411" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Justicars will corrupt this whole area if someone doesn't stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689411" id2="17" version="1065353216">Order must be restored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689412" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you'd understand, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689414" id2="17" version="1065353216">Justicars give the Republic a bad name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689414" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're brutes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you can show 'em how a real patriot fights.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give any idiot a blaster, they're bound to cause some trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Justicars are bad news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689418" id2="17" version="1065353216">Idiots, you got that right. Maybe you could help sort 'em out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689420" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry you had to endure their bullying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689420" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's terrible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689421" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll survive. My company's another story, but it's salvageable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689423" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think Justicars concern me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689424" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senate and such won't help; they don't want to face the Justicars. Also, they say they've got no record that it's my shop.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course those records are long gone, blown away during the Sacking of Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only proof I have now is the deed--and that's inside my old shop. If you get it, I can force the Senate to push the Justicars out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689429" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your company will be back on its feet in no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689429" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get your deed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to hear it! You'll always have a friend in Gonthor Industries!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689432" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the deed worth to you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689433" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm worth more than a few credits. Help me, and I help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's my personal security card. It's got an access code that will get you inside my vault. Once you're in, grab the deed and run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689437" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689438" id2="17" version="1065353216">They said I show my face near Gonthor Industries, I get disappeared. No way I'm going back--it's over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689440" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody kicks me out of my place of business and gets away with it.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
