<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>80</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/ilum/world/republic/the_last_battle/gentlemans_agreement/master_boudyn.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="450817" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you waiting for, Jiyan? The Imperials lost too many troops in the raid. We have the advantage! We need to storm the temple!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450819" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we storm the temple, Darth Arho might kill the supreme commander. We lost Commander Jub in the attack; we can't afford to lose Rans, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="450821" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree. Commander Rans is our best strategist, and a hero to the troops. We have to find a way to save him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Storming the temple is too risky. But maybe I can sneak my team inside without Arho finding out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad can get him back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="450823" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are no true warrior. Stealth and secrecy are the weapons of smugglers and thieves!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like another impossible mission for yours truly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Am I about to be volunteered?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="450825" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should be looking to warriors and soldiers to save him, not smugglers and thieves!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arho will be guarding against a direct assault, but I could sneak into the temple without him knowing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me go; I'll get Rans back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="450827" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought the Jedi Knights were warriors. Why do you want us to sneak around like smugglers and thieves?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where armies fail, a small group may succeed. It might be possible to infiltrate the temple and rescue Rans without alerting Arho.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450828" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must trust in the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="450829" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the problem with Jedi. Compromise and half-measures. A real warrior doesn't need to sneak around like some kind of smuggler or thief!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, you giant hair ball. I'm standing right here. Downwind. Big mistake on my part.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450830" id2="17" version="1065353216">That Wookiee just insulted me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450831" id2="17" version="1065353216">We all serve the cause in our own way, Caroowar. We must remember this if we hope to... wait. What was that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Smashing your head against a problem isn't the only way to solve it. Sometimes you need a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450833" id2="17" version="1065353216">A good warrior is smart, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450834" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must remain calm, Caroowar. Remember: There is no emotion, only peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450834" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't turn on each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="450835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't throw the Jedi Code in my face! Words will not save... wait. What was that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jiyan Dar is in charge now that Rans is gone. We follow his orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Respect the chain of command!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="450838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. You're right. I'm sorry. My temper sometimes... wait. What was that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450840" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must have friends in high places, Caroowar. I don't know how else a moron made commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are all Wookiees this stupid?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop this! If we turn against each other we'll never... wait. What was that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hit the temple with everything we've got. Arho won't stand a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450843" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Wookiee's right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450844" id2="17" version="1065353216">No! The risk to Commander Rans is too great. We have to... wait. What was that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do you think the Imperials captured Rans instead of killing him? They knew it would turn you against each other!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arguing is what Arho wants.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450847" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right, we must remain calm. There is no emotion, only peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="450849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meditation won't stop Arho. And it won't save... wait. What's that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rans is worm food. Better to accept it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget it. He's dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450852" id2="17" version="1065353216">He would not be so quick to abandon you! Maybe you should think about--</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="450854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Incoming holotransmission. Urgent priority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450856" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, Republic Commanders. My name is Darth Malgus. Time is short, so I will be blunt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450858" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been providing Supreme Commander Rans information to help him defeat Darth Arho. I'm here to offer you the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me guess: Arho's one of your main rivals within the Empire, so you're using the Republic to eliminate him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450859" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were working with Rans?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450860" id2="17" version="1065353216">More or less. The war is over. The Republic won. If we keep fighting, you will destroy us. I accept this. Darth Arho does not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450862" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were in charge of the prison where they were holding Revan! You tried to kill me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450862" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remember you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Much has changed since we last met. The Empire is in disarray. The war is over. You won.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450865" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we continue to fight, you will destroy us. I have accepted our new place in the galaxy. Darth Arho has not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why should I trust a Sith?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why should we trust a Sith?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450869" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a pragmatist. I know we lost the war. If we continue to fight, you will destroy us. I accept that. Arho does not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450871" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's a member of the Dark Council, but he's a thug. The Council needs someone more... progressive... if the Empire hopes to survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450873" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone like you, I suppose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450875" id2="17" version="1065353216">Openly opposing Arho would draw the wrath of the Dark Council. But by helping you eliminate him, we both get what we want.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell us how you're going to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Works for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450877" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a Sith. You use lies and deception to get what you want.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450877" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't believe you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450878" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm only here to provide information. Whether you choose to use it is up to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450880" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's true, then maybe we don't want Arho off the Dark Council. He's doing more damage than we ever could.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like Arho's helping us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450881" id2="17" version="1065353216">True. But how many lives will he throw away in war before his inevitable fall? Together we can stop this bloodshed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="450883" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about Commander Rans? What happened to him? Is he still alive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450885" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're holding him in a secret POW camp. The perimeter is ringed with droid-defended security towers. Any breach will set off the alarm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450887" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have one minute, Malgus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arho suspects Rans is working with someone on the Imperial side. Obviously, I'm eager to keep my role in all this quiet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450890" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're holding your Supreme Commander in a secret POW camp. Droid-defended security towers ring the perimeter. Any breach will trigger the alarm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450892" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm transmitting the location of the camp and the codes to disable the tower alarms. Use them as you see fit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450895" id2="17" version="1065353216">This could be a trap, but I think it's worth the risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450895" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to use those codes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="450896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be a fool! Malgus and Arho are working together. They set this whole thing up to lure us into an ambush!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are we really going to trust a Sith Lord?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450898" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure what to think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="450899" id2="17" version="1065353216">This won't end well.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="450900" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we know anything about the Sith, it's that they're always at each other's throats.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450902" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can trust Malgus for one reason: He's acting out of self-interest. He hates Darth Arho more than he hates us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="450904" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll send troops out to strike at key Imperial targets. That should draw most of Arho's troops away from the prison camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="450906" id2="17" version="1065353216">You head to the camp and use the codes to neutralize the defense towers on the perimeter. Once they're down, infiltrate the camp and get Rans out of there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="450911" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't keep Rans alive forever. Go take out the towers on the prison camp's perimeter.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
