<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>123</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x3/hk_51/imperial/the_legacy_of_hk/general_avrun.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669502" id2="17" version="1065353216">I saw one of the HK units follow you out. The sooner they're all recovered, the sooner I can go home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before Hoth, I was stationed on Dromund Kaas. Climate controlled and civilized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669505" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your records, General. Now at least the mystery is solved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669506" id2="17" version="1065353216">You work well together. I sent three squads in, and they crumpled like a house of pazaak cards. Let's hope it was worth something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, my lord. Many an Imperial will sleep easier tonight. Everything looks to be in order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent! The moment I saw you, I knew you could be relied on. Let's see what all the fuss was about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669514" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never heard of these HK droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669514" id2="17" version="1065353216">HK droids?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669518" id2="17" version="1065353216">With one HK droid, the Empire could make fast work of a troublesome Jedi or Republic leader. With an army, we would be unstoppable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like the HKs and I were meant to find each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669534" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sense things will work out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669535" id2="17" version="1065353216">I enjoy discovering new toys.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669535" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will be fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669536" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find a way to make it pay off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669549" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Fatality's cargo is top secret. Just imagine what kind of weapon might be down there....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669550" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's about time! I requested a heat source and a medic hours ago. Unless you're dying or dead, I--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669552" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not my reinforcements. Apologies. If you'd been through what we have, you'd be a little jumpy, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Same cold, same ice. Notice us not complaining.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speak for yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669557" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and your squad of scarecrows don't look worth attacking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669557" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not much of a target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669558" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're lucky to be alive. Half my men are at the bottom of that wreck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669565" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm armed and in a lot better shape than you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669565" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't mean I can't help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669571" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll put you out of your misery, if you like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop whining, or else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669572" id2="17" version="1065353216">That won't be necessary. I'd like to live to see what's so special about a crashed ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669574" id2="17" version="1065353216">High Command believes the Fatality's cargo is so important, they won't even tell me what it is. I'm just supposed to find it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669588" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Fatality's classified records will tell us what the cargo is. I don't suppose...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cargo worth dying for? This I have to see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. You've intrigued me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="669595" id2="17" version="1065353216">No chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="669596" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you reach an Imperial outpost, send reinforcements our way. Or at least a medic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dread Master legions... only thing worse than this cold....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027719" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord! I didn't recognize you. We're wounded, freezing and warding off attacks from the Dread Masters' forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, you can't be my reinforcements. Imperial Intelligence is disbanded... isn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027721" id2="17" version="1065353216">No... this isn't right. They wouldn't send a bounty hunter to aid us. Not even a Great Hunt Grand Champion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Point taken. I guarantee you'll be compensated for any assistance you provide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027725" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's on a need-to-know basis, General. The point is, I'm here--and curious why you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027725" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your question is irrelevant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027727" id2="17" version="1065353216">My mission is to reclaim a death trap. It's going about as well as you'd expect.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1027732" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me your mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027735" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll warn you in advance: my intel is far from complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Years ago, when the Dread Masters were first imprisoned here, one of their apprentices stole the Imperial destroyer &quot;Fatality.&quot; We never learned why.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027738" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Fatality was believed lost--until we discovered the Dread Masters excavating its wreck from the ice here. High Command sent me to recover the vessel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027739" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did a ship lost decades ago crash on a Republic prison planet we only recently learned existed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027739" id2="17" version="1065353216">It shouldn't be on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027740" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a lot of wasted resources. What's so special about the Fatality?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027740" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the point?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027741" id2="17" version="1065353216">There must be something very special aboard the Fatality if the Dread Masters are throwing forces at it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027741" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters have a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most likely, the Dread Masters' apprentice was attempting to free them on his own. Apparently, he almost succeeded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently the answer is above my rank.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027749" id2="17" version="1065353216">The elements feel a bit harsher after you've barely escaped the Dread Masters' forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027752" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we weren't prepared for the savages inside that vessel. The Dread Master legions are led by a Houk. He keeps our dead as frozen trophies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then consider acquiring the information a favor--one for which you'll be well-compensated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027755" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll hold this position. Enter the Fatality, eliminate the enemy forces and their Houk leader, then find out what's inside that ship. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027756" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters and their servants will learn the price of betraying the Empire. Give me coordinates to the Fatality--I'll handle this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not for long--I'm going in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027757" id2="17" version="1065353216">While you're in there, access the Fatality's classified records. That should clear up this little mystery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027759" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're more than welcome to express my embarrassment to that giant Houk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Getting inside the ship is easy. It's killing everyone there that's giving us trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027766" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can find a technician to reactivate the droids, but we'll need detailed schematics and suitable repair parts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027767" id2="17" version="1065353216">That seems only fair--and blast High Command if it disagrees.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027769" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just imagine what our enemy could do with them now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027769" id2="17" version="1065353216">They sound dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027772" id2="17" version="1065353216">No wonder that apprentice stole the Fatality all those years ago. He could've easily freed the Dread Masters with HK droids for his army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027773" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters must never be allowed to possess those droids--but destroying them is not an option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027774" id2="17" version="1065353216">It doesn't look like they ever got to leave the ship. What do you think happened?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027774" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did they fail?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clearly, Republic forces shot down the Fatality when it arrived at Belsavis. Why they never recovered the wreck remains a mystery--but no matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Incredible! The Fatality was crewed with fully-functioning HK droids! I'd heard rumors of a project decades back, but never imagined it was real.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027781" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll never find a more lethal assassin. A functioning HK hasn't been seen in the galaxy for centuries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027783" id2="17" version="1065353216">Records indicate the droids were all damaged and deactivated in the crash. To fix them, we need spare parts that may not even exist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027784" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not giving up yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027785" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I were to acquire these nonexistent parts, I'd expect one of those droids as payment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me one, and I'll help.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1027786" id2="17" version="1065353216">There must be a way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027787" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're telling me I just fought my way through that vessel for nothing, the Dread Masters will be the least of your worries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027787" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've wasted my time, fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Czerka Corporation created the HK droids. One of their laboratory archives might contain a complete set of schematics. Not much, but it's a start.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027790" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've accomplished more with less.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027790" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's all I need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our odds of success go up if we work together to find these things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you planning to help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027792" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep an eye on the Fatality. I don't want the Dread Masters or Republic forces getting in while I'm gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027792" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay here and guard the wreck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027793" id2="17" version="1065353216">High Command said the same. We'll do our best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027796" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a place you could look that won't involve any negotiations with Czerka. Try there first--and good luck!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027797" id2="17" version="1065353216">My orders are to keep the Fatality under constant surveillance. Believe me, I'd much rather go with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027799" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still have no medic or heat source--but better cold and alive than executed for my failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027800" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found everything we need to repair those HK droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Brilliant! And I have a chief engineer on standby. He's a bit twitchy, but knows his way around a droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027806" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll send him in behind you to repair one of the HKs, but I'm afraid a new problem has cropped up in your absence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dread Master forces have once again taken over the Fatality. Their leader is a powerful Sith calling himself the Lord of Agony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027810" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no Sith more powerful than the Emperor's Wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027810" id2="17" version="1065353216">He is mistaken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027811" id2="17" version="1065353216">That fool is about to learn the true meaning of agony--in excruciating detail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027811" id2="17" version="1065353216">He shouldn't have crossed me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027812" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that Sith is as stupid as his fancy title, I'll enjoy torching him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027812" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a dumb name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027813" id2="17" version="1065353216">They know we have what's needed to reactivate the droids. They're hoping to take it from our corpses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027813" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy is cunning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027814" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the droids were stolen by the Dread Masters' apprentice, will they attack us once they're reactivated?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027814" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm more worried about the HK.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your only job was to secure that crash site until I returned!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027815" id2="17" version="1065353216">You failed again!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027817" id2="17" version="1065353216">I lost almost a hundred men to that Sith and his followers. We're not equipped to fight anyone like him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027819" id2="17" version="1065353216">My chief engineer is awaiting word that you've retaken the Fatality. He'll meet you inside when all enemy forces are dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027821" id2="17" version="1065353216">According to the records you recovered, none of the HK units were reprogrammed. They remain loyal Imperial servants. Still... be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027824" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trust you won't permit them that convenience.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed. The Fatality could use some flames to brighten up the place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027828" id2="17" version="1065353216">I regret I won't be present to witness the lesson.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027830" id2="17" version="1065353216">I tried explaining that to him, but he's not what one would call a brilliant conversationalist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give him everything you've acquired, and he'll repair the HK droid for you. Best of luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing we can do for the dead, but I'd prefer to keep living. I can't do that if the mission fails.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't expect me to shed tears for your men. Dying is what soldiers are for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027915" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no sympathy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027916" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're telling me the Empire's best soldiers can't take down a single Houk?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027916" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's just another alien brute.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027917" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care about the cargo--I want that Houk scum dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027917" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just in it for the fight.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
