<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>36</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x3/hk_51/imperial/the_legacy_of_hk/hk_51.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Declaration: Self-diagnostics complete. Assassination protocols active. All systems go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701458" id2="17" version="1065353216">Salutation: Greetings, master. I am HK-51. I am armed, operational and at your command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701459" id2="17" version="1065353216">You belong to me now, droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701459" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am your master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Acknowledgment: I had assumed so, master. You are the only organic here who is not frozen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Summation: I can liquidate any undesirable organic with extreme prejudice. You have only to ask, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dismissal: We have identical chassis, but that is where the similarities end, master. The HK-47 was flawed and volatile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701469" id2="17" version="1065353216">The HK-51 series is a far more efficient model. You will not find a more lethal or reliable assassin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admission: I am optimized for combat. I hope you are not an organic who favors negotiation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701472" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I missed that part of Sith training.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I look like one?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Approval: I have always favored an Imperial education, master. Pacifism is inefficient.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701475" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer the art of manipulation, but when that fails, I'm open to alternatives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701475" id2="17" version="1065353216">I dabble, sometimes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Encouragement: I can provide many alternatives, master. Extreme brutality is my specialty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701478" id2="17" version="1065353216">People do what I say or they die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only if it involves a blaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assertion: I am pleased to hear that, master. My intimidation protocols are always at your disposal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701481" id2="17" version="1065353216">I favor direct methods when dealing with problems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701481" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not really.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Offer: If you prefer to shoot first and ask questions later, master, I am always happy to assist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701484" id2="17" version="1065353216">The word you're looking for is &quot;master.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't call me an &quot;organic.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Retraction: My mistake, master. I forget not all organics appreciate such terminology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701487" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do as I see fit. Complain, and you're scrap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="701487" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll listen anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reassurance: I do not object to conversation, master. I simply prefer the one-sided variety.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="701490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Information: I will locate your starship and familiarize myself with your crew. If I detect any hint of mutiny, I will notify you immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="701496" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This HK unit has been deactivated for quite some time. It will not respond to commands.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027919" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you any relation to the assassin droid HK-47?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027919" id2="17" version="1065353216">You look familiar.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027921" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you can do more for me than just talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1027921" id2="17" version="1065353216">List your functions. droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1030921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chief Engineer Vool'attar, reporting for duty. Thank you for securing the vessel, my lord. I'll take those parts and commence work immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1030922" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Chief Engineer Vool'attar. General Avrun sent me. Thank you for securing the vessel. I'll take those parts and get to work immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1030927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ahh!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
