<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>69</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/sith_sorcerer/chapter_2/intro/darth_thanaton.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638464" id2="17" version="1065353216">You truly are relentless. I can see now why Zash chose you. But this has carried on long enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, you've come prepared. By now, I should have expected it of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Astonishing. I didn't expect one as reckless as you to have prepared such a defense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately for you, I am older and wiser and studied in rituals you can't even imagine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638476" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have business on Malachor Three. Prepare my ship, and see that this one gets a respectful cremation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638478" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have business on Malachor Three. Prepare my ship, and dispose of this mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638482" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, you're awake!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638484" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to hurry out of here. If Thanaton finds out you're still alive, we're all in trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which one are you again?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="638485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638488" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm your apprentice, Kaal. We need to get back to the ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638489" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happened to me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="638489" id2="17" version="1065353216">My head hurts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanaton tried to kill you. Look, I'll explain when we get back to the ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let Thanaton find me. I'll kill him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="638493" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638494" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think you have the strength for that yet my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get back to the ship with the others. We can figure out what to do from there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638502" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. You've put me in a difficult position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638504" id2="17" version="1065353216">When Zash disobeyed me and had Skotia killed, tradition demanded that she be killed and her power base destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638506" id2="17" version="1065353216">Believe me when I say I wish that you had stayed in that tomb. It will pain me to watch you die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget tradition. &quot;The Force shall free me.&quot; Isn't that the idea?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="638507" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have to do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without these traditions, the Sith would be so awash in their own blood they couldn't see their enemies taking aim.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638509" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't understand. I didn't do anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="638509" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I'm innocent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your master openly defied me, and I cannot risk you following in her footsteps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spare me the false tears. I'm ready to fight you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="638511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't pretend to be hurt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638512" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are entitled to defend yourself; in fact, I'd expect nothing less.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638514" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force welcome you with open arms. Kill her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638516" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force welcome you with open arms. Kill him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for meeting me here. Respect for her superiors is the mark of a good Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for meeting me here. Respect for his superiors is the mark of a good Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, Zash would've disagreed, did disagree with me passionately on that point. But then, Zash never respected tradition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638525" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's wise to respect your superiors, at least until you're powerful enough to kill them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="638525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Respect until you can strike.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638526" id2="17" version="1065353216">A wise answer. You are not like your master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you call me here just to talk philosophy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="638528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Boring.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Philosophy gives structure to the delicately ordered chaos of our Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Being Sith is about being free, not blindly following an arbitrary set of rules.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="638531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why should she?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful. That attitude may get you in trouble some day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tradition. Principles. History. The threads that compose our society. Zash refused to acknowledge how one little tug could ruin the whole tapestry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your work was sloppy, brazen even, but the news of her murder was sweet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638537" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would hate for my actions to disappoint you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="638537" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad it pleased.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638538" id2="17" version="1065353216">I only hope that next time you'll be a little less obvious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638540" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't want to kill her. It was self-defense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="638540" id2="17" version="1065353216">She attacked me first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nonsense. Every apprentice wants to kill their master. It's not a fault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638543" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did my best to clean up the bloodstains.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="638543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Murder is messy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638544" id2="17" version="1065353216">I speak in all seriousness. Too many people saw you enter the Dark Temple. I trust you'll be more careful in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nevertheless, we're here to talk about you, not Zash. You have demonstrated remarkable ability.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Though I am a stricter master than Zash, I think you'll find that to loyal followers of our traditions, I am not ungenerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I will do my best not to disappoint you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="638549" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope I can please you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638550" id2="17" version="1065353216">In that case, I think we will have a very fruitful relationship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638552" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, if I agree to  your every whim, you might not kill me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="638552" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want minions, not Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suspicion can be a form of wisdom, as long as it doesn't lead to disrespect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638555" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the Sith Code. Is there something else I'm supposed to know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="638555" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean, loyal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638556" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith Code is only the start. You must study the history of the Sith, make it your own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638558" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, I wish to see how you work. This tomb belonged to Darth Andru, Sith scholar and alchemist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="638560" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm interested in his last writings, which were buried with him. Recover them for me, and we will discuss your place in my power structure.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
