<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>198</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/class/smuggler/master_sumalee.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520510" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm heading for the Voidwolf's flagship now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520511" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the only good news I've heard in weeks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send me the coordinates, and I'll try to get you backup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520514" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was kind of hoping for &quot;The Republic will take it from here.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520514" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll &quot;try&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520515" id2="17" version="1065353216">And in the meantime, full speed ahead?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520515" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you want me to do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520516" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got over a hundred major offensives around the galaxy, Captain. If you wait until we've got troops free, it'll be too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520518" id2="17" version="1065353216">This one is yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520520" id2="17" version="1065353216">After what he did to me, I'll take the Voidwolf down myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520520" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need backup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520521" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds a lot like revenge, Captain. You may not want to say that to a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shh. Jedi don't like r-e-v-e-n-g-e.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="520525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your gun. My hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't your Jedi tell people that revenge leads to the dark side?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520529" id2="17" version="1065353216">See, that's the kind of thing I always got wrong in my Jedi trials....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop the Voidwolf, Captain, and the Republic will recognize you as one of its greatest heroes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520533" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I will deal with anyone who questions your methods.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520535" id2="17" version="1065353216">The SIS tells me there is no way Councillor Caicos could have left that house.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520536" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're still recovering from Coruscant. If the Voidwolf strikes our shipyards, it'll cripple the navy. They could invade the Core Worlds!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520538" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need to find out where the Voidwolf is now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any idea where a certain corrupt Corellian councillor may be hiding?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dodonna said to find Caicos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520542" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm yours to command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Define &quot;need.&quot; I need money....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this a paying job?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. The Republic has already approved an award for apprehending Darmas and Dodonna.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. Let me transfer your reward for apprehending Senator Dodonna.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. Let me transfer your reward for apprehending Darmas Pollaran.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. It's unfortunate neither Darmas nor Dodonna survived for you to collect on those rewards. But here's a small honorarium for what you found.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520552" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dodonna indicated that Councillor Caicos is the only one on Corellia who has in-person contact with the Voidwolf.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520554" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seems from your transmission that Councillor Caicos is one of the few people who has in-person contact with the Voidwolf.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520556" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should be able to get coordinates for the Voidwolf's flagship from him, maybe even piggyback onto the next rendezvous they've planned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520557" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you talking about face-to-face or poking around in his underwear drawer when he's not home?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520557" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confront him or sneak around?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520558" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, he's home. The whole Corellian council has been holed up since the news came out of their betrayal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520560" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can even give you the SIS file on his residence, but you'll need to find your own way in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know where I can find Caicos?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where should I go?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520563" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Caicos tries to get between me and the Voidwolf, he's going down too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing will stop me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520564" id2="17" version="1065353216">The SIS has files on the entire Corellian council. I can send you the address and security specs for Caicos's residence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520566" id2="17" version="1065353216">But he was paranoid even before the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520568" id2="17" version="1065353216">The entire perimeter of his estate is lined with cameras and sensors. You'll have to destroy them all to get in unnoticed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything else, oh Mistress of Breaking and Entering?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520569" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know a lot for a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520570" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's just assume that anything Risha knows how to do, I know how to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful he doesn't take that the wrong way, Sumalee.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520574" id2="17" version="1065353216">The captain's still trying to figure me out, Sumalee.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520576" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not like most Jedi, are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="520578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Haha!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520580" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're very open-minded. For a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where were you when I was at the Jedi Academy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520585" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't think he'll be worried if all his cameras die at once?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520585" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's &quot;unnoticed&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520586" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least he won't be able to tell the Voidwolf it's you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you're past the perimeter, every entrance is equipped with neural scanners that only admit certain brainwave signatures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520590" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're not with someone authorized, the house will fry you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520591" id2="17" version="1065353216">The scanners won't notice if the authorized user has a blaster to the forehead, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520591" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get a guard to let me in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520592" id2="17" version="1065353216">As long as you don't pull the trigger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520594" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been full of surprising ideas. Got any for this one?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any suggestions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never been killed by a home security system yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520595" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not worried.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520596" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is military-spec hardware. Don't taunt it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps you could... gently persuade... one of his guards to accompany you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any further discussion might leave me ethically compromised.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520602" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck, Captain. Call me before you take on the Voidwolf; that's not something you should do alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520605" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voidwolf has his own fleet, and he's going after Republic shipyards!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520606" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's exactly what Dodonna just confirmed. She begged me to send you against the Voidwolf personally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520608" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you--? You found Dodonna? Did she give you anything?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520610" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need recordings, written communications-- wait! Is this Dodonna and the Voidwolf talking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clear the tunnels. Curske will meet you at the entrance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520615" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll send back the coordinates for one of our safe houses. Make sure no one is following, then meet me there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520617" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know what the Republic would do without you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darmas is dead. I have his file on Dodonna.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520621" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am going to preserve our good working relationship by assuming he shot first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520623" id2="17" version="1065353216">I turned Darmas over to the Republic forces. I have his dossier on Dodonna.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. I'll have him kept under guard, in isolation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520626" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have Darmas's evidence against Dodonna.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520627" id2="17" version="1065353216">This line is secure. Transmit anything he gave you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Draw out the Imperial troops. I will make sure you're covered going in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520630" id2="17" version="1065353216">Caicos was one of the councillors who opened the doors to the Empire. Imperial troops are using his factory as a field hospital.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I should send Darmas some flowers....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520631" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think they fled there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520632" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they're turning our droids against us, why hasn't the Republic cut them off?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520632" id2="17" version="1065353216">An easy target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520633" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not part of your army. I'm just after Darmas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who cares?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520634" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Darmas Pollaran retreated with the Imperial troops, that's where he'll be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520636" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been trying to blow through the Caicos factory, but they've got it surrounded like you wouldn't believe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520638" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've planted a doctor on the inside, but he hasn't found any weakness in their defense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520639" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's got to be an access point. Sewage pipe? Medical waste shipment?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520639" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find a way in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520640" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's soldiers out and casualties back in. Nothing else with a heartbeat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520642" id2="17" version="1065353216">But if we convince them they're under attack... enough to send all their forces out at once....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520644" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there's too many soldiers inside, they just need a good reason to come out....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520644" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can draw out their troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stage a big enough attack and no one will notice one man sneaking in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have enough men to cover the captain while he goes in?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="520649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attack and they will defend their base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial troops are predictable. The whole unit will rush to a point of attack. They don't hold back reserves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520653" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. No way. I'm not being bait. Not this time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520655" id2="17" version="1065353216">A clever plan, but we don't have the manpower for a large-scale attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520657" id2="17" version="1065353216">What should we do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520658" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to make the Imperials believe we have more troops than we do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520660" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you draw them out with staged attacks at multiple locations, we can keep them occupied with hit-and-run tactics. There's minimal risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then our doctor can sneak you in to the factory to find Darmas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520663" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want me to target specific locations, or should I just wander around taking pot shots?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me where to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520664" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm confused.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520665" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll mark the locations where you need to stage attacks. Once you draw enough Imperial troops out of the factory, you can go in and find Darmas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our men will hold their attention while you rendezvous with Doctor Shi Bata.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who is this guy? How's he going to get me inside?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we trust this doctor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Shi Bata. He's a medic for CorSec. His wife died in the Imperial attack. You can trust him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520672" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll tell him to meet you at the triage station. He can sneak you in along with the Imperial wounded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough Corellians are fighting with the Empire that you shouldn't draw immediate attention. Call me when you reach Darmas Pollaran.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks as if you did need some additional support.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520680" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darmas got away. He's fled back to his Imperial masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520682" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nevis Kitt, CorSec. Uh, sorry about that misunderstanding....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520684" id2="17" version="1065353216">These aren't Imperial droids, they're local models. Councillor Caicos's factory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry. The Empire must not encroach on this sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darmas seems to have hooked up with some rebel leader named Nevis Kitt. They're trying to blow open, uh, supply tunnel 26...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darmas ingratiated himself quickly, then. Nevis Kitt used to be a captain in CorSec, the Corellian police force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now he leads our fiercest squadron of guerilla defenders.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="520693" id2="17" version="1065353216">But to open supply tunnel 26... that is lunacy. It's sabotage; it's treachery piled on treason. Clearing the tunnel gives the Imperials a path straight to our hearts!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is this tunnel so important?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520694" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's supply tunnel 26?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520695" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never got the whole story--what are we trying to do on Corellia and what's happened so far?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520695" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me some background.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="520696" id2="17" version="1065353216">It has always been our quirk, that the Corellian council sells votes and takes bribes. But we believed them to have our best interests at heart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520698" id2="17" version="1065353216">The councillors sold Corellia to the Empire, never expecting the citizens to rebel.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="520700" id2="17" version="1065353216">But supply tunnel 26 is at the heart of the Red Light Sector. If Darmas Pollaran opens it, we could lose the ground it cost so many lives to take.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520702" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's working with your rebels! Against the Empire! Why are you determined to believe the worst of him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darmas is trying to help!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520703" id2="17" version="1065353216">He must be working with Nevis Kitt to undermine Corellia's defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520703" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's Darmas's plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="520704" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Selonian tunnel network is a labyrinth that connects the underside of every city on the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="520706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Supply tunnel 26 is the main artery into what the humans call the &quot;Red Light Sector.&quot; It cost many lives to block it so we could claim that ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520708" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to keep that tunnel sealed. The Red Light Sector's one of our only safe zones.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520709" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll talk to Darmas. He wouldn't do this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520709" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's all a misunderstanding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520710" id2="17" version="1065353216">If he agrees to turn Dodonna in, I will offer my apology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520712" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell him that opening this tunnel only serves the Empire. Perhaps he will yet surprise us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's show these Corellians the true face of Darmas Pollaran.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520713" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll unmask him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520714" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Darmas has the trust of Corellia's defenders, he can do great damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520716" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never thought a beautiful Jedi would be asking me into a red light sector, but I'm happy to oblige.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520716" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] I'll go stop Darmas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520717" id2="17" version="1065353216">From what Risha's said, you should know your way around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry. That tunnel will stay sealed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520719" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll go stop Darmas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520720" id2="17" version="1065353216">What else do we know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520721" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most of the Empire's heavy artillery should be on the far side of the tunnel. As long as it stays sealed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go now, and stop Nevis Kitt from carrying out this mad plan before the Imperials overrun us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520725" id2="17" version="1065353216">And bring Darmas back alive. His testimony is worth far more than his head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520739" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a  private facility... oh, Captain! Let me tell Master Sumalee you're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, that dossier was incredible. Or all too credible, perhaps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, Dodonna got wind of the arrest. She's fled to the Voidwolf.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me someone's head is going to roll for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who let her get away?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520745" id2="17" version="1065353216">This may shock you, but the Jedi Order doesn't generally encourage decapitation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then why all the lightsabers?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520749" id2="17" version="1065353216">No time to waste. Where's she heading?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we go after her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520751" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've traced her to the Museum of Alien History, which the Imperials are using as a POW camp. High Command doesn't want to go any further.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520753" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know she was more than just your employer. Can I ask you to apprehend her now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520755" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's ironic that it took Dodonna's patronage to turn your loyalties to the Republic. Can I count on you now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520757" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can give you your reward for bringing in Darmas Pollaran, or triple it if you apprehend Senator Dodonna alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Part of the Selonian tunnel network runs under the museum. You're the only one who might be able to sneak in and find Dodonna.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520760" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know where you people get this &quot;I'm the only one&quot; thing. I'm just a guy with a ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520760" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not that special.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520761" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm getting tired of your &quot;I'm the only one&quot; thing. I'm just a girl who's quick on the draw.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520761" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not that special.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps there is more to you than you realize.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520764" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. Tell me about this museum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520764" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where do I go?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520765" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can do better than that. I can give you a guide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520767" id2="17" version="1065353216">For a minute there, I thought you were going to ask me to lead an assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sneaking's good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520768" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have the troops to assault the museum directly. Anyway, isn't this more your style?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520770" id2="17" version="1065353216">Curske?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impassable how? Imperial minefield? Poisonous gas? Man-eating alien tunnel-beasts?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520773" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the problem?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520774" id2="17" version="1065353216">I take it you're a Selonian?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520774" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of alien are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once we're in, it's not abandoned anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="520775" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's always a way in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, this is Curske. She's going to help you get into the museum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520780" id2="17" version="1065353216">Done. The captain loves blasting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="520806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="940277" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's your problem now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="940299" id2="17" version="1065353216">That tunnel's impassable. I told you that. It's been abandoned for centuries.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="940305" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can give you a map, but that's all. It's suicide. Those tunnels are old. The roofs have caved in. You would need to blast a path through the debris.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
