<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>14</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/02/ep_07/holos.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1205220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Valkorion has given me free rein over his child. Death is the only line I am forbidden to cross.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1205221" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vaylin killed another keeper today. She must learn that defiance has consequences.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1205223" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fortunately, he has provided numerous subjects to test my more radical experiments on first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1205226" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isolation. Fear. Pain. Sometimes the simplest tools are the most effective.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1205236" id2="17" version="1065353216">Conventional methods only go so far. But the last subject I brought to the chamber went mad and clawed his own eyes out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1205238" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must recalibrate the machines before I use them on Vaylin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1205241" id2="17" version="1065353216">I made Vaylin observe our dissections today. Showed her each twisted, broken corpse from every failed experiment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1205243" id2="17" version="1065353216">I let her see the damage caused by the implants and chemicals. Now she knows what lies ahead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1205246" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought Vaylin would scream. Or cry. Maybe even beg for mercy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1205248" id2="17" version="1065353216">But when the pain from the machines became too much to bear, she started laughing--a hideous, high-pitched cackle. The glorious sound of her spirit breaking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217133" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have returned to Nathema, years after I once helped Valkorion tame his child.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217135" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now Vaylin wants me to undo her conditioning. Failure is not an option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vaylin hunted Senya to the shores of Ord Mantell. She eliminated her mother's knights--but let Senya live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217141" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this a sign of familial love? Or a predator toying with her prey? Only time will tell.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
