<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>126</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/world/republic/lost_and_found/lieutenant_laskin.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667889" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... thank you! I won't let you down!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Relieved of duty... what am I going to do now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back! I can't thank you enough for all this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667893" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got Private Falk in custody now. He'll be under guard until his court martial. I still can't believe it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667895" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just finished my report to Republic Command. General Ando wanted to speak with you when you returned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Put the general through; I'll speak with him now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667896" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd be honored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Master Jedi. One moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667899" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell the general I'll speak with him now, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667899" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, sir. I'll call him at once, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667902" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess I can spare some time for your general now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667902" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm always happy to chat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would General Ando want to talk to me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667903" id2="17" version="1065353216">What for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667904" id2="17" version="1065353216">The base wouldn't even be standing if it weren't for you. I think he just wants to thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. Let's get it over with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just a moment....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Laskin to Republic Command. General, do you read me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667911" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Ando here. Ah, these must be the people you spoke of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ando here. Ah, you must be the Jedi I've heard so much about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667915" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Ando here. I don't need to ask who you are, Captain; your reputation has preceded you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667917" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Ando. And you must be the spacer that Lieutenant Laskin has been telling me about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667919" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ando here. I've heard so much about you by now, I wanted to speak with you myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667921" id2="17" version="1065353216">On behalf of the entire Republic, I commend you. Your actions have saved countless lives, not only on Hoth, but throughout the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there anything you'd like to say on this occasion?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667924" id2="17" version="1065353216">The lieutenant held this place together through the worst possible circumstances. He deserves a promotion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some praise belongs to Laskin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667925" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's good advice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Laskin, you are hereby granted the rank of captain, effective immediately. Keep up the good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, sir! I won't let you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667931" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I hadn't come here, Aurek Base would be a smoldering crater. The lieutenant should be stripped of his rank.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Laskin is useless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667932" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have to admit, it was only good luck that you happened along.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667934" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Laskin, you are hereby relieved of duty. You'll be leaving Aurek Base on the next transport. Is that clear?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, sir....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667938" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't ask to speak with you solely to offer congratulations, I'm afraid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667940" id2="17" version="1065353216">We received a garbled transmission from Cresh Outpost. We suspect the signal was being jammed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667942" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only word we could make out was, &quot;Chiss.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667943" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd be extremely grateful if you could find Lieutenant Kieral at Senth Outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667945" id2="17" version="1065353216">The base there went silent, and last we knew, they were under heavy fire from pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667946" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll go there and find out what's happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667946" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll check it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667947" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want me to investigate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667948" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd like you to report to Admiral Revald. He's commanding the operations in the ship graveyard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667950" id2="17" version="1065353216">His mission is a matter of utmost secrecy, but if you can assist him, it would bring a major turning point in the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667951" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't just run off without any information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667951" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is he doing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667952" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't risk telling you via holocall; this channel isn't entirely secure. Suffice it to say, this is the most critical operation on Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667954" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll go there now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667955" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know we've asked a lot of you already. I assure you, the Republic knows how much she owes you for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck out there. Ando out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667958" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have business elsewhere at the moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667958" id2="17" version="1065353216">The admiral will have to wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667959" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand. Good luck to you, wherever you're headed next. General Ando out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667962" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope to see you again. We could certainly use more people like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, if you're here... no, don't tell me. If we're about to be blown to smithereens, I think I'd rather not know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667965" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Crescent Canyon Facility will be heavily defended. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667966" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Talz lose control of the power relay... none of us are going to make it out of here alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, a distress flare was just fired from the power relay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667969" id2="17" version="1065353216">That relay is the only reason we still have shields and heat. If the Talz defending it are being overrun....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667971" id2="17" version="1065353216">Orders, Lieutenant?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667973" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... don't know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667974" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no need to panic. I can answer the distress signal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay calm. I'll handle this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. I... don't know what we'd do if you weren't here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is &quot;Lieutenant&quot; your first name? For an officer, you don't seem to have any leadership skills.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667977" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're completely pathetic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667978" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... I'm sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667980" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something you need done?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, go to the relay. If you can't hold off the Empire... send up a flare. We'll try to evacuate as much of the base as we can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667983" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made it! Welcome back! With long-range sensors working again, it's starting to look like we might pull through this after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667985" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done us a huge service. The soldiers you rescued came back singing your praises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi, we're honored that you took the time to help us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, we can't thank you enough for finding our people. This base hasn't had any hope in a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667991" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a lucky day for us when you decided to come to Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667993" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't even want to think about what would've happened if you hadn't gone out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those men owe you their lives. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those soldiers didn't run into any Imperials on the way back, did they?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope it was an easy trip.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667997" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few more men and an early warning system aren't going to save this base from the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667997" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you going to do now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667998" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are most welcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667999" id2="17" version="1065353216">No problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668000" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know, I'm amazing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668001" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were headed for the long-range sensors. Thank you again for doing this. And good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you our reinforcements? Thank goodness!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi, I can't tell you how glad I am you've arrived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain! Good to see you, sir! We didn't expect reinforcements from Havoc Squad--this is the best news we've had in days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668010" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't tell you how happy I am to see just about anyone who's not in an Imperial uniform these days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668012" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you made it. I thought for sure the Empire had control of our airspace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Aurek Base--what's left of it. I'm Lieutenant Laskin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did Republic Command send you? Did they get my distress signal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668017" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think your signal got through. The station seemed pretty calm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668017" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one mentioned it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668018" id2="17" version="1065353216">This doesn't look like enough people to defend a cargo container, let alone a base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where is everyone?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668019" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's going on here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668020" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't know? If you're not here to answer my distress call... I don't know what we're going to do. We can't hold out much longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668022" id2="17" version="1065353216">An explosion in one of the speeder hangars knocked out main power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Within seconds, we were under heavy Imperial fire. Our shields hadn't switched to auxiliary power yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668025" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without the shields, you must have taken heavy casualties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668025" id2="17" version="1065353216">How serious was the damage?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668026" id2="17" version="1065353216">What you see here, Master Jedi, might be all that's left of the Republic presence in this area of Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can this base withstand another attack?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are the shields holding now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shields are at forty percent, Captain. We can take one shot--maybe two--from an ion cannon. I'd give the order to evacuate if I could.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you find out what caused the explosion? Or more importantly, who?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any suspects?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668032" id2="17" version="1065353216">No time to investigate. Everyone who's left is working around the clock to keep our heat and shields running.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where's the base commander?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668035" id2="17" version="1065353216">As the most senior officer left, I've been trying to contact Republic Command. I don't know what to do here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668037" id2="17" version="1065353216">This base is just a giant target for another Imperial attack. You should retreat to a safer position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668037" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need to get out of here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668038" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know, but I can't order an evacuation while we have people out of communication with the base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668040" id2="17" version="1065353216">We still have men in the field on a critical mission--or we did when we were attacked, anyway. Between the Imperials and the cold....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668042" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have enough people for a search party. Please, if you could head out there... you're their only chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668043" id2="17" version="1065353216">What makes you think they haven't already frozen to death?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668043" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think they're alive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668044" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know it's a long shot, but the mission they were on is vital.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, I'll look for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668047" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were headed out to check the long-range sensors. With those running again, we'd have some warning before another attack hit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668049" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you reach them, give them these--fresh weapons and supplies. Then they might make it back. And thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668051" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have time for this now. You'll have to send someone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="668051" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="668052" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... of course. I understand. Please, if you do find the time for us... we need help.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
