<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>48</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/bronze/project_hexapod/doctor_revis.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks again for your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304149" id2="17" version="1065353216">We got your information, and we ran into a speaking Colicoid who wanted to work with the Empire to continue the experiments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304151" id2="17" version="1065353216">I got your information, and I ran into a speaking Colicoid who wanted to work with the Empire to continue the experiments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304152" id2="17" version="1065353216">A speaking Colicoid? Repulsive. Fascinating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304154" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wasn't aware that these monsters were ever sentient. This unlocks new potential, opens up entirely new avenues of exploration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Truly great work... commendable. I can't thank you enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304158" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to know every detail about the Colicoid experiments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304159" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me... excuse me... pardon. Kanju's disease. I'll have my wind back in a minute.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304161" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's better. Doctor Revis, Imperial Science Bureau. Welcome to Project Hexapod. Not much, is it? Just me and a couple of obsolete computers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Empire's throwing all its resources into the war. What little good it does. But maybe you can help me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you can tell me what it is you need help with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="304164" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you need?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spare me the sob story.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="304165" id2="17" version="1065353216">We all have problems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304166" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not angling for sympathy here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304168" id2="17" version="1065353216">We might be able to reach some kind of agreement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="304168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Possibly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304169" id2="17" version="1065353216">The goal... excuse me, the goal of Project Hexapod is to analyze the weaponization of the Colicoids on Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304171" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're familiar with the weaponized Colicoids, right? You can't miss them. The results of some kind of sick, wonderful experiments. Got loose when the Empire bombed the place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304173" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm here to uncover and analyze every scrap, every detail of those perverse, amazing experiments. Where, why, who, how, what. And then put it to good use.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grotesque experiments on mutated life-forms--I'm surprised the Empire wasn't responsible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="304174" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire doesn't know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304175" id2="17" version="1065353216">Missed opportunity, isn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304177" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pursuit of knowledge is endless, isn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="304177" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider me intrigued.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knowledge is all well and good, but I'm more interested in the practical applications.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304180" id2="17" version="1065353216">People mostly hire me for live bounties, but I can get information just as easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="304180" id2="17" version="1065353216">As long as the pay's good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304181" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire hasn't given me much to work with, but I think I can manage a suitable payment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304183" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't usually run errands for sickly old men.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="304183" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why should I help you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304184" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scientific inquiry has its side effects. I gave my lungs to the Empire. All I'm asking is your time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304186" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean by &quot;good use&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="304186" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good use?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304187" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoid mutations are disgusting and remarkable, but they are only the barest hint of what we might accomplish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304189" id2="17" version="1065353216">These creatures are vicious enough already, don't you think?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="304189" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like madness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304190" id2="17" version="1065353216">We won't know until we try, will we? Either way, we find out what happened, we might be able to control them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304192" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've located &quot;ground zero&quot; of the Colicoid experiments, but between the mutated Colicoids and my bad lungs, I can't get in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304194" id2="17" version="1065353216">Need you to... need you to take this data spike and upload every scrap of information on those experiments you can find. Not just the formula. Everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="304195" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="304196" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess I can spare the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304197" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to hear. Project Hexapod might not be a wash after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304199" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ground zero isn't far from here. Big lab facility. Hard to miss. Good luck out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="304201" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304202" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you're missing the bigger picture. We have the ideal model of the invasive species, here. Imagine if we had the research and could expand on it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304204" id2="17" version="1065353216">You change your mind, you let me know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="304206" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry... busy.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
