<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tatooine/world/imperial/jawa_threats/lord_berow.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608316" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is a mistake to risk chaos for the sake of exposing these Jawa curiosities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608317" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire must not learn of these so-called &quot;shamans.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="608320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, of course. Hello.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you the group I was told to expect? I'm surprised you would lend your names to a job like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608324" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must be the bright young Sith I was told to expect. Frankly, I'm surprised you would lend your approval to this sort of mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608326" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must be the bounty hunter sent by Commander Vilos. I'm surprised someone of your reputation would even take this job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Vilos told me to expect you. I'm surprised someone of your background would agree to a mission like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608330" id2="17" version="1065353216">The idea that a Jawa, the lowest sort of alien scum, has the discipline it takes to use the Force is nothing short of insulting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608332" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Jawa &quot;shamans&quot; are simply charlatans putting on a show for the gullible. However, if it were true...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608333" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only way to know is to go after them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="608333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then they're a threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608334" id2="17" version="1065353216">No!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like your faith isn't as unshakable as you'd like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="608336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure after all?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="608337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there a point to this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch your tone!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608340" id2="17" version="1065353216">This has the potential to sow chaos throughout the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imagine if no one respected the power of the Sith; if they believed the lowest slave could master the same powers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608344" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the sake of the Empire, it is crucial that the Force remain mysterious, the province of the elite. Not... Jawas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608345" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think we should ignore any threat they pose?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="608345" id2="17" version="1065353216">What would you do, then?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="608346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hear hear!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this a bad time to ask for your advice on restraining Force users?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="608347" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess you're not on board.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608348" id2="17" version="1065353216">On the contrary, I will aid you in Commander Vilos's quest, but only because I expect you to redirect your goals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608350" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find this Jawa training ground, hunt down this shaman, but kill her and any Force users you see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608352" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bring Commander Vilos a regular Jawa warrior and tell him it's the shaman. Any studies will &quot;prove&quot; conclusively that Jawas have no connection to the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608353" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will help you preserve the power of the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="608353" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your loyalty is appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608356" id2="17" version="1065353216">I forged these shackles myself to hold Jedi and cut off their connection to the Force. Using them will suggest the danger this &quot;shaman&quot; poses.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="608358" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just take care which Jawa you use them on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608359" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not going to lie just to serve your political goals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="608359" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will do no such thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608360" id2="17" version="1065353216">My goals are the goals of the Empire. Commander Vilos is a fool!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608362" id2="17" version="1065353216">However, he has alerted our superiors to this issue, and they expect results. I suggest you reconsider, but I will not interfere with your mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="608364" id2="17" version="1065353216">These shackles have held Jedi before; they should restrain your &quot;shaman&quot; easily. If she exists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="608367" id2="17" version="1065353216">This planet is no home for those strong in the Force.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
