<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>51</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/rishi/class/warrior/darth_vowrawn.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful of those machines. I don't know the extent of their strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138077" id2="17" version="1065353216">My good Wrath, you look the same as ever. How many Jedi have you slain today?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138078" id2="17" version="1065353216">We meet again, Vowrawn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138079" id2="17" version="1065353216">In all seriousness--how are you? I understand you've been working tirelessly for our Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138081" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it satisfying, your craft? Putting down Hutts and cults here and there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our Empire is surrounded by those who would destroy us. I stand in their way. You know this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138082" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's enemies must die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138083" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do, and I admire your handiwork--yet I worry for your future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138085" id2="17" version="1065353216">These deeds must be done. But I grow weary of running the errands of others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138085" id2="17" version="1065353216">I seek more, it's true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138086" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I feared. I worry for you, Wrath--and for your future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138088" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are not here to discuss my passion for destruction. What do you want?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138088" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're wasting time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138089" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to understand you, Wrath, and I want to discuss your future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138091" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic claims the Emperor is dead, but I hear rumors to the contrary. The game pieces are moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138092" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speak plainly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138093" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider this: the last Wrath of the Emperor served in that position for centuries, only departing after turning traitor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138095" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I understand, you never chose to become the Wrath--the position was thrust upon you. What is it you truly desire?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138096" id2="17" version="1065353216">I seek the ultimate test. I seek to measure myself through battle, and to become greater.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138096" id2="17" version="1065353216">I desire challenge above all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138097" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Through victory, my chains are broken.&quot; There is no victory without contest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138099" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish to rule. I wish to exert my will and my vision upon the Empire and the Sith. That is our order's way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138099" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want power in the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138100" id2="17" version="1065353216">So it is. And though it may one day cause us conflict, I would not see your path inhibited.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138102" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am the Emperor's Wrath. I do not seek--I am our master's fury embodied, and to doubt that is to voice treason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138102" id2="17" version="1065353216">You dare question my loyalty?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138103" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, Wrath--forgive the confused words of an old man. I worry for you, and forget the glory of serving our Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138105" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a gift to aid your endeavors. I have come upon indications that you are being watched, and have been for some time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138107" id2="17" version="1065353216">These spies are mechanical, but ingeniously hidden using combinations of ancient and modern technology, welded into form using the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138108" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me how to find these droids. I would have words with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138108" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish to see this myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138109" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you learn about this? And who is behind these spies?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138109" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know any more?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138110" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;How&quot; must remain a secret so long as the spies may be listening. &quot;Who&quot; is a mystery to me. But we can find answers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138112" id2="17" version="1065353216">You make a bold claim. Why come for me? What do you want out of this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138112" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's your game, Vowrawn?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138113" id2="17" version="1065353216">If unknown forces are tracking you, spying upon you, then surely that concerns us all?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138115" id2="17" version="1065353216">An associate of mine with connections in the Gree Enclave manufactured this: a device to reveal your foe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use it to reclaim your privacy if you wish... or to look upon the face of your watchers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138118" id2="17" version="1065353216">How does it work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138119" id2="17" version="1065353216">Activation is simple, but I'd draw your foes somewhere remote--the jungle, perhaps--to avoid interference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138121" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is more I'd offer you, but not until I'm certain we are alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138122" id2="17" version="1065353216">The spies will soon be ash and scrap. Then we speak of the consequences.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138122" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will blind my enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138123" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your assistance will not be forgotten, Lord Vowrawn. Once again, our deals bear fruit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138123" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate your aid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138124" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those who seek to manipulate me come to bloody ends, Vowrawn. If these spies are your enemies instead of mine....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138124" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this is a trick, you die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138125" id2="17" version="1065353216">...then they will not deal the first blow, and you will know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138127" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will remain on Rishi as long as I can. Good hunting, Wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138150" id2="17" version="1065353216">A pleasure, as always.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
