<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>18</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x3/event/investigation/imperial/gyden_kall.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049171" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must ask you not to speak; this encryption is sender-side only. I'm Gyden Kall, a senior investigator in Darth Marr's service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me be frank. I think the Chevin Conglomerate has sponsored this scavenger hunt as a ruse, to hide some greater plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049175" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a way to find out. Several Chevin are camped nearby; the listening device on this transmitter, once planted, will pick up their conversation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049177" id2="17" version="1065353216">Help place the device, and I'll help you gather the items on your list. Best not to let anyone else find them. Kall out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1049198" id2="17" version="1065353216">A signal at last; the Empire's jammers are not simple to overcome. Report.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1049200" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sirs, please. I'm monitoring every interstellar sensor from here to the Cholganna system--there's no sign yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1049202" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the fleet could arrive at any moment, your statement is not acceptable. Preparations must be made.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049204" id2="17" version="1065353216">A fleet? A Chevin fleet, perhaps? We need to know more--if you're amenable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049206" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a man here, Fallaxen, who works as a courier for the Chevin. Perhaps you could... persuade him to part with any information he has? We can speak later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049218" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gyden Kall, reporting in. I have Fallaxen's data; it makes for fascinating reading.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently, several Chevin High Acquisitors are meeting on Nar Shaddaa, in secret. Perhaps they think the Smuggler's Moon is safe from spies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049222" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you could observe that meeting, unseen, we might have the answers we need. Notify me when you're in position, and I'll be in touch.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1049226" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Grand Acquisitions Race is competitive commerce which enriches your citizens. The SIS has no grounds to interfere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049372" id2="17" version="1065353216">That bantha-pat wouldn't fool a trainee, and it doesn't fool me. Be seeing you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1049374" id2="17" version="1065353216">He blusters to no profit. But the ideograms were traded; the time of greatest opportunity approaches.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049402" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intriguing. The Republic is also investigating. But I have something I can look into: these &quot;ideograms&quot; the Chevin mentioned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please; whatever their promises, the Chevin Conglomerate cannot be allowed to have the items they seek. They must stay in Imperial hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1049625" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you obtain them, place the items at these coordinates. I must return to work; I'll contact you with my findings.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
