<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>86</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/world/missing_link/danah_jor.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="524438" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Mercifully, there is no one in here anymore.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Approach. I am Bay-Yon Siu, of the Sanej Temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524441" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey! You, the one who killed the nekghoul! Open the lock, this holocron is crazy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm yourself. I am incapable of madness. Madness is internal chaos, and there is no chaos, only harmony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Back up. What did you call the dead thing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, what did I kill?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nekghouls. He named them, not me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before I open that door, maybe you want to tell me who's in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who's that captive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524448" id2="17" version="1065353216">He is the Jedi Knight Danah Jor. He came here seeking battle with the nekghouls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course I did. Anyone could sense the darkness here. And you, old man, are the source.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Danah misunderstands. The nekghouls became Force sensitive and activated me. I have taught them, but only to help them master themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Had he not invaded their territory, my lessons would have sunk in better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524455" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you a holo or what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524456" id2="17" version="1065353216">My body perished long ago. This holocron projects my recorded personality, which we Jedi use to educate future generations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524458" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great, a pretentious holocron.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524459" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was not perfect in life, nor am I now. But I teach what I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524461" id2="17" version="1065353216">The nekghouls activated me when they became Force sensitive. I saw them quest for knowledge and began teaching them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524463" id2="17" version="1065353216">All they learned is better ways to kill. You saw it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524465" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Jedi Knight, Danah Jor, entered the warren. He sought battle, and the nekghouls... reacted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524466" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can you justify teaching predators the Force?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524466" id2="17" version="1065353216">You taught them the Force?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Humans are predators, as are Twi'leks, Togruta and other sentients. Nekghouls, also, can choose their path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524469" id2="17" version="1065353216">He keeps saying that, but he's been trying to teach them manners for years. It won't work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are they keeping him alive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain this cage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524472" id2="17" version="1065353216">The nekghouls are currently drawing power from dark emotions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say it! They tear out colonists' hearts in front of me because they feed on fear and disgust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then this is no theoretical threat--they're sadistic, premeditated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524475" id2="17" version="1065353216">So they've attacked colonists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524476" id2="17" version="1065353216">What they do is from ignorance, not hatred. If you lived in a cave all your life, the first time you saw light it would be painful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524478" id2="17" version="1065353216">The darkness would comfort you, and you would only go toward light again when you found the courage. That is how it is with nekghouls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are you teaching these creatures? How can you defend them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody can justify that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524481" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some Sith have done worse before choosing another path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524483" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's mad. There's hundreds of those things beneath us, by the reactor. He sees them as no threat, but they can't be allowed to live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524485" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, we're gone. I'm popping this lock.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524485" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're getting out. Now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524486" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm popping this lock. You, the living one, get ready to run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever. I'm getting him out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank the Force! Just cover me for thirty seconds at that control panel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524489" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are hundreds of rakghouls and nekghouls in the deep warrens by the reactor. They can't be allowed to live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revenge is not the Jedi way, Danah. Your plan will create ruin and poison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524492" id2="17" version="1065353216">The creatures are dangerous, but I would hear both sides.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524492" id2="17" version="1065353216">This requires consideration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524493" id2="17" version="1065353216">How much ruin and poison are we talking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait a second.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524494" id2="17" version="1065353216">He wishes you to use that control panel to fire the reactor and lower its shielding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524496" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it wipes out these nekghouls or whatever it was I just killed, I'm listening.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Brief me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524497" id2="17" version="1065353216">At that control panel, I can override the safety features on the reactor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524499" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll listen to the one who's been fighting these things, thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524499" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trust him more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524500" id2="17" version="1065353216">No! Imprisonment has driven him mad. He would lower the reactor shielding with that control panel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524502" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would bathe them all in radiation. It would be the mass murder of sentient creatures and make this place uninhabitable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524504" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you don't like what you're about to see, turn off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then don't watch, holoman.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524505" id2="17" version="1065353216">It won't take long. Just let me reach that control panel and lower the reactor shielding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524507" id2="17" version="1065353216">What you plan is mass murder. No thinking creature deserves to die a lingering death from radiation. There are alternatives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524509" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were born of dark side sorcery. They cannot change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524511" id2="17" version="1065353216">It merely requires time, which I have. They cannot harm me. Leave me here with them and seek death no more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524512" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they can think and choose, they can learn. Reach them if you can. We will go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524512" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teach them, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your trust will not be forgotten. Now free this man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524515" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm free, but they live unpunished. If I can't give justice to their victims, what will I do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Return to the surface. Then meditate upon the actions that led you here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Learn from your mistake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524517" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been through a shock. This is normal. Talk to the other Jedi, get some help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524517" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll work it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524518" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... I will do so. Thank you for saving my life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Return to the Jedi. Tell them they can't invade this place like you did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell the Jedi to stay away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes... no one can enter here in hate. They will be fed upon, as you were.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524523" id2="17" version="1065353216">The surface is that way. Figure it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Run, you idiot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524526" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are a remarkable person not to give in to instinct, a lesson these nekghouls must also learn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524528" id2="17" version="1065353216">It may be generations, but what is done with the dark can be undone by the light. One day, they will walk on Taris as humans do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Professor Vraal here. We got everything recorded. Good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524534" id2="17" version="1065353216">We heard the plan. We'll keep watch on the site. Now, clear out of there before something hears all this talking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524536" id2="17" version="1065353216">These things are a danger to every colonist on the planet. Take them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="524536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Danah's right. They all die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you feel their agony, Danah? Even I, a collection of circuits, feel it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524541" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate him, but he's right about one thing. There's nothing good in this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Professor Vraal here. You did great, we got everything recorded. Now get out of there!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="524545" id2="17" version="1065353216">The multimeter's going crazy with radiation. Run! Run, and never look back!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="524547" id2="17" version="1065353216">[You thought you heard breathing from inside, but now it has stopped.]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
