<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>109</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/world/missing_link/mola_haxtor.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622606" id2="17" version="1065353216">The nekghouls' deaths were a loss to science... but frankly, I would have done the same thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622607" id2="17" version="1065353216">It must have been hard to spare the nekghouls. But studying that warren will teach us a lot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622608" id2="17" version="1065353216">The new species has a lair that looks like an ex-power plant. And it's got--get this--crude, recent construction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mola, the fact that they can build a ladder is the least of our worries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Day two, minute eleven--one of the new species pushes away the others in order to get at a food source.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622614" id2="17" version="1065353216">But he pushes them without touching them. It's very clear, there is no contact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622616" id2="17" version="1065353216">The new species can use the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakghouls know only aggression and fear. That's a recipe for the dark side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622617" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's disturbing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622618" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what we're afraid of. We're no experts in the Force, but this new species seems more psychotic than predatory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622620" id2="17" version="1065353216">The order will want to know of this... as well as a great many scientists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that's a discovery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622621" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll publish our findings soon enough, but right now we have greater concerns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad we didn't find this out during an attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622623" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least we know now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622624" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was the base commander's opinion, too. And we still don't know the most critical information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622626" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what you're saying is, if I have property on Taris, sell it all now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622626" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not good!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Depends on our colonies' chances. We've alerted the base commander and the rest of the garrison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622629" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the old kind... they never could, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622629" id2="17" version="1065353216">How is that possible?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622630" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is a widespread theory that the rakghoul plague was an artificial creation of the so-called &quot;dark side.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thus, their evolution deviates from the standard model. But it leaves us with some disturbing possibilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622634" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no other explanation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622635" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're sure. Obviously, we've alerted the base commander and the rest of the garrison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622637" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't know if just one of the new species is Force sensitive, or all of them. If it's all of them, the garrison is considering evacuation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622639" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the largest threat facing Taris. We need eyes in that rakghoul lair!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622640" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will risk it to protect the colonies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dangerous, but necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pitch-black cave, multiple dark side Force users, no backup. Where do I sign?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622641" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent idea. Just let me update my will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Crazy, but I'm up for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622643" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's the best plan we've got. The lair you want is an old power plant deep in rakghoul territory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622645" id2="17" version="1065353216">This could be easier than you think. An intelligent species might try to communicate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe they'll be reasonable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622646" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't think I'd take that bet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622648" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. The lair you want is deep in rakghoul territory. Some of the power plant structure is still recognizable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622650" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll fit you with a transmitter so we can see what you see. Get close enough to film the creatures--but if one notices you, do what you have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622652" id2="17" version="1065353216">This new species hasn't harmed us yet. Until it does, this is speculation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622652" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't do it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622653" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a point to consider. Thank you, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622654" id2="17" version="1065353216">This sounds like a game of tease-the-rancor. It's a game that doesn't end well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622654" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not wise. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622655" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want me to assess the threat, I can do that from here. They're a threat!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622655" id2="17" version="1065353216">No way. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622656" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. We'll have to beg the base commander to commit troops to this. Not that they'll stand a chance....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622658" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're back! Let's cue up that footage and see the rakghouls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm down, Mola. I think some thanks are in order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, of course. We'd never go into the warrens, even with an escort... this wouldn't have happened without you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622663" id2="17" version="1065353216">The swarms were pretty thick in that warren. You'll get something you can use.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622663" id2="17" version="1065353216">There were ghouls galore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622664" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the rakghouls are a danger, they must be confronted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622664" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is simply my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622665" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakghouls aren't dangerous... well, not with a blaster bolt in their head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622665" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622666" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could have mentioned that before I left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would have been good to know!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622667" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, this is a chance for a doctorate... for a significant contribution to xenozoology and the colonist effort. I got excited.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622669" id2="17" version="1065353216">And trust me when I say every Tarisian colonist could end up owing you their lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622671" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622672" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this works out, we'll be sure to credit you in the journal of sentientology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mola, how about phrasing it like, &quot;Tarisian colonists probably all owe you their lives&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622676" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't think that's more abstract?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622678" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll upload the footage. Let's talk after we've looked it over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622680" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you get into the warren, try not to blast the multi-recorder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622681" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is not a grooming behavior. That's tool use at the very least.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622683" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know that and you know that, I'm just saying neither the university nor the garrison--nevermind, we have company.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hi, I'm Mola Haxtor, this is Professor Vraal, we're applied xenozoologists. Could you settle something for us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to see some new faces. I'm Mola Haxtor, this is Professor Vraal. We're xenozoologists. Could you settle something for us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622687" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry... &quot;xenozoologist&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622687" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're what kind of zoologist?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622688" id2="17" version="1065353216">We study alien life-forms. On Taris, that pretty much means rakghouls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622690" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it's fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622691" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's better people than me to ask about... whatever you just said.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622691" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no expert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622692" id2="17" version="1065353216">Actually, we're looking for an average person's reaction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come look at this. We implanted a recording device in a rakghoul and released him. This image is from the footage of his warren.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622696" id2="17" version="1065353216">It looks like a new species of rakghoul. Taller, meaner, dominates normal raks, and when it was being recorded, it, uh....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622698" id2="17" version="1065353216">It reached over and shut the transmitter off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622699" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't think rakghouls were that smart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622699" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can they do that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622700" id2="17" version="1065353216">They may not be, but the evidence is compelling. If he were playing with a switch, he'd flick it on again. He hasn't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622702" id2="17" version="1065353216">If these ghouls are capable of tool use, our colony defenses need to be changed. But we need the footage off our device to be sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622704" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seem afraid that they're sentient--that's the larger threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622704" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sensing fear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622705" id2="17" version="1065353216">That means smart. Smart means dangerous. Is that where we're going?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622705" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not good!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly. I told you it wasn't so hard, Vraal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622708" id2="17" version="1065353216">So he wanted a little privacy with Lady Rakghoul. Why does this matter?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622708" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622709" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because rakghouls barely use tools. They're not sentient. If this new species can reason, we have to change our colony defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622711" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is why we need someone--you--to find our rakghoul and extract his recording device.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622713" id2="17" version="1065353216">So how does this affect me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622714" id2="17" version="1065353216">See? No one intuitively grasps that smart ghouls mean we must change the colony's defenses. If we take this to the garrison, they won't get it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622716" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we need more convincing footage. We need that camera off our rakghoul and back in our hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622718" id2="17" version="1065353216">Besides the obvious academic prestige, it is essential that the Republic find out how dangerous this new species is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622719" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last thing we want are organized rakghouls. I'll dig up your device.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622719" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll check out that lair.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622721" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say no more. I'll go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. Obviously, the footage and your life are top priority. Find the rak, kill the rak, grab the camera.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622724" id2="17" version="1065353216">And run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful. It's extremely unlikely this species evolved since the bombardment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Either it was under extreme pressure to diverge... or it had help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622730" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not playing fetch so you can make a nature documentary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622730" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not worth it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622731" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the scientific value, the discovery of a new sentient life-form--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622733" id2="17" version="1065353216">We made our case, Mola. We'll just have to convince the garrison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622735" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me? I'm here for fieldwork. Taris has some unique opportunities for xenozoologists.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
