<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>27</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/bronze/colicoid_expulsion/captain_augatta.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720092" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Colicoids are still scuttling in all directions. Good job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720093" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our bombers are pounding those Colicoid nests into toxic dust. You do excellent work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720095" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for your help--you've certainly earned this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720097" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid we need all those markers in place before we bombard the area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720100" id2="17" version="1065353216">You see, we're setting up a new base of operations where Outpost Freedom is now, but those Colicoids are proving a headache.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our orbital bombers have specialized toxic bombs to drive them off, but apparently they need infrared markers to aim at. I'm looking for someone to place those markers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720103" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this was so simple, you'd have placed those markers by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720103" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the catch?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, there are a ton of Colicoid nests in that area, but nothing you can't handle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720106" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't do it for free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720107" id2="17" version="1065353216">For you, I'm sure an appropriate reward can be arranged.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720109" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not much of a challenge....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720110" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I mention the markers must be placed near nests of swarming Colicoids?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720112" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need the markers placed in these locations. Once they're all in place, I can order the bombardment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720113" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can take care of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warn me first. If I look up and see toxic bombs overhead, I will be... unhappy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just let me get out in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720115" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll contact you when I read the markers are in place. Watch yourself around the Colicoids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720117" id2="17" version="1065353216">My concerns are of galactic importance. Seek someone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720117" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm busy. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720118" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure this is important, but I have business elsewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720118" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, thank you. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720119" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand. Thank you for your time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't talk now, I'm afraid. Colicoid problems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720124" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was hoping you'd have a moment, my lord. Commander Geates spoke highly of your work on the Republic relay stations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720126" id2="17" version="1065353216">Weren't you the one Commander Geates hired to attack the Republic relay stations? I could use your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720128" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Geates said you dismantled those Republic relay stations with barely a scratch. Could you assist me?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
