<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>120</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/sys/tips.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can form a guild at the Guild Register located on the fleet or in your capital city. Guilds can bestow you with several perks, such as increaed rewards and helpful abilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="2" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You gain an experience bonus for finding all the Codex entries in a category on a planet. Review your status in the Codex tab of your mission log.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="3" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can find Codex entries by exploring the world around you. Be sure to look everywhere!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="4" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can send idle companions on your ship off to perform missions, or direct them to craft.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="5" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Companions can run missions or craft items for you even while you are offline.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="6" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Crafters can reverse engineer some items. This will destroy the item, but when you do so, you can learn to make a more powerful version of that item.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="7" id2="233973" version="1065353216">When you are defeated, your worn items take damage and become useless when broken. Be sure to repair your items at a vendor when you visit town!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="8" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Players may acquire crafting, gathering and mission skills once they reach their capital world.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="9" id2="233973" version="1065353216">New missions are shown on your map as open triangles, and mission objectives and turn-in points are shown with filled triangles.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can reset all the points spent in your skill tree by interacting with the Skill Mentor. You can find the Skill Mentor aboard your Fleet's space station.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="11" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Emotes allow the player to perform social actions, such as /wave or /dance. View the menu next to the Chat window for a longer list of these commands.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="12" id2="233973" version="1065353216">If you find that your inventory is constantly full, you can store some items in the cargo bays of your ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="13" id2="233973" version="1065353216">The Abilities panel will tell you if new abilities are available to you. Seek out a trainer to learn new abilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="14" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Your companion characters can also wear gear, but only to alter their appearance and not their stats.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="15" id2="233973" version="1065353216">At level 10, you will be able to participate in player vs player warzones. To queue up for one, click the Warzone button found on the bottom right of your minimap.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="16" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can have a friendly duel with other players at any time and in most areas! To do so, target the player you wish to duel against, right-click on their portrait and select the Duel option.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="17" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can queue up for player vs player combat at any time, and you can join matches from anywhere. To do so, click the PvP Warzone button on the bottom right of your minimap.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="18" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Earn Warzone Commendations by queuing up for PvP Warzones. Warzone Commendations can be used to purchase unique armor, weapons, consumables, enhancements and supply packs (which may contain very rare combat reusables).</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="19" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can steer your ship towards space battles from your galaxy map. As you advance in level, additional missions will be made accessible to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="20" id2="233973" version="1065353216">While on your ship, you can outfit your starship with upgraded ship components on the Ship tab of your Character Sheet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="21" id2="233973" version="1065353216">While adventuring, you can send your companion back to town to sell any junk you've collected. They will automatically sell all gray quality items in your inventory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="22" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can earn titles through game activities, including missions, PvP, space combat or advancing your light side and dark side score. Choose a title from your Character Sheet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="23" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You earn experience bonuses for discovering all of the Codex entries on a planet. View the Codex entry for a planet to check on your completion progress.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="24" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Heroic missions and areas are significantly tougher than most content. Be sure to bring a group!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="25" id2="233973" version="1065353216">If you are far from your group members when they start a conversation, you can choose to take part in the conversation via holocall. However, you may be excluded from some choices that require you to take a physical action.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="26" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Many missions can be shared with group members. You can share them from your mission log.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="27" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Mission items are always placed in the Mission Items tab of your Inventory panel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="28" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can switch to a different companion from the Alliance panel. However, you can only have one companion out at a time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="29" id2="233973" version="1065353216">When you first log in, the loading screen will sum up your character's progress in their class story so far.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="30" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You may have up to four people in your group. However, companions count against this group size.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="31" id2="233973" version="1065353216">There is an experience bonus when grouping with other players--the larger the group, the bigger the bonus!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="32" id2="233973" version="1065353216">When you're grouped, your group members' mission objectives are shown with blue icons.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="33" id2="233973" version="1065353216">If you win rolls in a conversation, you will increase your social score. Advancing through social tiers grants you access to cosmetic gear.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="34" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Lots of equipment can be upgraded with Item Modifications. CTRL + Right-Click on an item to view and replace its Armorings, Mods, and Enhancements.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="35" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can toggle which icons are shown on your minimap with the Icon Filters button next to the minimap.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="36" id2="233973" version="1065353216">If a group member falls in combat, you can revive them by right-clicking on their body once combat ends.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="37" id2="233973" version="1065353216">When you mouse over a mission objective on your Map pane, the mission it is associated with will be highlighted on the Map pane's mission tracker.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="38" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can send mail messages, including items, to other players. You will need to find a mailbox, which are frequently found in towns and major mission centers.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="39" id2="233973" version="1065353216">If you get stuck, type /stuck.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="40" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Quick Travel allows you to transport from your current location to a quick travel point. Quick Travel points unlock when entering the map area they are placed in.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="41" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can sell items to other players on the Galactic Trade Network. Kiosks to buy and sell items are always found on the fleet and in major cities.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="42" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Each Companion can be set to fill one of three combat roles; they may protect you, aid you in combat, or tend to your wounds.  Companions start with some inherent abilities, and may unlock additional abilities as you gain levels.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="43" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Companion influence can often be improved by giving them lavish gifts. Note that different companions like different kinds of gifts.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="44" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can view the missions in your group members' mission log on the Group Mission Log tab of the Mission Log GUI.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="45" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can see who else is online via the Who list tab in the Social window. You can type criteria into the Filter pane to fine-tune your search. By default, the Who list will show you players who are currently on the same planet as you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="46" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Is someone bothering you? Type /ignore character name to stop seeing chat messages from that player.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="47" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Type /friend character name to add a player to your Friends list. You will then be notified whenever that player logs on and off.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="48" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can press ESC to temporarily leave an in-progress conversation. Click on the mission giver that is nearby to restart that conversation from the beginning.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="49" id2="233973" version="1065353216">If you're having trouble beating a close fight, use stims and medpacs to give you the extra boost you need.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="50" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can turn on subtitles in the Preferences menu.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="51" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can turn on additional action bars from the Interface Editor.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="54" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Endurance increases the amount of damage you can take before you are defeated. Each point of Endurance gives you about +10 Health.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="57" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Presence increases the combat effectiveness of your companion character.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="58" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Every time you gain a level above level 10, you advance down your Discipline Path. Press K to open the Combat Proficiencies GUI.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="59" id2="233973" version="1065353216">During space combat missions (not Galactic Starfighter), press SPACEBAR to do a barrel roll!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="60" id2="233973" version="1065353216">During space combat, click the right mouse button to lock your missiles on enemy ships and turrets.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="61" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Green arrows on your map and minimap point towards mission objectives. Mousing over those arrows will give you more information about those missions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="62" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can gain more experience if you are rested. You become rested by spending time or logging off in a cantina. Your experience bar will turn green if you're rested.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="63" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Looking for a group? Flag yourself as Looking for Group on the /who list. Other players who are looking for a group will be shown with a purple icon next to their name.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="64" id2="233973" version="1065353216">When you reach level 10, you can acquire a speeder license from your class trainer. This will allow you to buy and use speeders from vendors throughout the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="69" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Critical Rating increases the frequency of critical hits, which deals more damage (or restores more health) than normal.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="70" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Power increases the damage or healing done by all abilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="71" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Defense Rating increases your chance to parry, deflect or dodge both melee and ranged abilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="72" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Absorb Rating reduces the amount of damage you suffer when you absorb an attack with your personal shield generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="73" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Shield Rating increases your chance to absorb an attack with your personal shield generator. Shielded attacks deal less damage than usual.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="74" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Switching into Soresu Form activates your personal shield generator. This increases your chance to absorb incoming attacks with your shield, reducing damage taken.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="75" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Jedi Shadows activate their personal shield generators by using Combat Technique. This increases their chance to absorb incoming attacks with the shield, reducing damage taken.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="76" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Sith Assassins activate their personal shield generators by using Dark Charge. This increases their chance to absorb incoming attacks with the shield, reducing damage taken.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="77" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Vanguards activate their personal shield generators by turning on Ion Cell. This increases their chance to absorb incoming attacks with the shield, reducing damage taken.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="78" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Powertechs activate their personal shield generators by turning on Ion Gas Cylinder. This increases their chance to absorb incoming attacks with the shield, reducing damage taken.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="79" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Accuracy Rating reduces your chance to miss with all attack types. If your accuracy goes over 100%, it reduces your target's chance to parry, deflect, dodge or resist your attacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="80" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Alacrity Rating speeds up your activation times and channel times.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="81" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Surge Rating increases the magnitude of your critical hits and critical heals.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="82" id2="233973" version="1065353216">The Ranked Warzone Arenas solo queue requires Valor Level 25 before a player is allowed to enter. Complete matches in regular Warzones to gain Valor and increase your Valor Level.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10263" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can preview how items look on your character by pressing CTRL + left-clicking on the item.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10264" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Explore the galaxy! Look for light hexes on your map to find exploreable areas. Discover each region to earn experience points and survey a planet's entire map.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10266" id2="233973" version="1065353216">While engaged in space combat, you can hold down your blaster fire mouse button to fire continuously.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10267" id2="233973" version="1065353216">While in space combat, your shields will not regenerate while you're firing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10268" id2="233973" version="1065353216">A BioWare employee will never ask you for your password.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10269" id2="233973" version="1065353216">A security key is a great way to keep your account safe and having one gives you access to exclusive items at the Security Vendors in the game.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10270" id2="233973" version="1065353216">The answers to your secret questions provide an additional security layer on your account. It is important to keep them safe and not to share them with other players.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10271" id2="233973" version="1065353216">To protect your characters, you should not share your password or secret questions and answers with other players.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10272" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Most [HEROIC] missions are repeatable daily.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10273" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Influence improves a companion's combat performance and improves the results of crew skills and missions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10275" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can customize aspects of your GUI by selecting &quot;Interface Editor&quot; in the Options Menu. This will allow you to move and rescale GUI elements, as well as perform other GUI customization functions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10276" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Guild leaders may purchase access to guild banks. These are storage containers that all members of the guild can access.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10277" id2="233973" version="1065353216">At max level, you can continue to power up your character with better equipment to take on new challenges in PvE and PvP. The better your equipment, the better you will perform in Flashpoints, Uprisings, Operations and PvP.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10278" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Tutorials can also be accessed from the Options menu by pressing the Esc key. You can find previously viewed tutorials by clicking the 'Open Index' button in the lower-right corner of a tutorial window and then enabling the 'Read' checkbox.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10279" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Players on your ignore list will never be matched with your group when using the Activity Finder.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10280" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Are you looking to complete a Flashpoint but none of your friends are available? Activity Finder will automatically match you with a balanced group and transport you to your destination. Click the icon above your mini-map to open the Activity Finder.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10281" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Free-to-Play Players are not able to use some items, including Companion Customization kits and most Artifact Quality equipment. Permanent Authorization to use this equipment can be found in the Cartel Market.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10282" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Preferred Status Players gain many benefits including Secure Trade and an additional Quick Bar! Preferred status is attained by simply making a purchase of Cartel Coins!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10283" id2="233973" version="1065353216">The Cartel Market offers exclusive Cartel Packs. These packs contain an assortment of very rare items including equipment, mounts, titles, pets and much more!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10284" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Most items found on the Cartel Market can be traded to other players and sent via mail. Consider sending a gift to a friend, or even sell an item on the Galactic Trade network for extra credits!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10285" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Subscribers have an ability to teleport to their Fleet, the galaxy's central social area.  Free-to-play players lack this ability, but may purchase single-use Fleet Passes from the Cartel Market.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10286" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Items that are exclusive to the Cartel Market are indicated on their tooltip. Their item icons also display the Cartel Coin symbol, colored to indicate rarity. Gold symbols are super-rare items!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10288" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Subscribers receive 500 Complimentary Cartel Coins each month! Attaching a Security Key to your account grants 100 Complimentary Cartel Coins each month!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10290" id2="233973" version="1065353216">The Newcomer Bundle contains items perfect to give new players an edge. The Preferred Access Bundle adds additional conveniences perfect for Preferred Status players.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10292" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Boosts to increase your gain of Experience Points and Valor are available in the Cartel Market.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10293" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Weekly Passes from the Cartel Market allow unlimited access to Warzones, Space Battles and Flashpoints for Free-to-Play and Preferred Status Players.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10294" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Packs, available from the Cartel Market, contain rare items not found anywhere else.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10295" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Additional Character Slots are available from the Cartel Market.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10296" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Many Legacy Perks and Unlocks can be acquired using Cartel Coins as well as Credits. Additional playable species can also be acquired through the Legacy System this way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10297" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You may add Cartel Coins to your account at any time by visiting http://buy.swtor.com.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10298" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Expand your inventory with additional Inventory Modules and Cargo Bays, available from the Cartel Market.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10300" id2="233973" version="1065353216">The Cartel Market has many items available nowhere else in the game. You can find unique adaptive armor sets, weapons and mounts there.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10301" id2="233973" version="1065353216">The Cartel Market's Featured page always shows popular and discounted items.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10304" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can view your Galactic Reputation in your Legacy window. Increasing your Reputation ranks will unlock access to new Legacy titles and special equipment.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10305" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Macrobinoculars can be used to locate ambient dig sites for your Seeker Droid on several planets. Each ambient dig site contains one super-rare item!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10306" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Data crystals are a common form of currency that can be exchanged for gear upgrades and special items.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10309" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Operations are complex, challenging missions that can be attempted with 8 or 16 players. Check the Operations Terminal on the Fleet for a list of available missions, or open the Lockouts tab in your Mission Log.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10310" id2="233973" version="1065353216">When you enter a PvP Warzone, you will be bolstered to a minimum level of power to ensure that you are competitive with other players. Visit the PvP Missions terminal on the Fleet before you queue up!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10312" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Mastery is the primary statistic for every class. Increasing your mastery will improve your aptitude in combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10313" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Thank you for playing Star Wars™: The Old Republic™</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10314" id2="233973" version="1065353216">With Galactic Command, every battle you face at max level earns you Command Rank, unlocking increasingly more powerful rewards.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10315" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Boosts to increase your gain of Command Experience Points are available in the Cartel Market.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10316" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Guilds gain levels from members earning Conquest Points! This level will allow the guild to buy exciting Flagship perks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10317" id2="233973" version="1065353216">You can right-click on a beneficial effect that has been cast on you to dismiss it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10318" id2="233973" version="1065353216">Being polite while in a group with others will get you invited back. It's good to make friends!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="10319" id2="233973" version="1065353216">A group leader can reset their active phases from their portrait right-click menu.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
