<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>96</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/mandalorian_raiders/republic/master_satele_shan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="513617" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513619" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Allusis was returned safely to Coruscant, Master Satele. Clan Varad no longer poses a threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Repairing the damage those Mandalorians inflicted will take time--but the Allusis will now assist that process.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513622" id2="17" version="1065353216">The SIS intercepted another transmission from Darth Malgus to the Grand Moff. I thought you should see it....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513624" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic showed unanticipated initiative. Our inability to secure their warship for the Empire is regrettable, but the rebellious Mandalorians were punished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513626" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am gathering intelligence on the Republic agents who destroyed Clan Varad. Such formidable opposition must be dealt with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like we just went to the top of the Empire's &quot;to kill&quot; list.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513627" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should watch our backs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513628" id2="17" version="1065353216">We know the Empire has spies in Republic space. They'll be tracking your activities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513630" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Formidable opposition&quot;? He doesn't know the half of it. The Empire's days are numbered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513630" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understatement of the year!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513631" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm concerned for your safety--and what Malgus's statement implies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513633" id2="17" version="1065353216">We shouldn't give him any time to investigate. Now is the time to take him out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's kill him first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513634" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't question your ability, but that Sith is an entirely different threat from what you're used to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Judging by his transmission, Darth Malgus is determined to make examples of you. Take extra precautions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513638" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for your service. You saved many lives today. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513639" id2="17" version="1065353216">The tone of this transmission indicates the Empire has plans to break our treaty. The Republic is not prepared for another war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do everything in your power to preserve the peace for as long as possible. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="513643" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele, come in. We have arrived at Carrick Station. Brief us on the situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513646" id2="17" version="1065353216">So few have answered my call, but time is not our ally. We must act quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513648" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Mandalorian clan attacked and hijacked our warship &quot;Allusis&quot; while it was undergoing refit at the Fondor shipyards. They're using the vessel to raid defenseless Outer Rim systems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513649" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a bigger enemy behind this. Mandalorians don't sneeze without the Empire's permission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513649" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's the Empire's doing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513650" id2="17" version="1065353216">We thought the same--at first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513652" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't recognize that starship's designation. Someone famous?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513652" id2="17" version="1065353216">Allusis? An odd name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Allusis was a great Jedi who sacrificed himself at the Battle of Bothawui. The Republic honors his memory, but the Mandalorians are disgracing it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513655" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did the Mandalorians manage to capture a Republic warship? Where was the crew?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513655" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did they steal it from us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only a fraction of the crew was aboard. The shipyard's security forces were taken by surprise and overwhelmed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513658" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Mandalorians are inflicting heavy casualties and extorting tributes from the conquered worlds. They're demanding weapons, medical supplies--even food.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513660" id2="17" version="1065353216">But once their victims hand everything over, the Mandalorians jettison their plunder out the Allusis's air lock.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513661" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Mandalorians have been a scourge in our galaxy for too long. It's time they faced justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513661" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll pay for their crimes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513662" id2="17" version="1065353216">We aren't facing the entire Mandalorian people--only a faction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513664" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic has a responsibility to those victims. The Mandalorians are attacking them using our weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513664" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must end these raids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513665" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's reputation is not the only one that has been damaged.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like those bucket-heads are conducting psychological warfare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting war strategy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513668" id2="17" version="1065353216">These attacks are making a point: No one is safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly where would someone salvage all this loot? I ask purely for humanitarian reasons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any chance I can recover that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513671" id2="17" version="1065353216">The lost wealth of these worlds is not our concern right now. We must end these unprovoked attacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would these raiders demand tribute and then throw it all away?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513673" id2="17" version="1065353216">That makes no sense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wealth is not their goal. They're sowing terror and chaos to provoke a conflict.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513676" id2="17" version="1065353216">These victims have to stop giving in to the Mandalorians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513676" id2="17" version="1065353216">No reason to bow down, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513677" id2="17" version="1065353216">They have no choice. Worlds that resist suffer greater devastation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513679" id2="17" version="1065353216">The raiders are a group of rogue Mandalorians from an especially militant clan called Varad. They've broken away from the Empire and Mandalore's leadership.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clan Varad is also attacking Imperial planets--and the Empire wants revenge. Fortunately, its fleet has been unable to destroy the Allusis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513682" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Allusis attacked Imperial worlds and survived, it must be quite a ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513682" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's one tough starship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513683" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our engineers had just upgraded the vessel with advanced shields and weaponry when it was stolen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we have any idea where the Mandalorians are headed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513685" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we find it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Long-range scouts found the Allusis at a remote refueling depot. Unfortunately, Imperials have also discovered this location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513688" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of forces are the Empire committing to this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we know the Empire's plans?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic spies just intercepted a coded transmission sent to the Imperial Grand Moff by a Sith Lord named Darth Malgus. The news isn't good....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mandalore's scouts have tracked their rebellious brethren to the Tamarin Sector. An Imperial strike team is on its way to board Clan Varad's vessel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513693" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will terminate the traitors, capture the Republic's warship and add it to the Empire's arsenal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513695" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Allusis must not be captured by the Empire. We need its shield and weapons technology for our own defense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513696" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you need a team to capture that ship, you're talking to the right people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513696" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then let's take it back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513697" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's only one ship--and I assume we still have the technical readouts for those weapons and shields.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513697" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't we just replace it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513698" id2="17" version="1065353216">It isn't that simple. The Republic's resources are at all-time lows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513700" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you know about Lord Mashface? He seemed friendly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who was that ugly Sith we saw?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513701" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Malgus is a deadly and resilient foe. I faced him when the Sith Empire first returned to Republic space. He killed my Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our only hope is to board the Allusis, defeat Clan Varad and fly back to Coruscant before Darth Malgus's agents beat us to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thwarting Sith Lords is my specialty, Master Satele. Mandalorians shouldn't pose any greater threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513704" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force is with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513705" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clan Varad's warriors specialize in fighting Jedi. Don't underestimate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial forces are used to having Mandalorians for support, not adversaries. Our foes will be at a disadvantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513707" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire won't have it easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513708" id2="17" version="1065353216">That may be, but your fight will be much harder against two enemies. Better to get there first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad is trained for boarding actions. Those Mandalorians won't know what hit them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513710" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm locked, loaded and ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513711" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful. The Mandalorians will be ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513713" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know a thing or two about stealing starships. No matter how big they are, the principle is the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave it to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513714" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fear your task will be considerably more complex than reprogramming a navigation computer. Be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513716" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm already not liking this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513717" id2="17" version="1065353216">The risk will be considerable, but I would never send you into certain death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just let them try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not focus on revenge. Your first duty is to capture the Allusis with minimal damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513722" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm leading an attack fleet to your target's coordinates. Our ships will distract the Mandalorians so you can safely board the Allusis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513724" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your assault shuttle is waiting in the station docking bay. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513725" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start Veteran Mode]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="513726" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1111999" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start Master Mode]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
