<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>31</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/ilum/bronze/republic/icy_destruction/major_dumerin.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still can't believe the Empire was willing to spend turrets and repair droids on this. I'll get SIS to look into it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Outstanding. I'll get our retrieval teams out there on the double. Those weapons will save our hides.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179033" id2="17" version="1065353216">I owe you much more than this, but I hope you'll take it anyway. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful out there. Those turrets will still be operational while you're taking out the repair droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast it! A whole weapons shipment shot down! Seems like the Imperials finally got a decent gunner.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Two hundred missiles, three thousand blaster rifles, enough explosives to knock out a heavy walker brigade--and the enemy's swarming all over 'em.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179042" id2="17" version="1065353216">The lousy Imperials must've been planning this for weeks. They've set up turrets to protect their scavenging crews, and droids to repair the turrets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179043" id2="17" version="1065353216">Almost a small army.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179044" id2="17" version="1065353216">No kidding. I've ordered my people to keep their distance, but we're running out of time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179046" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're up to something.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right, and I don't want to find out just why they want all those weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179049" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to retaliate, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179050" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a strategy, sir, but it hinges on forces I don't have. Unless... you'd like to assist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial subtlety at work.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about it. They must want those weapons bad, maybe they have something planned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="179055" id2="17" version="1065353216">They brought in turrets and repair droids, just for some weapons? Seems excessive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179055" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's overkill.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179056" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't argue with the results. Our own retrieval crews can't get close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do your job and handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179059" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not a miracle worker. I need any resource I can find to get those weapons back. Including outside help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179061" id2="17" version="1065353216">The turrets are the real headache; the droids keep them firing whatever we do. But, destroy those droids, and the turrets are easy pickings.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179063" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate to ask, but if you're here, you must be handy in a fight. You might be able to slip through and take those turrets out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count me in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179065" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count me in.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179066" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember, hit the repair droids first. Without them, the turrets are vulnerable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179068" id2="17" version="1065353216">No backup?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179069" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be fine as long as you hit the repair droids first. Otherwise, you're effectively facing endless reinforcements.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179071" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry about the weapons shipment; we'll send a crew once it's all clear. Good luck!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not happening. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then move along. I've got to work this problem myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry. This report demands my full attention.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
