<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>56</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/smuggler/chapter_3/intro/darmas_pollaran.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back, Captain. Senator Dodonna's already called to rave about how you just saved her life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meaning the whole Republic's backing you when you finally take down Rogun. Not bad for somebody from the wrong side of the hyperlane.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635330" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Rogun goes down, as far as anyone's concerned, I did it single-handedly. With a spoon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635330" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sharing the credit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blindfolded and after four shots of Corellian whiskey. Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635333" id2="17" version="1065353216">When did you two decide that I want to start hunting down the most brutal gangster in the entire galaxy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635333" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're both trying to kill me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless you like being ambushed in every spaceport, I don't think the Butcher's giving you much choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635336" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're definitely off to a good start. He's lost a lot of influence since you cut him off from the Hutts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you find out what those beasts were that attacked her?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635338" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the creatures?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me get the Senator on the link. She's going to want to hear what I've found.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635341" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is it? And talk quickly. I got pulled out of a vote for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635343" id2="17" version="1065353216">Creatures Rogun sent at you seem to be cybernetically modified versions of native Vossian wildlife.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635347" id2="17" version="1065353216">As far as I know, no native animal has ever been legally exported off Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this somewhere I should have heard of?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635349" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss is a newly discovered world. Very isolationist--they're governed by some strange cult of Force users. I'll try to wrangle you a landing permit, but it will take time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635351" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time to track down who's been playing zookeeper for Rogun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635351" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone smuggled them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635352" id2="17" version="1065353216">How does this get me closer to feeding Rogun his own eyeballs?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635352" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who cares?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635353" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have direct access to Rogun, but maybe his suppliers on Voss do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635355" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss is a strange place, newly discovered, very isolationist. I'll pull some strings and get you a landing permit, but it will take a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635357" id2="17" version="1065353216">We shouldn't wait. Rogun's finally vulnerable, and the captain's gained quite a reputation recently.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635359" id2="17" version="1065353216">If anyone's going to step into Rogun's shoes, Captain, this is the time, and yours are the lovely feet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635360" id2="17" version="1065353216">If anyone's going to conquer his criminal empire, Captain, this is the time, and you're the man with the crown.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635361" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't turn down a chance to rule the galactic underworld with an iron fist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't think it will be that easy, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635364" id2="17" version="1065353216">But worth the price.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635366" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to help the Republic, not run some crime family.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635366" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a patriot, not a gangster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, the captain's no crime lord. She's a... a shining example of independent spirit!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635369" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah. The captain's no crime lord. He's a... a hero-for-hire!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635371" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rogun's got assets the Republic can't touch. Plus, if you take over for him, you can stop worrying about him always trying to kill you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rogun is a weapon in the Voidwolf's hand. You can do the Republic no greater service than to eliminate him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635375" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are Rogun's weaknesses?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635375" id2="17" version="1065353216">What else do we know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635376" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, the only one who knew all of Rogun's secrets was his mentor, Ivory. And he disappeared years ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635378" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not... entirely true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635380" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rogun's predecessor was arrested by the Republic. To my knowledge, he is still incarcerated in a top secret facility on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635382" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is highly restricted knowledge. Even within the Senate, not everyone knows of Belsavis. You must not repeat any part of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635383" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this Ivory's been locked up long enough, we should be able to buy his cooperation with a few rolls of spice and some shaving cream.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635383" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635384" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isn't that more the Empire's sort of thing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635384" id2="17" version="1065353216">A secret prison planet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635385" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's hard to be the good guy. If you don't kill offenders outright, you need a place to put them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635387" id2="17" version="1065353216">Voss sounds more promising.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635387" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems like a long shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635388" id2="17" version="1065353216">It may take months to get the permits for Voss. Belsavis will be easier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635390" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ivory and Rogun were like father and son. If you can find him, he'll know Rogun's hideouts, stashes, things we'd never find ourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635392" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a man who used to sell children to the Hutts for gladiatorial games. The Republic will insist on tight restrictions for dealing with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635394" id2="17" version="1065353216">But it's worth it. If you're going to war with Rogun, Belsavis will be your first battleground. I'll get the permits in order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rogun has no idea who's coming after him....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
