<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>70</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/world/exit_strategy/gabe_dovaro.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478697" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to see you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478700" id2="17" version="1065353216">I almost feel sorry for the Imps. When I asked you to help, I didn't know what I was throwing at them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478702" id2="17" version="1065353216">And word is, you even took down Lord Tharsis. I don't know whether to shake your hand or run for cover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Word is you even took down Lord Tharsis. I don't know whether to start shaking hands or running for cover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. For everyone you saved, I... I was wrong about you. It's good to see you really care about saving Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478707" id2="17" version="1065353216">As a Jedi, it's my duty to protect those in danger. I could never turn my back on Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478707" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi care for all in need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478708" id2="17" version="1065353216">Duty or not, we do appreciate it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once Tai's request for Republic membership is approved, entire armies will protect your people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tai Cordan will do even more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478711" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gabe Dovaro, Republic citizen. That'll take some getting used to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478713" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're all in this war together. I wouldn't abandon Balmorra to the Empire's mercy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course I care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478714" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know, it's just... the occupation's over. It's hard to believe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478716" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you start handing out the praise that fast, Gabe, it'll go to my head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478716" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful, I blush easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478717" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good point. I don't want to start thinking you're alright.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478719" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't celebrate yet--there's still Imperial stragglers to handle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478720" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fighting's not quite over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478721" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll see every Imperial soldier thrown offworld, I promise you. Maybe share a few of our tricks with the Republic military.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here, take this with you. You've more than earned it. Whatever happens, you'll always have friends on Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478729" id2="17" version="1065353216">The action's in Moraine Territory, not here. Talk to Wixx.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478732" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait--you. You're the ones everyone's talking about. They're saying you put a real dent in the Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478734" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold up. You're that Jedi, right? The one who swiped the Empire's juiciest tech from under its nose?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait. You. You're the one who assassinated Darth Lachris, aren't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold up, soldier. I know you. You and Vik did a real number on the Imperials, didn't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478740" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait a second, I know you. I hear the Imperials are short a whole shipment of weapons, thanks to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hang on, I know you. I hear you've been putting Imperials in their place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478744" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm resistance. Came for help--funny that I run into you. You have no idea what you've stirred up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478746" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's not taking defeat lying down. And we're the ones in the firing line.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478747" id2="17" version="1065353216">The resistance was a great help in securing the cloaking device. I apologize if my actions put you at risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478747" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry you're in danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478748" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one thought resisting the Empire would be a piece of cake, but the Imperials have been pushed to the brink.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478750" id2="17" version="1065353216">We removed Darth Lachris to stop the Balmorran people's suffering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478750" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't mean to endanger you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody's shedding tears for that tyrant. But if you don't help us, it'll have been for nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478753" id2="17" version="1065353216">The resistance put its neck on the line for me and Vik. Tell me how to make this right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I want to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478754" id2="17" version="1065353216">I busted Camp Vigil wide open and tossed the Empire's weapons offworld. What's it going to take?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478754" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials just don't quit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478755" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire didn't get where it is by rolling over easy, especially when a spacer makes it look bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478757" id2="17" version="1065353216">What &quot;firing line&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478758" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire wants to destroy the resistance. It doesn't need our actions as an excuse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478758" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't blame us for that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478759" id2="17" version="1065353216">True. But you rattled their cage... so maybe you can put the Imperial occupation down for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478761" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire wants to destroy the resistance. It doesn't need my actions as an excuse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't blame me for that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478762" id2="17" version="1065353216">True. But you rattled their cage... so maybe you can put the Imperial occupation down for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478764" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's attacking Moraine Territory. That's where the resistance started; mostly villages and factories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Moraine Territory's also where we hid our families. But now the Imps have found them. Hundreds... hundreds are already dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478767" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials are trying to break your will. I'll run them out of Moraine Territory first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unacceptable. Let me help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478768" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will stand between your families and the Imperial forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478768" id2="17" version="1065353216">This cannot continue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478769" id2="17" version="1065353216">You tell me how to get to Moraine Territory, and I'll teach the Empire some manners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478769" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me handle the Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478770" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did the Empire cause so much damage? Wasn't Moraine Territory protected?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478770" id2="17" version="1065353216">Weren't there any defenses?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478771" id2="17" version="1065353216">We didn't want to get the Empire's attention with a big defense network. Stupid, in hindsight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478773" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the resistance. Resist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478774" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't be--half the reason the Empire's so desperate is because of what you did! How can you walk?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478775" id2="17" version="1065353216">If my actions drove the Imperials to attack, it's only fair that I try to stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478775" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right, I can't. Sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478776" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose I could help....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478777" id2="17" version="1065353216">This whole area's a war zone, but you should have a clear path to Moraine Outpost--it's our oldest staging ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478779" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you get there, talk to Wixx. If she's still alive, she'll be fighting. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="478781" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very easily. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. Maybe we'll meet again, if there's still a Balmorra for you to come back to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="478786" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Empire's gone, we'll pull those red banners out of Sobrik and have ourselves a bonfire.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
