<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>9</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x4/daily/belsavis/republic/section_x/bounty_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059211" id2="17" version="1065353216">PRIORITY DISPATCH / FOR ALL SECTION X PERSONNEL

Brutal Trandoshan and Gamorrean criminals have been freed from their prison blocks and recruited as shock troops for the Dread Masters' army.

These new recruits are staging for an attack in close proximity to the Republic's main outpost. They must be intercepted and their weapons of war destroyed before they can initiate their attack.

The Republic can never stop the Dread Masters if we lose this foothold in Section X!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059212" id2="17" version="1065353216">PRIORITY UPDATE / FOR ALL SECTION X PERSONNEL

The Gamorrean and Trandoshan forces are in retreat! 

All forces are advised to resume standard operations and remain vigilant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059214" id2="17" version="1065353216">PRIORITY DISPATCH / FOR ALL SECTION X PERSONNEL

Containment cells beneath the surface of Section X are being sabotaged by Dread Master forces, releasing the creatures that were being held inside. 

These vicious creatures are an imminent threat to Republic operations against the Dread Guard. Further releases cannot be allowed.

It is critical that the sabotaged containment system be repaired immediately. Any agents of the Dread Masters attempting further sabotage should be neutralized before more damage is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059215" id2="17" version="1065353216">PRIORITY UPDATE / FOR ALL SECTION X PERSONNEL

All containment systems are in the green.

The rest of the imprisoned creatures will stay in their cells, where they belong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059217" id2="17" version="1065353216">PRIORITY DISPATCH / FOR ALL SECTION X PERSONNEL

Bio-forming nodes within Section X have been sabotaged by agents of the Dread Masters. They are now spreading an unknown mutagenic toxin into the surrounding environment.

Toxic plants are spreading rapidly, and nearby animals are being mutated and enraged, endangering our troops as they try to conduct operations.

All bio-forming nodes must be disabled immediately and any afflicted wildlife neutralized before more lives are lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059218" id2="17" version="1065353216">PRIORITY UPDATE / FOR ALL SECTION X PERSONNEL

All terraforming nodes have returned to normal. Our forces can continue the fight without being poisoned by the plants and animals around them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059220" id2="17" version="1065353216">PRIORITY DISPATCH / FOR ALL SECTION X PERSONNEL

Members of the Dread Guard have been searching one of the ancient prison complexes in Section X, apparently collecting data on the prison's former inmates.

It is vital that the Republic stop these Dread Guards and retrieve whatever data they're collecting. 

Any information we recover will put us one step closer to uncovering the Dread Masters' plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1059221" id2="17" version="1065353216">PRIORITY UPDATE / FOR ALL SECTION X PERSONNEL

All retrieved data has been forwarded to Strategic Information Service agents for analysis.

The volume of data is immense, so it should give us many insights into the goals of the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062240" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Republic by completing the following daily missions in Section X on Belsavis:

[DAILY] Bio-Reform
[DAILY] Imminent Threat
[DAILY] The Dread Guard
[DAILY] Priority Containment
[HEROIC] Long Shots
[AREA] Key to Decryption</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
