<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>266</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/world/corpse_counters/cera.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623025" id2="17" version="1065353216">This might give us our edge in the war against the rakghouls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hopefully, the Republic will agree to suspend our operations until rakghoul territories have been better studied.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623027" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic sent a unit to retrieve our team's bodies. They said to thank you for your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623029" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not going to ask if they went after your pet project?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aren't you going to ask if she went after your pet project?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aren't you going to ask if he wasted his time on your pet project?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do you always try to ruin everything? Do Sullustan moms not hug their children or something?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Um... did you get to the bombardment site? I don't see a scratch on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623038" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rakghouls didn't want to give up their blood, but I convinced them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623038" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have the samples.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623039" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you can be quite... persuasive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you check right now? I want to see if anything comes of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see if this was a waste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623042" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623043" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, you've certainly got her all google-eyed at the lot of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623045" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, you've certainly got her drooling over you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aw, is that hero worship I see there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just let me see the samples. I've got a portable scanner that can give us preliminary results right....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623051" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623053" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's amazing. There's over a fifty percent correlation. Genetic drift usually means a much less marked connection even in a normal population after so many years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623054" id2="17" version="1065353216">It should not surprise us that rakghouls retain some memory of their lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623054" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even a dog shows loyalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623055" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many animals show emotion toward their dead. It doesn't mean they think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623057" id2="17" version="1065353216">They cling so desperately to their lost humanity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623057" id2="17" version="1065353216">I almost feel for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623058" id2="17" version="1065353216">It could just be geography, remaining close to their initial infection site. We'll need a xenobiologist out to study this--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't just dismiss it now! This is an incredible find!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does that give us any insight into how to defeat them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talk tactics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623063" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we know they defend a territory, then we know where to avoid... or even how to draw them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623065" id2="17" version="1065353216">But consider what you're saying! This means rakghouls have remnants of sentience. We can't kill them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623067" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, they're not just related, they're inbred?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623067" id2="17" version="1065353216">The family tree doesn't fork?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess they're not any pickier about their mates than their food.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623070" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can you joke about this? This is incredible. There's no way this is coincidence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623072" id2="17" version="1065353216">They really are defending their ancestors, then?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623072" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does that mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623073" id2="17" version="1065353216">It means we just made one of the most important discoveries in Tarisian history.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623075" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll skip the science.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623076" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't leave now! Did you hear what she said? This is amazing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623078" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? Where's the cynical disbelief?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623080" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't dispute the numbers, Cera. You're right. This is amazing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623082" id2="17" version="1065353216">If rakghouls have enough rationality to remember people and places that matter to them, we can't keep treating them like mindless animals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623083" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've slaughtered millions of people, including your friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623083" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're still monsters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623084" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they can think, maybe someday we can make peace with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623084" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think they're sentient?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623085" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623087" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a disturbing thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623088" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to cancel our operations in these grave sites. We can't keep antagonizing them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623090" id2="17" version="1065353216">But if we know they come to the defense of certain territories, we can bait them, draw them out so the Republic can send in troops to exterminate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623092" id2="17" version="1065353216">No! If they're sentient, we can't just keep murdering them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623094" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll contact the Reconstruction Authority. Do you have an opinion on this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623095" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there's any way to coexist peacefully with the rakghouls, we should take it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623095" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should study this further.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623096" id2="17" version="1065353216">I--I guess it's a virtue to forgive, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623098" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least this way, maybe we can avoid those kinds of attacks in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623100" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakghouls are a contagious, predatory species. Our only option is to wipe them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623100" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kill them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623101" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isn't that the thinking that got Elihsu and the others killed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623103" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't reason with a monster, Garthe. You of all people should know that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623105" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll give the Republic your recommendation. Thank you again for all your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623107" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will be the only data ever brought back from one of the main bombardment sites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623108" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you notice anything about the number of rakghouls in that pipe? I think it's more than most places, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623110" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, not that nonsense again....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623111" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sound like there's something more on your mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623111" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's going on?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623112" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this leading up to something?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623112" id2="17" version="1065353216">More nonsense?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623113" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, this'll sound crazy--but there's more rakghouls at our grave sites than any of the Republic target zones.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623115" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're just drawn to the noise and the smell of flesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623117" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not any noisier or... fleshier than a platoon of soldiers. I think they're protecting their ancestors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623118" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ancestors?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623118" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623119" id2="17" version="1065353216">See, rakghouls descend from sentients. It's a disease. One we know little about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakghouls are beasts. Everyone knows they're not sentient.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impossible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623122" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not saying they discuss it over tea, but I think something is driving them to defend these grave sites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623124" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were human once, you know. The first ones, anyway. It's a disease that turned them into monsters. And we still don't understand how it works.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623126" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why should I care?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623127" id2="17" version="1065353216">All we know about rakghouls right now is they have a disease that can turn people into monsters, and they've taken over all of Taris.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623129" id2="17" version="1065353216">But if my theory is correct, it'll be our first insight into how they think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623131" id2="17" version="1065353216">This could be a first step toward taking the planet back from them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623132" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understanding your enemy is the key to defeating him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623132" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I assist in this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623133" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly. Right now, rakghouls are like something out of a nightmare. We never know when or where they'll attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623135" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only if we look through their eyes can we understand what they see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623135" id2="17" version="1065353216">A worthy goal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623136" id2="17" version="1065353216">I kind of hope they're really the beasts they seem. Imagine if there's still a sentient person, trapped inside....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623138" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing worse than fighting something too dumb to do the same thing twice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good strategy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623139" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing scarier than never knowing when or where they might swarm in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623141" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still seems like a long shot, unless you can sit them down and ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623141" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623142" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think there's a way. Now that you're here, anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623144" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not sending them to the bombardment site, are you? That place is so thick with rakghouls you can see them from orbit!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't you interfere! We know what you think of the people of Taris. I'm right about this. Why else would they be so determined to guard the bombardment sites?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623148" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly! Why so many rakghouls at the bombardment sites unless they're staying near their human ancestors?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623150" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you prove it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623151" id2="17" version="1065353216">The salvage team can't get to the main bombardment sites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623153" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are so many rakghouls there, you can see them by satellite, like a living carpet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623155" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you could get samples from both the rakghouls and the skeletons at one of the main sites, we could see if they're related.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623156" id2="17" version="1065353216">My specialty--danger and a worthy cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623157" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. The closest bombardment site is southeast of the Republic base. Believe me, you can't miss it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623159" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have details? What exactly are we talking about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623159" id2="17" version="1065353216">What will that entail?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623160" id2="17" version="1065353216">The closest bombardment site is southeast of the base. You won't be able to miss it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623162" id2="17" version="1065353216">There probably isn't a way to get a rakghoul to volunteer a genetic sample, so, um, I guess you'll be killing them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'll compare their blood samples with genetic material from corpses in the same area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623165" id2="17" version="1065353216">By tomorrow, you should be able to answer this question once and for all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623166" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is ridiculous. Are you really going to take up more of their time with your crazy theories?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623167" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. Cera, you cannot take up any more of her time with these ridiculous theories--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seriously, Cera, you think you can waste his valuable time on your crackpot theories?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623170" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't tell me what to do anymore! We know how you feel about the people of Taris.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let them decide if it's worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623174" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's her choice if she thinks it's worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623176" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's smart. He wouldn't do this if he didn't think there was a point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please don't let Garthe discourage you. This is important. And I don't think there's anyone else on this planet willing to brave those rakghouls to find out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623180" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be waiting to hear what you find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623181" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any payment?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623182" id2="17" version="1065353216">The bombardment site is chock-full of salvage no one's ever managed to get to--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623184" id2="17" version="1065353216">You never change, do you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623186" id2="17" version="1065353216">No! Those are important archaeological artifacts, not some kind of... pirate treasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623188" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I'm sure the Republic will pay something for the data. I'll give you whatever they offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623190" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you again. I'll be waiting to see what you find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623193" id2="17" version="1065353216">And maybe it's psychic vibrations in the sun spots. I've got better things to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623193" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds ridiculous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623194" id2="17" version="1065353216">I told you no one cares about your crackpot theories, Cera. Stick to counting bones. Let someone else do the science.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623196" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut up and wait to be arrested.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623197" id2="17" version="1065353216">Really. I think I can prove it....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623200" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I'll say &quot;thank you&quot; and leave it at that. Come back if you change your mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623202" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're back! And... I don't see anyone with you. Did you...? A--are they...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623204" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dead? What did you think? The rakghouls would buy them flowers and send them home?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623205" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry. Your friends are gone, but I made sure those rakghouls will never kill again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623205" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623206" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cold comfort. There's probably another swarm already moving in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623208" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623209" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you killed those freaks, I'll call it even. At least we can clear out the corpses without becoming one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623211" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me. I--I should call the base, tell their families what happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623213" id2="17" version="1065353216">Actually, one of them left you a message, Garthe....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623213" id2="17" version="1065353216">I learned a few things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623214" id2="17" version="1065353216">A message? Oh, that must be Elihsu. They were very close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623216" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll call the base and tell them what happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623218" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm putting in for a transfer. No job is worth this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623219" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear you've found a way to make it worth your while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623219" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that why you're stealing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wha--what did you find? Was Elihsu alive? What did that lying coward say about me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623221" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should have more respect for those murdered by the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623221" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's wrong to rob the dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623222" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three hundred years ago! All the Sith involved are just as dead as them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623224" id2="17" version="1065353216">Elihsu says he knows how the dead feel now when you desecrate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623224" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dead deserve more respect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623225" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've given five years of my life to this rock!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623227" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that's worth nothing because I laid claim to a few forgotten necklaces?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623229" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's the Republic you've been stealing from, not just the dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623229" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see you court-martialed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623230" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic doesn't care what we find! I gave them five years of my life--not a raise, not a trip home--we're all forgotten.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623232" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, fine. You found me out. Who cares?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623234" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greed's one thing, Garthe, but grave robbing's just low.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623234" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your secret's out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623235" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, fine. So I'm sending some trinkets into the black market instead of Republic archives. So what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623237" id2="17" version="1065353216">He said you've been stealing from the dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623237" id2="17" version="1065353216">He left a confession.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623238" id2="17" version="1065353216">So dramatic. It's nothing big. The corpses are still filed; the data is preserved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623240" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was just stuff--jewelry, mostly. No one was going to miss it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623242" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're talking about people who died generations ago!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623243" id2="17" version="1065353216">The message Elihsu left should be worth good money to hear. And keep quiet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623243" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's it worth to you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623244" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is this, blackmail? Are you accusing me of a crime or committing one?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623245" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll see if you think prisoners have as few rights as the dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623245" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm turning you in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623246" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very funny.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623248" id2="17" version="1065353216">With what you've been making off these corpses, you can share.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pay me and I'll keep quiet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623249" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. Take Elihsu's share. He won't be needing it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623251" id2="17" version="1065353216">The commander's sending a team to retrieve the bodies. Thank you for doing what you could.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623252" id2="17" version="1065353216">I also uncovered Garthe's crime. He's been stealing off the bodies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623252" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your partner's a thief.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623253" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ask your partner what's been happening to the valuables you find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623253" id2="17" version="1065353216">Garthe's got a confession.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623254" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of your dead teammates has evidence of a crime.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623254" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell them to check the bodies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623255" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, please. This is so humiliating. Yes, Elihsu and I were stealing some trinkets for the black market. The blasted dead don't cry over it, why should you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623257" id2="17" version="1065353216">How could you! You told me those boxes were going to the Republic archive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623259" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, so I lied. What... you going to turn me in for that, too?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623261" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll work this out later--we've asked enough of your time. Although... if you have a moment....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623262" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least you'll be able to retrieve the bodies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623262" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish I could have done more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623263" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the blasted rakghouls don't come back. They're everywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakghouls are nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, for us, it would have been impossible. So thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not like the rakghoul freaks don't show back up the minute you kill one. They're everywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mostly around us. Which makes me wonder....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623272" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you don't have another job for me, I should be going.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623272" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there anything else?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623273" id2="17" version="1065353216">Actually, there is something. The number of rakghouls that were in that pipe... I think it's more than in most places, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623275" id2="17" version="1065353216">This has taken enough of my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then goodbye.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623276" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, thanks for going in. You showed more concern than the Republic ever has.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, you're not leaving, are you? I wanted to... that is, you did us such a favor--could I maybe... ask another?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623280" id2="17" version="1065353216">I turned around and there was no one behind me. There's so many of them still lost in that pipe....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623281" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for coming so fast! I told you the commander would send someone, Garthe!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623283" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think they're from base? You ever seen a regulation group of soldiers look like that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623285" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, maybe. But that doesn't mean they can't help us. Please, sirs, have any of you ever faced a rakghoul?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623286" id2="17" version="1065353216">The commander didn't send her!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623288" id2="17" version="1065353216">The commander didn't send him!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't you recognize a Jedi when you see one?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we really are saved! Master Jedi, may I please beg your aid? Have you ever faced a rakghoul before?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623293" id2="17" version="1065353216">A lieutenant on duty wouldn't be out here without a full squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623295" id2="17" version="1065353216">On duty or not, please... sir... do you have any experience with rakghouls?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623296" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not any uniform I've ever seen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623298" id2="17" version="1065353216">She got here on her own somehow, past all the rakghouls. She could still help us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623299" id2="17" version="1065353216">He managed to get out here past all the rakghouls. He could still help us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623300" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this a research station or something?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623300" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you doing here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623301" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're a Republic archaeological salvage team cataloging those who died in the Tarisian bombardment. Mostly they call us the &quot;corpse counters.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakghouls are nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Really? Because they're the most terrifying things I've ever seen. Dragged down three quarters of our team before we could do anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623306" id2="17" version="1065353216">You look pretty secure here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623306" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's so urgent?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623307" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakghouls dragged off most of our team. We don't know if anyone's still alive, but if they are, every second counts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623309" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're a Republic archaeological salvage team. They call us the &quot;corpse counters&quot; because we're cataloging the bodies from the bombardment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623311" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were in an old Czerka Works pipe this morning when those monsters came out of nowhere. They killed our guards and half a dozen of our team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623313" id2="17" version="1065353216">They might not be dead. We ran, we didn't see. Could you please... just check if anyone survived?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623314" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is risking your lives to gather up some ancient bones?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623314" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're counting bodies?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623315" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's important work--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623317" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's pointless work! People are dying out here so the Republic can have a list they'll never look at.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623319" id2="17" version="1065353216">These people deserve someone to acknowledge their deaths.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623321" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only... most of our team were lost this morning when rakghouls cut us off. I was hoping... that you might go see if anyone is still alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623322" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there is any chance your friends live, they deserve every effort to save them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623322" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll go right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. I'm honored that you would help us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623325" id2="17" version="1065353216">A life snuffed out to feed a monster--I will leave no one to that fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623325" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will rescue them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623326" id2="17" version="1065353216">To think a virus can turn a sentient being into one of those creatures....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't expect miracles. If your friends have been gone long, there's not much hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623328" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623329" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I've been saying. Rakghouls don't leave survivors. They just make more rakghouls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone could have hid... you never know!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623333" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't want to be the one left behind in a hole full of those things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623333" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll give it a shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623334" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wanted to go back for them--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be ridiculous, Cera. Then we'd just be dead, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Might give it a shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. It means a lot, knowing we're not abandoning them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623341" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were in the Czerka Works pipeline. If you go soon, there may still be someone there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623343" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. There's no hope for our friends now... but maybe you can make those monsters pay for what they did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not my job. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623346" id2="17" version="1065353216">More important than people's lives?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623349" id2="17" version="1065353216">But they could die!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623351" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let it go, Cera. They're dead already. Another few hours won't matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623353" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you think this jawbone goes with that skull or this one?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623356" id2="17" version="1065353216">And what about our deaths? Who'll remember those?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623357" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one deserves to end their life in the belly of a rakghoul.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623357" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll try to help your friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623358" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dead need an advocate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623358" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your work is important.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then please, help us. The rakghouls hit our team this morning inside the Czerka Works pipeline. We had to leave them. If anyone's still alive, they don't have much time.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="770246" id2="17" version="1065353216">This better be quick.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="770259" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fascinating.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="770420" id2="17" version="1065353216">You lost me.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="770421" id2="17" version="1065353216">You lost me.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
