<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>43</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/bronze/republic/shatter_the_siege/sergeant_volos.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234051" id2="17" version="1065353216">With those cannons gone, CorSec can finally torch the blasted Imps off our world.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234054" id2="17" version="1065353216">CorSec's already on the move. With those cannons down and the Imp lines broken, you gave us plenty of room to maneuver.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234056" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's gonna be a hot time in Uptown Sector tonight. The Empire will wish it never came here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your team's done its part. Leave the cleanup to us. For Corellia!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234059" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't ask any more of you, Master Jedi. This is our fight now. For Corellia!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234060" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know Havoc Squad's needed elsewhere, sir. Leave the mop-up to my people. For Corellia!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't need Jedi when people like you are around. We'll win this war yet. For Corellia!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234065" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you take out those cannons and clear us a path, I guarantee CorSec will finish the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blasted Imps! We'll die before we give up Corellia! You hear me, you scum?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch yourselves here, people--the Empire's hitting this position with mortar cannons.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234072" id2="17" version="1065353216">This position's not secure, Master Jedi. The Empire's mortar cannons are blasting everything in sight.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234074" id2="17" version="1065353216">I recommend you fall back, sir. The Empire's pounding the sector with mortar cannons.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless you want to wind up as little pieces all over the sector, run. The Empire's mortar cannons are making short work of tourists.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234078" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm leading CorSec commandos to push back Imperial forces, but they're dug in with heavy artillery support. We're getting our tails handed to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234079" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy will kill everyone unless you hold the line.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234079" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must drive back the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234080" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not let fear guide you, Sergeant. Now is the time for courage, resolve and sacrifice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234080" id2="17" version="1065353216">Focus on victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234081" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fight harder, Sergeant. Make those casualties mean something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234081" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never surrender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds to me like the Empire needs a big taste of its own medicine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234082" id2="17" version="1065353216">So return the favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then why stay in the sector?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234084" id2="17" version="1065353216">Retreat's not an option. We'll burn the Empire off Corellia like a sand tick from a bantha--or die trying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234086" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're obviously inept.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234087" id2="17" version="1065353216">CorSec's Tactical Response Teams are the best. My people are giving their lives to burn the Empire out of here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234089" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic High Command is rallying forces to take back this sector, and CorSec's doing its part. We're just not equipped to handle heavy artillery.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234091" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your team looks like it could handle anything. If you can disable those mortar cannons and crack the Empire's forward lines, we'll do the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234092" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll give it our best shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234094" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're too busy. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234096" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi, on the other hand... you could shut down those mortar cannons and punch us an opening through the Empire's forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234097" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know Havoc Squad's reputation, sir. You can knock out those mortar cannons and punch a hole in the Empire's forward lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234098" id2="17" version="1065353216">What we need is heavy artillery of our own. Something to knock out those mortar cannons and scatter the Empire's forward lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="234099" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire won't hold this sector--not if I have anything to say about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234099" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll give it my best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234100" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a noble cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234101" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll tell my men reinforcements have arrived. Report back when it's safe to move out. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knowing the Jedi are on our side will give us hope to keep fighting. Let me know when the way is open.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234103" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I tell the men Havoc Squad is with us, it'll raise morale a thousand percent. Report in when our path is clear, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234104" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're either brave or just crazy, but who cares? We'll take all the help we can get. I'll be waiting to hear from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="234106" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm too busy. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe we can hold out long enough for real reinforcements to arrive. Good luck out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="234111" id2="17" version="1065353216">CorSec will burn the Empire off Corellia one soldier at a time if we have to.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
