<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>80</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/world/coms_away/fixer_66.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714630" id2="17" version="1065353216">The resistance are confiscating their own comm units to figure out what happened. So much for their communications.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714631" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have little to say to each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714632" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's been chatter on the resistance frequencies while you were off planting the ordnance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Resistance grenades have been malfunctioning. Would you know anything about that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toybox had an idea to limit civilian casualties. I went with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714635" id2="17" version="1065353216">We implemented a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714636" id2="17" version="1065353216">No.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Funny, because Toybox said something quite different when I asked him why he still had trapped comms on his table today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714639" id2="17" version="1065353216">He suggested the two of you disobeyed our battle plan and neglected to inform any Imperial units of the rather explosive changes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714641" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a strategy to ensure military targets. I will take both the credit and the blame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714641" id2="17" version="1065353216">I came up with that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Civilian casualties are intentional. Both civilian and resistance must fear the bombs, it's how we kill their morale.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714644" id2="17" version="1065353216">But besides that point, when you countermand my orders, Imperial troops need to be notified of any change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714646" id2="17" version="1065353216">We now have to throw out every salvaged grenade in the mix because we don't know which ones are rigged to blow!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714647" id2="17" version="1065353216">The resistance has to do the same, and they lost soldiers. You're still ahead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714647" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll balance out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714648" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is one point in your favor, but a war of attrition was not what I had in mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that all?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be grateful for your Sith rank. For his part in this, Toybox is going to the stockade to receive lashes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be grateful for Watcher Two's interest in you. For his part, Toybox will go to the stockade for a few days and receive lashes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be grateful you are not part of our rank structure. For his part, Toybox will spend a few days in the stockade and receive lashes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714657" id2="17" version="1065353216">You I cannot punish, but I would offer free advice. There are people on this planet who replace everyday items with explosives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714659" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not push them beyond reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714660" id2="17" version="1065353216">I overstepped my bounds. I apologize.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714660" id2="17" version="1065353216">I failed you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714661" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose that will do. You're lucky you're not in our rank structure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714663" id2="17" version="1065353216">For his part in this, Toybox will spend a few days in the stockade and receive lashes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714665" id2="17" version="1065353216">You I cannot punish, but I doubt we will work together again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714667" id2="17" version="1065353216">The resistance has set off three bombs so far. The first blast sent them scattering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then, of course, they attempted to stay in touch via comm unit, so you can imagine the results. Quite a successful operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714670" id2="17" version="1065353216">They defied the Empire. Now they will fear it again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714670" id2="17" version="1065353216">They deserved their fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714671" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll say. One bomb went off near the resistance's medical bay. They say they're treating wounded on conference room tables now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714673" id2="17" version="1065353216">No problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, it's delivered the punishment. One bomb went off near their medical bay. They'll have quite a time recovering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Has there been any collateral damage?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714676" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about civilians?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Positively. One of the comm units wasn't far from their medical bay, and we think some teenager had the second one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714679" id2="17" version="1065353216">Both are good. Without a medical bay, resistance wounded will suffer, and the boy will serve as a lesson for looters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714681" id2="17" version="1065353216">And with the investigation they'll have to launch to discover our method, we'll be ahead for quite some time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714683" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we get lucky, the resistance will take the units back to the barracks or an armory. Then... bang.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to the front, my lord. Your reputation precedes you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, the apprentice. I was wondering when you'd reach the front lines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714690" id2="17" version="1065353216">The bounty hunter. I've heard of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714692" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Watchers said new agents were in the area. It's good you're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714694" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Fixer 66. I'm with the operations branch of Imperial Intelligence, and if you have a moment, I'd like to show you something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714695" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have my attention, Fixer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714695" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll listen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714696" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714697" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see you're monitoring communications. What more should I know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714697" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such as comm units?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714698" id2="17" version="1065353216">On the left is an ordinary Republic comm unit issued to resistance fighters. You've probably seen hundreds before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714700" id2="17" version="1065353216">This other one is a Republic comm unit that has undergone some surgery. Please look, don't touch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714702" id2="17" version="1065353216">The second one contains a half-kilo of high explosive that detonates when the &quot;talk&quot; button is pressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714703" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume this is meant to deal with the resistance?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714703" id2="17" version="1065353216">A trap for the enemy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714707" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can imagine the effects when it is held to one's ear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714707" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714708" id2="17" version="1065353216">A cruel joke. Better still, an effective one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714708" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714709" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is why I never let my holocom out of my sight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714709" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice trick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714710" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're leaving them next to each other like that, I recommend some kind of sticker.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't mix them up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714711" id2="17" version="1065353216">The plan is to take a few of these sabotaged comm units behind the resistance's lines and plant them on their dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714713" id2="17" version="1065353216">The resistance should soon salvage the comms and take them back to their headquarters. The resulting explosions will cripple and panic them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714715" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd prefer someone like you to take point. Someone who won't break if captured, and who can go without reinforcements. Can you do this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714716" id2="17" version="1065353216">The resistance will soon see death everywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714716" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will annihilate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714717" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your instructors at the Korriban Academy must have loved you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, if that's your business, you certainly came to the right planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714721" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sign me up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Head over to our technical man, a Balmorra local we drafted. The men call him &quot;Toybox.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714724" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'll give you the ordnance and show you how to transport it safely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714726" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have other priorities right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not today. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I won't bother you more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shh. Monitoring radio traffic.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
