<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>29</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/world/imperial/droid_repossession/rehmar_thul.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506404" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Thul grows stronger every day. Your efforts proved invaluable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506405" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sensors detect readings from the facility. The droid factory's back in Thul's control!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506407" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Thul will flourish with our supply of droids replenished. Soon, no one will oppose us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506411" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank goodness! I've been requesting backup all day, but my blasted comm unit's malfunctioning!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506413" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least I'm not completely cursed. You lot look like all the luck I could ever hope for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506415" id2="17" version="1065353216">No matter. You're better than an army of reinforcements, my lord. Just what I require.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506417" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least you've arrived, agent. This operation demands as much precision as force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your presence here could benefit us both. Nothing turns a profit like war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Typical. Nothing ever works when you've got a catastrophe on your hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506423" id2="17" version="1065353216">My mission was to wrest the droid factory from Ulgo's grip, but my men were ambushed and killed. I need the job finished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506424" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's so important about this facility?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="506424" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why fight over a factory?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="506425" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't finish it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506426" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a strategist, not a combat expert. We can't afford another loss here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506428" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not cleaning up after your failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="506428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't involve me in your mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506429" id2="17" version="1065353216">There was no way we could've predicted Ulgo's ambush.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506431" id2="17" version="1065353216">That factory belongs to House Thul! Its droids were made by the Empire to defend and rebuild our crumbling fortresses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since Ulgo stole the facility, our progress has ground to a halt. There's only one way to fix this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506439" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have complete faith in your abilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506442" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry. House Thul takes care of its friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spend more time on Alderaan. You'll soon appreciate the need for Ulgo's defeat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="506449" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't rest until Ulgo's men are in the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh...I'm Miles. Got a plan to take back the factory, with your help. Won't need an army, just these dataspikes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insert 'em into the factory terminals, and I can remotely shut the whole place down. If Ulgo don't stop you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764899" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get past them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764900" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the price is right.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="764902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's the dataspikes. I'll contact you once we're ready for the switch. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not worth it. [Refuse quest]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
