<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>151</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/yavin_4/talos/talos.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah! Just like old times! I haven't been chased by marauding life forms on an expedition since you disappeared. Quite missed the thrill of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171558" id2="17" version="1065353216">We couldn't have done it without you, my lord. This should be everything I need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah! I haven't been on an excavation quite this thrilling since my old master vanished. Never a dull moment when it comes to Sith archaeology, you know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171561" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were a great help. These specimens should be more then enough to conduct the necessary tests.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything to help bring down the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just find something good for practical use.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171564" id2="17" version="1065353216">On the honor of the Drellik family, I'll find something worth pursuing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171566" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alas, moon of Yavin, we part again with your air of mystery unblemished. So, where are we headed next, my lord?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171567" id2="17" version="1065353216">To Odessen, I have allies there who are eager to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Odessen? I've never heard of it. I should bring my journal.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171570" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to have you back, Talos. I've missed our chats.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171571" id2="17" version="1065353216">As have I. As have I.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wherever my mood leads me, be sure to keep up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171574" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are truly a lightning rod for wonders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171576" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, this Alliance of yours, it requires individuals of learning and conviction?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171577" id2="17" version="1065353216">It does. We have to understand how the Eternal Empire so easily overpowered us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then it sounds like the perfect lot to throw in with. Truth be told, the Empire doesn't have its heart in that fight yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171580" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dr. Oggurobb thinks so anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171581" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done so much for my research and asked nothing in return. I am in your debt.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171582" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can see why Oggurobb thought you'd be a good fit for the Alliance. We could use people like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171583" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a colleague of Doctor Juvard Oggurobb? That's wonderful news. I couldn't ask for a better engineering consultant.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171585" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is something I'd like in return. I command an Alliance against Zakuul. I want you to join us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not just a lucky turn of events after all, but still auspicious. Truth be told, the Empire doesn't have its heart in that fight yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171588" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll begin preparations to depart the Yavin system forthwith. Exciting times lay ahead!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171592" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back, my lord. Still no word on our support and the Massassi remain an obstacle.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171593" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will handle them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Back again? You're welcome to take shelter from the elements for as long as you like. Given any more thought to my request?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I've come back to help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171596" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Refuse Mission] I still can't help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wishful thinking, I suppose. Safe travels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh--my lord! It's good to see you whole! I'd half-expected to encounter your ghost in a place like this. Hoped, really.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171601" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to see you alive as well, Talos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171602" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not to cast a pall on the good news, but I'd given quite a bit of thought to your tomb. The ancients would have envied it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171604" id2="17" version="1065353216">You hoped I was dead?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171605" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many believed you had already passed on. I thought you might be able to reach out to me in a place like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171607" id2="17" version="1065353216">It would have been only a minor setback for a Sith of your cunning and knowledge, I'm sure of it!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still clawing through the dirt, I see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171610" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know me, lord--no one else can show the care of a true archaeologist. Bridging the past and the future takes such a careful hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Yavin 4, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171614" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is not the first time you've been here, I know, nor will it be the last, I'm sure. A lifetime of knowledge is buried on this world.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171615" id2="17" version="1065353216">What secrets have brought you here now?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Combating the Order of Revan left me little time for exploration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171617" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's criminal that so much of your time gets stolen away from your true calling. This might cheer you up!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171619" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can feel the dark side pulsing through this place in ways both familiar and foreign.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Echoes of the ancient alchemy of Naga Sadow? Oh--or possibly the man himself? They say his ghost still dwells on this world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps you're even feeling the very thing I'm researching. Could it be calling to you? Wouldn't that be something!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171624" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need for a welcome, we won't be staying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171625" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you say, my lord. Might I share my findings with you before we pack things in? You may find them interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171627" id2="17" version="1065353216">I came to Yavin 4 to study the mechanisms of the Temple of Sacrifice. Your strike team was quite thorough disabling it, but portions are still woven throughout the area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171629" id2="17" version="1065353216">My theory is that this ancient piece of technology may share traits with others built by the Sith Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171630" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such as the Eternal Throne. Good thinking, Talos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spot on, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171633" id2="17" version="1065353216">And your findings so far?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171634" id2="17" version="1065353216">You realize how preposterous that sounds?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171635" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know that it's a tenuous connection, but without access to relics of the Eternal Empire this long shot is the best we have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171637" id2="17" version="1065353216">What little has been revealed about Zakuul indicates that their Eternal Fleet is attuned directly to their emperor's will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171639" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Temple of Sacrifice seemed attuned to our former emperor in a similar way. If you'd help me exhume a few samples, we could take them for analysis.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well, let's not dally about.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't your team handle that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171642" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Massassi warriors dwelling here seem unnaturally drawn to our areas of interest. I've been trying to get military support for a while now.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171643" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see why you brought it up to me. I'll handle them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171644" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Refuse Mission] It's not a priority for them, or for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171645" id2="17" version="1065353216">It just feels like wasted potential left laying about. Chin up, our day will come!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171646" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Bypass Mission] That is far more trouble than it's worth when there are other options.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171647" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Refuse Mission] That's not something I have time for right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171648" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Bypass Mission] You've wasted enough time on this hunch of yours. I have need of you elsewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, my lord. I wouldn't put my own vanity above the needs of my master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171651" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't wait to hear what you've learned of Zakuul. To think, you were the first to make direct contact with such a remote society!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stand down, team! I'd wager we're not looking at an attack. No need to pick a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi are usually quite reasonable. So what brings you out today? A disturbance in the Force? Oh--or the seductive call of the dark side?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171656" id2="17" version="1065353216">You, actually. You come highly recommended as a scholar and my Alliance needs great minds to defeat the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171657" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dark side is no joking matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too true, I've spent enough time in Sith tombs to pay it a healthy respect. That was insensitive--my apologies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171660" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have the look of Special Forces. Scouts, perhaps? So long as you don't trample our work, I'm happy to let you go about yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171661" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm more interested in cooperating. You come highly recommended as a scholar and my Alliance needs great minds to defeat the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you always this cordial to your enemies?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171663" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's never been in my nature to judge a tome by its bindings.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171665" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think scouts would just walk up and announce themselves to the opposing force?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171666" id2="17" version="1065353216">It would be a first, but since you're here I thought I'd clarify our intentions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless, of course, you're a looter. I simply can't abide tomb robbers.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171669" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm more interested in picking at your brain than a tomb wall. You come highly recommended and my Alliance needs great minds to defeat the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey! I wouldn't dream of taking anything that doesn't belong to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171671" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I apologize for casting aspersions on your character.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, with all the deadly traps and horrifying ghosts, it's you guys I should be afraid of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171674" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wouldn't be the first to underestimate the wherewithal of the Imperial Reclamation Service, but deadly traps and ghosts are our daily victuals!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ho! A friendly face. We don't see that too often out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Wrath. Have you come in search of lingering traces of the Sith Emperor? Oh--or yet another hidden scheme missed in the battle with Revan?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171679" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing so dire. You come highly recommended as a scholar and my Alliance needs great minds to defeat the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171680" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seem rather eager for calamity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perish the thought. I only imagine that whatever business brought you here is of great import. I'm intrigued.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171683" id2="17" version="1065353216">What I do is not your concern unless I deign to make it so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me for forgetting my place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171686" id2="17" version="1065353216">My, are you a Mandalorian? Fascinating culture. Carrying on the traditions of an ancient co-mingled species--not unlike our Sith Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171687" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must be the one I'm looking for. My Alliance needs researchers like you to defeat the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess I've got more in common with you Imps than I thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171689" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not my area of expertise but I know the Mandalorians and Sith have a long history. I'd love to compare our records of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171691" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no comparison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171692" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nonsense! The long histories share a--oh, I take your meaning. Forgive me if I caused offense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171694" id2="17" version="1065353216">You haven't been hired to ransack the tombs, have you?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171695" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's you I'm here for. My Alliance needs researchers like you to defeat the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171696" id2="17" version="1065353216">Treasure isn't my preferred form of hunting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171697" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, that's a relief. So much is already destroyed by conflict, why add plunder to the mix?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171699" id2="17" version="1065353216">You calling me a crook?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apologies if I've insulted. I just have an interest in preservation and if your business is contrary to that, I thought we could work something out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Especially not one bearing the hallmarks of a covert operative. Sith Intelligence?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not quite. You come highly recommended as a scholar and my Alliance needs great minds to defeat the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171704" id2="17" version="1065353216">My reputation precedes me? I'm quite tickled.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Formerly Imperial Intelligence. Now, more independent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171707" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no stranger to unconventional career paths myself. Life prefers winding paths, and they really are more scenic anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171709" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you're with the Imperial Reclamation Service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recently returned, after a stint in the direct service of a member of the Dark Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171712" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talos Drellik, at your service. Welcome to my humble expedition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171714" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know what you're thinking: &quot;What dastardly evil could they be unearthing here?&quot; The answer is less sinister than you might assume.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171716" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're studying the Temple of Sacrifice, or parts related anyway. In hindsight I realize that isn't helping my case.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171717" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right, that was destroyed attempting to prevent the Sith Emperor's resurrection. No good can come of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171718" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even if it were inherently evil, which I doubt, knowing its workings can be used for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171720" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should elaborate. Quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171721" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know what you're thinking: &quot;With all the turmoil of the last five years, why devote resources to something like this?&quot; Our interest isn't purely academic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knowledge is power and here lays the closest technological cousin of the Eternal Empire: the Temple of Sacrifice.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171724" id2="17" version="1065353216">That temple was destroyed in the battle with Revan. For good reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171725" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh yes, it's essential functions are antithetical to our goal, but this isn't an act of restoration.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Temple of Sacrifice?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171728" id2="17" version="1065353216">A device intended to feed power to the Sith Emperor through offerings of the living. No longer functional after the fight with Revan.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171730" id2="17" version="1065353216">The two are related?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171731" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's my hypothesis.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171733" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't really need to hear about your work here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171734" id2="17" version="1065353216">If your fight really is with the Eternal Empire, I beg to differ.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171736" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you have a stake in the future of our galaxy, I would beg to differ.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171738" id2="17" version="1065353216">The temple was created by the Emperor's design, much like the Eternal Empire. I suspect there could be shared elements in the technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171740" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're working to exhume functional samples, but the Massassi make the work quite dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171741" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're right, this might give us an edge against the Eternal Empire. I'll help however I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are the Massassi dangerous?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171743" id2="17" version="1065353216">They are ancient Sith bred into hulking warriors through the alchemy of Exar Kun himself. A wondrous anthropological find, were they not so bloodthirsty.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171745" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can take you to Zakuul for that. You've wasted enough time here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quite an offer, but I would be remiss to leave potential breakthroughs unexplored. Especially when we're so close to a discovery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171748" id2="17" version="1065353216">With your assistance I think we could gather what we need before departing. Wouldn't take a day, even.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lead the way, Talos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171750" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the spirit! Here are the locations we should search. I'll be right behind you!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171752" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Refuse Mission] I can't right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171753" id2="17" version="1065353216">A shame. We'll just have to wait for support to arrive. They're weeks out I'm afraid. We'll be here if you change your mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171757" id2="17" version="1065353216">Centuries old... sometimes I forget the kind of being our Sith Emperor really was.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171758" id2="17" version="1065353216">Brr. Did you feel a shiver down your spine too?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without the Force, these mechanisms simply wouldn't function.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Almost finished. I've identified one more sample to excavate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171761" id2="17" version="1065353216">There, that should do it. We should return to camp before any of these pieces are damaged.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171762" id2="17" version="1065353216">This world is a wonder. Such darkness just beneath a tranquil surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173159" id2="17" version="1065353216">Strange... there are pieces here that shouldn't be found together. Very strange.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173161" id2="17" version="1065353216">The time periods are completely at odds... hmm....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173163" id2="17" version="1065353216">In any case, an investigation for another day. Let's continue with our present task.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173164" id2="17" version="1065353216">More elements that don't belong. Hmm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1173165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another piece out of place. I can't quite put my finger on it.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
