<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>30</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/bronze/imperial/derailing_the_rocket_tram/zyman.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235178" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you ever need something exploded, turn to Zyman.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235179" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha! I'd recognize the sound of my own bombs at almost any distance. And was that the sound of a rocket tram crashing I just heard? Sounds like success.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235181" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have my sincerest gratitude. Here. Take one of my smaller explosives. You never know when it might come in handy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235183" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rocket tram must be stopped. Or it's my life, I'm afraid.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235186" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunter. I can tell you're the best. You know how I know? You work for the Empire, and they only hire the best.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235188" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord. It is terrifying to make your acquaintance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235190" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir! Long live the Emperor! May the Empire conquer the whole galaxy!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235192" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah! Friend of the Empire! Long live the Empire!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235194" id2="17" version="1065353216">Name's Zyman, but you can pick what you call me. &quot;Zyman,&quot; or &quot;you,&quot; or &quot;alien scum.&quot; Don't worry, I'm used to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235196" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire needs things exploded, and no one makes stuff go boom like Kapp Zyman. Though, it'd help if the Republic didn't fight back so hard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235197" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the problem?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235198" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can handle the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235199" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd be truly indebted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235201" id2="17" version="1065353216">You talk big, bomb-builder.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235202" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've heard of the third continent of Zarak-Nine? Created by one of my bombs, sunk into a fault line and detonated.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235204" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's using the rocket tram's green line to run fresh troops and supplies across Coronet City. The Empire wants that tram derailed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235206" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got the bombs built, but no way of getting to the tracks and setting them up. The Republic's got squads and snipers patrolling the entire line.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235207" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hasn't the Empire supplied you with any troops for the job?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235207" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could use some soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235208" id2="17" version="1065353216">They did. They all died. When I requested more, they said something about &quot;the stupidity of hiring an alien to get a job done.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then they said something about &quot;Blow up that tram, even if you have to blow yourself up to do it.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235212" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope you'll pardon my rudeness in asking, but I like living. And I'm sure someone like you could destroy those tracks in no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235213" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. Enough guilt-trip.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235214" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235215" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not really. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235216" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can plant the bombs.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235217" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. Truly, I'm indebted to you. Here. Take the bombs and let me know when the job's done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235219" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do it yourself. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, it was worth a shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="235222" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. Perhaps if we place the bombs here... no, who am I kidding. That will never work.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
