<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>27</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/bronze/republic/invisible_foes/captain_grollix.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="537874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't tell you how nice it is not to be looking over my shoulder constantly.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="537876" id2="17" version="1065353216">You stay sharp out there. Otherwise those Sith will cut you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="537877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shh! You hear that? Sounded like... footsteps. Listen!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="537878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Steer clear of the starship graveyard. Trust me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="537880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hm. Maybe it's nothing. But stay on your guard. Death can strike anytime out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="537883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations on a successful op. Hoth will be a safer place without those Sith skulking about.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="740506" id2="17" version="1065353216">A cadre of Sith assassins recovered some prototype stealth units from the starship graveyard. Now they're invisible and slaughtering us at whim.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="740507" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can handle a few Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="740509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Invisible Sith? Not good.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="740516" id2="17" version="1065353216">They &quot;tested&quot; the stealth tech on our patrols first. Wiped out entire platoons before our people could fire off a shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="740518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now they've gotten bolder, started sneaking into the base and killing our troops in their cots. This has to stop. Now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="740522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our scouts picked up their tracks. We have a rough idea of where they're hiding out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="740525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fight back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="740526" id2="17" version="1065353216">How are we supposed to fight those blasted Sith when we can't even see them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="740529" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll defeat the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="740537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Invisible Sith? Not good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="740538" id2="17" version="1065353216">What stealth units?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="740539" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's experimental technology, went down with a Republic troop transport. We spent months searching for it, but the Sith beat us to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="740541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Combating Sith is tough enough, what with all their Force trickery. Now they've got some of the Republic's most advanced technology at their disposal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="740565" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I see you recovered the stealth units. Glad to have our tech back in our hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="740567" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll be nice to get some shut-eye without having to worry about some Sith assassin stabbing me in the back. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="740569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps I can assist.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="740570" id2="17" version="1065353216">You haven't faced Sith like these before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="740573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess I don't have a choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="740575" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those stealth units they're using are Republic property. Bring them back and maybe we can salvage a win out of this debacle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="740577" id2="17" version="1065353216">You stop them. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="740578" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll have to quarantine the entire sector if those Sith aren't dealt with.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
