<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>30</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/sith_sorcerer/chapter_2/event_and_finale/kaal.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483278" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, it looks like Thanaton's man will catch us before you arrive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483280" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corrin and I will try our best to stave him off, but Lord Cineratus is not a man to be trifled with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483282" id2="17" version="1065353216">The item we stole was the key to a hidden entrance to Darth Thanaton's private meditation chambers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483284" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is the perfect ambush spot for when you have enough power to face him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483286" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Corrin and I don't make it, we hope you'll avenge our deaths. Crush Thanaton, and usher in the new era for the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483296" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks as if we have two new travelers, the ghost and a little Jedi pet. Wonderful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483298" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pirate thinks he has another ghost story for us to investigate, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483300" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord! It's Kaal. Your apprentice. Corrin's here with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483302" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have much time to talk. Thanaton tried to make us his. Claimed you were dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483304" id2="17" version="1065353216">We managed to flee Dromund Kaas, but his lords have been hounding us through every sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483305" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd think he'd focus his efforts on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="483305" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483306" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were part of Zash's power base, apparently we need to be destroyed as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483308" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where are you now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="483308" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's your position?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483309" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've set a course for Quesh, a nasty little swamp world. The warfare on the planet should allow us to hide from Thanaton.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483311" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need your help. We took something from Thanaton. Something to help you beat him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="483313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yawn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483314" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, Thanaton insults you by striking at us! It's a signal to other Sith--you're not worthy of apprentices!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Also, we might have... taken something from him. Something to help you beat him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483318" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't talk about it here. If somebody's intercepting this, Thanaton will be at our throats.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483319" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let Thanaton lay a finger on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="483319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold tight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483320" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you give me your location, I can help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="483320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483321" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're near Quesh. We're hoping the warfare there will provide a diversion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="483323" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope this is worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483324" id2="17" version="1065353216">We wouldn't risk our lives for a trifle, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast! Ship's hit... emergency landing on Quesh... hurry!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="483328" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Thanaton kills your apprentices, you will appear very weak indeed. It looks like hunting ghosts will have to wait.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
