<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>64</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/class/republic_trooper/senator_arnus.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534719" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we need anything further, we will have General Garza contact you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant, make yourself comfortable. On behalf of the Senate of the Galactic Republic, I want to thank you for appearing on such short notice for this informal inquiry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534721" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm at your service, Senators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534721" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's an honor to be here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just doing my duty, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534722" id2="17" version="1065353216">No problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534723" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think I'd be here if I had any say in the matter?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like I had a choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534724" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assure you we will not hold you from your duties any longer than necessary, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534726" id2="17" version="1065353216">The purpose of this inquiry is to investigate the defection of several members of Republic Army Special Forces squad number 326, code named &quot;Havoc Squad,&quot; to the Sith Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, you recently served in Havoc Squad on Ord Mantell, Lieutenant. Is that correct?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534729" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right, Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Correct.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534730" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no recollection of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534730" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't remember.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534731" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't play games with us, Lieutenant. This is a serious situation, and your cooperation is required by law.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534733" id2="17" version="1065353216">We understand that your work requires a degree of secrecy, and I assure you nothing you say will leave this room. So please, answer truthfully.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534735" id2="17" version="1065353216">You already know the answer. What are you asking me for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534735" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't waste my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534736" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a simple question, Lieutenant. Your hostility is unwarranted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534738" id2="17" version="1065353216">While serving on Ord Mantell, all of the members of Havoc Squad, excluding yourself, defected to the Sith Empire. Is that correct?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534739" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not recall the events you describe, Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534739" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm unaware of any defections.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534740" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that so? Our sources tell us that not only were you present at the time of the defections, you were, in fact, the one who discovered them!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534742" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Vander's reports on the incident were frustratingly vague--and you, apparently, share his need to conceal the truth!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, Senator, my squad defected right in front of me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534744" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is correct, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534745" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're looking to make a point here, just say it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534745" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you trying to say?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant, you are a soldier of the Republic and sworn to obey the commands of the Senate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534748" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, we're only trying to discover the truth. If critical members of the Republic armed forces have defected, we'll need to take proper precautions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534750" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, did Commander Tavus or any of the other members of Havoc Squad show signs of, say... instability? Anger? Frustration?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534751" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't believe there were any such signs, Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534751" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, sir, none at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534752" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, they were all pretty off-balance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534752" id2="17" version="1065353216">They did, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534753" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid I don't know the people you're referring to all that closely, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534753" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't really know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant! You are lying to the Senate of the Galactic Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, no one wants this to turn into a full-blown investigation. If you just answer honestly now, we can avoid all of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534758" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant, let us speak hypothetically: Do you believe that anyone serving on Ord Mantell should have seen this situation coming?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534759" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, I'm not sure I know what you're referring to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534759" id2="17" version="1065353216">What situation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534760" id2="17" version="1065353216">He refers to the situation in which your entire squad defected to the Sith Empire, and then you failed to aid a Senate investigation into the matter!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534762" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we don't receive satisfactory answers now, we'll have no choice but to open a formal investigation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534764" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think anyone could have seen this coming, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534764" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one could've predicted it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Tavus and the others must have been quite subtle indeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Jorgan worked closely with everyone. He should've known.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aric Jorgan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534768" id2="17" version="1065353216">You son of a--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534770" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have not asked for your input at this time, Sergeant Jorgan. Please remain silent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I see here that the man was demoted for his involvement in the incident... then placed under your own command? That's highly unusual.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534774" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have one final question, Lieutenant: What connection, if any, exists between the events that occurred on Ando Prime and Havoc Squad's decision to defect to--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senator, I would remind you that the circumstances of Ando Prime are classified and occurred before the lieutenant's involvement in Havoc Squad. You may ignore that question, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534777" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you wish, Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534777" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tavus said the Republic left Havoc to die on Ando Prime. Is that true?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ando Prime started everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534779" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I said, Lieutenant, that subject is classified. You needn't trouble yourself about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="534781" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I go now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your part in this inquiry is concluded. You may return to your duties now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Goodbye, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="534788" id2="17" version="1065353216">We did not summon you here. You should leave.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
