<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>28</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/event/bounty_hunting/shared/clients/coruscant_client.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113082" id2="17" version="1065353216">As requested: Samovan Bann.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Samovan Bann will never trouble anyone again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113084" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the news on Samovan Bann?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113085" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got a present for you, Tam.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here, Tam. Proof of partial completion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you the client?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113088" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's it, then. No more reign of terror for that ex-Czerka piece of aurodium-plated trash.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113089" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's really dead? He's really dead. Him and his Black Sun franchise plans. Good riddance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113090" id2="17" version="1065353216">You haven't heard? Ever since his people were yanked out of the picture, Bann's been stepping up the violence in their place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113091" id2="17" version="1065353216">One less Black Sun bottom feeder off the streets. Works for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113092" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got one dead instead of alive, in other words? Music to my ears.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113093" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't look like I could afford to put out a bounty, is that it? Well, truth be told, I can't. Not on a custodian's pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113096" id2="17" version="1065353216">Name's Tam Daral. I represent a bunch of folk like myself--people who lost loved ones to those no-good Black Sun thugs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113099" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some former Czerka exec, Samovan Bann--he wants to revamp Black Sun into a galactic franchise. People working for him are brutal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113100" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make sure these lowlifes are brought to justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1113100" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll avenge them for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113101" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know how to deal with criminals like Black Sun: mercilessly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1113101" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're goners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you asking me to hunt down the entire organization?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1113102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which Black Suns am I after?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113103" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. Doesn't matter how much you dole out to them, they've got it coming. Watch yourself, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113104" id2="17" version="1065353216">You ask around, you'll find the particular scum I'm talking about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only other thing I can think to say is, you know, &quot;good luck.&quot; So, good luck. I'll be here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113109" id2="17" version="1065353216">Justice. A little justice would mean the world to me right now. But a word of caution before you do your thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113113" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me and the rest of us working stiffs thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Raiding local businesses. Firebombing homes. Anything he can do to scare us into submission. And from everything I hear, he's loving every second of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113119" id2="17" version="1065353216">An electrician who lost her kids in one of those fires got a bead on Bann's location. Go get him. Make him pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113121" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish my partner could've been here to share this moment, but you can't have it all, right? Thanks for this.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
