<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>34</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/event/bounty_hunting/shared/clients/dromund_kaas_client.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Trok's life of crime is over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113023" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pawns have been eliminated from play, Officer Manus. You know what comes next.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Officer Manus--I've brought you one of Lord Trok's associates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113025" id2="17" version="1065353216">Officer Manus, I presume. What is this madness about a Sith Lord turning common criminal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Trok is dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113027" id2="17" version="1065353216">The size of Lord Trok's syndicate has been reduced by one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Opted for mercy, I see. Very well. Perhaps I'll have her sent to the Sith Academy for reeducation--if they do that sort of thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113029" id2="17" version="1065353216">A vile corruption, permanently removed from under the Empire's skin. Exhilarating, isn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113030" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose we could use this one to test the efficacy of our interrogation probes. Fine work, as expected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent work. Not that I ever had any doubt, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113037" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must be Officer Manus. Do I understand this contract of yours correctly? A Sith Lord is running rackets?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113038" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know it sounds ludicrous on its surface, but please hear me out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Trok's extremely ambitious, even for a Sith. I know; I used to work with her regularly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113043" id2="17" version="1065353216">Somewhere along the way, her thirst for power became out-and-out greed. She overthrew a prominent crime syndicate on Nar Shaddaa, transplanting their lieutenants here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113044" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle these lieutenants.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1113044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave them to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113045" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never mind the help. I want this errant Sith Lord to face me--now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1113045" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want Trok dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113046" id2="17" version="1065353216">You weren't appointed by the Empire to deal with Lord Trok. Where do your credits come from?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1113046" id2="17" version="1065353216">How are you paying for this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of that I have no doubt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113049" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a contractor? I mean no disrespect, but clearly, your kind are capable of all manner of surprises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113053" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I cannot convince anyone of Lord Trok's guilt, I've had to create a special fund for &quot;extraordinary circumstances&quot;.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113054" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll wish they never set foot on Dromund Kaas--and then they'll be dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1113054" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll gladly take their lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113056" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understandable; however, Lord Trok won't be drawn out unless she feels her operations are in jeopardy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113059" id2="17" version="1065353216">A suitable outcome, to be sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1113061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take care of these outsiders who would dare thumb their noses at the Empire's absolute power, and I'll see to it that you're properly compensated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your payment, and my gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113067" id2="17" version="1065353216">The scrubs are taken care of, Manus. How about we discuss their boss's fate?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. Lord Trok. Any lieutenants still standing in your wake have been wiped out by her, she's so angry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trok's reckless now, leaving herself open to attack--but that doesn't make her vulnerable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113072" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take note of her location, and use it well. I'm quite looking forward to the end of Lord Trok's reign of foolishness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113076" id2="17" version="1065353216">As much as I'd like to, I cannot offer an official commendation. I do hope my honoring the terms of our contract will suffice.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
