<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>34</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/event/bounty_hunting/shared/clients/nar_shaddaa_client.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112756" id2="17" version="1065353216">You took out a contract?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112758" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's one part of your problem taken care of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112760" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand there's now enough information to go after the casino owner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's Arkan for you. I don't think he'll provide much competition for you anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, that's me--Otheros, owner of the Haven's Blaze casino.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112770" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm concerned about the &quot;debt facilitators&quot; hired by the Lucky Runner casino. They're nothing more than gangsters. Street scum--like their boss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112772" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm tired of people thinking we're all criminals. The Haven's Blaze is a legitimate establishment; what's more, these thugs are killing our potential customers!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rest assured they won't be conducting business much longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1112773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112774" id2="17" version="1065353216">By the time I'm through, there won't be a single &quot;facilitator&quot; left breathing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1112774" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're as good as dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you're looking to eliminate the competition, if you ask me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1112775" id2="17" version="1065353216">I question your motives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Happy to hear it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112777" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't say they need to die--but if that's how it has to be done....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Competition only makes me work harder. I welcome competition. This is entirely different.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112780" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've taken the liberty of compiling a list of the places one might find these brutes--nowhere respectable, to be certain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, please excuse me; I'm quite busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112786" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have one of your &quot;facilitators&quot; for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wonderful! Glad there's plenty of space in the casino vault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112788" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, my. Must have put up a fight. Not surprising.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Credits well spent. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112793" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. Your activities have left Arkan vulnerable--well, vulnerable enough to be found, at any rate. He's still quite a danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arkan was raised on the streets. Slaughtered his way into the Lucky Runner, then all the way to the top.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112797" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now he tries to pass himself off as a wealthy businessman like myself, but he's nothing like me. He's a monster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where do I start looking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112799" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know exactly where to find him. I have the coordinates and everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112801" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the other ones, I admit I had some trouble with the idea that they might be killed because of me. But with Arkan, I'd prefer it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arkan will never pose a problem for you or your casino again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112804" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you didn't kill him after all? Just as well, I suppose--I'd been meaning to find a new work of art for my office.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112806" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll call it &quot;Arkan in Carbonite&quot;. It can serve as a reminder to my employees not to press their luck with me. Heh....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112808" id2="17" version="1065353216">So he's dead? He's really dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even though it's what I wanted, I thought I'd feel some sort of remorse over his death. I don't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1112812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for this. It's really opened my eyes. Arkan may have been onto something after all....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
