<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>29</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/event/bounty_hunting/shared/clients/tatooine_client.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113130" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kreegan Ramar's thieving days are over, Meerko.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113131" id2="17" version="1065353216">No more Kreegan Ramar, Meerko. He's dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113132" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, Meerko. The underlings are out of the picture. It's time to deal with Kreegan Ramar himself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113133" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look what I have for you, Meerko.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113134" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here, Meerko. This is practically all that's left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113135" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm here about a Mandalorian named Kreegan Ramar.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1113136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooh! Meerko not sell this metal-freeze bad! Meerko keep as droid-fix table!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1113137" id2="17" version="1065353216">No more big-bad armor-man! Meerko Clan back to trade-sell!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1113138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Metal-freeze bad! Metal-freeze bad! Maybe Meerko Clan sell metal-freeze bad. Or maybe make into swing-wall for home.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1113139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooh. You make armor-man friend dead. Much-much happiness.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1113142" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooh! Meerko get big-time help! Maybe Meerko Clan have much happiness after much-much sadness.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1113144" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meerko want big-bad armor-man gone! He and friends make all Meerko Clan fear. Make much trouble for droid-part sandcrawler trade-sell. Take all Meerko Clan stuff!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ramar's smash-and-grab operation will be over soon, and you'll be able to go about your business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1113145" id2="17" version="1065353216">No more taking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113146" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't be able to toy with you anymore once they've stopped breathing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1113146" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're done for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113147" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any particular reason this Mandalorian is raiding your business as opposed to some other Jawa's?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1113147" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why did Ramar target you?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1113148" id2="17" version="1065353216">No! Meerko do nothing to armor-man. Armor-man greedy. Armor-man bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1113149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooh! Much happiness! Much fear! Meerko more happy than fearing, though, yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1113150" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meerko like this much. Big-time help go smash-and-grab armor-man friends!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1113153" id2="17" version="1065353216">You find big-bad armor-man friends. You stop. Meerko calm. Meerko pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1113162" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meerko calmer now. Meerko pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113164" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be interfering with one of my own, but Ramar's making all Mandalorians look bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1113164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dishonorable for a Mando.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1113169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meerko feel same when have to fight bad-bad Jawas.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1113172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meerko have much fear, but much strength. Let big-bad armor-man attack sandcrawler. Armor-man take more trade-sell stuff. But Meerko make Jawas follow armor-man.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1113175" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now Meerko have location of big-bad armor-man! You get armor-man. Meerko pay lots-lots.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1113184" id2="17" version="1065353216">Much-much happiness! You take pay!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
