<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>80</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/world/republic/sudden_death/commander_bradel.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720708" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lady Katei of the Panteers is waiting for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720709" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've received word from Katei Panteer, the heir to the house. She'd like to meet with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720711" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Panteer's current location is well guarded and not common knowledge, but the brass is granting you temporary clearance to visit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720712" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this just a friendly &quot;thank you,&quot; or is she looking for something more?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720712" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does she want?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720713" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think she hopes you're the heroes Alderaan needs to get that tyrant Ulgo off the throne.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720715" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think she hopes you're the hero Alderaan's been waiting for to get that traitor Ulgo off the throne.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720717" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm honored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720718" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720720" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Panteers owe us... you... their lives now. It's crucial this goodwill lasts long enough to get a Republic government on the throne.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720722" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got better things to do than hold court with some spoiled princess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it part of the job. The Panteers have requested all of you, and it's crucial to the Republic that we keep their goodwill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720725" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I may be so bold, Master Jedi... I'd remind you that the Panteers' goodwill is crucial to putting a friendly government on the throne.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720727" id2="17" version="1065353216">That wasn't a request, Sergeant. You're expected at the Panteer refuge and that's where the Republic needs you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just think of the reward waiting for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720731" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still sucking up, even after they turned their backs on the Republic in its darkest hour--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720733" id2="17" version="1065353216">Politicians are like planets. They orbit around whatever glows the brightest. But that's the game here, and if we don't learn to win it, the Empire will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720735" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for your service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720737" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for taking on those strike teams. I think that's the last of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720739" id2="17" version="1065353216">There aren't many who'd take on such a dangerous mission on short notice. The Republic owes you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720741" id2="17" version="1065353216">But not half as much as House Panteer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Has Bouris Ulgo called off his attack?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are they safe?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720743" id2="17" version="1065353216">The attack is off, for now, but no one on Alderaan is safe while Bouris Ulgo holds the throne.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720745" id2="17" version="1065353216">How much are we talking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Owes?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720746" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was speaking metaphorically, but I'm sure House Panteer will put a figure to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720748" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing I can't do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720749" id2="17" version="1065353216">The reports said the strike was imminent. Go quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720750" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why help the Panteers? They left! The minute the Republic disagreed with them, they up and seceded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720752" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Panteers ruled Alderaan for the past century. If they're still alive, no one takes the throne without their blessing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah. I was hoping you'd make your way here. Major Cressen told me of your actions at the bridge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah. I was hoping you'd come. Commander Keikana spoke highly of your role in defeating the Killiks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720758" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, I was hoping to see you here. Duke Organa has said you prove the strength of the Republic's regard for House Organa.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, you could not have come at a better time. I've heard about your deeds here. Most impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720762" id2="17" version="1065353216">How long were you listening? Are you aware of the situation with House Panteer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Former ruling family, we need their support. Anything new?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720763" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got the basics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720764" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assume I don't know anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720764" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Panteer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me the briefing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alderaan's rulers have come from House Panteer for generations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720768" id2="17" version="1065353216">After the last Panteer queen's death, Bouris Ulgo invaded, slaughtered the entire bloodline. Until a few days ago, we believed he'd wiped them out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720770" id2="17" version="1065353216">However, we have new intelligence that some of the Panteer survived and are in the mountains.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720771" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, that's good news, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720771" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's great.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Except that Bouris Ulgo knows it too, and he's massing strike teams to finish what he started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720774" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does this threaten our plans on Alderaan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720774" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we're with the Organas....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does this threaten your plans on Alderaan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720775" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you're with the Organas....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720776" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Panteers served the Galactic Senate for centuries. Our concern is for their safety. Bouris Ulgo is currently massing strike teams to finish what he started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Skip the history.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bouris Ulgo knows this too, and he's massing strike teams to destroy what's left of House Panteer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720781" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the Republic wants us to risk our lives to stop them!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720783" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic must stand against genocide, Captain Scov.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720785" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the troops I sent never returned. And our reinforcements won't be here in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see how these strike teams like fighting Jedi instead of defenseless nobles.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720786" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720787" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suspect they won't have long to make up their minds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720789" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force cries out at so many deaths.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720789" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must prevent this massacre.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720790" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi are legendary for their compassion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720792" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider me your reinforcements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720792" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720793" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got a weakness for imperiled noble families. So much treasure and so few people to share it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720793" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can probably help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720794" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Panteers survive, I'm certain they'll see you well-rewarded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720796" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do I get?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720797" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Panteers could buy and sell most of the Outer Rim. You'd be well-rewarded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720799" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Ulgos will be staging their move into the mountains for the assault by thranta. To track down the strike teams, look for their transports.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't look here. I've got no obligation to these Panteers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh-uh. Not me. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720804" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be a harsh blow to the freedom of the galaxy should the Empire triumph here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ask anyone--the Republic's fate on Alderaan is tied up with the Panteers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720808" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you change your mind, come back. You could make all the difference in this battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alderaan is a core world of the Republic. We cannot lose it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720813" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're honored to have you, Sergeant.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
