<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>67</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris_imp/world/blackout/lord_komo.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your reputation is well-deserved. Thanks to you, the Republic's access to power has been seriously limited.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Brilliant! With those generators offline and the Republic hungering for a power source, the advantage is ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618427" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope those fools will be quavering in the dark for a good long while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618427" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their weakness is my pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed. I am in your debt. And rest assured, I will spread word of your strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618430" id2="17" version="1065353216">This success should put you in Darth Gravus's good graces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your master will be pleased.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618431" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expect he will be quite satisfied. I am in your debt, and I will gladly spread word of your power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, modesty would feel misplaced. But I am in your debt, and I will gladly spread word of your power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618436" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm also pleased you found evidence of my squad's demise. Perhaps now Gravus will grant me more veteran troopers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618437" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's unfortunate you found no evidence of my squad's demise. But with Gravus appeased, perhaps I can coax more veteran troopers from him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618439" id2="17" version="1065353216">The longer the Republic draws power from those generators, the more secure their foothold becomes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618440" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't brief Lord Gravus now. I need time. Delay him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618442" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord... how? He won't be pleased...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use that undersized brain of yours to think of something, or I'll have it out of its little shell. Dismissed!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618448" id2="17" version="1065353216">My apologies. Such esteemed company is a welcome change from the fools I deal with. And timely, if you would help with my... problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618449" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunter, your reputation precedes you and is a welcome change from the ineptitude here. Your help could make a difference with my... problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618450" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard of you, agent. Such professional talent could make a difference with my... problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me. One wishes for competence, but wishes often go unfulfilled. Perhaps you could help me with a... problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only the weak tolerate fools. Tell me your problem and I will consider it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618452" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have to convince me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618453" id2="17" version="1065353216">The trials of being a Sith--all are fools by comparison. Tell me your problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618453" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have to convince me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever has you so worked up sounds... expensive. Gut feeling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618454" id2="17" version="1065353216">My help isn't cheap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618455" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire pays its debts, have no fear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618457" id2="17" version="1065353216">It depends on why you're dodging a briefing with your lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe, but I have concerns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618458" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you'll find our desires share common ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Threatening your men--while amusing--is not the best way to inspire loyalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quite a temper you've got.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618461" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need results more than loyalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618463" id2="17" version="1065353216">My schedule's full.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618464" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand, but our desires share common ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618466" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've learned the Republic has secured sections of the lower city hydro plant to serve their power needs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Gravus ordered me to destroy their generators, but the squad I sent went missing before they even reached the objective. Useless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meanwhile, the Republic reinforced its position. My men are simply outmatched.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is the hydro plant such a priority?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618471" id2="17" version="1065353216">So why not strike elsewhere?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618472" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't imagine Lord Gravus will let such failure pass unanswered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your master won't be pleased.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618473" id2="17" version="1065353216">True enough. Another failure and he will revoke my command. Fortunately, you and I have converging interests.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your problem, not mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618476" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Republic strengthens its foothold on Taris, it's a problem for us all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Gravus believes cutting off the Republic's power will cripple their operations enough to shift the balance of power on the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618480" id2="17" version="1065353216">With your strength, you could disable those generators and strike a decisive blow against the enemy. And I would keep my lord happy. Agreed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618481" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will crush these Republic fools and leave them in darkness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618481" id2="17" version="1065353216">They will suffer greatly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618482" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will leave them trembling in darkness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618482" id2="17" version="1065353216">They will suffer greatly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618483" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can pay, I'll play.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure, why not?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618484" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've always had a soft spot in my heart for sabotage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count me in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent! Go to the hydro plant. Identify the functional generators and rig them to overload. Watch the Republic wage a war with no power!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Saving you from your master's wrath will put you in my debt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, but you will owe me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well. Go to the hydro plant. Find the functional generators and rig them to overload. I will, as you say, be in your debt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618490" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't care less about your command, but I'm happy to hit the Republic where it hurts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618490" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it for my own reasons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618491" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose that will do. Go to the hydro plant. Find the generators that are still functional and rig them to overload.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618493" id2="17" version="1065353216">And one final request about the squad that went missing today....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618495" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you find any evidence explaining their disappearance, I would be pleased to see it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="618497" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618498" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is unfortunate. Come see me if you reconsider your priorities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="618500" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave me. I have command duties to attend to.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
