<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>392</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/yavin_4/multi/shared/camp_rep.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135839" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place is worse than Rishi! No cantinas, no sabacc games, no fun at all!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135841" id2="17" version="1065353216">My master wishes to report that the surrounding terrain is quite rugged. The Revanites are based in an ancient temple nearby. We found no usable supplies or shelter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135843" id2="17" version="1065353216">The other scouts gave similar reports. There has been some contact with Revanite patrols, but no heavy resistance as yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can feel the Emperor's presence here. I'd know it anywhere. But that presence isn't alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135845" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is so much darkness here... it's difficult to get any sense of specifics in the environment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135846" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor isn't the only Sith to have left his mark on this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135848" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got a base camp, elevation, decent perimeter... bring me up to speed on the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like you've settled in pretty well. Catch me up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135850" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need better eyes on the region around us. Scouts can only patrol so far in brush this dense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135852" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is more than that. I sense their fear. Their distrust. This world is mired in ancient hatreds, and we have brought more than our share already.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was there a suggestion somewhere in all that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135856" id2="17" version="1065353216">The troops are too distracted by each other to keep a proper lookout. They're expecting to be stabbed in the back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'll set an extended perimeter past the outer guards, and make it impartial. Sensor equipment doesn't pick sides.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135859" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can take care of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good, I'm sick of this place already.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135862" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once our position is secure, we can focus on Revan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we know any more about how Revan is intending to bring the Emperor back?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1135863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any word on Revan's plans?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135864" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're thinking about attacking the others while I'm gone? Think again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1135864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't try anything, Marr.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135865" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to get those sensors running. Keep me informed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1135865" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd better get to it, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough. I will wrench the information we need from this... man. The rest can be settled later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why not let Master Satele have a try at that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1137146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Satele should question him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137147" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not push me further.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137148" id2="17" version="1065353216">Violence is what drove him into his current state. More will only make him worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137150" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're welcome to observe everything. But a gentler hand will be more successful--I'm sure of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137151" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm betting the Guard are trained to resist torture.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137152" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got a feeling torture is something this guy has seen plenty of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137154" id2="17" version="1065353216">It can't hurt to try something different. You're free to watch--no secrets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137155" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get this over with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137157" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's more like therapy in there than an interrogation. I think we're close to a breakthrough, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele's techniques are... interesting. And rather effective, I must admit. I think we'll have the information we need very soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137162" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interrogate him however you see fit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1137162" id2="17" version="1065353216">Proceed, Marr.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137163" id2="17" version="1065353216">I encourage you to observe. I have no need for secrets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137184" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Marr's techniques are quite effective. I don't believe we'll have much longer to wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137217" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sense it too. Not the ancient Sith, or the Emperor. Not Revan. Another presence... different from the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137219" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. It is more like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137220" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sense it too. Is it really possible that a light side presence could exist here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137221" id2="17" version="1065353216">The light can flourish anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137223" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137225" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you saying there's another Jedi somewhere near us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137226" id2="17" version="1065353216">No Jedi could survive here alone. It is a vestige at most.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137228" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sell us a bit short, Marr.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137230" id2="17" version="1065353216">But, in answer to your question, no: the presence isn't exactly that of a Jedi, either. It's still very difficult to pinpoint.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sensors are picking up something a bit more solid. Large structures, mixture of ancient and modern materials... looks like they've been ransacked. Lots of debris.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137234" id2="17" version="1065353216">Check for broadcasts in signal range forty-seven point two.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137236" id2="17" version="1065353216">What am I seeing here? It's encoded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137238" id2="17" version="1065353216">The facts behind a rumor. That signal range is used only by the Imperial Guard. The structure we've found must be their training facility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137239" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fought the Imperial Guard on Corellia. They were dangerous opponents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1137239" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperial Guard are tough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137240" id2="17" version="1065353216">They might be broadcasting something we could use. Can you decode it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1137240" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are they broadcasting?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137241" id2="17" version="1065353216">No--only the Guard has that capability. But given the destruction Theron describes, it's most likely a distress call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137243" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rumor? Are you telling us you never knew where the Imperial Guard came from?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1137243" id2="17" version="1065353216">A rumor? What do you mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137244" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor's inner circle guards its secrets carefully.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137246" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Guard has a facility here, they may have information on the Emperor's hiding place--that would lead us straight to Revan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. As this concerns only Imperial interests, I will assemble a team of my own to investigate. Beniko--with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137250" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't sit back and watch. There's no telling what they might pull out of that facility--we can't just take their word for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137252" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry--while Marr is gathering his team. Make your way out of the camp and search the Imperial Guard base, as quickly as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137254" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll stall the Imps as much as we can. Let's just hope this doesn't turn ugly....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1137255" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137257" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll need our full strength to defeat Revan when the time comes. Don't do anything to jeopardize that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137258" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith are prone to aggression as it is. Don't give them a reason to indulge their darkness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137259" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't start a fight just to cover for me. It's not worth the risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137260" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just don't get in over your heads. That's more my specialty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1137261" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure this is wise?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137263" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one knows betrayal better than Sith. They won't ignore what we're doing here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trust is in very short supply right now. I'm not sure it's best to gamble what little we have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137265" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen more than one covert op that backfired when the truth came out. Is this worth the risk?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody likes getting conned, and Sith aren't exactly forgiving. Doing this could wreck the truce for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1137267" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugly is fine with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137269" id2="17" version="1065353216">Try not to start any serious fighting until I'm back. I wouldn't want to miss out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137270" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I return, and all of the Imperials are dead? All the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137271" id2="17" version="1065353216">If things get bloody, just be sure to leave some Imps for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1137272" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't mind seeing a few less Imps around camp when I get back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138195" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are we ready?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138196" id2="17" version="1065353216">All teams report ready. You've done very well--all of the soldiers here look up to you, Imperial and Republic both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138198" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's proceed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138200" id2="17" version="1065353216">All units--move out!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138204" id2="17" version="1065353216">All units report success. The weapon has been shut down, and all Revanites neutralized. Only one more left to deal with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138207" id2="17" version="1065353216">My team shut down the Sith device. Revan tried to intervene, but we managed to drive him away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138208" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive. We have prepared a joint assault force to secure the area and pacify any remaining enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Iven told us where Revan might go. The Emperor's final sanctuary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138212" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got speeders prepped. You won't be facing him alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138213" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then let's begin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138214" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take all the backup I can get. Let's move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138217" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, then. Let's settle this so we can all go home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138220" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was an Imperial matter. Your Jedi had no place in it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138222" id2="17" version="1065353216">I told you this was an Imperial matter. Your soldier's involvement was... unwelcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138224" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was an Imperial matter. Your... associate... was not needed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138226" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're supposed to be working together. If the situations were reversed, wouldn't you have done the same thing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138228" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't trust us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138229" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you trusted us, having me involved wouldn't have been an issue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138229" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you trust us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138230" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a dangerous game you play.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138232" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were concerned, and we acted. We should have left this to you. Apologies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138232" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right--and we're sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138233" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't speak for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138235" id2="17" version="1065353216">Betrayal is the core of your beliefs! You can't honestly find this surprising.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138235" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get over it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138236" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it surprise that you hear in my voice?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kill each other now, wait until later, it's all the same! It all fuels the flame!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138244" id2="17" version="1065353216">Allowing this torture makes us no better than Revan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138245" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can be better than Revan after he's dealt with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138246" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to meditate on the path ahead. There must be a way forward without such sacrifices.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138248" id2="17" version="1065353216">And at least a few of us had better check up on Marr and Lana.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138249" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not pretty in there. Don't think the guy can hold out much longer, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138251" id2="17" version="1065353216">We cut it pretty close on this one. Doesn't take a Jedi to see how angry Marr was.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138253" id2="17" version="1065353216">How are you holding up? Everything has been happening so fast....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138254" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been through my share of tough times. I can handle this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138254" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be all right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138255" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to hear. I have a feeling things are only going to get tougher.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138257" id2="17" version="1065353216">You had mentioned that you weren't particularly close to your mother... has working together been good or bad?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138257" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Honestly, I'm not sure. There hasn't been a lot of time to think about it. But we work well together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138260" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been chasing Revan down long enough. I just want to end this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138260" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready to finish this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138261" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't agree more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138265" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want you to know, I advised against Marr's plan with the Guard facility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138267" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've come so far together... I'd hate to see that progress ruined by territoriality.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138268" id2="17" version="1065353216">This truce is only as strong as our trust in each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138268" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138269" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then with our guidance, I think it can only become stronger as we proceed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you worried about keeping the truce together, or were you thinking more about the two of us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this about the truce, or us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138272" id2="17" version="1065353216">Both, I suppose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138274" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you don't agree with Marr, why follow him? Just kill him and take his place--that's how it works for Sith, isn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138274" id2="17" version="1065353216">So take Marr down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Short-sighted infighting is what brought the Empire to its current state. I won't take part in that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1138279" id2="17" version="1065353216">The guard broke! He is telling them everything!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138281" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought the interrogation we faced on Manaan was severe... Darth Marr made that little session seem like a picnic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138282" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must say, Master Satele is quite a pleasant interrogator. Theron should be quite proud!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138283" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's find out what we're up against.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138286" id2="17" version="1065353216">A &quot;device for mass ritual sacrifice&quot;? That's seriously what he called it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Capable of killing every living thing on this moon, as fuel for the Emperor's resurrection.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138290" id2="17" version="1065353216">And housed within the very temple the Revanites are using as their base of operations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138297" id2="17" version="1065353216">So we'll have to breach the temple and shut the weapon down before Revan can activate it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138298" id2="17" version="1065353216">Getting inside at all will be challenging enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138300" id2="17" version="1065353216">The temple entrance has a locking system that can be overridden from the outside, provided we find the right mechanisms.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138302" id2="17" version="1065353216">On it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1138304" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is strange that one bad deal could lead us to such bizarre circumstances.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138306" id2="17" version="1065353216">I certainly never thought we'd be killed by an ancient Sith murder machine!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1138308" id2="17" version="1065353216">The life of Jakarro has been full of fine adventures, but this one is the greatest of all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138309" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're fortunate to have run into each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138309" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to have your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138310" id2="17" version="1065353216">You might not be so grateful if we don't get that weapon shut down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank me when we win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138311" id2="17" version="1065353216">We didn't exactly have a choice. Everywhere we go, you follow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1138311" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't seem to get rid of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1138312" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need our help! There is no shame in admitting it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Among the most dangerous in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138317" id2="17" version="1065353216">We won't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138319" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have any other options. Trust is hard enough when we're on even footing. If they get an edge on us? Forget it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138321" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, hurry. And may the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's just hope it doesn't come to that, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138324" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything about the Emperor is a mystery, even to the Dark Council. Speed is our only ally now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1138330" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll keep in touch while you're getting those sensors up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139520" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials are leaving a small force of volunteers behind to watch for any further activity from the Revanites or the Emperor. We'll be doing the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your actions are... confusing, to say the least. I don't appreciate being left in the dark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does the Supreme Commander share these concerns, Chancellor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139529" id2="17" version="1065353216">He does not. But that is hardly--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139531" id2="17" version="1065353216">The two of us have been fighting this war for quite some time now. We know what we're doing--and we appreciate your trust in us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just as I'll appreciate being informed when your fleet is back in position. Saresh out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139535" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess ignoring the boss runs in the family.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where are we planning to go from here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139536" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's our next move?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139537" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing left for us on Yavin Four anyway. No point in staying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139537" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were done here anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ignoring Saresh is always a good idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139538" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never liked Saresh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never knew you were so political.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our forces are preparing to launch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139543" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should make sure ours are ready to do the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139545" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's strange. The next time we meet, our circumstances will be... quite different.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, don't take it personally, but I'm hoping that you'll never see me again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah. And I'll hope that I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139551" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm gonna see if Satele needs any help. Catch me later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well. Our time has come, even sooner than I'd feared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139555" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan is gone. We've accomplished what we set out to do. But now we have an entirely new problem, and no truce to face it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know if the Dark Council has a plan for how to move forward?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does the Empire have a plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139557" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've shown that it's possible to ignore our differences. Maybe there's hope for a real treaty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139557" id2="17" version="1065353216">So let's get the truce back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139558" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not afraid of the Emperor. He'll be taken care of soon enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139558" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139559" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish I shared your optimism.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139561" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's next for the illustrious Jedi? It sounded as though your Grand Master is about to become quite busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139562" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will go wherever the Council decides I'm needed. That's the life of a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever the Order requires.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139563" id2="17" version="1065353216">We aren't so different after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139565" id2="17" version="1065353216">I walk whatever path the Force lays out for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139565" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139566" id2="17" version="1065353216">You always seem to find your way into the middle of grand things regardless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139568" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you were to abandon the Sith, I imagine I'd be busy teaching you our ways.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Depends, will you defect?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139569" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid that won't be possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139571" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's next for the Republic's most decorated soldier? Surely even Havoc Squad gets vacations every now and then?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139572" id2="17" version="1065353216">With everything that's happened, I doubt I'll have the chance for any vacation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139572" id2="17" version="1065353216">No time for a break.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I'll just disappear for a bit. Surely the Republic can get by without me for a little while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vacation would be nice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bringing in a Sith defector will mean lots of forms to fill out. It'd be worth it, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Depends, will you defect?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139575" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's next for the galaxy's most notorious smuggler? After everything that's happened, I imagine you're even more in-demand than ever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139576" id2="17" version="1065353216">I go where the work is, and the Republic's bound to have a lot of it coming up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139576" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got that right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139577" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure the Republic will ask me for one thing or another. Parades, banquets... few medals, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139577" id2="17" version="1065353216">A break would be nice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139578" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was figuring we'd be going on a tour of the galaxy's finer hot spots.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Depends--will you come with me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139579" id2="17" version="1065353216">If only.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139581" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not at all sure what my future holds. But the future doesn't have to start for a while yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139583" id2="17" version="1065353216">For now... I'd like to make the most of the present.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. [Kiss her]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139586" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing I'd like more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139589" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to miss you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139590" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to miss you, too, Lana.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139590" id2="17" version="1065353216">The feeling is mutual.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139592" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me a call if you ever want to change sides.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139592" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can still defect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139593" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be the first to know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on. Sith aren't supposed to go in for all that mushy nonsense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get sentimental.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith do whatever they like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139597" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've gone as far as we can go, Lana. Any further, and we'll both regret it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139597" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to move on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hm. Suit yourself. But I would rather regret something I did, than something I was afraid to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139603" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad we could put aside our differences and achieve so much. It's been quite interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139604" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been a pleasure working with you, Lana. Strange, but a pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139606" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have to go back, Lana. You aren't like them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why return to the Empire?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139607" id2="17" version="1065353216">This truce ends the moment you're gone. If we meet again, don't expect any mercy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139607" id2="17" version="1065353216">From now on, you're the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139608" id2="17" version="1065353216">A traditional Sith farewell. You're so thoughtful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until next time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well. Quite a ride, huh? Revan's down, the conspiracy's over... I even got my job back. Wonders never cease.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139613" id2="17" version="1065353216">The SIS is lucky to have you back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well deserved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139614" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the Emperor back, I have a feeling things are going to get even more interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139614" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ride isn't over yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139615" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor still managed to come back. I'd call that a mixed result at best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139615" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could've done better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139616" id2="17" version="1065353216">We did everything we possibly could have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139618" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's funny. You're this famous Jedi, but since we started working together, you've been a spy, a saboteur, a fake pirate... How'd you pull it all off so well?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139619" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi's responsibilities can lead to many different situations. Adaptability is important.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi must be adaptable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Honestly, I feel more at home with all of that than I ever have meditating in the temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139620" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never fit in with the Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139621" id2="17" version="1065353216">With help as good as you, everything is easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teamwork is everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139622" id2="17" version="1065353216">I always knew you were one hell of a soldier. But it turns out you can swing the spy game, work undercover, even run with a bunch of pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139623" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wasn't surprised that you could hold your own with the underworld crowd. But all this spycraft, sabotage, tracking down targets... not exactly textbook smuggler stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139624" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know how else to explain it. I'm just really good at everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139624" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just that good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139625" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I'd known there was a textbook, I'd have pretended to read it by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139625" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a textbook?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139626" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's possible you might have pitched in a little bit along the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139626" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may have helped a little.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139627" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess there's at least an outside chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before we get going... there's just one last thing I had in mind. If you think you can keep up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139630" id2="17" version="1065353216">...Is that what you had in mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139630" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're on. [Kiss him]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139631" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a start.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just like I thought. Good at everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on. Let's go see what's next for the best in the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139638" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've had fun, Theron. But you have your life, and I have mine. We'd never match up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1139638" id2="17" version="1065353216">We shouldn't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hm. Can't win 'em all, I guess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on. Let's go check up on the bosses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1139643" id2="17" version="1065353216">All units report success. The temple is secured, and all remaining Revanites have been downed. Just one left, now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1140233" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't count me as one of your volunteers!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140235" id2="17" version="1065353216">As it happens, Jakarro and I have received several lucrative business offers. Various acquaintances made on Rishi, nothing to concern yourselves with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140237" id2="17" version="1065353216">That being said, we have sincerely enjoyed our time with you, and would gladly provide our services again at any time!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1140239" id2="17" version="1065353216">The droid babbles, but speaks the truth. This has been fun!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140240" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope these new opportunities go better than the Manaan job. Take care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140240" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck to you both.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1140241" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will do that! No one will fool the mighty Jakarro again!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140243" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why go work with someone else? I'd be happy to have you stick around and join my crew.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140243" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should join my crew.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140244" id2="17" version="1065353216">A tempting offer!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1140246" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mighty Jakarro will consider it--but for now, these deals are too good to pass up!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140249" id2="17" version="1065353216">I honestly can't believe we put up with you as long as we did. Beat it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140249" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good riddance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140250" id2="17" version="1065353216">How dare you! After everything we've done!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1140252" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget this, we have credits to make!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140254" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your work against Revan and his followers has been truly exceptional. And your expertise in combating the Emperor is second to none.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140256" id2="17" version="1065353216">You embody every ideal in the Jedi Code. The Council is unanimous in its decision to name you Battlemaster of the order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140258" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Council has often sensed darkness in your actions, and we hope to guide you away from such influence. But your prowess cannot be dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140260" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do not always follow a path the Council understands. But we have seen the results of your unorthodox approach time and again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140262" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hereby name you Battlemaster of the Jedi Order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140264" id2="17" version="1065353216">As Battlemaster, your strategic insights will guide the Council's decisions, and you will share your lightsaber skills with the order's most promising students.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140266" id2="17" version="1065353216">But most important of all, you will lead the charge against the Sith Emperor, along with any who choose to follow him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140267" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am honored to be chosen for this role in the order. I will do everything I can to fulfill my duties with wisdom and skill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140267" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you very much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140268" id2="17" version="1065353216">With your help, I believe we can finally bring an end to the Emperor's assaults on the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140270" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready. How should we begin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140270" id2="17" version="1065353216">When do we start?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140271" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to know that the Council finally appreciates what I'm capable of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally, proper acknowledgment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140272" id2="17" version="1065353216">What we are capable of and what we accomplish are often different. We're hoping you'll accomplish a great deal of good in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your role in bringing light to the Revanites' conspiracy is only further proof of your tremendous skill and connection to the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140276" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's more, you've battled against the Children of the Emperor and triumphed where so many others fell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140278" id2="17" version="1065353216">The order needs to remain vigilant against the Emperor's influences, and to uncover the true origins of his power so that we can fight him more effectively.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140280" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Council is proud to have such an ideal Jedi to lead those efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140282" id2="17" version="1065353216">Despite the darkness we have sensed in you, the Council can think of no one better suited to lead those efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140284" id2="17" version="1065353216">You walk a... unique path, but your insights are equally unique, and the council believes that you are the best choice for our investigations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140286" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations, Barsen'thor. You will be the light that guides us through the coming darkness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140287" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a grave task, and I'm honored that you would entrust it to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140287" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you very much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knowledge will be our greatest weapon in the battles to come.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140290" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no time to waste--the Emperor is already far ahead of us. Where can I begin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140290" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should begin immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140291" id2="17" version="1065353216">After all that I've accomplished, you think this is a suitable reward?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140291" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not much of a reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to your old boss, SpecForce division is going through some changes. We can't afford to lose Havoc Squad in that mire of bureaucracy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140294" id2="17" version="1065353216">A special joint task force is being assembled between the Jedi, the SIS, and the military. Destroying the Sith Emperor is the group's sole purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140296" id2="17" version="1065353216">On the recommendation of Supreme Commander Malcom, you have been appointed to serve as the task force's primary military advisor. Congratulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140297" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't think of a more important mission to be a part of. I'm honored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140297" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you very much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140298" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we have any intel to act on yet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140298" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do we know so far?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140299" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take whatever title you want. But don't expect me to sit behind a desk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't pull me out of the field.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140300" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this situation with the Revanites has proven anything, it's the value of having eyes and ears outside of the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140302" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done good work as a licensed privateer, but the SIS wants you to be able to go even further.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140304" id2="17" version="1065353216">This card is programmed with authorization codes from the director of the SIS himself. Complete immunity from Republic prosecution of any kind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take any job you can find, if you think it might lead to information on the Emperor and his followers. I mean it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140307" id2="17" version="1065353216">The minute I hear anything useful, I'll send it your way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140307" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140308" id2="17" version="1065353216">This has to be the best reward I've ever gotten for a job. I can't decide where to go first!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140308" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't wait to try it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140309" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, sure, I'll get right on that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140309" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] Of course! You've got it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just don't make us regret trusting you, all right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140312" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're attempting to calculate where the Emperor might have gone, but we don't know enough about his capabilities to determine anything for sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140314" id2="17" version="1065353216">While we get the task force up and running, we're going to need you out there, acting on your own. Follow every lead you can find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until the Emperor is destroyed for good, the entire galaxy is in danger. We must be ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140514" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's more for us to discuss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140516" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was not intended as a reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140518" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're lucky to have you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wouldn't dream of it. &quot;Primary military advisor&quot; just sounded nicer than &quot;head bad-guy killer.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just remember, that only works for Republic security forces. You get arrested on some unaligned planet nobody's heard of, you're on your own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140526" id2="17" version="1065353216">And remember, the threat of the Empire remains--they will not hesitate to use this situation to gain an advantage over us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Back to toeing the line, at least for a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140531" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't, though Marr did ask to speak with me as soon as we've launched.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Despite our work here, trust is still in short supply. We can thank the Revanites for that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Neither will I.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140537" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd say you've earned it. Though I doubt your superiors would be interested in my opinion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140539" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate the offer, but... no.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I'd say so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140544" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I'll probably just take off on my own for a bit first. It's about time I enjoyed some of my credits again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140545" id2="17" version="1065353216">As sound a plan as I've ever heard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140547" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate the invitation. But the Empire is my home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I get that in writing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140551" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd bet on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our jobs have a lot in common.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140555" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could say the same about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140557" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't say that surprises me too much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soldiers are only as good as their training, and I went through my share.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Training is everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140560" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then your teachers deserve some medals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140562" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did it all because I had your help every step of the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140562" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's all about teamwork.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Other than when I was captured. But I appreciate the sentiment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140565" id2="17" version="1065353216">Following orders, staying in formations... I've never been big on any of it. Missions like this are much more exciting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1140565" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was the fun stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140566" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't have to convince me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140568" id2="17" version="1065353216">That a fact?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140570" id2="17" version="1065353216">There can't be much left to learn anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1140573" id2="17" version="1065353216">This has all been much more fun than dying at the bottom of an ocean!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1140575" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have never seen you fail before! You will not start now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think I've found the locks Iven mentioned. You'd better get out there and take a look--we'll feed you info as we find it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140580" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force serve you well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142584" id2="17" version="1065353216">...I'm sure we'll be fine. I'll stay in contact while you're getting those sensors up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on. We'd better go check up on the bosses.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1145921" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thank you, tiny friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1147118" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're on. [Kiss him]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
