<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>76</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/bronze/republic/lab_animals/doctor_rassan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169845" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure how to explain this on the insurance claim....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it done? Did you thoroughly decon the lab?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169847" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever research you were doing, stop. Those creatures were monstrosities!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing could be worth that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169849" id2="17" version="1065353216">We had expressed some concerns to upper management about the direction the experiments were going....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps we'll turn our research to counter-bioweapon applications. I've seen some of what the Imperials are testing....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169852" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's done. Pay me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. I'll arrange a transfer... the rest of our grant money. We'll be writing the whole thing off to insurance anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. Without your quick work, all of Nar Shaddaa might have fallen to the plague.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169857" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please hurry. If the lab isn't decontaminated, who knows how quickly the virus might spread.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't go in there!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait! I know you. I've seen your faces. Maybe you could help before this gets out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169862" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh! Master Jedi! Thank goodness you're here. You're exactly who we need to deal with this mess before it goes public.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh! You're Republic military, right? Thank goodness you got here before this went any further.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait. Are you...? You look familiar. Have you done work for the Republic? Or would you be willing to now?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169868" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm the chief scientist at ChemFlex. Our rival Xenobi sent a sabotage team to--forget the details. We've got hundreds of lab animals loose down there!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169869" id2="17" version="1065353216">What animals? Are they dangerous?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lab animals?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169870" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm here for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just contain the whole place. Kill everyone in it. They're all infected by now....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169873" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not getting involved in your internal corporate rivalries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169873" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a private matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169874" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't ask you to. But this threatens the whole planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169876" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been working with biotoxins, viruses native to Nar Shaddaa that are highly communicable and lethal to every sentient species we've tested.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169878" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they escape, it could cause a pandemic... and if the press learns the Republic's doing bioweapons experiments....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169879" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will make sure nothing spreads this plague.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169879" id2="17" version="1065353216">We cannot risk it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Master Jedi. Your compassion is legendary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169882" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expect to find unethical human experiments in an Imperial lab, not one of our own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169882" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic should stop.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169883" id2="17" version="1065353216">We tried to keep the protocols humane. But when Xenobi attacked... everything in there is infected by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169885" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle your cleanup... and make a full report to High Command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's keep that classified.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169886" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand. Do what you have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="169888" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't heard the words &quot;great reward,&quot; once yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169888" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's in it for me?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169889" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll pay you the remainder of our grant from the project. Just please hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169891" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have something in mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Xenobi's thugs are still in there. They're almost certainly infected by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169894" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have just enough inoculation doses left to protect you from the virus. Once injected, you can enter the lab without fear of contagion....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you're in, kill anything alive, then release the decon spray hoses. It's the only way to cut our losses now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="169898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169899" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was hoping you'd see reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="169901" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew doing delicate research on Nar Shaddaa would backfire on us....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656953" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks again. But if you run into any Imperials, we never met, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, Doc Rassan, your friend is back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, Doc Rassan, your friends are back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656962" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you'll excuse me, I must return to the lab. This is going to involve a lot of paperwork.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks a lot. The doc's maybe a little focused on his work, but he's a good guy, really. Some of the boys will get him to the lab safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656966" id2="17" version="1065353216">How's that &quot;favor&quot; coming?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Friends. I take it we have a common enemy, and maybe a common friend. You're with the Republic, eh?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656971" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi? First, can I just say what a great honor and privilege it is to meet a Jedi?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656973" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're Havoc Squad, aren't you? My old man was a Republic grunt. The stories he told....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Friend. I've seen you doing work for the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656977" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make this quick. A friend of mine needs help. Urgent-like.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656979" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's a Republic scientist. Empire trashed his lab. Me and the other workers are hiding him here, but we can't keep him safe forever. The Imperials are getting suspicious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="656980" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do my duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656981" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like to think I'd do the same in your shoes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="656983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make it quick.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656984" id2="17" version="1065353216">You won't regret it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="656986" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see what I can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doc Rassan. You can come out. These folks are on our side.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doc Rassan. You can come out. He's on our side.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doc Rassan. You can come out. She's on our side.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Greggo. And thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656995" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm chief scientist at ChemFlex doing research for the Republic. Or I was. I doubt that will hold true now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656997" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire found out about us. They sent thugs to sabotage--forget the details. We've got hundreds of lab animals loose down there! I barely escaped with my life!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="656998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like sick experiments.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="656999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your concerns are merited, I'm afraid.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="657000" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they escape, it could cause a pandemic... but that's nothing compared to what will happen if one of the Empire's thugs manages to escape with the formula.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="657001" id2="17" version="1065353216">We tried to keep the protocols humane. But when the Empire attacked... everything in there is infected by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="657002" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's thugs--of course they didn't send their own soldiers--are still in there. They're almost certainly infected by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="657005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better get going. We can't let the Empire catch the doc here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="657007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on, friend. Please give it another thought. We have to stop the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="657009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, if the Empire catches me talking to you....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
