<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>53</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/world/republic/savage_attack/captain_armaruk.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667244" id2="17" version="1065353216">We mourn a loss. You have our thanks--for answers and for vengeance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667246" id2="17" version="1065353216">I located the remains of your recon team. There was no Talz among them, but I did find the combat sensor logs.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667247" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no Talz? But... we see him die in his final transmission. He is our only son.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667248" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't realize. I'm sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667249" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no time to grieve. Our son wants the mission completed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667251" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analyze the combat logs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667252" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analyze the combat logs.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667253" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is work to do. We are finding retribution against the enemy who kills our son.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667255" id2="17" version="1065353216">You both knew the risks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667256" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it is your child dying, you are not so indifferent to the pain.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667258" id2="17" version="1065353216">The combat logs require time to analyze. Patience....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667260" id2="17" version="1065353216">These readings do not make sense. Wampas, whitefangs, skels--all working together. Attacking as one. Something leads them. The sensors do not identify it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667261" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we keep looking.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667262" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is beyond our ability to help you--but there are others, close by.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667264" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what does all that mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hoth's predators are natural enemies--but here they kill together, like an army. Something unknown leads them. That is our true foe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667267" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another useless dead end.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before, there is a hidden enemy. Now, we know its shape and means of attack. This is progress.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667270" id2="17" version="1065353216">The sensor logs show the beast's leader moves toward the Jagged Plains. Republic forces are there. You must warn them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667272" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is a group of Jedi at the outpost. They are useful allies. Show them the sensor logs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667273" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay. Get yourself indoors.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667274" id2="17" version="1065353216">We remain on watch. If the enemy appears, we will not hesitate to strike.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667276" id2="17" version="1065353216">But what about you?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667277" id2="17" version="1065353216">We mourn our son in private. There are songs to sing, words to recite. They are not for your ears.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667279" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll deal with this my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667280" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi pursue our mutual quarry. They know more than they tell us. Perhaps they tell you more.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667282" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go to the Republic outpost on Jagged Plains. Find the Jedi. Make my son's murderer pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667286" id2="17" version="1065353216">You retrieve the combat sensor logs. They contain the answers we seek.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667289" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are General Nadab's team. We greet you as fellow Republic warriors.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667291" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are General Nadab's recruit? This is no fight for lone warriors.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667293" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are Captain Armaruk, recon team leader. We fear we send you to a quick death, like all our teammates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667294" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry for your loss.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667295" id2="17" version="1065353216">All who are seeking the hidden enemy hope not to find it. That path ends in death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667297" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why say &quot;we&quot;? You're alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667298" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are Talz, and all Talz are one. Talz remind ourselves of this always. Our language is not your concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667300" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were bad at their jobs.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667301" id2="17" version="1065353216">We lead the best recon team on Hoth. We find Imperial bases and White Maw hideouts. Now, we find death.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667303" id2="17" version="1065353216">We receive a distress call from our team, minutes ago. The enemy that butchers without mercy attacks them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667305" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last survivor is a brave Talz. He transmits a final message and speaks of a &quot;living shadow.&quot; There is nothing more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667306" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a clue we can follow.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667307" id2="17" version="1065353216">We plan for every outcome. We know the team's death is possible. They do not die in vain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667309" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no way to save him?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scout team's death is fate. Brave Talz's death is past. There is no changing these things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667312" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're off to a lousy start.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667313" id2="17" version="1065353216">You understand our fear for your safety. This enemy kills all that it finds.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667315" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is still hope of victory--revenge for the fallen. Our team carries advanced combat sensors. They are always recording.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Combat sensor logs contain readouts, scans, data. Analysis reveals our enemy's face. You retrieve the combat sensor logs from the ambush site.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667318" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. I'll get the sensor logs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667319" id2="17" version="1065353216">This seems like a long shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667320" id2="17" version="1065353216">The combat sensor logs are our best hope--to know the hidden enemy, find it and kill it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough weird talk. Just point.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry. Go to these coordinates, recover the combat sensor logs and return them to us. Hopefully, you do not die.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667325" id2="17" version="1065353216">We monitor a mission. Do not interrupt us.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
