<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>137</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/world/republic/savage_attack/general_ilic_nadab.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our weapons will make the Imperials and White Maw sorry they were ever born.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667327" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're slowly gaining ground in Clabburn Sector. We'll win this planet yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back. Word's all over the comm channels of your victory against a Sith and... some beast army? Just when I think I've heard it all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667330" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad I had a Jedi war hero around to handle things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667331" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was just doing what had to be done, General. The Force was with us today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667331" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Today and until this war's over, I hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667334" id2="17" version="1065353216">For a diplomat, you're certainly good at eliminating a threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi must be ready to fight when words aren't enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667335" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm more than a negotiator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Words won't solve anything on Hoth. Nobody's listening.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad earns its reputation again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667339" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we didn't keep achieving the impossible, my people would get bored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Happy to serve, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667340" id2="17" version="1065353216">The best of the best, indeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667342" id2="17" version="1065353216">I took down my share of bad guys--not that it was a competition....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667342" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a team effort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667343" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't pay by the enemy, if that's what you're getting at.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently, Senator Dodonna has good taste in privateers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't give her too much credit. She's only a politician.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe she just got lucky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha! I won't tell her you said that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667349" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were fortunate to have such a brave warrior on our side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667349" id2="17" version="1065353216">My friend led us to victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667350" id2="17" version="1065353216">High praise, coming from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667352" id2="17" version="1065353216">My friend has a talent for surviving impossible odds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667352" id2="17" version="1065353216">Truly, an impressive ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667353" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clearly, so do you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667355" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wish I'd gotten holos of my friend in action. It was quite a show.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667355" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should've seen the fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressing the leader of Havoc Squad is a feat in itself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667358" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was quite a ride.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667359" id2="17" version="1065353216">The men are telling some pretty outrageous stories. I hope they're true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Naturally humble, hmm? Humility's overrated, in my book.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that our men are safe, it's time to end this quagmire. We've wasted too many good soldiers fighting a conventional war on Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667366" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic has reserves of pathogenic and toxic weapons. There's no reason not to use them here, besides the Senate's squeamishness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe the Senate has reason to fear using them. How do they work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Describe these weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667368" id2="17" version="1065353216">The toxins and pathogens are in gaseous form. They're launched via missile and disperse on impact. Anybody caught inside the gas cloud regrets it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667370" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those sound like weapons the Empire would use, not us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667370" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aren't those things illegal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667371" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think it's high time the Empire got a taste of its own tactics. As for White Maw, those pirates get what they deserve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667373" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only reason they have the luxury of moralizing is because we protect them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ignore the Senators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667374" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fighting honorably is what almost got us destroyed in the last war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667376" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once Clabburn Sector is fully secured, we'll move in artillery platforms. Hit the enemy with every nasty poison and disease we've got.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667378" id2="17" version="1065353216">The best part is, our enemies won't die right away. They'll run back to their bases and share the pain with friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667379" id2="17" version="1065353216">General, what you're planning won't discriminate between friend and foe. Those weapons could kill innocent people, including ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667379" id2="17" version="1065353216">We shouldn't use such weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667382" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sound like those blasted Senators.... The only difference is, I respect your opinion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667384" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you think we can win Hoth the hard way, I'm willing to try. Maybe conventional missile payloads will be enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667386" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you've found a winning strategy, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667386" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. Kill them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667387" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll show those White Maw scum and Imperials that the Republic knows how to fight a war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667389" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll take some time to get the missile platforms down to the surface and set up. But the fight? That'll be short.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your service was exemplary. The men won't forget what you did. Neither will I.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667393" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we don't deal with whatever's murdering my men out there, Hoth is a lost cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667394" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bureaucratic fools. Never seen the business end of a blaster, but they'll tell me how to run a war....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider yourself lucky, Master Jedi. You can fight your battles without answering to politicians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667397" id2="17" version="1065353216">We all have our masters. The Jedi Council's standards are high.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667397" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, but I answer to someone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667398" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's never been a Jedi who hasn't faced death. You people understand the cost of fighting a war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667400" id2="17" version="1065353216">No offense, Master Jedi. As diplomats go, you're alright. Not like those politicians full of &quot;useful advice.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667401" id2="17" version="1065353216">In my experience, most politicians are decent enough--if you take the time to understand them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667401" id2="17" version="1065353216">They aren't so bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667402" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've dealt with elected leaders for most of my career. I'll never fathom what goes through their so-called minds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667404" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know what I mean, don't you, Captain? Havoc Squad's had more than its share of political interference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667405" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the government didn't sign my pay vouchers, I wouldn't have any use for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667405" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can say that again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha! Have to remember that one....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667408" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should look into the private sector. The pay's great, you set your own hours and you still get to shoot people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667408" id2="17" version="1065353216">I answer to nobody.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senator Dodonna's privateer. She speaks highly of you, Captain--for whatever that's worth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667411" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least Senator Dodonna has a clue what it takes to win--even if it means hiring mercenaries like you. No offense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667412" id2="17" version="1065353216">I pride myself on being a good value for the credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667412" id2="17" version="1065353216">None taken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your kill count's impressive, I'll give you that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667415" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're winning the war for Hoth. The Empire and those White Maw pirates won't last much longer, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't give in to frustration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667416" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you've done your part, but the Senate keeps tying our hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667418" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone contributes to the war effort in their own way--even politicians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667418" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're all doing our part.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667419" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senate contributes plenty of bad ideas, that's for certain. You, on the other hand, are an actual war hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never mind the politicians, sir. If there's a war to win, we're the ones who will do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667421" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's under control, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad's a blasted fine outfit, Captain. But you can't replace the troops we've lost from the Senate's bad decisions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667424" id2="17" version="1065353216">Back up. Tell me everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry. Long flight getting here. Obviously, I know who you are--and I'm glad you're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667427" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen most of what this planet has to offer. Still can't figure out why anyone is fighting over it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667427" id2="17" version="1065353216">The war on Hoth is pointless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667428" id2="17" version="1065353216">The war's not pointless--how we're fighting it is. That has to change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667430" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Hoth's new chief strategist. My predecessor dug us into a deep hole fighting this war by the Senate's rules.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667432" id2="17" version="1065353216">He controlled Clabburn Sector--a prime piece of real estate--for months and never capitalized on it. Now we're in danger of losing our best shot at victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667433" id2="17" version="1065353216">What makes this patch of ice and snow different from the others?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it really that important?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667434" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's perfectly positioned for accurate long-range artillery attacks on enemy bases. Whoever controls that sector takes this world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667436" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victory belongs to the brave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our men are fighting with all they've got--but they need help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me know how it turns out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667440" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hang on. You don't understand what's at stake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667442" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could win Hoth using Clabburn Sector's artillery position, but my predecessor let the enemy crowd us out. We need to secure that region.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667444" id2="17" version="1065353216">And now we've got another problem. Whole squads being ripped apart by... something. Don't know what. All we find are butchered remains.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667445" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are lots of hungry beasts out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hoth has many predators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667446" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not talking about some rogue wampa or whitefang pack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Butchered with what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667449" id2="17" version="1065353216">So little is left of our men, we can't tell what happened to them. They aren't being killed by conventional weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667451" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's war. People die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667452" id2="17" version="1065353216">These aren't random attacks--but it's not the Imperials or White Maw, either. Whatever's doing this is vicious. Slaughtering us for pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667454" id2="17" version="1065353216">This enemy takes our men by surprise, tears them to pieces and vanishes without a trace. The soldiers are terrified, but we can't retreat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667455" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need someone who specializes in dealing with extreme threats.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667455" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is no ordinary enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even our best men aren't equipped to fight what they can't find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667458" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not even to save your men?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Under any other circumstance I'd order a tactical withdrawal. But if we fall back, we may as well give up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667461" id2="17" version="1065353216">How is this my problem?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667462" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've been fighting for us since you landed here. Thought you might care whether or not we win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless someone takes out this enemy, we'll lose Clabburn Sector--and then Hoth. Everything we've sacrificed will be for nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667465" id2="17" version="1065353216">People are waiting on me, General. I hope this mission won't take long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667465" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't refuse a call for aid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667466" id2="17" version="1065353216">The sooner you get rid of our problem, the sooner we take this planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667468" id2="17" version="1065353216">I promised my allies I would drive Imperial forces from this sector. I'll honor that commitment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667468" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire must not win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667469" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's good for them is even better for the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667471" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't slog through all that snow so we could lose. Give me coordinates. I'll handle the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave it to me, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667472" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I ask is that you come back alive, Captain. We've lost enough good soldiers here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Start polishing my medals, General. And don't forget my credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Relax, I'm on the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667475" id2="17" version="1065353216">You handle this, and I'll pay you out of my own pocket.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667477" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine--you win. I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our best recon team is scouring the sector to pick up the enemy's trail. Their leader is a Talz commando.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coordinate with Captain Armaruk. Find whatever is slaughtering our people, and stop it. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667482" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't help. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667483" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep looking for some real heroes. Dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me. I'm reviewing battle reports.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
