<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>47</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/world/republic/savage_attack/padawan_elsor.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for everything. I'll stay here until I'm healed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667488" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith Beast-Lord is dead. His army's attacks on our people are over.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. It helps knowing my Master died for a greater good.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667491" id2="17" version="1065353216">The soldiers say General Nadab sent you here. I'm sure he'll want to know of your mission's success.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667493" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will stay here until I'm healthy enough for the journey back to Tython. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667495" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith Beast-Lord must be stopped. Hurry!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667496" id2="17" version="1065353216">The comm channels are clear. I found Master Heljus, but she's hurt!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen to me, all of you... the Sith secret weapon is no machine. It's a man. A Beast-Lord of Onderon, powerful in the dark side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667499" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Beast-Lord? Onderon?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667500" id2="17" version="1065353216">The planet Onderon's Beast-Lords dominate predators with their minds. Direct their actions. But this Sith... many times more powerful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667502" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're coming to help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667503" id2="17" version="1065353216">No--no. You must focus on the Sith. He threatens all of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667505" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know this for a fact?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667506" id2="17" version="1065353216">The thing that attacked our expedition dragged the survivors back to its lair. I followed. Thought I could save our friends. I was wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667508" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith Beast-Lord was there, waiting. Sent dozens of creatures at me. I barely escaped to send this final message.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, no... we can still save you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667512" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's too late for me, Padawan--but not for you. The Sith has gathered an army of beasts to destroy our forces. Stop him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave it to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe the Sith will negotiate?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't make my mistake. Our enemy is more animal than man. He cannot be reasoned with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Animals armies don't scare me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667518" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen what those things do. They'll leave nothing alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667520" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm transmitting coordinates to the enemy's lair. Hurry. May the Force be with you....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667522" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd offer to help, but in my state I'd only get in your way.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please... make that Sith pay for all the suffering he's caused.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667526" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to clear the comm channels. Farren Dulz knows what to do. Speak to him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="667528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever is slaughtering our people out here is recorded on these sensor logs. Captain Armaruk thought you'd want to know.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667529" id2="17" version="1065353216">The captain was right to send you, but I'm not sure how much I can help. My Master--our team--they're missing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667531" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were investigating a remote area during a snowstorm. Something attacked us. I never saw it. Just heard the screams.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667533" id2="17" version="1065353216">My Master created an avalanche that carried us to safety, but we were separated. I came here to heal. My Master hasn't returned yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, Jedi are tough.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sometimes, I sense my Master's presence. At least, I think I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667537" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should be in the medbay.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667538" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is my duty as a Padawan to remain here until my Master returns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to find a new Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Heljus is strong in the Force. She can't be dead. I would have felt it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667543" id2="17" version="1065353216">We came here hunting rumors of a new secret weapon. We believe the Sith have deployed it somewhere on Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intelligence reports indicate the device twists native wildlife into a weapon. These sensor logs prove it. My Master must see this. We have to find him!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay here. I'll go look.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667547" id2="17" version="1065353216">It isn't that simple. The avalanche that carried me to safety disoriented me. I don't even know where to start the search.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we really need him?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever attacked us was just like the thing your sensor logs picked up. I'm only a Padawan. My Master has the answers you seek.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="667552" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is this &quot;we&quot; nonsense?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at me. I wouldn't last an hour out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667555" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been trying to reach my Master's holocom, but White Maw pirates are jamming all frequencies. We need to focus on that problem first.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667557" id2="17" version="1065353216">A soldier named Farren Dulz has a plan to stop White Maw from blocking our comms. You help him, and I'll find my Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="667559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something's hunting our people out there. If you're traveling on the plains, may the Force be with you.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
