<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>15</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/world/inside_help/natho.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="459537" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire will think twice before relying on battle droids again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="459540" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just ran a full diagnostic on our droids--looks like they've all been infected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="459542" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't go ballistic until they've been shipped and deployed, but when they do... watch out, Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="459544" id2="17" version="1065353216">This wouldn't have happened without your help. The Republic doesn't realize what you've done for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="459545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't forget your part. You acted in spite of their distrust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="459545" id2="17" version="1065353216">You helped, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="459546" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had to do something. Otherwise, I really would be the Imperial scum they think I am.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="459548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="459549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, I'm trying to do my part, too... even if I have to put up with some nasty looks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="459551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will you continue working at the factory?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="459551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any chance you'll be quitting?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="459552" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assuming the Empire doesn't shut the factory down once those droids go haywire, yeah, I'll probably keep working there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="459554" id2="17" version="1065353216">So long as the Republic thinks I'm a traitor, the Empire will, too. Might as well stick around, do some more damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="459558" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make sure you infect all of the relay droids. We want that virus to spread as much as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="459559" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't help the Republic if they won't even listen to me.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
