<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>47</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/world/inside_help/republic_officer.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290892" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire may be calling the shots at Okara now, but they don't own me! This is a golden opportunity!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="290894" id2="17" version="1065353216">The day I take orders from an Imperial collaborator is the day I marry a Gamorrean. Now beat it, Natho.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="290896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. The Empire overruns my workplace, and suddenly I'm a traitor. I'm in a perfect position to ruin their operations, but the Republic won't even hear me out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where exactly do you work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your workplace?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290898" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Okara Droid Factory--which the Empire controls now. Not ideal employers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290900" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you've got a plan to sabotage the Empire, let's hear it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290900" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you up to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gladly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't blame the Republic for not trusting you if you still work with the Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290903" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't believe you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290904" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not like I'm killing Jedi. I build droids--poor ones, at that. But that's just deliberate laziness. It's time for some outright sabotage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290906" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the past few months, my factory's been putting together a massive shipment of battle droids for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290908" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the interest of &quot;quality assurance,&quot; I developed a virus and uploaded it to one of the droids, just to see what would happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290910" id2="17" version="1065353216">The droid malfunctioned--violently. Now imagine if we infected the entire shipment of droids with that virus....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290911" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire would have a horde of rampaging battle droids to deal with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290911" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'd be in big trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290912" id2="17" version="1065353216">An incident like that could shake the Empire's faith in droids altogether. It's just a matter of distributing the virus to all the units.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Infecting that many droids sounds more complicated than infecting one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290915" id2="17" version="1065353216">It can't be that simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290916" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe, but thanks to the Empire's obsession with efficiency, the groundwork for spreading the virus has already been laid out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290918" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been using special relay droids to upload all the necessary programming to the combat models.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290920" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we infect the relay droids, they should transmit the virus to the rest. I'd do it myself, but they're guarded by sentry drones.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290922" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can get past those sentries and upload the virus, you'll corrupt thousands of the Empire's droids. Will you do it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290923" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt those sentries can stand up to a lightsaber. I'll upload your virus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave it to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290924" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've already sacrificed enough for the Republic. Leave the rest to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290924" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll finish what you started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290925" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic can't afford to let a tactical opportunity like this slip by. Count me in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290925" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290926" id2="17" version="1065353216">My ship could use the scrap metal. I'm in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="290926" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290927" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's about time someone listened. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Last I checked, the relay droids were still circling the factory. Use this transmitter to upload the virus when you get close enough to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="290933" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess I'll just keep pestering the Republic....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="459454" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Okara droids are turning on the Imperials. I can't believe Natho was right.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="459455" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful around those sentry droids. For your sake, I hope Natho's virus works.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="459456" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have time for this, Natho. You're jamming my channel. Again. Don't you have work to do?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="459459" id2="17" version="1065353216">The day I take orders from an Imperial collaborator is the day I marry a Gamorrean. Buzz off!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="459467" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what's your plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="459471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where are the droids?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="459472" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been scouting this area for the Republic. If this means Natho will stop comming me, I'll help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="459474" id2="17" version="1065353216">The relay droids he's talking about are at these coordinates, near the Okara Droid Factory. The virus is on there too.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="459476" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the virus actually works, contact me at the Okara Droid Factory public terminal. There might be more we can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="459481" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's your job. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="459485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another time, huh? I need to transmit these scouting reports to the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="459486" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Sergeant Forren. Can't broadcast this over the comm-- contact me on the Okara Droid Factory public access terminal.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
