<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>58</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/world/republic/war_crimes/fyrel_cannor.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720425" id2="17" version="1065353216">The heat that's building off of the war crimes story is incredible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back. Ulgo's name is becoming sludge as we speak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720428" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're getting calls from all over Republic space. Usually when this happens, Organa recruitment goes up. Donations, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not bad for one well-placed junior reporter and his security team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720431" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not bad for one well-placed junior reporter and his security professional.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720432" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's important to get the truth out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720432" id2="17" version="1065353216">It needed to be shown.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not just important, essential--if there's ever going to be any justice on this planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720435" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get credit, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720436" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there's one thing we accomplish in this office, it's to publicize our successes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720438" id2="17" version="1065353216">We just exposed a torture program and a mass grave site. I wouldn't sound so upbeat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't celebrate this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, of course. I didn't mean to come off that way. But exposure like this helps the Republic and Organas immensely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720441" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did well out there. You gave us one of the biggest gifts a newsman can receive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720443" id2="17" version="1065353216">You got our junior reporter back from a war zone alive. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful out there. The Ulgos on that ridge would shoot a grain of sand if it got too close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720448" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it. It's better to risk losing me than anyone important to the team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720450" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't about you or me, it's about what'll be left of Alderaan if the Ulgos win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720452" id2="17" version="1065353216">See that? Dedication. Not easy to come by these days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where do we go?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where to, first?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720455" id2="17" version="1065353216">The house is on a ridge not far from the Ulgo headquarters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720457" id2="17" version="1065353216">This kid is laser bait. You seriously think he'll live?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720457" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a bad idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720458" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a risk--so stay hidden and on the move. The main thing is to get inside that building.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get holo evidence of what went on there, and get out before the main army is alerted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then drop him off at a safe rendezvous point where we can pick him up. He knows the place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fyrel Cannor, holo-editor for the Nova. Good to meet you. You've made a name for yourself around here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720466" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got an ugly security situation. Some of our senior staff investigated a structure--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me, Fy. Ulgo's hiding something and whatever it is, they think it's worth killing reporters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720469" id2="17" version="1065353216">What exactly is the story you were chasing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Slow down and start over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720470" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's an outlying building in Ulgo-occupied territory. Something's going on there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720472" id2="17" version="1065353216">When we got close, Ulgo soldiers fired on us, even after we called out that we were press.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720474" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is serious. You're sure it was Ulgo?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isn't that a war crime?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720475" id2="17" version="1065353216">I got a good look. Even after it was clear we were press, they shot to kill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720477" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't know that the orders came from the top, but we do know our evidence leads to that outlying building on Crystal Ridge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you thought of carrying a blaster?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720479" id2="17" version="1065353216">So defend yourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720480" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. The last thing we need is to be labeled as &quot;assassins.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720482" id2="17" version="1065353216">We got near a particular Ulgo building. Our sources were terrified of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720484" id2="17" version="1065353216">We think Bouris Ulgo, besides being a tyrant and usurper, has ordered war crimes perpetrated on prisoners in that building.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720485" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need an escort? Done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720485" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can protect you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Outstanding. Now we just need a volunteer to go back to the area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720488" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you want me for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720489" id2="17" version="1065353216">You get one of us in and out of that house alive. We'll do the rest. Now, we need a volunteer to be escorted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720491" id2="17" version="1065353216">But before you speak, I should disclose we still don't have the body armor we ordered.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="720493" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Silence.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="720495" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Silence.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720497" id2="17" version="1065353216">I came to this planet to win a war, not cover one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not my job. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720498" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not asking you to. Just protect one of us while we do our job. Now, who's willing to penetrate Ulgo territory?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720500" id2="17" version="1065353216">The truth will prevail. How fast it does is up to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720503" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. Tret it is. You ready for this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tret's footage is going live now. It's already getting requests for galactic coverage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="764717" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm impressed.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
