<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>102</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/alliance.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Theron Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Commander,

I request your permission to run potentially nonlethal experiments on C2-N2 and 2V-R8. I've been analyzing Emperor Arcann's droid forces with Admiral Aygo, and I believe my previous success with isotope-5 could bear fruit against our enemy. SCORPIO would be the ideal test subject, but when I brought the matter to her attention, she threatened to liquidate me from the inside. I'm certain the protocol droids will be much more agreeable.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Isotope-5</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Commander, 

I've been reaching out to scientific corporations with bold products that exemplify cutting-edge technology. Not an easy task since many companies sold out to the Eternal Empire during the first year of the war--shortsighted opportunists! But my inquiries have yielded results. After Rasmus Blys's bungling of CZ-198, I'd initially taken Czerka Corporation off my list. Honestly, I find their operations lackluster and stale. Then I remembered Blys has a daughter--Fiorah. While her father was an overweening yes-man, Fiorah is a gifted artist who specializes in biological weapons. She's agreed to help our cause, although from the comfort of her personal lab. It is a great day for science! And the Alliance, of course.

On a side note, Fiorah wrote her thesis on the effects of carbonite freezing. Perhaps she could run some tests on you remotely. Only minorly invasive. Think about it!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Czerka Corporation</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Doctor Oggurobb</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I'm sending a couple of my boys to Nar Shaddaa--and before you ask, yes, it's in a professional capacity. Someone found Karagga the Unyielding's old protocol droid and, with it, all the dead slug's dirty secrets. Lucky for us, instead of keeping the droid for himself, this individual's putting it up for auction. We could use the secrets of a former Supreme Mogul--even a dead one. Plus, I heard the droid's seen better days--keeps repeating, &quot;Karagga graciously reminds guests this area is not intended for visitors.&quot; The repair costs alone should deter buyers. Fortunately, I don't need the droid to talk when I can manually remove the information from its head. 

All hail Karagga the Unchallenged, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="879184" version="1065353216">FYI</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Hey, Commander,

Told you I'd keep an ear to ground, see if I heard anything you might find interesting. Well, I think I got something. The Hutt Cartel's been licking its wounds since Makeb, but they must be feeling better now. Three of my contacts are reporting the Cartel's set their sights on Zakuul's Old World. The slugs see an opportunity to capitalize on all the morbid stuff Zakuulans are into behind closed doors. Can't say I blame them--definitely a market there. Wouldn't say anything to Doctor Hutt, though. Last time I mentioned the Supreme Mogul, he cracked his scanner raving about lack of vision and incompetency.

On second thought, go ahead and tell him. That was hilarious.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="879184" version="1065353216">New Intel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Hylo Visz</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Commander,

I'm no longer part of the Republic Navy, but I get updates from former crew members worried I've gone rogue or curious about the Alliance. Usually nothing to get excited about, though a good line to new recruits, but I got a new piece of intel I think you'd find interesting. Not sure how much you know about the political scene in Coruscant; I try to know as little as possible--gives me a headache. Apparently, a small group of military officials tried to arrest former Supreme Chancellor Saresh for extortion, blackmail and a laundry list of other charges. Sad to say it didn't work. A rat in their ranks sold them out. The new chancellor had them quietly arrested, and no one's heard from them since. 

I know I made the right decision joining the Alliance. News like this just solidifies it.

--Aygo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Intel from the Republic</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Commander,

Things are going well, but the troops can always use a morale booster, so I'm flying in the band Black Sabacc to perform a few nights at the cantina. They're friends of the family, who owe my parents a few favors. Don't worry, I'm taking all the necessary precautions to keep our location a secret. I may have decided against a career in the arts, but that doesn't mean I don't recognize what they can do for soldiers.

--Aygo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Training exercises</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Admiral Aygo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Commander,

My visions are usually limited to Voss and how to grow the Enclave, but last night I saw something different: Sith and Jedi embodied as an ouroboros. As it ate, dull scales peeled away to reveal untouched, radiant ones. I relayed the vision to Voss-Ka, but the interpreters cannot align on one meaning. Still, I thought it too important not to bring to your attention. Perhaps time will bring clarity.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="879184" version="1065353216">The Jedi Order and the Sith</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Commander,

A dispute over Valkorion arose in the Enclave today. Lord Kaius blamed the Emperor for the Sith's current woes, while Acolyte Leta argued that he was merely testing their worthiness and that everything they have suffered is part of his vision for the galaxy. The conflict was quelled, but it brought to light a surprising parallel between Voss and the Eternal Empire. Valkorion used Force sensitives to guide the common people and relied on the Scions' visions to steer the course of Zakuulan society. This is not unlike the Mystics. Voss culture is built around our visions. Like Valkorion, we turn our backs on the teachings of outsiders, and we believe we are chosen. The thought is unsettling. Emotion has no place among facts, yet the comparison troubles me. I have not decided whether to share this with my fellow Mystics, but considering your unique relationship with Valkorion, I wanted to share it with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Valkorion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Sana-Rae</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Good work</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="879184" version="1065353216">It's done, Commander. The Star Fortresses are neutralized. Still kind of hard to believe--they've terrorized the Core Worlds for so long. Not that I doubted you. Somehow you always get results. And usually of the victory variety. Without the fortresses literally looming over their heads, the local resistance cells will grow, and so will the Alliance's reputation and influence. Arcann will be feeling this one for a while.

I might even celebrate with a drink.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Commander!

I must commend both your keen eye and sense of exploration! 

This dormant holocron you've recovered is fascinating indeed --and most definitely related to the pair we found on our inaugural Yavin 4 expedition! This brings our total up to three. Is this the full set, or are yet more to find? Oh, how Yavin taunts us with its endless mystery.

I swear on the Drellik name I shall do everything in my power to pry the secrets out of these artifacts. I shall notify you at once of any breakthroughs.

Thank you again, Commander!
Dr. Talos Drellik</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Your Recent Discovery</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Talos Drellik</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Jreely</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="879184" version="1065353216">For Big Boss</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Scary Sith lady teach Jreely how to use big message box. Jreely send message to Big Boss.

Blizz very good to Jreely, even when Jreely mean to Blizz. Blizz very good to all friends. Sometimes Blizz too nice, trust wrong friend and get into trouble. So Big Boss better stay right kind of friend, or Jreely make holes in Big Boss.

Jreely plan to steal power core from scary Sith lady's message box. Big Boss cover for Jreely.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Mako</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Thanks for having me!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Hey! Sorry I tried to shoot you earlier--no hard feelings, right? It's been a rough few years. I tend to shoot first these days.

I can't believe Akaavi talked you into letting me onto the crew. I gotta say, it's nice to be a part of something. It's been just the two of us for so long, I almost forgot what it's like. And Akaavi has sung your praises for as long as I've known her. Although, she thought you were dead, so maybe she exaggerated.

Anyway, I'll make sure to earn my keep. If you ever need me, just shout and I'll be there. Thanks for taking me aboard!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Akaavi Spar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Thank you</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I apologize for turning my blaster on you earlier. For so long, Mako and I have watched each other's backs. My first instinct is to protect her.

I wanted to thank you for allowing me to join your crew. It has been a long time since I had a place to call home. I hope, in time, I will think of your people as my family. I already like the one called Tora. She has the heart of a Mandalorian.

I will do my best to earn my place among you. Just call, and I will fight by your side. I appreciate the new life you've given me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I've received word about the new development between you and my son. Of all the people in the galaxy, I'm glad he fell for you. He's always felt everything so strongly. But you have a way with him. I know his heart is in good hands.

For Arcann's sake, I will try not to seem too overjoyed at this turn of events. And for my sake, I will avoid your quarters from now on.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="879184" version="1065353216">New development</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Senya Tirall</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I won't pretend to understand your reasons for doing this. Perhaps my need for control finally drove you away. Or you simply don't feel as strongly about me as I do about you.

I'll remain as your advisor, of course. I'm sure I'll get past this eventually, but I'll need time.

I've reserved the training ground for my own personal use. Keep the troops away for their safety. And send in a cleaning crew when I'm finished.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Us</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Look, I get it--feelings fade. But did you really have to just throw me away, like we never mattered? To you, maybe we didn't.

Whatever. I'll get over it. And I'll still stick around. But the cantina is now closed for a private party of one. I'm going to see if I can break Tora's personal record.

I'll see you around.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Really?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Koth Vortena</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Of all the men in the galaxy, it had to be him. Do you realize how much this stings?

Five years. That's how long I fought Arcann to get you back. And now you're shacking up with him, like none of that ever happened.

When I first saw you that day on Zakuul, I thought you'd finally come back to me. Now I see I was wrong. You've changed.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="879184" version="1065353216">You have to be kidding me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Aric Jorgan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Tell me the rumors about you and Emperor Genocide aren't true, so I don't have to slug you in the face.

I know I said I wouldn't make a fuss if you ever wanted out. But I didn't expect you to pick the guy who took everything from us in the first place. Blazes, it was bad enough when you let him live.

I'm not mad. Not even upset. Just disgusted.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Seriously?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Kaliyo Djannis</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Heard about you and Arcann. Word travels fast around here. And to be honest, none of us are surprised. We all saw how devoted he is to you.

I just wanted you to know it's okay. I kinda always knew you were out of my league. I tried to keep you for as long as I could--and I guess my time is up.

I'll be sad for a while. But hey, I hear there's a soldier around here with a crush on me, so maybe I'll try my luck with a rebound. But seriously, I hope you two are happy. For real.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="879184" version="1065353216">It's okay.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Vette</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I challenged your new mate to an honor duel, but he refused. Said he wouldn't want to make you angry. He doesn't know you like I do.

I don't care what he's done in the past. But he'd better deserve you, cyar'ika. Or I will make him pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="879184" version="1065353216">A duel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Torian Cadera</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="879184" version="1065353216">When you took me back, I knew it would not last for long. But I didn't expect it to end so quickly.

I understand, of course. A woman such as you must take what she wants, without regard for others. It's what first drew me to you. And a former emperor--this is the caliber of man you deserve. He suits you much better than I ever did.

Nevertheless, I remain yours. Should you ever tire of him, my lord, I will be waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I knew this day would come.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Malavai Quinn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="879184" version="1065353216">It's bad enough that you flung me aside for someone new. But to leave me for the man we've fought against for years--that I can't accept.

I thought you had more respect for the Republic--for me--than that. But I suppose our time apart changed you more than I thought.

Even if I forgive you for this, the galaxy won't.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I can't believe this.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Elara Dorne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I guess I was just temporary after all. I'm not offended by your decision, and I know it's your nature to move on to new things. I just wish you hadn't said all those nice things to me--it makes this harder.

I pledged myself to your cause, and I won't go back on that. But I may need a little time to adjust. I hope you understand, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I always knew</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Raina Temple</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I received the news of your decision. In truth, I have sensed you pulling away. Your aura was not the same. I worry it was because of my actions--a misstep I made without knowing. If that's the case, I apologize.

I wish for your happiness, regardless of my own. You are the writer of your own song. No matter where it takes you, I will happily listen. Even if you no longer want me to sing along.

I will always love you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I'm sorry</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Vector Hyllus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Really? After all that romantic nonsense, you drop me without a second thought? Gotta give you credit--you're cold. Colder than me, even.

Don't get me wrong. I couldn't care less whether we're an item or not. I just think it's funny.

Good luck with him, kid. He'll give you hell.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="879184" version="1065353216">You kidding me?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Risha</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="328" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Corso Riggs</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="879184" version="1065353216">You gotta be joking.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Well, this is a kick in the pants. You let me go on and on about love, and then drop me for someone else. Granted, you've known that someone else for a long time. Who knows how close you got while I was away? Maybe you've been lying all these years. I'd believe anything at this point.

Okay, no, that was uncalled for. You know I respect you. I just wish things turned out different. That's all.

I want you to be happy. Really, I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Ashara Zavros</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I understand</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="879184" version="1065353216">You need to follow what makes you happy. And if your heart wants him, I support it. I think this is better for both of us, you know? I was so young when I fell for you--maybe I still have some growing to do.

I'll always be here for you, as a friend and supporter. That will never change. I wish you only the best.

You owe me a drink after this, though. Just saying.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Andronikos Revel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Yikes</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="879184" version="1065353216">So, chucked for another guy. Gotta say, this doesn't feel great.

I said we'd be in each other's orbit forever. But that's not how things work, huh? Only one planet can do the orbiting, and now I know it was me.

It's fine. I'm a big boy--I can handle a little heartbreak. But if your entire supply of Trandoshan ale goes missing, don't go looking for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Kira Carsen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Ouch</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I'm trying not to feel really hurt. But it's not working out so well. I keep pacing around, trying not to cry. Then I hear you telling me to calm down and meditate, and that just makes it worse.

I really did love you, you know. No, blast that. I still do. And I hate it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Lord Scourge</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="879184" version="1065353216">You're not to blame</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="879184" version="1065353216">It was a mistake for us to begin anything--I see that now. Expecting you to be patient as I navigated my new emotions was unfair and selfish. You cannot be blamed for seeking companionship elsewhere.

I want you to know--despite its brevity, our time together taught me much about what it means to feel. Now I understand that I'm capable of being alive again, and that means everything to me.

Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="343" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Felix Iresso</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="344" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I get it</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="345" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Heard about what happened between you and the other guy. There's no hard feelings. I'm not exactly in the best shape for love right now, and you deserve better.

I'll always be in your corner, for as long as you want me around. And don't worry, things won't be awkward. I just want you to be happy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="346" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Well, this stinks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="347" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I won't pretend I'm not hurt. I mean, I thought we were happy. But I guess communication was never really your thing, was it?

I guess it was silly to think you were waiting for me all this time. Of course you found someone new while we were apart. Patience isn't really your thing, either.

I'll be okay eventually. Just give me some space for a few days. Man, love really stinks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="348" id2="879184" version="1065353216">It's in your nature</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="349" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I always thought death would part us. I see now I was wrong.

You have always sought the stars--never staying in one place for long. It was foolish to think you would stay for me. I blame myself for hoping you were capable of more.

I hold no resentment. I will continue to fight for as long as you need me. And I will burn these emotions away.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="350" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Jaesa Willsaam</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="351" id2="879184" version="1065353216">[No subject]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="352" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I heard about your new plaything. It would be a shame if any trouble were to befall him, wouldn't it?

It would be so easy for an accident to happen in a place like this. A slip of the hand...

Keep him away from me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="353" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Arcann</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="354" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I suspected</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="355" id2="879184" version="1065353216">When we last spoke, I expressed my fear that I would never deserve you. It appears I was right. Why do I always pursue the affection of those who cannot give it?

I put in a request for a week's leave to clear my head. I'm sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="356" id2="879184" version="1065353216">Theron Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="357" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I'm an idiot</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="358" id2="879184" version="1065353216">I can't focus. I just keep thinking about you. I'm usually so good at controlling my emotions, but I guess you're my weak point. This is a good lesson for me. Don't open up. Don't let anyone in.

I need to be on my own for a while to forget about us. Shake away my lingering feelings.

This is why spies should never fall in love.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
