<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>114</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/bounty_hunter.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Error 449: &lt;&lt;sender ID missing&gt;&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="359" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Loose ends</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="360" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Quite a mess you left on Hoth. It's amusing that you left one alive. Was it to send a message or was it mercy? Not that it really matters. He may have run, but his odds are poor. Our operatives succeed or die trying. Anything less is unacceptable.

This setback was costly, but you're still a valuable target. We won't be taking the direct approach in the future. Remember that when you lie down at night or take your next drink.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="361" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Error 449: &lt;&lt;sender ID missing&gt;&gt;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="362" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Impressive</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="363" id2="575045" version="1065353216">That mess you left on Hoth is one of the most costly setbacks in our organizational history. To use so many operatives seemed excessive, but it was obviously insufficient. We've learned a lot more about your capabilities, however, and it's hard to attach a value to that.

Don't think you've discouraged us. Your removal is still quite profitable, and we will not make the same mistakes twice.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="364" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Mako</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="365" id2="575045" version="1065353216">In case you forgot how awesome I am.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="366" id2="575045" version="1065353216">So, you know how we &quot;made it official&quot;? Well, I made it official official. I slipped our names into the Imperial and Republic marriage databases last night. Quit making that face, there's nothing that can be traced back to us and it makes me happy.

I may have also vandalized the ten highest traffic sites on the HoloNet. Hearts were involved. Kind of a lot of them. Don't judge.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="367" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Mako</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="368" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Hope you like it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="369" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Did you know Czerka Corporation has wedding registries? Well, they do. It was kind of fun to set one up even though no one's going to get us anything on there. Well, almost no one. I saw the best set of shape-conforming blast armor on sale. I think it'll look good on you, so really it's a present for both of us.  

Love you, big guy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="370" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Mako</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="371" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Honeymoon?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="372" id2="575045" version="1065353216">I was thinking about it, and I'm really glad we didn't try to do some crazy ceremony. I'm not going to lie, I was checking out some 'zines at the time and I wanted to have my girly moment, but everyone I'd have wanted to be there... couldn't have been. You never talk about family either. It would have just been for us, and we had that. I'm a little sad I'll never get to see Blizz as a flower girl, though.

So anyway, I figure that since we saved all that money keeping things simple, we should make up the difference on a big honeymoon vacation. It'd do us some good to lay low for a little while anyway, right? Think about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="373" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Torian</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="374" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Admission</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="375" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Never been the nervous type. Never been scared about facing anything.

Day I asked about our future, had the shakes so bad I left a clean target on the range.

Guess I better not cross you, cyare.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="376" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Torian</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="377" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Hunting trip</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="378" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Feel a little guilty, letting things get this far and still never introducing you to my friends. Was thinking next time I hear from Corridan, we go on a hunt. Think you'd like a Mandalorian vacation. Nothing takes your mind off things like ducking a stampeding boma.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="379" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Torian</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="380" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Got you something.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="381" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Heard a Mirialan saying: &quot;Love's the armor of the heart.&quot; Mandos are a bit more proactive. Never been much of a metal worker, but Corridan helped me work the beskar. It'll protect you when I can't.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="382" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Mandalore</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="383" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Damn fine hunt</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="384" id2="575045" version="1065353216">I'm staring at a man I thought I'd never see again, and I hear I have you to thank for that. I hope he gave you a run for your money, I'd hate to hear the old rabble-rouser just laid down and accepted his fate after all these years. That's not the Jicoln I remember.

He's going to be hard to kill. Our friendship died a long time ago, but the hate bled out of that grudge years ago. Never thought I'd become a sentimental old fool. I've got some thinking to do before I thaw him out.

I understand his boy is with you now. Take care of him. He's got a lot to live up to.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="385" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Mandalore</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="386" id2="575045" version="1065353216">You did well.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="387" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Jicoln Cadera's been dead to me a long time. Taris was as good as a death sentence, but somehow I knew he was still out there. He'd always been too stubborn to die.

Honestly never thought I'd see him again. Hard to believe he's actually gone. Ten years ago, I wouldn't have thought twice about putting a knife in his heart. Now, I remember the good old days. Wonder if he'd have felt the same before we crossed blades for the last time. No sense in dwelling on it.

I understand Jicoln's boy is with you now. Take care of him. He's got a legacy to carry on.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="388" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Adasca BioMechanical Corporation</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="389" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Our sincerest apologies</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="390" id2="575045" version="1065353216">It has come to my attention that you were troubled by an incident that occurred during your recent visit to our Quesh refinement facility. While Adasca BioMechanical cannot be held responsible for the extraneous circumstances surrounding the incident, we do apologize that your visit was disrupted and would like to extend this complimentary gift to make up for your visit being cut short. We hope that you will continue to consider Adasca BioMechanical for all your future adrenal and pharmacological needs.

Sincerely,
Peyton Swole, Director of Galactic Relations
Adasca BioMechanical Corporation of Arkania, in association with the Draay Trust

Adasca - Unleash Your Potential</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="391" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Ki-Ta Kren</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="392" id2="575045" version="1065353216">To my sibling in the stars</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="393" id2="575045" version="1065353216">As I laid in our mingled blood, I heard the thunder of your confrontation with our brother echo throughout the bones of the dreadnaught. It pained me not to be there to see it to its conclusion, to wonder what remained after all fell silent. I know now you were the victor, and I am glad the Blooding did not take you both from me. The stars are too large and lonely to travel alone.

The White Maw holds nothing for me now that Reneget is gone. I have left them to their hapless plundering while I find my way. Until our paths cross again, I will think of you as I walk the sky.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="394" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Ki-Ta Kren</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="395" id2="575045" version="1065353216">I will bide my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="396" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Remember me, hunter. My name is Ki-Ta Kren, you have spilled my blood, not as my kindred, but as my enemy. You left me to bleed and listen, helpless, as you took from me my last brother. Of all the wounds you inflicted on me, his death has been the slowest to heal. Without Reneget, I have been left to wander the stars without kith or kin. Alone.

One day, I will come for you. I will cut free your heart and drink deeply as he would have done. This is how I will honor my fallen brother. For now, I will cut my teeth on beast and man until I am ready to hunt you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="397" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Mandalore</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="398" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Make them pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="399" id2="575045" version="1065353216">My people tell me the Republic attacked you. They tell me those cowards crept into your celebration like insects and cut down my friends and comrades while they raised glasses. None of those Republic dogs had the spine to face any of you in a fair fight, not even the Jedi. They've blackened our history and dishonored you. 

Burn them, champion. Blaze a trail over every last one of these gutless mongrels and trample their ashes into the mud where they belong!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="400" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Captain Horn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="401" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Celebrating my promotion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="402" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Darth Tormen was unusually pleased when I informed him of your success on Belsavis. His expectations are uniformly high, and it's rare for anyone to exceed them.

My lord Tormen saw fit to reward me for my role in the operation as well, and--in addition to my promotion--he has taken me into his confidence. Everything I'd hoped, if I may be candid. Darth Tormen's plans are bold and ambitious, and I look forward to helping him accomplish them. We'll be working together again soon, I think. I look forward to it.

Horn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="403" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Darth Tormen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="404" id2="575045" version="1065353216">You have served well.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="405" id2="575045" version="1065353216">When the Dark Council convened over the triumph at Corellia, Decimus expected to receive the highest honors. He was disappointed. None could question my supremacy.

Rage boiled under his skin as I presented the Supreme Chancellor to Darth Marr. The envy of the Dark Council is mine alone.

Your role in my plans is known to Darth Marr. He has interest in such an effective tool. Should the day come, serve him as you have served me, and you will be appropriately rewarded.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="406" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Janarus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="407" id2="575045" version="1065353216">There will be hard times ahead.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="408" id2="575045" version="1065353216">I had to pull in a few favors with my old staff and the SIS to see that this communication reaches you. It shouldn't come back on either of us.

An emergency Senate hearing just voted in Governor Saresh of Taris as acting Supreme Chancellor of the Republic. She's spent most of her career lobbying for stronger action against the Empire, and after Corellia, she'll have the support she needs to get it. I fear there's no stopping this war now.

I won't ask you to get caught up in this mess again, but if you have to make a stand for something in this war, make it for a future. Don't let this madness consume us all.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="409" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Albea</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="410" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Safe on Coruscant</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="411" id2="575045" version="1065353216">You're probably going to find this silly, but I wanted to tell you I made it home in one piece after you saved me from Fa'athra's palace. I know I wasn't the reason why you were there, but I can't think of anyone on Hutta who wouldn't have just shot me for the credits in my pocket, let alone an Imperial bounty. So, I hope this helps you in the Great Hunt and be careful out there, it wasn't hard for me to dig up this address.

P.S: Thank your partner for her blaster, I don't think I'll be able to sleep without it for awhile.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="412" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Ministry of Logistics Freelance Rewards Program</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="413" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Incentives Earned</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="414" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Our database indicates that your account has claimed several bounties this week. Your diligence in bringing swift justice to these fugitives from Imperial law has earned you a merit reward. In accordance with section 47/b of the Freelance Enforcement edict, an incentive has been rendered into your custody.

Your incentive is non-transferable. Your incentive is not intended for resale. Any dissatisfaction with your incentive may result in an infraction. Failure to comply with all section and subsection codes of the Freelance Enforcement edict may result in termination of your account.

The Ministry of Logistics looks forward to your continued excellence in service of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="415" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Lady Dak-Ah</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="416" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Such a lovely gloom</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="417" id2="575045" version="1065353216">I'm feeling inspired, bounty hunter. I want to share the gift you gave me. Half a lifetime of bittersweet memories to wash away with every excess I can imagine. When I think back to my juvenile love for that rebellious Alderaanian boy, I can still smell his hair during our tenderest embraces. Now that mixes with the smell of his hair burning as a petulant Alderaanian man. It sends a shiver up my spine.

I don't think I'll love again. Why dilute that exquisite heartache and loathing with crude attempts to relive the moment?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="418" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Lord Altaca</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="419" id2="575045" version="1065353216">A token of appreciation</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="420" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Mother advised me against this, but my vision has mostly returned and I wanted to give my own thanks.

I shudder to think of what my life would have been like stuck on Dromund Kaas. I may have escaped the work camp, but I was still a slave to my--to Lady Dak-Ah. I know she's an Imperial, but she was so different back when our paths first crossed. She gave me a reason to respect the Imperials. Now all I can see is the sneering hag she turned into. I still can't believe that witch tried to kill me.

Home isn't how I remembered it, but Alderaan at war is still better than Dromund Kaas at the best of times. I wouldn't wish that dismal place upon anyone. Hopefully you've moved on to greener pastures.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="421" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Major Pirrell</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="422" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Resounding Success!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="423" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Greetings from the desk of the newly appointed naval attache to the governor of Balmorra. I just had the last of Colonel Sartius's effects sent off to the garbage hauler--fitting, don't you think?--and I thought I'd give you the privilege of receiving the first message penned with my official holomark. Consider it a memento, evidence of what might have been your finest work. Things didn't go exactly as planned, certainly, but we adapted and overcame our obstacles. That's what separates us from incompetents like Sartius.

We have a new governor on Balmorra, another replacement for an incompetent leader. Darth Lachris is an unforgiving mistress, but she has a ruthless streak I can get behind. I'll have to introduce you next time you're through Sobrik.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="424" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Major Pirrell</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="425" id2="575045" version="1065353216">All clear</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="426" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Murghir has taken the fall for Admiral Ivernus's assassination, like I said she would. Anyone who could claim otherwise has already met their untimely demise, and since the admiral didn't make a habit of keeping his activities on record, I painted a very pretty picture of the situation. You'll find you are decidedly absent from any records regarding the admiral or myself. So far as anyone can tell, you've had a very profitable trip working to crush the Balmorran resistance.

I may not be the poster boy for Imperial fighting spirit, hunter, but I know the power of meticulous datawork.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="427" id2="575045" version="1065353216">ODX-9</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="428" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Have you seen my master?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="429" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Greetings. My memory core indicates that you were recently under the employ of my master, Lieutenant Major Pirrell. He has not returned since he departed on business with you and his pet. If you could tell him to contact me as soon as possible, I would be most grateful. Tell him it is urgent; there is a Lieutenant Ean who is under the impression that Major Pirrell is no longer serving on Balmorra and has begun clearing out his office and slated me for a memory wipe by the end of the week.

I understand your kind expects compensation for most requests, so I've included my petty credit allotment from the lieutenant major. Expeditious service would be appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="430" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Solash</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="431" id2="575045" version="1065353216">The Grand Mogul is pleased.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="432" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Your exceptional work in dealing with the treacherous Eidolon has caught the attention of the almighty Karagga the Unyielding, Grand Mogul of the Hutt Cartel. The Eidolon is presently the most popular fixture in the Grand Mogul's garden menagerie, particularly among the roosting xuvva gliders, and the Grand Mogul expresses his gratitude for the great amount of entertainment the Eidolon will provide him in the coming months as he concocts fresh indignities to inflict upon the traitor. 

Karagga the Unyielding insists that you enjoy this token of his esteem.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="433" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Solash</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="434" id2="575045" version="1065353216">A regrettable decision</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="435" id2="575045" version="1065353216">I represent the Hutt Cartel, more specifically, I bear a message from Karagga the Unyielding, Grand Mogul and master of the Hutt domains. The Grand Mogul was extremely displeased to learn that the assassin known as &quot;the Eidolon&quot; met a hasty end. Such defiance should have been rewarded with a prolonged and humiliating demise as a lesson to others who would think themselves beyond the reach of the Hutt Cartel. 

The Grand Mogul chooses to believe that this opportunity was missed due to mishandling of his edict rather than the whims of an unruly bounty hunter. Those responsible have been punished, and Karagga the Unyielding hopes future bounties he places will be fulfilled according to his desires.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="436" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Baron Raffid Girard</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="437" id2="575045" version="1065353216">How's knighthood suiting you?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="438" id2="575045" version="1065353216">I was just savoring a glass of avedame with a lovely lady in waiting--equally blush--and I thought to myself: &quot;I can thank our rugged advocate for all this.&quot; 

My &quot;wife&quot; can certainly make a nuisance of herself when she wants, but by and large, I am free from endless lectures about decorum. You should see the little lordlings scuttle about trying to impress the great Baron Girard!

Anyway, I thought I'd share the wealth with my favorite knight of the house. It's a little something I seized from my uncle's estate after I relocated him to the thranta stables. Ha!

Enjoy, my friend,
Raffid</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="439" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Baroness Aitalla Girard</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="440" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Free at last</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="441" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Things have been considerably quieter here since you left, advocate. I suppose it isn't really &quot;advocate&quot; anymore, but I think you deserve at least that much respect after all you did here. 

The ambitious little lords still come angling for my hand in marriage, but I find it much less bothersome now that I'm involved in the conversation. Not that it changes the outcome. I'm the unquestioned master of my destiny now, I won't be leashing myself to more scheming men.

You have a friend on Alderaan, should you need one.

Fond regards,
Aitalla</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="442" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Baron Raffid Girard</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="443" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Hello, my dear</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="444" id2="575045" version="1065353216">I hope you've been throwing your noble station around since you left, it's sure to irritate your more pedestrian peers to no end and really, what use is power if you can't dangle it over someone? I think I'll tell Heitor that's what you've been doing regardless, it's sure to get a rise out of him.

I have to say the company's been quite dull since you left. Why, hardly anyone's been shot and the ladies can hardly muster a harsh look if anyone rubs them the wrong way. Oh well, there's always rubbing them the right way until the next time you come around. I've set aside a nice vintage from the Organa vineyards just for us, I'm sure it'll complement your next visit nicely.

Love,
Raffid</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="445" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Baroness Aitalla Girard</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="446" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Fond regards</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="447" id2="575045" version="1065353216">I have to thank you for your excellent advice, advocate. I haven't had so much as a knock from a gentleman caller since our little stroll. With Raffid out of the house, my father relegated to the guest wing, and nary an ambitious lordling to be seen, it's been wonderfully peaceful within the walls of House Girard. I suppose it will be lonely in time, but for now I'm going to savor every quiet moment.

If you should visit Alderaan in the future, I wouldn't be opposed to having your private council again.

XOXO,
Aitalla</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="448" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Juda</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="449" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Hello!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="450" id2="575045" version="1065353216">I've been keeping up with you in the Great Hunt. Everybody is, even Nem'ro. He'd never admit it, but I've signed off on enough of his credits to know he's got a lot riding on you winning. Maybe I shouldn't have mentioned that, don't want you to throw the match just to spite him! Hee hee!

I let mom bet a little of the money we saved. I know I shouldn't, but it makes her happy and this time, when she says it's a sure thing, I believe her. Stay alive out there. Okay?

Love,
Juda</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="451" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Juda</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="452" id2="575045" version="1065353216">I hope you die.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="453" id2="575045" version="1065353216">I just brought my mother home from the clinic. After you squeezed me over the Great Hunt target list, I couldn't scrape together enough for her debt payments. The loan shark's thugs nearly killed her. The clinic's droid said she'll live, but she'll spend what's left of her life bedridden. I'll never be able to work off her gambling debts and medical bills in ten lifetimes. We're stuck here. I'm going to be a slave to Nem'ro for the rest of my life.

You should have just killed us, it'd have been more merciful, you heartless scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="454" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Thendys Noori</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="455" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Turn yourself in.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="456" id2="575045" version="1065353216">I've come to terms with the tragedy of the Aurora. The masters at the temple helped me clear my mind of the hate I held for you, and I see things clearly now. I don't believe you're evil, but you are misguided, and the path you walk can only bring you to a dark place. You can be saved, there's still time to choose a different life for yourself.

Please, answer for what you've done.  You can't run forever, and you're only hurting yourself by trying. If you accept responsibility for the harm you've caused, you can earn a second chance in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="457" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Crysta Markon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="458" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Don't be a stranger.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="459" id2="575045" version="1065353216">How's the big time treating you, Grand Champion? Heard old Lek sent you off to have a one-on-one with Mandalore. I'm so jealous I could spit! Heck, I ain't even seen Mandalore, and I've been knocking heads with these people more years than a lady cares to admit. You put in a good word, hear? I ain't going to stay this good-looking forever, and I want to hear the clank clank of little Mandalorian boots before I see my last good fight!

Now don't go getting a big head while you're off living the high life and pay a visit to your friends next time you're around.

Good hunting,
Crysta</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="460" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Crysta Markon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="461" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Keeping in touch!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="462" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Hey there, Grand Champion! Bet you never thought you'd be hearing from me again!

Can you believe these BBA yahoos? Letting every sleen trapper and their third cousin pick up bounties like hunting ain't no big deal! Shameful. Course, I know you don't worry yourself about piddly stuff like that no more. With all I've seen that you've been up to, I know you got bigger ferrazids to fry!

Say, how's that Mantis holding up? Saw one just like it on vacation out to Rishi. Made me think of you. Ever get a chance, sugar, you should head out there. Beautiful beaches, loads of blaster fire--you'd like it!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="463" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Crysta Markon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="464" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Strange days</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="465" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Hey sugar,

I'm sure you know I spend a good lotta days in Kaas City. Most of that time's spent within a soft holler's reach of the folks who run the Empire. They don't usually see fit to even look in my general direction, which was always fine by me. Now all that's changed, and it looks like it's thanks to you.

I got people with titles I never heard of looking me up, asking how close the two of us are, if I know where you live--I swear, you didn't get this much attention when you won the Great Hunt!

Between you and me and a deaf gundark, I don't think this is the &quot;good&quot; kind of attention, you get me? I know you do what you want and all, but whatever you got into lately? I'd just politely suggest you might wanna think about easing yourself back out of it.

Take care and good hunting,
Crysta</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="466" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Crysta Markon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="467" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Always beware the &quot;big bounty&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="468" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Finally! No more questions, no more weird requests to meet the Grand Champion in person, none of that. Now, I'm sure it doesn't mean you're not popular anymore. Just means whatever Killik hive you dug up or what have you has moved on to other business. And that's fine by me.

Have you seen these couple new bounties popping up all over the place? Major credits from the Empire for a DoA contract on a Sith lady. And this other one--this &quot;rogue government employee&quot;--I got it on good authority someone in the Republic is footing the bill on that campaign from under the table.

Whenever these big-money deals come along, I always shake my head. You watch, it'll end with a lot of dead bounty hunters who mostly killed each other falling all over themselves to make a fortune. And even if anyone is successful, there'll be ten kinds of holo hoops to jump through to get paid.

Okay, sugar, I'm off to enjoy some travel time. I'll be in touch!

Good hunting,
Crysta</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="469" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Thera Markon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="470" id2="575045" version="1065353216">Sunsets</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="471" id2="575045" version="1065353216">I was all fueled up and ready to go when I decided to stick around a little longer. Crysta had really become a fan of Rishi, kept telling me to come here. Figured it wouldn't hurt to take the place in.

Sat on the beach and bit my nails. Kept stumbling on a mountain hike because I couldn't keep my eyes off my datapad. Went for a scenic skiff ride and the whole time I wanted to knock out the pilot and push the throttle to full. Guess I don't have the patience for all that outdoorsy vacation stuff.

I'll give her this, though: those sunsets are every bit as beautiful as she claimed, and then some. It's like the vastness grabs you, takes control, sets you at ease. I can see why she would've liked those. I'd come back for those.

I think she'd be glad I finally saw what she saw on Rishi. And that you did, too.

Thera</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
