<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>21</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/chapter_5_rep.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="806202" version="1065353216">PUBLIC TERMINAL</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="806202" version="1065353216">You need me!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="806202" version="1065353216">Greetings!

I was watching from one of the gutter grates when you spared Grumm, and I must say you're nothing like people say! Serious image problem here, my friend! I can help!

Before various unpredictable factors led to my current sabbatical in the Raider's Cove slums, I worked as a public relations specialist! I can work miracles, I assure you. We'll even get people to stop all this cannibal business altogether, I'll bet!

Just let me know where you're staying and I'll stop by sometime to talk branding. Maybe I could also borrow your sonic shower? And why don't we make it a lunch meeting while we're at it? Perfect!

Tyfor Renadal
Renadal Consulting</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="806202" version="1065353216">Kai Zykken</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="806202" version="1065353216">We Square?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="806202" version="1065353216">Just making sure my favorite fellow captain is doing well! Did you get that recording we were talking about?

I've just been hearing about you doing a bit of killing around town, and I wouldn't want to be on the list, so to speak. But we're good, right?

Anyway, if you need anything at all, you just take it straight to Tomota, no problem. Because I might be out of town for a while. Captaining! You know how it is.

--K-Zy--</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="806202" version="1065353216">Captain Milenec</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="806202" version="1065353216">Made It</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="806202" version="1065353216">I've got my team over to Raider's Cove; we've booked a flight back to Republic space. Smuggler named Kaya says she can get us out 

of here without anyone noticing. Here's hoping, huh?

You gave us a second chance I wouldn't have even given myself. Thank you.

I just hope we can still make a difference when we get back to civilization.

-M-</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="806202" version="1065353216">ANONYMOUS</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="806202" version="1065353216">Milenec</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="806202" version="1065353216">Found the security vid of you taking out Milenec. He should've known he was in over his head. 

The rest of them won't go down so easy. 

Keep strong. You're really shaking things up.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="806202" version="1065353216">ANONYMOUS</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="806202" version="1065353216">Your Actions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="806202" version="1065353216">I witnessed your defiance of Darth Marr, both in the field and the command center.

This is the only personal contact that many of us have had with members of the Republic. We are intrigued. You assert your will through personal strength alone. 

Perhaps we are not so different after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="806202" version="1065353216">Darth Marr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="806202" version="1065353216">Well Done</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="806202" version="1065353216">While I am certain Satele Shan lacks the resolve to truly punish your defiance of her leadership, I am certain she will not reward it, either.

The Empire will.

That is all.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="806202" version="1065353216">Theron Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="806202" version="1065353216">Back on Coruscant</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="806202" version="1065353216">It's strange to be back in the SIS offices after all this time. Judging by the looks I'm getting, a lot of people thought I was dead or worse. Fun.

Trying to debrief on everything that happened out there hasn't been easy. Satele has been a big help; people don't second guess her. Two Revans, incorporeal Emperor's return, doesn't matter--if Satele says it, the brass listens.

We've actually grabbed lunch and caf a couple of times. Not that we hadn't talked before, but it's getting easier.

Reaching out isn't something I used to do much of. Now I'm trying to put together a joint task force with who-knows-how-many people in it. You, Lana, D4, and Jakarro really did a number on me.

Thanks.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
