<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>24</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/chapter_4_rep.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Foreman Tiero</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="732431" version="1065353216">New Worker</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="732431" version="1065353216">So, not only are we no longer plagued with Veedrig's constant plundering of Project Failsafe, we've found ourselves an impressive new mechanic to boot! That's right--we put that Devaronian slimeball to work. Who knew Veedrig could install turbo compressors like a pro?

Of course, with a guy like that, I had to give him the proper incentive. I started with offering to snap off his horn, he countered by begging for mercy... we worked out a compromise from there. That Veedrig sure knows his way around a negotiation.

Thanks again for rescuing my team from the Hutts. Here's hoping we get this ark finished in time to escape for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Foreman Tiero</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="732431" version="1065353216">No More Veedrig</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Without Veedrig around to bleed Project Failsafe dry, we're finally making progress. Now that we know why the ark's being built, we're working harder than ever, of course--but at least we aren't lining the pockets of that Devaronian slimeball in the process. Good riddance.

Turns out his Twi'lek lackey, Batza, isn't so bad. Hard worker, quick with a joke, and grateful to be alive. I think you left a lasting impression on him.

We'll get the ark finished in time to evacuate, whatever it takes. Hope you're making those Hutts sorry for what they've done to my planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Mayor Erkens</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Official Commendation</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="732431" version="1065353216">As Mayor and on behalf of the Settlement of Tarlam, I offer this official recognition of your act of heroism in the face of great adversity.

While I do not pretend to know the unique pressures you must endure, I have learned a thing or two about making snap decisions in times of strife. I also know that many Tarlam citizens including myself were spared as a direct result of your actions. For these reasons, I find myself inspired by your durasteel temperament and sound judgment.

I would have preferred a proper ceremony, but as there is simply no time for such formalities, I hope that this communication will suffice as a token of my gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Councilor Soler</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Bittersweet victory</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="732431" version="1065353216">I'm lucky. In my lifetime, I haven't had to fight. Political differences and arguments, sure, but I've never had to pick a side, take up arms and do battle.

I don't know what it must have been like to have been in your position when the lives of Mayor Erkens, myself and others were on the line. I do know, however, that anyone who could hold innocent civilians hostage is a terrible coward who must not be allowed to succeed. What I'm saying is, I have come to appreciate that you ultimately did not back down.

We've held a short vigil in memory of Mayor Erkens and the others. For their noble sacrifice, we will forever regard them--and you--as heroes.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Ritte Nikols</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Thank You</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Mom says I should write you a letter and say thanks for not killing Dad. I told her I didn't think you'd really kill him, cause you're a Republic hero and everything, but she said to say thanks anyway. She says we probably won't see Dad a lot offworld, but I can send him letters while he's in jail and this will be good practice.

The Protectors are telling us it'll be our turn to get on the ark soon. So thanks for not killing Dad. He was just trying to save us. He's a hero too.

Sincerely,
Ritte Nikols</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Bryn Samsin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Backpay</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Wanted to say thanks again for dealing with Nikols and the rest of that Regulator scum. Makes me think disasters like this happen for a reason, you know? Survival of the fittest and all that. The Protectors aren't happy, but I can usually tune 'em out. I just think of finding Nikols' body--always puts a smile on my face.

Me and a couple of the boys raided the Nikols house afterwards. Had to tear the place apart but we eventually found the nest egg. Figured you deserved a cut.

Bryn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Shalim Avesta</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Gratitude</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="732431" version="1065353216">I'll admit it: when I failed to reason with Toborro, I thought we were doomed. To be on the other side of all that now, safely off Makeb... all I can do is express my heartfelt thanks once more.

No one's decided where we'll end up, but one thing is certain: our new home will not be a dump. You should have heard the anguished Hutt wails when Chancellor Saresh demanded that the Cartel fund our refugee colony. It was an unnatural, haunting sound, actually, but it sure brought a smile to my face. Lemda's, too.

Speaking of my niece, she sends her warmest regards. Well, her version, anyway. &quot;Can't you see I'm busy, Uncle?&quot; But we both know what she really meant.

Be well.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="732431" version="1065353216">General Fanrill</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="732431" version="1065353216">Thanks to my surprise benefactor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="732431" version="1065353216">I meant to message you earlier, but you've made me so busy I can barely find the time to type! There are millions of new faces in our training camps and munitions plants. This is exactly the shot in the arm I've been calling for!

A lot of them are raw, no clue whatsoever--but we can work with that. I just wish this Lemda Avesta who's been rallying to unionize our factories would give it a rest. What a handful, that one!

This resource windfall you sent me can only make for a stronger Republic. Drinks are on me when the Empire is finally defeated. Keep up the outstanding work!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
