<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>21</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/chapter_5_imp.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="804757" version="1065353216">Morran Kovoe</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="804757" version="1065353216">Ha ha, thanks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="804757" version="1065353216">I heard the Howling Tempest Gang were supposed to be a serious crew! &quot;As ruthless as their name is laughable,&quot; they said! Lucky for me, they're all WRONG. 

I told them you're EXACTLY as laughable as your name--IF NOT MORE--and I put down the credits to back my big mouth up. They all took my bet, the suckers. And now I don't have to lift a finger for months--unless it's to order another refreshing ale from my BEACHFRONT CABANA. So thanks for having a crew name that makes you predictably LAME.

M. Kovoe
Former Refueling Technician
Current Doer of NOTHING</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="804757" version="1065353216">Wain Prospecting</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="804757" version="1065353216">About time!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="804757" version="1065353216">Someone needed to put an end to Grumm and Gorro. Those two were bad news, acting like they ran Raider's Cove. And they were running it--into the ground!

I moved to Rishi to get away from having a bunch of laws forced down my throat. I knew there'd be downsides to moving to the fringes and I'd have to protect myself from thieves and gunslingers, but those two were on another level. Grumm more than Gorro, but Gorro had such a chip on his shoulder. So you won a thing, give me a break. But, yeah, Grumm, anytime I saw him I knew I was about to kiss my face and credits goodbye.

Maybe now I can enjoy Rishi the way I was hoping I would--in (relative) peace.

Korrick Wain
Owner, Wain Prospecting</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="804757" version="1065353216">Captain Milinec</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="804757" version="1065353216">Second chance</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="804757" version="1065353216">I feel like a fool.

I don't say that because I chose to side with Revan. I still believe his aims are right and just, and I desperately hope you fail to stop him. No, why I feel like a fool is because I turned and ran when you gave me the chance. I should have fought you. I'm fairly certain I would have died, but I should have stood up for my beliefs, whatever the cost.

Instead I'm unable to return to the Republic or to the order with no idea what my future holds. All I can do is promise myself to never compromise under the threat of death again. And promise that if I ever see you again, I'll do what I should have done the first time.

-M-</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="804757" version="1065353216">Sergeant Tarsten</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="804757" version="1065353216">Who I am....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="804757" version="1065353216">I know how lucky I am to be alive right now, and I realize I'm tempting fate just by contacting you, but I want you to understand something.

I've never been sure of any Sith Lord's motives, but when I worked under Darth Arkous he struck me as especially crooked. I knew what my fate would be if I spoke up--even if my suspicions were correct. So I remained loyal to Arkous until his death. And since being reassigned to Lord Ivress, my loyalty has been to him.

Ivress betrayed the Empire. Whether you dealt with him appropriately isn't for me to say. But Revanite or not, Captain Milenec was an enemy of the Empire who deserved to die, and I applaud you for sealing his fate. Despite how it looks, I do want in my heart to see the Empire thrive and the Republic fall. But I am a survivor. 

If we ever cross paths again, I hope you'll bear this in mind.

--Sgt. Tarsten</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="804757" version="1065353216">Lt. Ershall</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="804757" version="1065353216">Commandant Iven</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="804757" version="1065353216">I've never been moved to write a letter to a stranger before. And, really, when I replay the moment in my head it's not as if it was an obvious grand gesture on your part. But you siding with Grand Master Shan to interrogate Commandant Iven without torturing him was of profound significance to me.

I can't say I expect this truce to last any longer than it has to, but if working together lets us see each other as more than broad &quot;enemy&quot; charicatures then I hope we find another excuse to cease fire and cooperate.

Lt. Arven Erhsall</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="804757" version="1065353216">ANONYMOUS</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="804757" version="1065353216">Nice work.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="804757" version="1065353216">I won't pretend I enjoy working with you people. Every moment I have to stand there and endure the Empire's presence is an insult to the memories of all my fallen brothers and sisters. But it's the job right now, and that's what I keep telling my soldiers and myself to keep from taking every last one of you down.

That Iven deal, though. You and Marr taking control of the situation, the egg on high-and-mighty Shan's face when it worked. Oh, man. The people in charge on my side need to understand that when the lives of our own are on the line NOTHING is off the table.

Maybe this will help sway the Jedi the next time they get skittish. Maybe if we get through this, we'll apprehend you and I'll get to lead your interrogation the way I want. That would be thanks to you, you know. If nothing else, the thought makes all this more bearable. Even makes me smile.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="804757" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="804757" version="1065353216">My new role</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="804757" version="1065353216">How unexpected all of this has been. 

I must admit I was flattered by Darth Marr's proposal, and the point-blank manner in which the position was offered led me to believe there was only one answer to give, but I do not intend to execute the role of Sith Intelligence Minister with ego or disdain. I am dedicated fully to the same pragmatic approach I brought to bear against Darth Arkous and the Order of Revan.

You'll be interested to hear I've learned that Theron has moved up the SIS ladder himself. As I'm sure you know, I have no ill will toward the man--point of fact, I respect him a great deal--but that doesn't mean I'm going to make his life easy. I'm already taking steps to lessen his effectiveness.

I will always look back on our work together fondly. Fate willing, it won't be the last time.

May the Force serve you well,
Lana</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
