<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>93</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/chapter_1_rep.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Harson Nild</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="575053" version="1065353216">&quot;Lost&quot; Communications Device</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="575053" version="1065353216">I understand you helped one of my operatives with a problem on Ord Mantell--an Imperial spy who was communicating with her superiors through a &quot;family heirloom.&quot;

Ebenga says you performed &quot;with dutiful competence and professionalism.&quot; High praise from him. We're learning valuable information from the spy, though I'm afraid the details are classified.

I think the Republic Strategic Information Service may find use for you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Alma</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="575053" version="1065353216">My Heirloom</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="575053" version="1065353216">I wanted to thank you again for helping me find my necklace. I'd nearly lost all hope, and then you came along and retrieved it from the scavengers.

I know there was an Arcona saying things about me--claiming I was in league with the Empire. You were right to ignore the freak, and I hope you won't let his lies spread.

I stumbled into a few credits--I'd like to pass them on to you to emphasize just how grateful I am. Maybe someday we'll meet again.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Mennaus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="575053" version="1065353216">We Learn and Fight As One</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Not so long ago, we met in the Gnarls. I am Mennaus--my companions were Avitla, who led us, and Jerridan, whom the Flesh Raiders had injured.

Avitla wished to fight the Flesh Raiders and complete our trials. You helped us return to the temple and did not grant her that chance. For this, I am forever grateful.

Avitla is a kind and brave Padawan. She is also a woman of passionate intensity, and I think this is her great flaw.

She is tending Jerridan now. I think she is learning.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Avitla</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Our Trials</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="575053" version="1065353216">We didn't have much time to talk in all the chaos, but we met in the Gnarls during the Flesh Raider attack. My name is Avitla--you helped my friends and I fight back.

I'm sorry to say that Jerridan won't recover from his injuries for a few months. But I believe we struck a blow, and we retrieved the knowledge of the Jedi Code our Masters asked.

Mennaus won't speak to me. He feels guilty, and he feels he shouldn't have allowed us to fight. You know better.

The galaxy is a terrible place. Tython is where we learn to confront evil and defend ourselves and others. We are Jedi, and we battle together.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Senator Vanara Kayl</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Follow-up on the Merchants' Guild Crisis</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="575053" version="1065353216">I'm pleased to tell you that the troubles with the Migrant Merchants' Guild are coming to an end. We've arrested many of their major leaders and shut down their attack; the citizens of Coruscant are safer, thanks to you.

The citizens of Coruscant also retain their faith in our system of governance and will succeed in rebuilding this planet. This is also thanks to you.

You should know that I'm giving serious consideration to not running for re-election. I know you have doubts about how I achieved my position and the deals I made, but I think you understand that, in the words of the poet Boh-orus, &quot;Better for a few to sacrifice purity than for all to surrender to darkness.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Supreme Chancellor Janarus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="575053" version="1065353216">A Message from the Supreme Chancellor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="575053" version="1065353216">To the hero of the old Galactic Market:

Your recent actions defending Coruscant against the Migrant Merchants' Guild deserve to be applauded--and they will be, by ordinary citizens and the security forces alike.

But equally important, to my mind, are your actions afterward in pursuit of justice. By exposing Senator Kayl's corruption, you defended the spirit of the Republic we hold dear.

Senator Kayl was not an evil woman. But the moment she placed her political goals--however noble--above the principles of the people and state she served, she ceased to possess the right to govern.

As of today, the Senate has accepted Kayl's resignation. Further action will be left to the discretion of the courts.

I am proud to work for a citizen like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Governor Saresh</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Death's Claw Pirates</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="575053" version="1065353216">I understand you recently struck a double blow to the Death's Claw pirates--not only staging a devastating assault on their base of operations, but also confiscating the supply of rakghoul serum they used to vaccinate their forces.

The pirates are now vulnerable and unable to maneuver--I've begun refocusing operations to take advantage of this situation. There is some risk of a rakghoul outbreak inside the pirate camp--but unlike pirates, rakghouls can't erect defenses against bombardment.

Once again, I'm in your debt. Stay on Taris as long as you like.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Doctor Ryamn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Doctor Death's Claw Says Hi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Remember that time you shot your way into a Death's Claw pirate camp and met the local medic? Remember how he convinced you not to subject his patients to a horrible rakghoul-y death by stealing his vaccine supply?

That was me. How's things with you?

I wasn't always with the Death's Claw, you know. I won't give you a whole sob story, but I'm here now because these guys took me in. They're my brothers. Brothers who are jerks, true... but jerks deserve a chance, too.

Anyway, I owe you one. There's talk of pulling out of Taris, and I hope it happens. You ever find yourself in the wrong place and need to get patched up, let me know.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Cera</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Fighting the Rakghouls</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="575053" version="1065353216">I thought you'd want to know that I spoke with the Reconstruction Authority about our discovery. Everyone is in agreement that the rakghouls possess some basic level of intelligence--just enough to remember and value what was once important to them.

But rakghouls aren't people, and we can't forget how many of us they've killed. Or how many innocents they transformed as they rampaged after the Taris bombardment.

Garthe says I'm turning hard, but it's time to wipe the rakghouls out. Now we understand them better, and the governor is already planning a series of traps.

Thank you for everything. Most of all, thank you for making sure no one else on my team dies to those beasts.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Cera</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Finding Peace</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="575053" version="1065353216">So you know--I passed your recommendation on to the Taris Reconstruction Authority. Now that we know the rakghouls are &quot;intelligent&quot;--or at least have some vestigial sense of what was once important to them--strategies are changing.

We can't negotiate with them, of course, but if there are non-violent ways to contain them in the long run, the authority wants to try. Maybe even look for ways to reduce their aggression.

I know I overreacted when I said they should be destroyed. It's just hard, after seeing my people get killed.

Stay safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Private Sakal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Non-human Relations</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="575053" version="1065353216">A little while ago, you helped us out with a dispute regarding property rights--something going back a few centuries, to when human and non-human relations on Taris were ugly (to put it mildly).

I wanted to let you know what's happened since. Word spread that you favored the non-humans, and angry messages poured in from across the Republic. But we also had a reporter in the other day, and people are starting to discuss it in the street. Not pushing-and-shoving discussions, but real, actual talks.

I'm just a grunt. I don't have a clue if this will end with an official government apology and offers of restitution or if it'll just fade away. But it's in the open now, and that has to be a good thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Relus Poh</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Home at last!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="575053" version="1065353216">I wanted to thank you again for helping us reclaim our ancestral home. Jaymizu and I are settling in, and it feels right for our family to be back on Taris.

The squatters who were occupying the land haven't come back. I'm not entirely unsympathetic to their claims, but ultimately, we were in the right. They can look for restitution elsewhere.

In any case, we're grateful, and I'd like to provide this additional recompense. Once the estate is cleaned and furnished, we'd love to have you as a guest.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Ambassador Averdon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="575053" version="1065353216">The Republic's relations with Bareesh</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="575053" version="1065353216">I must thank you again for safeguarding the Republic's interests on Nar Shaddaa from the Kintan Kings gang. I requested additional security forces to the Nikto Sector and am confident we will establish a peaceful base of operations there.

Regarding your discovery of Bareesh's criminal past, the Republic has decided to limit its interactions with him until we are more confident he can be trusted. Nar Shaddaa is dangerous enough without &quot;friends&quot; like him. We will see how sincere Bareesh truly is about aiding the Republic. In the meantime, we will be more vigilant about our alliances.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Bareesh Fenn'ak Torill</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="575053" version="1065353216">A pleasure working with you</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Warmest regards! I trust you are finding Nar Shaddaa a profitable place for your endeavors. My alliance with your representative Ambassador Averdon has flourished now that those Kintan Kings gangsters are so much recycled agricultural nutrient paste.

I deeply appreciate your discretion regarding my past endeavors. What's done is done, and I look forward to a golden age of cooperation between the Hutts and the Republic. In the end, you are far better business partners than the Empire could ever be.

May your cup never run dry, nor your credits voucher go unfilled.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Captain Trezin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="575053" version="1065353216">The Red Light Sector is all clear</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Just wanted to express personal thanks for getting me out of the Red Light Sector. That butcher Doctor Charnagus left Nar Shaddaa in binder cuffs. He won't be talking his way out of a nice long prison sentence for what he did.

We rounded up all the Imperial saboteurs who had infiltrated our warships before they could do any damage. Your actions saved thousands of lives throughout the fleet.

All Republic personnel have been warned away from Club Ufora and the rest of Nar Shaddaa's &quot;entertainment district.&quot; There are healthier ways to let off steam between rotations.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Captain Trezin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Doctor Charnagus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="575053" version="1065353216">I owe you my life over that business in the Red Light Sector. Figured the least I could do is update you on Doctor Charnagus. He was true to his word--surrendered all his research to our SIS contacts. They hustled him off Nar Shaddaa and put the lunatic to work.

We hunted down all the Imperial saboteurs who infiltrated our warships. It wasn't pleasant seeing the faces of men I knew were dead and gone, but at least our fleet is safe.

I'm recommending Republic personnel take shore leave someplace other than Nar Shaddaa from now on.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Grand Master Satele Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="575053" version="1065353216">The rogue Jedi Ako Domi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="575053" version="1065353216">I'm told you were responsible for returning Ako Domi to the Jedi Order. You have my sincerest thanks. I wish you to know that he is being cared for by our best healers--not only those of the body, but the spirit as well.

Though he continues to profess he is beyond redemption, I can sense that the true Ako is not lost to us forever. The atrocities inflicted on him by the Empire can be undone, in time.

It is when the world is darkest that we must see the light in others. Thank you for having such clear vision.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Master Jaric Kaedan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="575053" version="1065353216">The rogue Jedi Ako Domi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="575053" version="1065353216">I was tasked with investigating the death of Ako Domi, and my search ended with conclusive proof he had fallen to the dark side. The order thanks you for your efforts overcoming a dangerously unstable enemy. Left unchecked, Ako Domi could have inflicted great harm on the Republic.

Although it is the order's policy to keep records open and accessible to all, I would consider it a personal favor if you did not publicize this incident. This is a sensitive time not only for the Jedi, but the entire Republic. We must remember who our true enemies are.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Gayem Leksende</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Czerka Corporation Thanks You!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="575053" version="1065353216">My dear friend: 

It feels like a lifetime since we met on Tatooine! All the Senate hearings, our friend Kamus Orden testifying in public... you've certainly kept Czerka Corporation busy. But we'll come out ahead, and think of the publicity!

For my part, my superiors have instructed me to stay out of the limelight awhile. That's fine with me--a few consultants and I have been spending time with that alien mystery box. It's told me some fascinating things... so many stories.

I've enclosed a small gift. It's important that we keep our Czerka Corporate Partners happy.

THE IMPRISONED ONE IS REBORN THE IMPRISONED ONE IS REBORN THE IMPRISONED ONE IS REBORN THE IMPRISON//</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Kamus Orden</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Life after Czerka!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Hope you don't mind me writing, but I wanted to say &quot;thank you&quot; for all you did on Tatooine. I know the SIS tried its best to protect me, but Fauler and I would be dead if it weren't for you--and who knows what Czerka would've gotten away with.

Today was my first day of private testimony to the Senate about Czerka's activities. More tomorrow, then public hearings... it's my whole life now! Fauler keeps telling me the SIS needs specialists to follow money trails--maybe I've got a new career ahead of me.

Anyway, the company won't be closing down, but we caused them some trouble. You take care of yourself--this galaxy is too dangerous to lose you!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Junter Galt</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Militia Status</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="575053" version="1065353216">My name is Junter Galt. I expect you remember that some time ago, I brought you in to help train up the Anchorhead militia.

When things went sour during that battle with the Geonosians, I couldn't figure out why you made the recruits keep fighting. They were kids--they weren't ready for that sort of engagement. 

Now I'm starting to understand. The men who died... they're on my conscience, same as yours. But the survivors are harder now. They know how to make a kill shot, and they're training new blood.

Maybe the militia needed some steel. Maybe I'd gotten old and soft.

Just wanted you to know.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Vastil</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Fighting for the Militia</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="575053" version="1065353216">You probably don't remember me. My name's Vastil, and I was one of the Anchorhead militia recruits you helped train.

You kept us out of the fight with the Geonosians, and I can admit now that I was pretty angry. You were supposed to be teaching us how to fight, and when it came down to it... we weren't good enough?

Of course I get it now. The longer I'm doing this, the more I understand that there are fights you can't win--and that a good leader thinks as much about his team as about his enemy.

That's all I wanted to say. The militia's doing good work--I think you'd be proud.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Onya Oruel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="575053" version="1065353216">The Twin Suns</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Sheriff Encot told me how to reach you. I hope you don't mind--my name is Onya Oruel, and I'm one of the people you saved from the Twin Suns slavers in Anchorhead.

The scum captured me on my sister's moisture farm and held me in the spaceport for a week. They barely fed us and screamed at us all the time. They didn't hurt us much, thankfully, so as not to &quot;damage the goods.&quot;

When we heard shooting, we were terrified. Then we saw you fighting through the crowd, and it was like I could breathe again after drowning for days.

We put together a gift for you. Thank you for everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Duke Charle Organa</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Keikana Herot</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="575053" version="1065353216">I feel I owe you an apology. My men have reclaimed the Ulgo &quot;Pain Factory&quot; facility and reported back on their findings. What horrors you must have witnessed.... I am shocked at how far our brothers in House Ulgo have fallen--though I have no right to be, given the brutality in my own house.

I am reassigning Science Commander Keikana Herot. Her insistence that we preserve as much as we could from the Ulgo facility shows that she is not fit for her post. Please know that she does not represent the wishes of House Organa, and accept my thanks again for dismantling that evil place.

Duke Charle Remmot Organa</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="328" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Keikana Herot</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="575053" version="1065353216">FW: Experiment #16 Results [Autogenerated Message]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Thought you'd like to see what we're accomplishing with House Ulgo's research on the Killiks--pretty impressive stuff!

To: Keikana Herot
From: F8-N0
Subject: Experiment #16 Results [Autogenerated Message]

Administered 20 kilograms of Ulgo serum. Killik subjects remained hostile.
Administered 30 kilograms of Ulgo serum. Killik subjects appeared distressed.
Administered 40 kilograms of Ulgo serum. Killik subjects appeared extremely distressed.
Administered 50 kilograms of Ulgo serum. Killik subjects began acting out against each other.
Administered 60 kilograms of Ulgo serum. Killik subjects became docile and obedient to administrator's direction.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Andra Cressen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="575053" version="1065353216">One Good Turn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Just wanted to thank you again for the rescue from House Rist, and for your advice. My father is still being stubborn, but I think he'll change his mind once he sees my next report. I'm posing as a long-lost cousin to House Thul now--and a cousin can get much farther than a servant girl ever could.

You understand why I can't go into details. I've enclosed some of the spoils of my new position. This should make us more than even!

Andra</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Major Cressen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="575053" version="1065353216">In Thanks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="575053" version="1065353216">You already have the gratitude of my house for your assistance against House Ulgo, but I feel I must thank you again for rescuing my daughter from those Rist thugs. I don't know what I would have done if anything had happened to her. Andra's heart was in the right place, I suppose--but war is no place for a young lady.

I have sent my daughter back to the Apalis Coast, where the fighting has mostly subsided. She sends me scathing comm messages, but I know she will forgive me some day. After all my family has given to this war... well, I have earned the right to be a little selfish, I think.

Respectfully yours,
Major Corlis Brado Cressen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Katei Panteer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="575053" version="1065353216">In Thanks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Bouris Ulgo is dead. My life has been consumed with revenge for so long that even now, I find it hard to believe the old viper is gone. My family is safe again--though I don't think we'll ever stop looking over our shoulders.

Of course, there are many in the Republic who would like to absolve Bouris Ulgo of his crimes. My opinions of such people are not befitting of a princess, but I want you to know how grateful I am that you did the right thing.

Princess Katei Elinari Panteer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Captain Scov on behalf of Commander Bradel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Bouris Ulgo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="575053" version="1065353216">The commander asked me to pass along a little something extra, for helping us take Bouris Ulgo into custody. We used to study some of his victories during training--can't believe he ended up in a jail cell. 

The Panteers aren't happy, of course, but personally I don't care what those traitors think. Alderaan needs a ruler who's loyal to the Republic. Hopefully after this war is over, we'll get one.

Captain Scov</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="343" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Ria Deleru</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="344" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Free and Clear!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="345" id2="575053" version="1065353216">I just wanted to thank you again for your help with Nik. I'm sure he gave you quite the sob story, but we're really better off apart. I've got dreams, ambitions, you know? All Nik ever did was complain!

I don't know how long you'll be on Coruscant, but I've sent some gifts that'll help you enjoy the nightlife. Come back and see me anytime!

Ria</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="346" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Nik Deleru</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="347" id2="575053" version="1065353216">Urgent! Please Help!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="348" id2="575053" version="1065353216">I know you already rescued my beloved Ria from that filthy dance hall, and for that I will be eternally grateful. But alas, further tragedy has befallen us! I put Ria on a transport back to my family on Glee Anselm, but my family says she never arrived!

Now I have received a disturbing letter from Ria that says she left the transport at the first refueling stop and never wants to see me again. She must have been kidnapped by slavers who forced her to write me these lies--my poor, beautiful mate!

Please, you must help me. I have already sent compensation, and I can send more if that's what it takes--I must have Ria back!

Nik Deleru</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
