<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>36</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/chapter_2_rep.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="575664" version="1065353216">General Korvan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Regarding Moff Dracen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="575664" version="1065353216">I'm pleased to report that Moff Dracen, the Imperial you captured on Quesh, has provided SIS interrogators with key strategic information about the Empire. As we suspected, their presence on Quesh was an attempt to incite us to war.

Reports show Dracen tried to goad you into killing him. I'm glad you had the poise and composure to ignore his taunts; he's far more valuable to us alive. The Republic needs more individuals like you; those who think before they act.

General Korvan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="575664" version="1065353216">General Korvan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Quesh status update</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="575664" version="1065353216">I'm pleased to report that the situation on Quesh remains relatively stable, though I'm still trying to come to grips with Major Treeg's betrayal. He was a brilliant tactician, but he never understood the value of careful consideration before taking action. Yet I never imagined he lusted so strongly after war that he'd join the Empire.

Fortunately, your presence thwarted his plan. The Republic needs more individuals like you, and I'm proud to know we're on the same side.

General Korvan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Chief Engineer Soobo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="575664" version="1065353216">For your wonderful help on Hoth!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Thank you, thank you again for saving our geothermal plant, and for defending us so magnificently! You've been an inspiration to all of us. The defense system to protect the plant is progressing very well indeed. When we can finally settle on Hoth, my people will have a safe haven with all the power they could ever need.

Please, take this! You've done so much for us, it's the very least we can give!

Baleeq Soobo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Major Vinson</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Update on the geothermal plant</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="575664" version="1065353216">We've sent a recovery crew in to check out the geothermal power plant after the blast. Those charges did the trick. Unfortunately, we found a number of Ortolan civilians among the pirate casualties. I'm sorry, but they didn't make it. Don't blame yourself; the White Maw probably turned on the Ortolans when they realized they couldn't hold the plant any longer.

We've already started gathering what salvage we can find. Those Ortolans might be small, but their engineering was amazing. Some of the equipment we've recovered might benefit Cresh Outpost; more importantly, it's out of Imperial hands. 

Major Vinson</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Kieral</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="575664" version="1065353216">The Hailstorm Brotherhood</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="575664" version="1065353216">We're keeping an eye out for any resurgence of the brotherhood, but it looks like they're going to stay scattered. Thanks again. You do nice work. 

I suspect I won't be on Hoth much longer. Meeting Captain Biron's got me thinking more about the war. It's getting harder and harder to order our forces against Imperials when I know at least one of them was an honorable man who could be reasoned with. I'm considering a transfer to the Diplomatic Corps; if there are Imperials out there who are willing to talk, there should be Republic citizens willing to listen.

Lieutenant Kieral
Hoth Outpost Senth</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Sergeant Katcho</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Captain Biron</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="575664" version="1065353216">They took Captain Biron away for interrogation. I hope the SIS takes their time. Trust me, Biron might have seemed reasonable and such, but that's exactly his style. I'm glad he didn't have you fooled. He's more dangerous than the Hailstorm Brotherhood could ever be.

This is for you. A little sweetener from someone who once saw that slime-eel's plans firsthand. If the Imps try playing nice again, we'll know what to do.

Katcho</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Iain Sarkus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="575664" version="1065353216">As Promised</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Just wanted to thank you again for getting the Hawkeyes out alive. They didn't deserve what Riserre tried to do to them. Glad to hear he's out of commission!

I'm sure the commander was steamed, but he'll get over it when we show him what we've been working on. Sending along a little preview of what we can do!

Iain</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Wes Durga on behalf of Commander Madine</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="575664" version="1065353216">FW: Markaran Plains Casualty Report</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="575664" version="1065353216">The commander thought you'd like to see what real victory looks like. SIS picked this up off the Imperial wire.

To: [UNABLE TO DECRYPT]
From: [UNABLE TO DECRYPT]
Subject: Markaran Plains Casualty Report

Total Deaths: 1,048
KIA: 691
Non-hostile: 0
WIA: 357

Remarks: The Republic invasion began in conjunction with a special forces attack on Balmorra's satellite system. Although the system was shut down upon the Republic's unauthorized access, the enemy was able to locate our dispatch console. The majority of those killed in action were at the regional command center; they were unable to request backup or relay orders as a result.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Doctor Carsiri</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Long Overdue Thanks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="575664" version="1065353216">First off, let me apologize. When the Barrager laboratory went up in flames, we ran so quickly from the chaos that I didn't get a chance to properly thank you. I'd like to remedy that now.

You'll be pleased to hear we've begun rebuilding. We're even getting help from Doctor Ortis himself. You may remember him--one of the weapon's original designers. He sends his thanks for rescuing him from the Gorinth Brig. From the stories he tells, I'm truly glad you were able to destroy that place, too.

Life is getting to be rather routine again, but I think I've had all the adventure I need for a lifetime. Thank you, truly, for saving our lives--and for everything you've done for Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Dannax</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="575664" version="1065353216">FW: Transfer Request Form 4187</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Commander Madine's report indicated you were involved in the &quot;Barrager&quot; mission. Could you offer any insight into this unexpected request?  

To: Lieutenant Dannax, Department of Personnel Action
From: Commander Madine
Subject: Transfer Request Form 4187

Section I: Personal Identification
Name (Last, First): Madine, Cassius
Grade or Rank: CDR

Section II: Duty Status Change
I request the following action: Reassignment

Section III: Remarks
I feel that my continued presence on Balmorra will pose a serious threat to the ultimate success of the operation. A coalition of Republic and local forces has secured the planet, and the time is right for a transition in command. Further justification for this request can be found in my report on the failed &quot;Barrager&quot; weapon reclamation mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Doctor Meln</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Perceived Design Flaws</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Commander Madine informed me you were the one responsible for preserving the &quot;Barrager&quot; weapon. As one of the weapon's designers, I wanted to thank you for this decision, and to set the record straight. I'm aware you may have heard some alarming reports on its environmental impact.

While it is true that the Barrager requires an immense amount of power to operate, this is only its first iteration! My team and I are already hard at work on a more efficient design. And even in its current state, the benefits far outweigh the risks--we haven't seen hide nor hair of the Empire since the Barrager was deployed.

As you can imagine, I'm extremely gratified by this. But don't think it's gone to my head! In gratitude for your decision (as well as rescuing me from the Gorinth Brig!), I have sent you one of my team's creations. Please enjoy! 

As for Doctor Ortis, he has declined the opportunity to join my team and retired to the Outer Rim. It seems some men just can't handle success.

Sincerely yours,
Doctor Otak'or Meln</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Ari Skyff</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Thanks Again!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="575664" version="1065353216">Bummed your frequency off some resistance fighters--hope you don't mind. Thought I'd thank you again for getting those supplies back for me and getting me a piece of the Corvani. My grand old girl was really something, wasn't she? 

Figured since I was stuck here, might as well make myself useful, so I started making runs for the locals again. Turned out to be a pretty nice gig! Even starting to get fond of this junker they've got me flying. I call her the Corvana.

Ari

P.S. Almost forgot! The resistance reclaimed another warehouse last month. Passing along some extras. I owe you one.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
