<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>57</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/chapter_3_imp.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Ellis Ruger</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="575666" version="1065353216">A Sign of Respect</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Still can't understand why you let me live on Belsavis. Credits from the ransom seems too obvious. Maybe you figured I'd be broken and humiliated if you spared me. But I think you're smart enough to know I'm stronger than that.

I deal with scum and filth everyday, but I got the sense you were different. I think there's some nobility in you, even if you are working for the wrong side in this galactic war. So here's something to remember me by; a sign of respect.

But if we cross paths again, I won't hesitate to try and take you down.

Marshal Ellis Ruger</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Commander Calum</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Ellis Ruger</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Word of Ellis Ruger's death on Belsavis has spread to the highest echelons of the Imperial Guard. My superiors feel the brutal execution of one of the Republic's most respected peace officers is worthy of special recognition. In the Empire, excellence does not go unrewarded.

Commander Calum</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Trea Kobbeth</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Sergeant Kobbeth</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="575666" version="1065353216">My husband is Sergeant Kobbeth of the Republic military. He told me an Imperial saved him from those horrible Esh-kha on Belsavis, then spared his life. I told him he should do something to thank you, but he said it would look bad for a Republic soldier to correspond with &quot;the enemy.&quot; So I'm sending this message on his behalf.

I don't consider you &quot;the enemy.&quot; In my eyes you're a hero. We can never repay your act of kindness, but I wanted to send you something to let you know we appreciate everything you did.

Trea</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Colonel Grang</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Belsavis</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="575666" version="1065353216">You really bailed me out on Belsavis. My troops didn't stand a chance against those Esh-kha freaks. Only I couldn't thank you properly with Commander Calum listening in. Bad enough I couldn't get the job done, but actually admitting it would kill my career.

We both know you're the only reason my next of kin isn't getting notification I was killed in action. Figure that's got to be worth something.

Colonel Grang</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Commander Calum</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="575666" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="575666" version="1065353216">As the one who freed the Dread Masters from their prison on Belsavis, I thought it fitting you should be updated on their status. After long deliberations with the Emperor, the Dread Masters retired to a secret stronghold to recover from their long incarceration.

Since then, there has been no contact with the Dread Masters, though I am certain they are gathering their strength and planning how to best use their power to influence the current galactic conflict. When the time is right, the Emperor will unleash them against the Republic--another devastating weapon to bring  our enemies to ruin.

Commander Calum</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Darth Serevin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="575666" version="1065353216">The end of Master Keln</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Your destruction of the Ruined City tablets was timely. My archaeologists have been charged with recovering Master Keln's belongings, in case there are any other trifling, politically devastating discoveries they may have overlooked. I have enclosed the more interesting pieces found to date; please consider them trophies of war.

Darth Serevin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Overseer Temereth</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="575666" version="1065353216">The Ruined City Tablets</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="575666" version="1065353216">The tablets you recovered from the Jedi Master Keln on Voss have arrived here, at the Korriban Academy. My students and I have made an extensive study of the tablets, and they appear to be genuine, if written in a rather overblown style. They describe an ancient war between Sith explorers and the native Voss people, but the description of the Voss does not seem to match the notes Darth Serevin sent me. More ancient hyperbole, perhaps.

Regardless, there's interesting data here. It suggests the ancient Sith may have roamed further than our records suggest. This will be corrected. My thanks for bringing these to our attention.

Overseer Temereth
Third Keeper of Antiquities</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Darth Serevin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Congratulations again!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Events are moving on Voss since your little &quot;revelation&quot; of Jedi involvement in the Dark Heart. I understand that Jedi ambassadors have been denied audiences with Voss dignitaries three times. Republic gifts are left ignored on the steps of the Tower of Prophecy. The weather is clement in Voss-Ka, but somehow I sense the Republic is in for a long, chilly winter.

The Voss, on the other hand, have thawed considerably toward us. Great strides have been made, and I am confident we will see Voss marching under the banner of the Empire before too long. We have achieved more than I hoped.

Darth Serevin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Darth Serevin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Recompense</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Days of patient negotiations, endless gifts and delicate political maneuvering in both Voss-Ka and Kaas City--then one sentence from you and our entire position on Voss comes crashing down. The Voss are no longer interested in discussing an alliance against the Republic and are now focused on the Gormak. I hope you are satisfied. 

The sole advantage to come out of this disaster is that the Voss Mystics seem to have warmed to us slightly in the interim. Your &quot;discovery&quot; is spoken of with interest, as are you. I cannot possibly imagine why, but the Mystics will not be satisfied until you are furnished with a reward. In the interest of not jeopardizing our situation here further, I enclose both the gift... and a heartfelt request that you consider the Empire's future more carefully from now on.

Darth Serevin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Captain Visrak Ortano</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Thanks for the help</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="575666" version="1065353216">I just wanted to thank you again for getting rid of the baradium bomb so quickly. There's no telling what the Voss might have done if they'd found out about it, and I couldn't say a word with Karish-Ma hanging over me. Those blasted Gormak have been picking over our supply dumps for weeks now. With luck, this near-miss will be enough to requisition some guards and get those dumps properly secured. 
This will not happen again.

Captain Ortano</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Captain Visrak Ortano</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="575666" version="1065353216">A narrow escape</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="575666" version="1065353216">All right, I think I've finally convinced the Voss that the baradium bomb was a Gormak plot to discredit the Empire, and that their scavenging of our technology is more proof of Gormak inferiority. (They loved that.) This isn't the first time we've seen our designs in Gormak hands, though. Maybe they actually are trying to discredit us. Who knows how those animals think?

We seem to have scored a few points with the Voss over this--they're sympathetic to anyone suffering Gormak troubles. My superiors send their compliments.

Captain Ortano</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Yem Leksende</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Apologies and Thanks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Dear Czerka Partner, 

The Czerka Corporation board of directors was greatly distressed to learn of your recent troubles with our head of Corellian operations, Brall Tavar.

We apologize wholeheartedly for Tavar's actions--it is Czerka policy to never become involved in political matters, and we hold the greatest respect for your handling of the situation.

Please accept the attached as a token of our appreciation, and as reassurance that the Czerka Corporation looks forward to servicing your needs in the future.

Regards,
Yem Leksende
Czerka Corporation Special Executive</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Brall Tavar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Deepest Thanks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Honored Imperial Representative, 

I am extremely pleased to report that Czerka Corellia operations have managed to resume in the wake of your humbling and potent attack.

We have all doubled our efforts to ensure that we can put our full production capacity into the Empire's service as quickly as possible.
I've attached a small token of our unending gratitude and loyalty--please enjoy it in good health and victory.

With utmost respect,
Brall Tavar
Czerka Corellia</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Major Tradik</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Tunnel Clearing Proceeding</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="575666" version="1065353216">My men are working their way through the Selonian tunnels as we speak. I've authorized collapses wherever flame projectors don't get the job done.

They're taking blood for every inch they give up, but we're not going to stop until there isn't a single Selonian beast left, rest assured.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Major Tradik</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Selonians</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="575666" version="1065353216">My men are rounding up Murthil's hairy kin as we speak. Whatever you did down there, it worked--they're perfectly docile now.

We'll put the beasts to work making maps for our commando units, then ship them out for labor details wherever they're needed.

Nice bit of work.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Darbin Sull</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="575666" version="1065353216">From the Desk of the Prime Minister</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Greetings! 

Things are going really well here on Corellia now that I'm in charge--you made the right choice, I assure you!

Of course, there are still a few scattered elements who insist on dragging out the violence, but I'm sure they'll give it up soon enough.

I've included a small gift--let no one say that Prime Minister Sull doesn't support his constituents!

Best wishes,
Darbin Sull
Prime Minister of Corellia</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Darth Charnus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Corellia</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="575666" version="1065353216">My master tells me that your choice to ensure direct Imperial control of Corellia's government continues to pay dividends.

Our fight to crush the last of these rebels is difficult enough as it is; I can only imagine the problems we would face with that fool Darbin acting as intermediary.

Such wise forethought is deserving of reward. Congratulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Apprentice Tinray</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="575666" version="1065353216">The Kaleesh</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Darth Malgus wishes you to know that General Gelrex and his Kaleesh warriors have joined the Imperial ranks. With their strength added to our own, it cannot be long until the stealth fleet becomes a reality.

My master is impressed by your forward thinking, though it required you to defy a direct order. He hopes this gift ensures you will remain his ally in the battles to come.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Major Dogran on behalf of Grand Moff Regus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="575666" version="1065353216">Operation Dark Ice</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="575666" version="1065353216">I have been authorized by Grand Moff Regus to provide you with the attached compensation, in recognition of your assistance against the Kaleesh General Gelrex and his forces.

The Grand Moff appreciates your adherence to traditional Imperial values in light of dissenting opinions. He hopes he can rely on your continued support in this matter.

Respectfully,
Major Dogran</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
