<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>96</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/chapter_1_imp.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Kendrel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Escaping Hutta</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="575055" version="1065353216">I didn't get a chance to thank you for helping my son and I escape Hutta. Now, with a few hundred light-years behind us, it occurs to me how much I owe you.

If Gianna had managed to send Zi'am to Korriban, he'd be dead in a matter of months--or he'd have become a monster. I've seen too much of the Sith Academy to think otherwise.

Now the boy has a chance. If he's gifted in the Force, I'll teach him what I can and keep him away from Sith and Jedi. There must be somewhere in the galaxy we can find peace.

Thank you for your compassion, however you found it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Overseer Harkun</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Zi'am on Korriban</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="575055" version="1065353216">I understand you are responsible for the acquisition of a new student for the Sith Academy--a boy named Zi'am. He recently came under my tutelage, and I wished to thank you.

Zi'am is uncooperative, foolish and unappreciative of his gifts. He spends most of his time whining about his father--the one you murdered. But while he may be unpleasant company, he is passionate--which gives him great potential in the dark side.

The Academy is grateful for your assistance. Consider yourself duly rewarded.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Emic Sandor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="575055" version="1065353216">The Destruction of Heretics</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="575055" version="1065353216">The Order of Revan will soon cease to be. Tari Darkspanner was taken in secret and is being unburdened of her heresy to the Dark Council even as we speak. An infiltrator is speaking to the Revanites in her place, laying the foundation for their eventual destruction. It is an old ruse, but a useful one. In time, the Revanite camp and so-called holy places will burn.

Darth Charnus expresses a continued appreciation for your efforts. From Darkspanner's confessions, it seems the Revanites' influence had spread further than anticipated, reaching even beyond Dromund Kaas. Now this pernicious rot will finally shrivel and die.

May you continue to serve the Empire.

--Sandor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="575055" version="1065353216">CAUTION: CANNOT VERIFY SENDER</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Friendship and Masks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="575055" version="1065353216">The Order of Revan remains hidden. Already the name of Darth Charnus is shunned in Kaas City. Turning the strength of his apprentice against him; a worthy master stroke for a follower of Revan.

You have done a great service for us, but the restoration of Revan's mask to us is greater still. I fear, however, that it cannot remain in our hands indefinitely. The mask of Revan has a higher purpose to fulfill.

Carry our teachings with you. Know the power of death and rebirth, and their ability to cleanse the mind of outdated preconceptions. Embrace wisdom, no matter its source. Seek allies who may teach, as well as serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Ismar Brengle</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Good news!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="575055" version="1065353216">How magnificent the pursuit of science can be, and how delightfully profitable. Those cybernetic research files you stole from Lord Grathan proved to be revolutionary, even more so than I had hoped. Grathan has no idea what slipped through his sweaty, nerveless grasp, and hopefully never will. 

My buyer was very pleased with the files. I understand a veritable cyborg horde is already in production, so here is your share, as promised. Enjoy!

--Ismar Brengle</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Lanniter Droge</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Thank you very much</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="575055" version="1065353216">My cybernetic research data is safe. Project ARC will continue, with Lord Grathan's backing. I've already done preliminary trials on several volunteers, and the results are incredible. Our wounded veterans can look forward to new medical treatments and cybernetically regrown limbs and it's all thanks to you.

By the way, I heard that Ismar Brengle is in a spot of trouble. It seems she tried to sell some cybernetic research data on the black market, but the data turned out to be the breeding notes for Lord Grathan's pedigree tuk'ata. Just for that, I'd like to send you a little something.

Lanniter Droge, Project ARC Lead Researcher</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Major Tyrus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Force sensitives in hiding</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="575055" version="1065353216">I wanted to thank you again for your handling of the &quot;special cargo&quot; at Cave 52 on Balmorra. We managed to sterilize the cave with little resistance. 

More importantly, we were able to recover information from the rebels' computers, suggesting how they planned to smuggle their Force-sensitive &quot;cargo&quot; offworld. As a result, we've cracked one of the rebels' key supply lines and seized a large amount of contraband. I've included a sample with this message--merely for your inspection, of course.

Major Tyrus
Commander, Second Battalion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Jeraa Sulyan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="575055" version="1065353216">I remember Cave 52</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="575055" version="1065353216">I shouldn't be sending this to you. You're the enemy. People like you ground Balmorra under their boot heels. But you didn't kill us or turn us in when our lives were in your hands. I can't feel the Force hardly at all--barely a whisper, like a hand I can't use--but I can sense how close I came to being killed. It's like being on the edge of a cliff.

I feel like I owe you something. I can't get it out of my mind. Take these. I made them with my own hands, somewhere secret and safe.

Take them. I want to forget.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Gann Sakoal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Please delete this after you read it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="575055" version="1065353216">I must be swift, but I wished to thank you for your assistance in the matter of my wife. Kelara, much to my dismay, was discovered during a patrol. Her death was quite clearly the work of Balmorra's insidious resistance elements. It is a tragedy.

As you also knew Kelara, I'm enclosing a small gift as a consolation. Forgive the briefness of my message; I am late for a very important performance evaluation.

G. Sakoal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Kelara Sakoal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="575055" version="1065353216">I'm off Balmorra....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="575055" version="1065353216">I'm writing this in a grimy little corner of Vaiken Spacedock while I wait for my transport to arrive. I can't even remember the name of the planet it's going to. On Balmorra, I was so bored I thought anything was better than being stuck there with Gann. It turns out &quot;anything&quot; covers a lot of ground. You can even wind up with your no-good husband trying to frame you as a traitor.

Talk about starting over. But I'm alive. Plus Gann was a little slow about changing our credit account password, so I've been able to buy everything I need--including a first-class ticket. I think you deserve what's left. 

--Kelara</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Lerek Serrus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="575055" version="1065353216">For your service to Balmorra</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="575055" version="1065353216">My master, Darth Lachris, extends her compliments. Grand Marshal Cheketta's confession regarding the Republic's illegal invasion has had a greater impact than previously thought. His words have been heard from the Core Worlds to the Outer Rim. The Republic Senate is shivering in anticipation of our response to Cheketta's actions--exactly as the Dark Council hoped. A key element in the Council's strategy has been achieved.

My master sends this, with her continued appreciation for your efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Lerek Serrus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Your work on Balmorra</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="575055" version="1065353216">My master, Darth Lachris, extends her compliments. The Republic's public disownment of Grand Marshal Cheketta's actions has cut deeper than we anticipated. The Balmorran resistance has been heavily demoralized, and we have even been able to recruit deserters from among them. It cannot be long before the rebellion on Balmorra is but a distant memory.

My master sends this, with her continued appreciation for your efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Maro Vizhen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="575055" version="1065353216">The Shadow Syndicate</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Your assistance crushing the Exchange's campaign against the Empire has been communicated to the Diplomatic Service leadership. We are currently reorganizing Nar Shaddaa's Shadow Syndicate into a more useful configuration for our future interests.

Vaarko Tiyai has proven highly compliant and provided us numerous negotiating advantages, while the DX annihilator network has been put to work removing various targets in our path. Godoba the Hutt, main instigator of the Shadow Syndicate's betrayal of us, remains within our custody. His humiliation sets an example for the others, but he is not through serving us.

The attached gift was liberated from Vaarko's private reserves. I felt you deserved it most.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Godoba the Hutt</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Regards from the Shadow Syndicate</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="575055" version="1065353216">On behalf of Vaarko Tiyai and DX-TX, I wish to congratulate you again for furthering the Shadow Syndicate's alliance with the mighty Sith Empire. We shall all prosper from this friendship. May the day soon come when Nar Shaddaa's lights shine only for us.

We attended a brief Imperial memorial service for the unfortunate Maro Vizhen. We are confident no unpleasantness will come of her untimely passing.

As promised, we pursue the remnants of Ukabi's forces and drive the Exchange from this sector. We wish to share the fruits of our efforts with you.

Onward to profit!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Madel Felth</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="575055" version="1065353216">The Flame has gone out</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="575055" version="1065353216">I am ashamed to confess that I was secretly unsure releasing the Flame and his rebels from Nar Shaddaa was the correct course of action. However, intelligence reports indicate he and his people have left the Hutt moon and relocated to the distant planet of Garqi on the Outer Rim.

The rebels appear to have traded their blasters for farming implements and founded an isolated agrarian community--to which we say, good riddance. Even Admiral Jefand seems pleased with this resolution. He wished me to forward a small token of his appreciation for your service.

May the Empire prevail.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Admiral Jefand</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="575055" version="1065353216">The Nar Shaddaa rebellion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="575055" version="1065353216">The Flame and his pitiful minions have all been exterminated, and further investigation reveals no remaining traces of the rebellion against us on Nar Shaddaa. Your combat prowess against the Gen'Dai was a pleasure to witness, and I will not forget your timely arrival that saved my life.

I have ensured that all records of the Flame's fate--and your role in it--be made public. It's important for the citizens of this Hutt colony to understand what happens to those who pit themselves against the Empire. Anti-Imperial dissent across the sector is falling off dramatically. Thank you for your service.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="575055" version="1065353216">General Kolvin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Darth Revan's device</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="575055" version="1065353216">I have just received word from our scientists on Dromund Kaas. The machine you recovered from Darth Revan's storehouse on Nar Shaddaa is nothing short of unique. Scans indicate the machine appears to be expanding at a molecular level.

More importantly, the device has produced several &quot;offspring&quot;--intriguing weapons of alien design that we haven't previously encountered. Our scientists are eagerly unlocking the machine's full potential.

Given the sensitive nature of your discovery and its potential impact on our future plans, Imperial High Command requests that you keep the details of your mission confidential. Secrecy is security.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="575055" version="1065353216">General Kolvin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Darth Revan's legacy</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="575055" version="1065353216">I have just received word from our scientists on Dromund Kaas. The &quot;seed device&quot; you extracted from Darth Revan's storehouse on Nar Shaddaa appears to reconfigure nearby matter in order to grow. We speculate this ability may even one day allow it to produce separate machines of many configurations.

Unfortunately, the seed's growth rate could take decades or even centuries to produce anything of use. By then, the Empire should have long since conquered every star from the Unknown Regions to the Core.

Nevertheless, the device is apparently of scientific value, and your contribution to our Empire's future has been noted for posterity.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Lord Berow</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Incident with the Jawa Shaman</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="575055" version="1065353216">You have acted in the interests of the Sith Order and eliminated an enemy of the Empire. Well done. 

The troops now laugh at the Jawa &quot;shamans,&quot; claiming their mythical powers amount to superstition and technological trickery. There are no more rumors of the Jawas' Force sensitivity, and this is as it should be.

The idea that such disgusting creatures could wield the might of the Sith would have been poison among the lower classes. We must forever remain vigilant--if Sith are not feared, we do not deserve our position.

When the Jedi are dead and the Republic is defeated, we will make a galaxy where only Sith wield power. Until then... small steps.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Darth Serevin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Lord Berow and the Jawa Shamans</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="575055" version="1065353216">I understand you were recently involved in the discovery of Force-sensitive Jawas. Furthermore, I understand Lord Berow attempted to conceal this new threat in a misguided attempt to uphold Sith supremacy.

Let me assure you that you acted wisely, and that Lord Berow will be punished when she returns to me.

The Empire will never triumph if we refuse to acknowledge our enemies' strengths. Power in the hands of others must be controlled, not denied.

You have earned my respect. Perhaps we shall meet some day.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Aichiya Wonn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="575055" version="1065353216">The Sons of Palawa Remember</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="575055" version="1065353216">You brought the ghosts of the desert upon us. You have been asked never to return.

Yet you are a warrior born.

We fought the ghosts as they transformed our village, one by one, into whispering machines. You met them and slew them at our side, fighting with the Sons of Palawa.

Some of us honor you, even as we hate what you brought. You will be remembered in secret, and we will learn to fight as you fought.

Under two suns, we live on. We rebuild, and we become greater through hardship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Captain Golah</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="575055" version="1065353216">FW: Sons of Palawa Report</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="575055" version="1065353216">We had a small squad do a sweep of the Sons of Palawa village. Report enclosed.

To: Captain Golah
From: Private Tannrel
Subject: Sons of Palawa Report

As anticipated, the baradium explosives atomized all matter within the village. Particle size is within acceptable limits. The machines should not regenerate.

We spotted a few Palawa scouts returning home to discover the ruins. We avoided engagement. Unclear how many survivors may be at large. If they manage to regroup, they may seek revenge in the long run; I took the liberty of alerting nearby Imperial stations.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Captain Golah</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Tatooine Expedition Aftermath</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="575055" version="1065353216">We're in the final phases of cleanup for the Czerka expedition on Tatooine, and I wanted to bring you up to date.

We're wrapping up studies of the Czerka base and completing download of all remaining data. Once we're done, we'll lock down the site; it goes against my instincts, but we can't risk contamination.

Surviving team members are being reassigned, mostly to Hoth and Ziost. General Threnoldt has offered me a position at headquarters--a privilege, but I'm sorry to leave my men. If you run into any Reclamation Service teams, keep us in mind.

I said it before, but we're forever grateful for your aid--when Darth Silthar died, we thought we were doomed. We may not have found everything, but we're alive thanks to you.

Stay safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Captain Golah</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Tatooine Expedition / Czerka Box</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="575055" version="1065353216">You were as much a part of the expedition on Tatooine as myself or Darth Silthar. Instead of suffering major casualties, my team would have been wiped out without your aid. So I wanted to pass this along, despite regulations.

The Science Bureau has been examining the alien box you recovered from the Czerka laboratory. I can't get a full report, but I gather they built a secure clean room in which to communicate with it.

Progress is slow, and rumor has it one examiner has already lost his mind. Maybe it's best it's out of our hands.

They also sent a small package marked for you, attached. More progress.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="328" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Lord Jorad Thul</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Regarding Lord Killesa</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Our mutual ally, Moff Sarek, suggested I reward you further for your assistance against the lawless rebels who refuse to accept my house's right to the throne. I have enclosed an additional gift that I hope better reflects House Thul's gratitude.

However, I also wish to offer you my personal thanks for conducting yourself honorably against Lord Cedarik Killesa. I was willing to allow my former friend to be crushed beneath cold rock. Instead, you defeated him through a duel--and showed me that we do not need to sacrifice our civility in order to claim the crown.

I remain in your debt,
Lord Jorad Sindarus Thul</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Geor Vers on behalf of Moff Sarek</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="575055" version="1065353216">An Excellent Performance</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Moff Sarek wishes to convey his appreciation for your assistance with Lord Jorad Thul, who is proving to be more pliable than we had previously believed. He has ordered several sneak attacks on House Organa forces and requires less and less guidance from Moff Sarek every day.

The Moff is certain this is due to your influence, particularly in how you handled the rebel Killesa and his men. It is the Moff's hope that the ideals of &quot;civilized warfare&quot; will leave Alderaan forever. He thanks you for your contribution.

Respectfully,
Geor Vers</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Daria Thul</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Our Thanks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="575055" version="1065353216">We have been asked by the one called Stanel Thul to send a message of gratitude. We were made to leave the Kind to protect the nest, though we wish we could return every day. We are forced to swallow vile poisons. The humans watch us and worry. They smell of death and disease--especially the one who calls himself our father.

We do not bear you ill will. We know you are violent, separate, not of the Kind. We pity you. If only you could know the peace of the nest, as we once did. But now, we can no longer hear the song.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="575055" version="1065353216">General Stanel Thul</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="575055" version="1065353216">For Your Discretion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="575055" version="1065353216">I feel I must apologize for my emotional display when you delivered news of Daria's fate. In my grief for my daughter, I neglected to think of my house and the shame this would bring on us were it public knowledge.

You are the only one who knows of my poor Daria's true condition. I have enclosed a gift in the hopes that it will stay that way. When this war is over, I will lead my troops into that foul Killik nest and free my daughter--somehow.

Cordially,
General Stanel Andaren Thul</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Muir on behalf of Darth Viktus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Bouris Ulgo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="575055" version="1065353216">My lord wishes me to thank you again for your swift elimination of the usurper, Bouris Ulgo. Our allies in House Thul were most pleased to hear that he will no longer be a threat to their interests--or, for that matter, the Empire's.

Rumor has it that the Thuls plan to raise a young Sith of their house to the throne. My lord attributes this directly to your efforts on Alderaan. He hopes the enclosed gift will convey his appreciation.

Respectfully,
Lieutenant Muir</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="343" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Aurren Panteer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="344" id2="575055" version="1065353216">On Behalf of My House</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="345" id2="575055" version="1065353216">I have already thanked you once for bringing the tyrant Bouris Ulgo to justice. But I have since realized that my thanks do not go far enough. News of the usurper's capture spread to the wayward members of my house, and we are a family again.

When this war is over, we intend to call a summit and allow the houses to judge Bouris Ulgo for his crimes. It is my hope that this trial will show us who the true ruler of Alderaan is--whether he be in House Thul or not.

You have united a house once divided and on the brink of extinction. You will forever be our friend and ally, and we will forever be in your debt.

Lord Aurren Tuile Panteer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="346" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Apprentice Malora</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="347" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Lord Renning's Research</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="348" id2="575055" version="1065353216">You have no idea what you've done, do you? That tuk'ata brain was just the beginning. Lord Renning's after k'lor'slug eggs now, and I'm expected to get them. Punishment for my weakness, he says.

Before I become brood meat, my master has ordered me to send you this gift. He hopes it will lessen the chance of you being killed. May he be as wrong in that as he is in everything else.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="349" id2="575055" version="1065353216">Apprentice Malora</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="350" id2="575055" version="1065353216">In Thanks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="351" id2="575055" version="1065353216">What you did for me, moving against Lord Renning, was risky and took vision. The overseers are beginning to talk. Soon the Dark Council will see my master for the lunatic that he is.

Now I hear you're close to completing your trials. I've sent a small gift. A sign of respect and thanks. Never let it be said I was slow to see the next Sith Lord in the making.

Be well, Sith, and remember me later.
Malora</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
