<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>6</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/chapter_5_shared.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="804759" version="1065353216">Elloise Moru</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="804759" version="1065353216">Thank you!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="804759" version="1065353216">You don't know what a relief this is, you breaking my man out of that slave prison. I been trying to save enough to pay the Blades' back taxes and get Ren out, but the interest is so high! Pretty much a way to keep him working for free for the rest of his life. Not no more, though.

We're packing up before the Blades get wise and come looking. You're a way bigger priority for them, I'm sure, but we're not taking chances. Ren says he promised to go back to Harlow Ricks and his old pirate life for you anyway. Wasn't a fan the first time he was into all that, but at least this time around I'll be there to keep him out of serious trouble.

Thanks again. My Ren thanks you too.

-Elloise</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="804759" version="1065353216">Qaraah</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="804759" version="1065353216">WOW.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="804759" version="1065353216">Hey, remember me? We chatted on the docks of Raider's Cove and I lived to tell the tale!

Well, okay, now it turns out you weren't a pirate after all, so maybe I wasn't in (as much?) danger from you, but still! The relief I felt after you walked away and I was still breathing? That was intense!

Everyone's still talking about the whirlwind you caused. Not just the stuff with Gorro and Grumm here in the Cove but shaking up the Nova Blades and those folks across the way with the camps and all the ships! We get a lot of excitement around here, but I think we'll all be anxious for a bigger batch of crazy for a long time to come, thanks to you.

Wherever you are and whatever you're up to now, I hope you're rocking someone else's world the way you did with us!

QARAAH</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
