<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>48</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/chapter_2_imp.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Darth Gravus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Thorough Work</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Our soldiers just discovered a few burnt-out transports full of civilian corpses.

It is a rare pleasure to work with someone who is so thorough in doing the Empire's work.

Accept this as a token of appreciation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Darth Gravus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Word has Spread</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="575662" version="1065353216">I've just received word--the civilians who managed to escape your mission of destruction have spread the terrors of our victory to other systems, just as we expected.

You have proven yourself a shrewd and valuable servant of the Empire--one deserving of further reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Thana Vesh</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Scraps</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Once again, I find myself overloaded with the spoils and rewards due a Sith of my power.

Naturally, I have no use for all of these prizes. But rather than discard them, I thought it best to give you the barest glimpse of how the galaxy's true elite are rewarded.

Perhaps you'll be inspired to raise yourself up from such utter mediocrity.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Darth Gravus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Thana Vesh</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="575662" version="1065353216">I've found some of my apprentice's effects. I have no need of them, and as the one who bested her, they are yours by rights.

Use them in good service to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Melkor Dinn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Delightful collateral damage</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="575662" version="1065353216">A trio of captured Republic scouts was brought to me for questioning, but all had suffered severe radiation poisoning. Apparently, at least one nekghoul escaped the reactor you destroyed--albeit temporarily.

The prisoners were attacked by what they described as a &quot;glowing, flaming rakghoul,&quot; which I confess forced me to leave the room for several minutes. By the time I stopped laughing, two prisoners had succumbed to poisoning from their contact with the creature. 

Regardless, the thought of an irradiated nekghoul tearing through Republic forces in its final moments filled me with unexpected glee. I simply had to share.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Melkor Dinn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="575662" version="1065353216">The Nekghouls</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="575662" version="1065353216">I thought you'd be interested to know we just captured a Republic scout investigating the nekghouls. Naturally, the scout was brought to me for questioning--and her interrogation was most illuminating.

Apparently, the Republic was counting on the nekghouls' assistance in attacking us, but the creatures have no intention of fighting someone else's war. The nekghouls have moved into the wilderness beyond the city ruins.

While I would have preferred having the nekghouls as immediate allies, I can't help but admire their independence--and at least we no longer need worry about them interfering with our efforts on Taris.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Moff Dracen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Regarding Broga the Hutt</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Broga is honoring the deal you made with him on Quesh. Hard to say if he really disliked the Republic all along, or if he was just desperate to save his slimy hide after you killed his Jedi guardian. Not that it really matters; Broga is with us now and the Republic is livid. 

With Broga's help, Imperial adrenal production is ramping up quickly. It's only a matter of time until Quesh is ours.

Moff Dracen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Moff Dracen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Quesh status update</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Imperial adrenal production on Quesh is ramping up. Since the defeat of Jedi Master Fraal at your hand, our forces have encountered only token resistance as we continue our conquest of the planet. Quesh will soon fall, and the Republic will have no choice but to engage us in full-scale war... a war they cannot possibly win.

We have started down the path of victory; now we must only hold fast to our course.

Moff Dracen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Colonel Tritan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="575662" version="1065353216">The Republic won't catch us napping again</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Thank you for supporting my promotion to leader of Dorn Base. Moff Braynor made the correct call thanks to your advice. Captain Yudrass is a competent subordinate, but he is far too cautious to be effective against the enemy.

My men also appear relieved they will not have to take orders from an outsider. It's hard enough keeping morale high on this frozen wasteland without asking soldiers to accept commands from someone like Yudrass.

Rest assured, Dorn Base will remain secure. I have tripled patrols and initiated a &quot;fire first&quot; policy against anyone who does not display proper Imperial identification.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Colonel Yudrass</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Dorn Base secured</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="575662" version="1065353216">I must thank you again for the honor you bestowed on me at Dorn Base. My promotion to colonel came as a surprise, but I have put emotion behind me to focus on bolstering our defenses.

The Republic made a bold strike against us, but you clearly demonstrated that their success was more a matter of our own overconfidence than their competency as warriors. &quot;Vigilance&quot; and &quot;preparation&quot; are the new watchwords under my command.

Although Commander Tritan was clearly disappointed to be passed over for promotion, he has been unswervingly loyal during this transition. I will see he is appropriately rewarded.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Admiral Holtz</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="575662" version="1065353216">The White Maw</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="575662" version="1065353216">We've already begun field tests with the Loramarr chipset you recovered from the White Maw's cache. The results have been astonishing--so much so that I felt compelled to thank you again for recovering such valuable technology.

The Fixer's report also said that all of the White Maw leaders have been neutralized. I commend you for taking a strong stance. Intelligence often recommends making deals with these pirates, a practice I find both pointless and distasteful.

On behalf of the Imperial war effort, please accept my gratitude and additional compensation for your efforts.

Admiral Holtz</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Ellis Tarn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Nice Save</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="575662" version="1065353216">I said things with Undro wouldn't end well, didn't I? Your Imperial Intelligence is keeping me safe from what's left of the White Maw. All they want in exchange is information. I'm happy to oblige, as long as they keep the heaters turned on high.

It seems taking your offer was the best decision I ever made in my life, and I know full well you didn't have to make it. The military is busy confiscating most of the White Maw's haul, but here's a little something from my private stash.

Ellis</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Chief Engineer Arim</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Hard at work</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="575662" version="1065353216">I'm finally away from Hoth, and I've got a whole team helping with the repairs to the Null Cannon.

Fixing this thing won't be easy, of course, but we're not about to give up--living through that icy nightmare kind of puts things in perspective, you know?

Thanks for all your help!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Admiral Revald</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Test Firing Successful!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="575662" version="1065353216">The Null Cannon passed her first firing trials like a champ! The Sith aren't even going to know what hit them!

There's no telling how many battles you've won us just bringing this prototype in. You're a blasted hero!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Captain Revar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Status Update</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="575662" version="1065353216">The generators you helped us secure remain an invaluable resource.

Technicians are deciphering the Ortolans' mechanical manuals. Progress is steady.

Your success stands as proof of the Empire's inevitable victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Ooren Tai</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="575662" version="1065353216">Hard at work!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="575662" version="1065353216">My friends and I are working hard to expand our generators' capacity for the Empire's needs!

Your associates will be very impressed with what we can do, I assure you. And so far, they've shown a lot more gratitude than those Republic cheapskates.

Thanks for giving us a chance!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
