<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>27</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/chapter_4_imp.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Katha Niar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Solida Hesk fallout</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="732433" version="1065353216">We observed a Regulator squad arriving at Solida Hesk's resort shortly after your termination sweep. Communications transcript enclosed along with upgraded supply drop.

PARTIAL TRANSCRIPT FOLLOWS

REGULATOR 1: Victims confirmed. Khobisho, Prodoranya and Manju are all dead. 

REGULATOR 2: So's Solida Hesk. Looks brutal.

REGULATOR 1: No security footage. Someone planned this sick massacre.

REGULATOR 2: Don't get squeamish--call it in to Vice Commandant Grevin. We'll let him be the one to tell the Archon.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Solida Hesk</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Great beginnings</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="732433" version="1065353216">To my newest business partner:

The Hutts' people were crawling all over the resort within minutes of your departure. I spent almost an hour with the Regulator Vice Commandant, trying to convince him that the Empire is attempting to prevent the Republic from seizing Makeb's financial resources.

I expect he believed me. I was appropriately weepy and bruised, and he's confident that no one would dare deceive him. Why the Makeb business council hired traitorous idiots to protect the planet, I'll never know.

Still, we'll want to be careful. I can only skim our accounts or else the Hutt auditors will get suspicious. Once this is all over and my company is restored, I'm sure we can do more together. Mineral and spice mining, metallurgical recombination... these are the building blocks of a kingdom. Your kingdom.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Major Raveen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Lurker Status</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="732433" version="1065353216">To whosoever serves as operational commander on planet Makeb:

I don't claim to know what's going on down there. Darth Marr has instituted a need-to-know policy regarding your mission, and despite the fact that I'm military intelligence coordinator for the sector, I apparently don't &quot;need to know.&quot;

Nonetheless, I am told that our agent code-named Lurker was eliminated by your forces. We're having enough trouble staying apprised with Imperial Intelligence gone; must you remove the few sources we have left?

You have our full support, of course. And I realize your mission is vital to the continuation of the Empire. But be aware of how hard things are out here.

Warm regards and best wishes, etc.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Katha Niar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Lurker Status</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Captain Hanthor briefed me on your extraction of the Lurker and his family. The Lurker is serving adequately with the scout teams, but you should also know this:

One of the Lurker's family members had, apparently, been romantically involved with a member of the InterStellar Regulators. We learned this during the family's transfer to Dromund Kaas; the Lurker's cousin freely offered his cooperation.

We're still going through the new data, but there's enough insider information here to make our jobs a bit easier.

I've signed off on offering the family full Imperial citizenship (so long as there's an Empire to house them). Barring your veto, I figure they've earned it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Darth Ravage</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Lord Cytharat</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Lord Cytharat was stained by the blood of a traitor. It was Darth Malgus who brought him out of the academy on Korriban. It was Darth Malgus who Cytharat followed at the Battle of Ilum.

I argued for Cytharat's execution, but for practical reasons, I permitted him to join the mission to Makeb.

He did not deserve that chance, but I understand he died well.

His shame will be purged from the records.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Katha Niar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="732433" version="1065353216">FW: Medical Brief on Lord Cytharat</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="732433" version="1065353216">See below. 

To: Katha Niar
From: Doctor Evresh Mandritis
Subject: Medical Brief on Lord Cytharat

Patient suffered from multiple blaster burns resulting in severe tissue damage and blood loss. Emergency surgery and life support equipment stabilized patient during transport; upon patient's arrival at Vaiken Spacedock, medical staff proceeded with kolto tank immersion.

Prognosis is generally positive. Patient's rehabilitation includes several hours spent outside the kolto tank each day, and he has expressed a desire to return to active status on Makeb.

Patient has requested the following message be sent to Makeb operational control:

&quot;It was necessary, and it was good. I thank you for my redemption. May we fight as one again.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Katha Niar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="732433" version="1065353216">FW: Intercepted Communications</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="732433" version="1065353216">We intercepted a communications fragment from Republic forces on Makeb.

To: Supreme Commander Jace Malcom
From: Captain Muntanye
Subject: Imperial Activity

Following the Pollus Avesta incident, we have an additional Imperial sighting on Makeb. Enemy forces intercepted caravan 47-B (&quot;Whiteraft&quot;) and kidnapped several civilian engineers with government ties. SIS is attempting to analyze why; working theory is that the resource-deficient Empire may want to begin deep core mining on its own homeworlds.
	
I'm not convinced, but we don't have anything better. On the bright side, there were no casualties. To be honest, that caravan probably would have gone down with all hands if the Imperials hadn't swept through an attacking Regulator force.

We owe them a few dozen lives. I won't be spreading the word about that.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Katha Niar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="732433" version="1065353216">FW: Intercepted Communications</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="732433" version="1065353216">We intercepted a communications fragment from Republic forces on Makeb.

To: Supreme Commander Jace Malcom
From: Captain Muntanye
Subject: Destroyed Caravan

We have confirmed the destruction of refugee caravan 47-B (&quot;Whiteraft&quot;). Scouts found the wreckage and identified the bodies. Our people and the Makeb refugees were there alongside a group of dead Regulator mercenaries. No survivors.

We're not entirely sure what happened; we're guessing a second squad of Regulators finished the job when the first squad was defeated. Following their victory, the second squad withdrew to safety.

It's bloody, though, even for them. Dozens of people murdered, and even the Regulators have been reluctant to engage in the mass slaughter of unarmed civilians. Maybe it was a Hutt kill squad?

No time to investigate, or even catalogue the dead. Maybe tomorrow. Or next year.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="732433" version="1065353216">Katha Niar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="732433" version="1065353216">FW: Intercepted Communications</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="732433" version="1065353216">We intercepted a communications fragment from Republic forces on Makeb.

To: Supreme Commander Jace Malcom
From: Captain Muntanye
Subject: Caravan 47-B

Following the Pollus Avesta incident, we have an additional Imperial sighting on Makeb. Enemy forces intercepted caravan 47-B (&quot;Whiteraft&quot;), eliminated all Republic personnel and kidnapped several civilian engineers with government ties. Other civilian refugees were permitted to escape; the caravan survivors arrived at the rendezvous point and reported in a short while ago.

SIS is attempting to analyze the Empire's motives here, but we don't have much to work with. We're also dealing with some significant unrest among the people of Makeb--the Empire was careful to spare them, and some of the refugees are starting to feel they're safer on their own.

Honestly, they may be right--if the Empire keeps this up, giving the civilians military escorts may just turn them into targets. But I don't have a better answer.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
