<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>60</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/chapter_3_rep.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Senator Tudos</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Project Noble Focus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="575667" version="1065353216">It seems Deputy Warden Graal has decided to remain silent about my little project pitting the prisoners against each other on Belsavis. I couldn't have convinced him to keep quiet without your help.

I have made some discreet inquiries and have found several weapon manufacturers eager to purchase the data compiled from the experiment. I feel it's only fair to offer you a portion of the profits, as you were instrumental in persuading Graal not to file an official report.

Obviously, a Senate investigation is the last thing either of us needs. 

Sincerely,
Senator Tudos</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Deputy Warden Graal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Project Noble Focus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="575667" version="1065353216">A special investigation committee officially condemned Senator Tudos for pitting the prisoners on Belsavis against each other in his grim experiments. He's been stripped of his position and publicly disgraced, though he won't serve any hard jail time.

I don't think I would have reported him if you hadn't backed me--the last thing I need is a politically powerful enemy. Thanks for helping me do the right thing.

We found some useful items in the personal effects of the prisoners slaughtered during Project Noble Focus. Figured you might be able to make the best use of them.

Graal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Nyranos</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Freedom</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Deputy Warden Graal is as good as his word. As promised, he has given me and the other Condemned a small plot of land on Belsavis, far from the prison. Here we live a simple but honest life, no longer punished for the crimes of our ancestors.

You saw the justice in our cause and supported our emancipation. We can never truly repay you for that, but we would be honored if you would accept some small token of our gratitude.

Nyranos</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Deputy Warden Graal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Nyranos and the Condemned</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="575667" version="1065353216">The threat of the Condemned on Belsavis has been contained. When you executed Nyranos, you left them without a true leader, and they offered little resistance to the guards. Now Warden Playt and Officer Kelsa Gerro can rest easy knowing their killers have been brought to justice.

The guards found a store of supplies Nyranos had collected. I think they should go to you. Consider it a reward for taking that filth out.

Graal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Lurking Doom</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="575667" version="1065353216">The Master Lives</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Beneath Belsavis dwells the Great Master of the Esh-kha. The World Razer gathers strength while we--the faithful--prepare for the glorious return. Generations will pass, but the way is open. You were the guide, the catalyst. The servants of the Master honor you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="575667" version="1065353216">General Skylast</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="575667" version="1065353216">The World Razer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Now that things on Belsavis are more under control, I sent a team to take some readings down in the vaults. Happy to say they didn't find anything out of the ordinary. No sign of that &quot;World Razer&quot; the Esh-kha were looking for. 

Whatever crazy plan they had in mind, looks like you put a stop to it. For good.

My team did find a small storage vault hidden out of the way. Happy to let you have what was inside after all you did for us. Enjoy.

General Skylast</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Ambassador Jannik</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="575667" version="1065353216">The Lost Potentials</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="575667" version="1065353216">There's been more rumbling about those young Mystics, the lost potentials who fell alongside Lord Beldiss. Laryn-Ki averted a military response, but protecting the Mystics is deeply ingrained into the Voss psyche, I'm afraid. I've done my best to mitigate the damage.

On the other hand, a Voss woman in Voss-Ka gave me this. She said it was for &quot;the one who saved the lost, whose place was not as slaves.&quot; I think she might actually have been the mother of one of the potentials. I suppose that means this is for you?

Sometimes I wonder if I'll ever understand these people.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Yashu-Vo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Beginning</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="575667" version="1065353216">We came to Tython. Master Delsa's lessons are harsh, but fair. His words spur us on.

Lord Beldiss taught much that was wrong. We are slow to unlearn. 

But here, we are not lost. We begin.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Ambassador Jannik</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Stirred up</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Careful. The political situation in Voss-Ka is like a red-hot sandwasp hollow. Senior Voss commandos are being called back for consultations about the Gormak; every Mystic not in seclusion is being asked for advice. You took thousands of years of Voss culture and gave it a good shake. I can't imagine what it's going to look like once things settle down, but I want to be here to see. 

I still can't believe the Voss and the Gormak share a common origin. Neither can they, I imagine. One thing's certain: We're not getting any Voss allies any time soon. For what it's worth, I think you did the right thing by telling them. My superiors might not agree, but they don't know the Voss like I do. We're going to help them work this out, and someday, there'll be a place for them in the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Laryn-Ki</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Honor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="575667" version="1065353216">You entered the Nightmare Lands. You brought the secret of Jokull's corruption.

The endless war must end. The last Gormak must not die, but there must be a closing.

We see clearly. The Republic is a friend to Voss. As are you. You risked chaos to find truth for us. We honor you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Sallius Wen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Regarding the Mirr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="575667" version="1065353216">You did well to destroy the Mirr. There are dark things enough on Voss without risking the corruption of the Mystics. Unfortunately, they do not agree. The Voss attitude to &quot;outsider meddling&quot; is a difficult one to manage, but I hope in time they will understand.

There are some in the order who would prefer to study the artifacts of the Sith, or say we should leave the Voss to their own devices. But I have heard such arguments before and seen them lead to ruin. I offer this in thanks, for the danger you have averted.

--Wen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Tolec-Da</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="575667" version="1065353216">The Mirr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="575667" version="1065353216">The Mirr was brought to the Mystics. They study in silence. They see.

The Jedi Wen offers more warnings. He speaks of darkness and the philosophy of evil. He speaks of things not Voss. We see no corruption.

The Mystics thank you for the Mirr. They say this is yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Cole Cantarus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Good Work</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Thought I'd thank you again for destroying those neutron emitters. A lot of the refugees hiding on that tram came through the Red Light Sector before going offworld. They were shaken, but alive--and damn grateful for it.

I don't believe in handing out medals every time someone does the right thing, but there's a lot of Corellia left to win. Here's a little something to remind you what we're fighting for.

Cole</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Corporal Hartke</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Whoo-ee!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="575667" version="1065353216">So me and my squad get temporarily reassigned from spaceport patrol to rocket tram defense. I figure my number's up, right? The Imps have control of the trams, and they're sending more troops through every day. 

Imagine our surprise when the tram rolls up and dead Imps start falling out! It was prettier than an Alderaanian sunrise, and the general says we have you to thank. Sure glad I stopped you in the spaceport when I did!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Danison Varik</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Thanks for Nothing</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="575667" version="1065353216">I've been ordered by the Republic to send you this message. As if being branded a traitor and thrown in jail weren't bad enough, now they have me in some sort of reform program. I'm supposed to thank you for allowing me to get help.

So, thank you. Thank you for destroying my life's work and ruining my career. Here's one of my creations, confiscated from the ruins of my lab and redistributed to the front lines by court order. I hope it blows up in your face!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Deena Behar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Thanks and Appreciation</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Our mutual friend hopes this message finds you well. He was pleased to hear that the Empire's droids will no longer be a problem for you, and hopes this will serve as proof of his genuine desire for a Republic victory on Corellia.

Our mutual friend also approves of your decision to allow Danison Varik to continue his work. Although he may have started this war on the wrong side, Varik deserves a second chance. Our friend hopes you will remember this later.

Deena</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Senator Arnus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="575667" version="1065353216">A Historic Day</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="575667" version="1065353216">General Aves has informed me that you were the one who reclaimed the Museum Republica. First, let me congratulate you on your victory. The museum holds so much of our treasured history. Now, it can document another historic moment: the capture of Commander Tainor, leader of the Emperor's own Imperial Guard.

The commander clearly did not expect to survive the battle, and Republic officials tell me he must be kept under constant supervision. I have given them the power and resources to do so--he is too valuable a prisoner to be allowed to die in his cell.

On behalf of the entire Senate, I would like to thank you for your heroic actions. We look forward to seeing what you'll accomplish in the future</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Corporal Hartke</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Good Going!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Just like every other grunt on Corellia, me and my squad had been fighting across Axial Park for days. We lost a lot of good men out there. Had me wishing I was back in the spaceport, watching the paint dry.

Then we got word that the leader of the Imperial Guard--the Emperor's men!--had been killed. We pulled what we had left together and sent those blasted Imps running for Capitol Square. Thanks for the shot in the arm!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Master Boudyn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="575667" version="1065353216">A Last Word</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="575667" version="1065353216">I know I already thanked you for protecting the Jedi Temple during our assault, but I am ashamed of my reasons for asking you to do so. Our artifacts and relics are priceless, to be sure, but it is not the way of the Jedi to value material objects.

The Sullustan pilots wanted to avenge their fallen commander. You chose not to indulge them. In doing so, you may have saved much more than artifacts and relics--and reminded me of what we fight for. Please accept my thanks again.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Ensign Din Suub</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Ilum Temple Run</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="575667" version="1065353216">Me and the boys just wanted to drop you a line and thank you for letting us get back at those Imperial scum for what they did to Commander Yet Jub. A lot of people sell us Sullustans short, but we can do some serious damage when we want to. The Imperial casualty reports made us smile.

We don't have much to repay you, but we found this in the commander's footlocker. We think he'd want you to have it.

Ensign Din Suub and the rest of V'buk Squadron</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
