<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>169</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/daily_area.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Sgt. Darren Rakal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Hope this reaches you....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="763171" version="1065353216">On Oricon, I was forced to live a nightmare. Had to fight for my life while unspeakable horrors were constantly whispered to me.

Now I'm living a different nightmare: one where I can't see my own reflection without being disgusted. Where I can't forget that I fought for the Empire.

I've tried to rationalize it. Tried to bottle it up. But it's no use. I helped the Sith Empire, and I never once tried to sabotage or abandon them because I was too scared. I wanted to live.

I'm off that rock now. Alive. Thought about leaving the military, abandoning this war. I can't. I have to make up for my wrongs.

Here's hoping I see you again on the front lines sometime so there can be one less Imperial stooge in the galaxy, and so I can be one step closer to redeeming myself.

Darren Rakal, Sergeant
Republic Army</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Pvt. Darren Rakal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="763171" version="1065353216">For the Empire</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="763171" version="1065353216">I used to think nothing in reality could be as terrifying as the stuff you make up in your own mind. Oricon proved me wrong. The things those Dread Masters whispered to me, what they made me see--I know I'll never be able to erase that.

I also won't forget how I was treated by my rescuers. How I was reasoned with, told I wouldn't be placed into slavery. And then, finally, after surviving the nightmare that was Oricon, how the Empire's operatives kept their word and set me free.

But I couldn't leave. That whole time I was fighting for my sanity and my life, I felt something I'd never felt in the Republic Army. I felt safe, in control of my destiny. So I've abandoned the Republic and joined the Empire. Lost my rank because I have to start at the bottom, but I'll work my way up the ranks soon enough.

Here's hoping I see you again on the front lines sometime so I can have your back. It would be my honor.

Darren Rakal, Private
Imperial Army</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Alli Krieger</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="763171" version="1065353216">My brother the private.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Hello,

You don't know me and we've never met. I'm a small business owner in Galactic City with a little brother who wanted to protect his family by joining the military in its fight against the Empire. We (me, my parents, my sister) were all proud of him, but also afraid for his life, as you might imagine.

Well, my brother--Private Erek Krieger--is home once again. We've been told that he was on a very important mission, and that he suffered unavoidable mental anguish from it, but they won't say anything more than that. (And that's fine. We don't need to know.)

Things were a bit shaky at first, and we had to take turns watching over him and keeping him rooted in reality, but now Erek's recovering nicely. He told us how you rescued a lot of soldiers and that, because of you, he and others were evacuated before their conditions worsened.

So, on behalf of Erek and my family, thank you so much. Good luck and stay safe.

--Alli Krieger</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Doctor B'arud, MMS</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Oricon's Lingering Effects</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="763171" version="1065353216">FROM: Military Medical Services (MMS)
TO: Participants in Republic Activities on Oricon
REPORT BRIEF: Effects of Prolonged Exposure to Oricon &quot;Madness Waves&quot;

Scenario: Soldiers under distress from crash landing on Oricon further traumatized by arcane, madness-inducing phenomenon; placed back into service rather than being evacuated for treatment.

Symptoms: Continued exposure to uniquely hostile atmosphere of Oricon resulted in drastic, unpredictable shifts in disposition. Subjects reported to alter from blind rage to immobilizing terror then back to rage again within moments. Paranoia and hallucinations consistent with acute dementia persist beyond exposure to Oricon.

Prognosis: Soldiers unable to function in military and/or social capacities. Life expectancy maximum of five years. Assisted care required to term.

Doctor B'arud
Applied Medical Sciences Division, MMS</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Darth Marr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Ziost</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Early reports from Ziost had been rushed and nonsensical, but Minister Beniko has set everything straight. She has told me of Vitiate's return and your involvement, and now of this ill-timed offensive strike from the Republic.

As matters stand, I will not be sending any further resources as they would ultimately assist Vitiate in his mad goal. I have full confidence in your ability to work with Beniko and her people toward a solution.

I will monitor the situation, and will contact you directly should the need for drastic measures become absolute.

Darth Marr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Supreme Chancellor's Office</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="763171" version="1065353216">The Ziost Offensive</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="763171" version="1065353216">The Chancellor would like to convey her deepest regret that she cannot reach out to you personally at this time; she has asked me to contact you in her stead. 

We understand that you are currently working with Theron Shan on Ziost and are aware of our military offensive in the broadest sense. We also understand that your activities involve a group of Jedi that the Chancellor has a great deal of interest in. As such, your direct involvement with the offensive will not be required; rather we ask that you continue to work with Agent Shan in limiting the exposure of this &quot;Sixth Line&quot; group on Ziost.

As the offensive requires the Chancellor's full attention, you should expect to hear from me if and when priorities shift in any way. Thank you.

Hance Rugel
Special Aide to the Supreme Chancellor of the Galactic Republic</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Agt. Rane Kovach</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Status Update</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="763171" version="1065353216">[ENCRYPTION] I won't pretend to know why you kept quiet about me or how difficult that may have been for you, but rest assured that [/ENCRYPTION] I continue to play my part in stopping Vitiate. He's not yet shown that he can take control of a droid, so that is the area of interest where Minister Beniko has allowed me to place my focus.

[ENCRYPTION] I suppose if we get through this, you probably won't much care for keeping quiet anymore. All the same, [/ENCRYPTION] I'd like to thank you for the opportunity to assist you in ending all the madness.

--Kovach</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Agt. Rane Kovach</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Thanks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="763171" version="1065353216">My credentials have yet to be revoked amidst all the madness, so I'm using the opportunity to free a large slave camp and get them offworld. If I can find a droid to pilot a ship, I'm going to stay here and repeat.

I'm not telling you this to flaunt my freedom, but rather to illustrate that your decision was not in vain. I am still dedicated to the end of Vitiate's insane grasp for power. Whatever compelled you to see me spared of Minister Beniko's punishment, I truly appreciate it.

--Kovach</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Agt. Rane Kovach</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="763171" version="1065353216">My Role</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="763171" version="1065353216">As you might have suspected, I have not returned to the Chancellor with my tail between my legs. That would have accomplished nothing in this time of crisis. Instead, I have resumed duties with Minister Beniko. If we survive Vitiate's surge I will continue in my position, which will no doubt prove invaluable to our overall efforts.

Maybe you and Agent Shan can't trust me--and I understand that--but the Republic still can.

--Kovach</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Agt. Rane Kovach</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="763171" version="1065353216">[AUTO-SEND-PROTOCOL]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Mentally composing this message in case I meet an untimely end on Ziost, which I now see is even more of a distinct possibility than when Vitiate first surfaced. The Republic has gone to war, possessed combatants line the streets of New Adasta, and you may very well like to kill me yourself.

If my service here is cut short, know that it was ultimately life that I served. My own life, yes, but also Agent Shan's, Minister Beniko's, the Supreme Chancellor's, those of the millions in New Adasta and the countless masses across the entire galaxy--even yours. If Vitiate wins, no one wins.

Farewell.

--Kovach</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Darth Marr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Vitiate's Power</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Something went awry with the communications platform. I had intended to commend you for your work thus far, but I have just received word that your breakthrough against Vitiate was only temporary.

This is most distressing. Vitiate may be more powerful than any of us assumed. And as he does not appear to have any manner of physical form, he cannot be restrained or destroyed by conventional means.

The order to evacuate Ziost in priority sequence has been approved. I will attempt to contact you again if anything changes.

Darth Marr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Supreme Chancellor's Office</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Interruption</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Greetings again. 

It appears a glitch on your end cut short your communication with the Chancellor. She wants you to know that she is aware of your deeds and is monitoring the severity of these &quot;possessions&quot;--which, we are pleased to report, have yet to surface on any fronts outside of New Adasta.

We have come to understand that the Sith Emperor is behind this madness, so we do not take the threat lightly; however, it appears from our vantage point that he may not be as powerful as once assumed.

We will endeavor to reach you should the need arise.

Hance Rugel
Special Aide to the Supreme Chancellor of the Galactic Republic</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Darth Marr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="763171" version="1065353216">[NO SUBJECT]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="763171" version="1065353216">We have lost much this day.

Think on what has happened to Ziost, and what it means for our future.

Then prepare.

Darth Marr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Supreme Chancellor Saresh</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Strategic Withdrawal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="763171" version="1065353216">It was not an easy decision to retreat from Ziost. I firmly believe we had strong forward momentum in our favor, but it was also apparent that something far beyond our ability to control was growing in power and intensity.

Now the Sith Emperor has struck, devouring the populace of an entire world. An Imperial world, no less.

I never took his threat lightly, but that didn't mean the Republic was going to cower in fear. Even in the wake of his monstrous victory on Ziost, we cannot tremble. But we must reevaluate our plans as we redouble our efforts under the Joint Task Force to end the Emperor's threat.

We have lost many to the Emperor's madness. We will lose more. But we cannot give up. Not for a moment, not ever.

Stay vigilant,
Supreme Chancellor Leontyne Saresh of the Galactic Republic</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Republic Fleet Access</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="763171" version="1065353216">I know you sided with the Empire, but I wouldn't dock your ship with the Imperial Fleet just yet. Vaiken Spacedock's not safe. I ran a full security assessment, and Lana reached out to some old contacts to see if we could work out an arrangement. No matter how you slice it, we can't guarantee that you--a decorated Republic hero--could walk through the Imperial station without getting ambushed. Then there's the risk of your ship being stolen or sabotaged. I guess some Imps aren't as accepting as Empress Acina.

Luckily, yours truly worked out a fix.

Thanks to my handiwork, your ship's updated with new-and-improved landing credentials. They'll let you dock with the Republic Fleet at Carrick Station without raising any alarms. As long as you don't whip out any Imperial banners, you should be fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Imperial Fleet Access</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="763171" version="1065353216">I know you sided with the Republic, but you should think twice before docking with their fleet at Carrick Station. I ran a full security assessment, and there are too many variables--from the risk of an ambush to ship security. No matter how you slice it, we can't guarantee that you--a former champion of the Empire--could walk through the Republic station without a hundred people taking a shot at you. Not even Malcom can ensure your safety.

Luckily, yours truly worked out a fix.

Thanks to my handiwork, your ship's updated with new-and-improved landing credentials. They'll let you dock with the Imperial Fleet at Vaiken Spacedock without raising any alarms. Just try not to redecorate the place with Republic insignias.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Surveillance Initialized</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="763171" version="1065353216">As you requested, we've begun surveilling the Eternal Alliance and its many partners in an attempt to root out the traitor on Iokath. Impartial third-party agents are conducting the investigation. They've compiled the following encrypted report for your eyes only. Not even Theron or I can see its contents.

SURVEILLANCE REPORT

Scans are complete for all Alliance communications sent in the past 24 hours. Of these messages, 11% contained language that implicitly or explicitly criticized the Commander and/or the Eternal Alliance. Flagging these 1,681 Alliance personnel for Stage 2 Monitoring.

The remaining messages broke down as follows: 

- 67% official Alliance reports (Iokath surveys, battle updates, etc.)
- 18% employee complaints (food, living conditions, etc.)
- 6% family missives (birth announcements, recipes, funerals, etc.)
- 4% letters expressing love/affection between Alliance personnel
- 3% encoded transmissions (contained financial data, nothing suspicious)
- 2% unsent drafts

Next Steps: Prioritize suspects and begin targeted investigations. Mass-scale monitoring will continue. More reports to follow.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Breach of Trust</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="763171" version="1065353216">I'm sickened, Commander. I was just informed that you approved a plan to spy on every member of the Eternal Alliance. I called them lies, but then I confronted Lana--and I learned that it's all true. 

Our people sacrificed everything to follow your cause. This is how you repay them? By betraying their trust, invading their privacy, and digging through their personal lives? I know you've been stung by a traitor's actions, but this isn't the answer. While you wage a war to root out one corrupting agent, you risk laying waste to everything else you've built, and betraying everything the Alliance stands for.

I considered sending you my resignation, but I won't abandon the people who look to me for guidance. I've surrendered my files to your spies. I will continue to fight for the Eternal Alliance.

I sincerely hope you find this traitor before more damage is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="763171" version="1065353216">The Monitors</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Surveillance Report: Lana Beniko</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="763171" version="1065353216">[Note: The following surveillance report was compiled for the Alliance Commander only.]

Subject: Lana Beniko, former Minister of Sith Intelligence. 

Family: Parents Jaren and Kelsa (deceased). No siblings. 

Beniko follows a regimented daily schedule of meditation, sparring practice, coordination of Eternal Alliance spy networks, a strict diet, and a mixture of tea and bourbon before bed. Writes poetry on (poorly) encrypted datapad. Judging by email scans, adherence to routine, and professional pride, Beniko has a low likelihood of sedition. However, Intelligence training gives her the necessary tools to mask true motives.

Threat Degree: Inconclusive.

Next Steps: Elevate Beniko to Stage 3 Monitoring. Focus on her communications with spy network contacts. Send poetry to cryptographers to search for hidden messages.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="763171" version="1065353216">The Traitor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Whoever betrayed you on Iokath is smarter than we thought. Lana and I are running down leads, but they've covered their tracks well. The best we can do is investigate top suspects and rule out others.

Captain Elara Dorne and Major Malavai Quinn are both innocent. Multiple sources confirmed they were nowhere near you when the throne was sabotaged. I scanned their personal files, and their stories check out.

All your advisors have agreed to be questioned. Hylo nearly gave me a black eye when I asked, but Lana calmed her down. Oggurobb, Aygo, and Sana-Rae were all cooperative. Lana and I are first up for interrogation.

As for Malcom, we're just not sure. Most of his communications are shielded by the SIS. He was on the battlefield when the superweapon overloaded, but there was so much chaos I can't find anyone who can confirm his location. We'll keep digging. I know it doesn't count for much, but as his son, I don't believe he's the conspiracy type.

We will to find this traitor. It's just going to take some time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Whoever betrayed you on Iokath is smarter than we thought. Lana and I are running down leads, but they've covered their tracks well. The best we can do is investigate top suspects and rule out others.

Captain Elara Dorne and Major Malavai Quinn are both innocent. Multiple sources confirmed they were nowhere near you when the throne was sabotaged. I scanned their personal files, and their stories check out.

All your advisors have agreed to be questioned. Hylo nearly gave me a black eye when I asked, but Lana calmed her down. Oggurobb, Aygo, and Sana-Rae were all cooperative. Lana and I are first up for interrogation.

Acina's a tougher nut to crack. Most of her intel's guarded by Sith Intelligence. Luckily, I planted some tracers on Dromund Kaas during our last visit, and they just happened to grab a classified message sent to the Empress within a few minutes of the throne's sabotage. I'll decrypt it and alert you if we find something.

We will find this traitor. It's just going to take some time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Surveillance Report: Theron Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="763171" version="1065353216">[Note: The following surveillance report was compiled for the Alliance Commander only.]

Subject: Theron Shan. Former Republic SIS agent. Alias: Technoplague. 

Family: Parents Jace Malcom (Alliance ally) and Satele Shan (status unknown). No siblings.

Shan's routine is unpredictable, but marked by daily calibration of his cybernetic implants, managing Alliance crisis reports, and reading aid requests. Drinks caf (to wake up) and whisky (before bed). Shan is constantly hyper-alert and routinely scans his surroundings, a possible sign of guilt or residual SIS training. He detected one of our slicers as they monitored his files, but made no attempt to block their investigation. He either has nothing to hide, or he's hiding something elsewhere.

Threat Degree: Inconclusive.

Next Steps: Elevate Shan to Stage 3 Monitoring. Intercept all messages to father Malcom. Watch for communications to mother Satele, whose location is unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="763171" version="1065353216">[Note: The following surveillance report was compiled for the Alliance Commander only.]

Subject: Theron Shan. Former Republic SIS agent. Alias: Technoplague. 

Family: Parents Jace Malcom (deceased) and Satele Shan (status unknown). No siblings.

Shan's routine is unpredictable, but marked by daily calibration of his cybernetic implants, managing Alliance crisis reports, and reading aid requests. Drinks caf (to wake up) and whisky (alone before bed). Shan is constantly hyper-alert and routinely scans his surroundings, a possible sign of guilt or residual SIS training. Recently made several anonymous donations to Republic charities in Jace Malcom's name. He attempts to hide his grief, but his father's death still affects him. 

Threat Degree: Inconclusive.

Next Steps: Elevate Shan to Stage 4 Monitoring. Flag any personality spikes or other abnormal behavior as he mourns his father. Watch for communications to mother Satele, whose location is unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Theron</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="763171" version="1065353216">I know it's not my business, but I'm worried about Theron. 

He's more agitated than usual and judging by the bags under his eyes, he's not getting enough sleep. I'm concerned he's still distraught over his father's death. He'd never show it, because he wants to be strong--for you, and for the Eternal Alliance.

I'll keep an eye on him, but I thought you should know.

P.S. Don't mention this to Theron. If he knew I was worried, I'd never hear the end of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Surveillance Report: Jace Malcom</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="763171" version="1065353216">[Note: The following surveillance report was compiled for the Alliance Commander only.]

Subject: Jace Malcom, Supreme Commander of the Galactic Republic.

Family: Son Theron (estranged?). Former lover Satele Shan (status unknown).

Malcom rises before dawn, runs five kilometers, meditates, runs battle simulations, and discusses strategy with his advisors. He sharpens his combat knife, an antique relic from his campaign on Alderaan. He has a refined palette, drinks brandy to take the edge off. Some of his personnel call him &quot;Malcom the Machine,&quot; which he discourages, but secretly appears to like.

His messages are locked behind SIS safeguards, but we recovered several communications and are working to decrypt them. Included in this discovery was an unsent draft addressed to his son Theron Shan. It's incomplete, but contained a heartfelt apology--for what, we don't know. If this refers to his treachery, we will find proof shortly.

Threat Degree: Moderate.

Next Steps: Elevate Malcom to Stage 3 Monitoring. Decrypt intercepted messages. Identify compromised members of his staff and probe them for more intel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Surveillance Report: Empress Acina</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="763171" version="1065353216">[Note: The following surveillance report was compiled for the Alliance Commander only.]

Subject: Acina. Empress of the Sith Empire. Former Dark Council member, Sphere of Technology.

Family: None.

Acina stays up late and rises early. Few visitors. Diligently practices saber technique. Dabbles in horticulture, which is unexpected from the former head of the Empire's Sphere of Technology. Drinks only purified water (elitist affectation or precaution against assassination attempts?) from Dromund Kaas. All messages are heavily encoded, but we intercepted one sent to Darth Vowrawn, her former colleague on the Dark Council. Could Vowrawn be the traitor or a fellow conspirator?

Threat Degree: Moderate.

Next Steps: Elevate Acina to Stage 3 Monitoring. Begin observation of Darth Vowrawn. Identify compromised members of her staff and probe them for more intel.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Settling In</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Your Eternal Alliance is most impressive, my lord. I always knew you were worthy of such a following, but I never imagined fate would bestow you with such a monumental status. Between the Eternal Fleet and your burgeoning army, I pity anyone who defies your authority. 

After my welcome tour, Admiral Aygo briefed me on the strategies we use to police the galaxy. I offered a few suggestions, but he has the situation well in hand. I plan to acquaint myself with the rest of your followers over the coming weeks.

Speaking of which, I was sorry to hear of Vette's untimely passing. The two of us rarely saw eye to eye, but I always respected her role in your rise to prominence. She will be missed.

Thank you again for welcoming me back into your fold.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Your Eternal Alliance is most impressive, my lord. I always knew you were worthy of such a following, but I never imagined fate would bestow you with such a monumental status. Between the Eternal Fleet and your burgeoning army, I pity anyone who defies your authority. 

After my welcome tour, Admiral Aygo briefed me on the strategies we use to police the galaxy. I offered a few suggestions, but he has the situation well in hand. I plan to acquaint myself with the rest of your followers over the coming weeks.

Speaking of which, I ran into Vette while making my rounds. She's her usual colorful self. As much as I love her friendly ribbing, I think I'll station myself far from her quarters.

Thank you again for welcoming me back into your fold.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Resource Crisis</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="763171" version="1065353216">I've got some bad news, Commander. While you've been butting heads with our friends on Iokath, I've been keeping an eye on the rest of the galaxy. People are talking. Sure, they're scared of the blowback from your war, but that's not what keeps them awake at night.

There's no easy way to say it. The galaxy's resources are running dry.

Things already looked dicey before the Eternal Empire rolled in and stripped the galaxy of every resource they could find. Then we had to patch things up after they wrecked entire planets. Now, raw materials are in low supply, rebuilding efforts have slowed to a crawl, and we're running out of supplies to keep the Eternal Alliance going.

I reached out to my underworld contacts, hoping they'd have an angle on more resources. But no such luck. They're more panicked than anybody. You can smell the Hutt flop sweat from the next system.

I'll keep hunting. In the meantime, you should hold onto Iokath with everything you've got. That world may be our last shot at nailing down the supplies we need to survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="763171" version="1065353216">My lord,

When we expressed our feelings to each other, I thought my embarrassing, boyish admiration of you would finally end. But seeing the empire you've built without me, I find myself awestruck once more. You are still the fierce, powerful warrior I fell in love with--and now you are an empress. I'm so proud to stand with you again.

I spent more than six years chasing the intoxicating passion I felt while serving you. Now, in your presence, I've finally tasted it again. My love for you burns as strongly now as it did all those years ago. With your permission, I will follow you to the ends of the galaxy. All I ask in return is that you allow me to remain by your side, as your faithful ally and loving partner.

I love you, my lord. I always will.

Malavai</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="763171" version="1065353216">A few sentiments</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="328" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Quick Trip</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Dearest,

I'm joining Fleet Admiral Aygo for a strategy conference with the Republic's Sixth Fleet command staff. Before I leave, I wanted you to know that my personal effects and research equipment have been delivered and installed smoothly. I must confess to some concerns regarding the safety procedures in Doctor Oggurobb's laboratory, as well as the flagrant lack of shipping documentation from Captain Visz. I'm sure I can help resolve both situations upon my return. In the meantime, I will note a few potential improvements for later discussion.

The Alliance you've built is truly exceptional. Just this morning, I found an old friend from the Imperial Academy overseeing hangar security. Needless to say, I never thought we'd see each other again, let alone sit down for a caf and catch up after so many years on opposite sides. A chance encounter, but it filled me with hope for what we can achieve.

I'll think of you every single moment we're apart.

Yours always,
Elara</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Checking In</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Commander,

I'm pleased to report that my personal research equipment has been delivered and installed successfully, though I must call attention to the abysmal safety procedures in Doctor Oggurobb's laboratory, as well as the flagrant lack of shipping documentation from Captain Visz. I've noted a few potential improvements for later discussion.

Exploring the inner workings of your Alliance has been a true pleasure. If we can bring the same spirit of cooperation and purpose I've experienced here to the rest of the galaxy, the future will be bright indeed.

Respectfully,
Elara Dorne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Raina Temple</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Discretion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="763171" version="1065353216">To All Alliance Command Staff:

Given my role as a liaison with the Chiss Ascendancy, I would prefer to have my name left out of any staffing or roster information shared with our allies in the Sith Empire.

Your discretion in this matter is much appreciated.

Respectfully,
Raina Temple</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="763171" version="1065353216">T7-O1</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="763171" version="1065353216">T7 = Conflicted</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="763171" version="1065353216">T7 = loyal to Republic
You = aligned with Sith Empire
You + T7 = good team + save galaxy
Politics = complicated
War = terrible
You + T7 = good team + save galaxy?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Aric Jorgan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Loyalty</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="763171" version="1065353216">There's nothing I respect more than loyalty. It cut me to my core when I left the Republic to help your Alliance, but I knew it was the right move - you were fighting for the greater good of everyone.

If you ever need me for that kind of work again I'm all yours. But I need you to know that I'm not up for any assignments that will put me up against Republic troops.

I'm still proud to be a part of this Alliance. But there are some lines I can't cross. I hope you can understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Yuun</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Diverging Paths</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="343" id2="763171" version="1065353216">We each follow our own path, unique to ourselves. Some paths meet and continue together, only to later split apart. This need not be cause for sorrow.

Yuun understands your loyalties, and does not resent them. Should our paths converge once more, Yuun will be glad.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="344" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Provost Marshal Rusk</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="345" id2="763171" version="1065353216">The Only Imp I Trust</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="346" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Commander,

You're the only Imp I ever met that I didn't want to shoot right away. And no matter what you're doing now, you once saved every single life in the Republic. I won't forget that.

I will never betray the Republic. But I will help you fight any other threat out there.

You know where to find me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="347" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Elara Dorne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="348" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Notice 18-4-TTX57: Termination of Liaison Status</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="349" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Commander,

I must regretfully inform you of the termination of my status as a Republic liaison to the Alliance, effective immediately.

With my duties officially discharged, please allow me to state for the record that I continue to believe that reaching across political boundaries can sometimes be the best way to achieve the greatest good for the galaxy. Should you ever have interests not at odds with the Republic, please don't hesitate to contact me for assistance.

Respectfully,
Elara Dorne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="350" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Qyzen Fess</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="351" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Hunting</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="352" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Warstalkers admire your score, and will earn their points at your side still. But I seek different game than war provides.

Summon me if you have worthy prey, and we will hunt together.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="353" id2="763171" version="1065353216">To All Alliance Command Staff:

Given my role as a liaison with the Chiss Ascendancy, I would prefer to have my name left out of any staffing or roster information shared with our allies in the Galactic Republic.

Your discretion in this matter is much appreciated.

Respectfully,
Raina Temple</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="354" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Talos Drellik</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="355" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Deepest Regrets</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="356" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Commander,

I write to you with a heavy heart, as duty requires that I sever my official relationship with the Alliance. My services are requested immediately by my superiors in the Imperial Reclamation Service, and so I must obey.

My time in the Alliance has been splendid, and I would relish any future opportunities to work together again, provided any such opportunity were not at odds with the Empire's goals. Please don't hesitate to contact me should such circumstances arise!

Apologetically Yours,
Talos Drellik</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="357" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Vette</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="358" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Nothing to worry about</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="359" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Hey, I'm sure you know I've got a lot of history with the Empire, but that's just what it is now - history. There are some people there I care about, but I'm no loyalist. 

The Alliance is my home now, end of story. Whatever comes next, I've got your back, just like you had mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="360" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Xalek</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="361" id2="763171" version="1065353216">I am Sith</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="362" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Your strength is proven

You can command me still

But that may not always be</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="363" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Kaliyo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="364" id2="763171" version="1065353216">get Lana to back off</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="365" id2="763171" version="1065353216">just because I used to hang out with an Imperial spy doesn't mean I am one, all right? like she's one to talk.

i'm not too bored yet, so you've got nothing to worry about from me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="366" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Eckard Lokin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="367" id2="763171" version="1065353216">The Game Continues</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="368" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Commander,

I understand the galaxy is back to its old hostilities. Allow me to pre-empt any unpleasant inquiries: all of my contacts in the Empire are dead or long lost by now. 

I have no interest in rejoining the game to anyone's benefit but my own; for now, I see the most to gain here at the Alliance, where my research can be carried out with minimal distraction.

Your continued patronage is most appreciated.

Gratefully,
Eckard Lokin

P.S. - Rumor has it that a new friend of yours has sent along a superb gift: Gatalentan tea. I'm told it's best when shared; if you're so inclined, you would find me quite grateful.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="369" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Malavai Quinn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="370" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Unpleasant News</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="371" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Commander,

I'm afraid my time as an Imperial representative to the Alliance must come to an end. In light of recent developments, I am called to return to Dromund Kaas immediately.

Please accept my apologies for this unfortunate turn of events. I have enjoyed my time on Odessen, and I believe you could still be a powerful ally in days to come.

Naturally, I cannot betray my Imperial commission, but should you ever have need of my help in other matters, I would be honored to oblige you.

Regretfully,
Malavai Quinn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="372" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="373" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Imperial Loyalties</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="374" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Your return to the Imperial fold has been received well by most Alliance personnel. 

Naturally, there are some with non-Imperial backgrounds who have expressed reservations; I will monitor all such individuals and inform you if there is cause for concern.

Should you wish it, I can also begin installing subliminally pro-Imperial signage and audio throughout the base. I came across very promising research on the subject during my time at Sith Intelligence; something as mundane as an elevator chime can be modified to have a surprisingly potent impact on political opinions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="375" id2="763171" version="1065353216">NR-02</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="376" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Pleasing Results</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="377" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Your actions on Ossus have cemented my superiors' view that the Alliance will play an invaluable role in attaining overall victory for the Empire.

I will keep you apprised as new opportunities develop. In the meantime, please continue your support of Imperial efforts wherever possible. The galaxy will know the proper order of things soon enough.

Glory to the Empire,
NR-02</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="378" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Republic Loyalties</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="379" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Your public support of the Republic has been received well by most Alliance personnel. 

Naturally, there are some with non-Republic backgrounds who have expressed reservations; I will monitor all such individuals and inform you if there is cause for concern.

In the meantime, I will begin a review of Alliance operations to ensure compliance with Republic laws and guidelines. I suspect Doctor Oggurobb and Captain Visz will not be thrilled at the prospect, but I'm certain that workable compromises can be reached.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="380" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Jonas Balkar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="381" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Great job!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="382" id2="763171" version="1065353216">You couldn't have done a better job on Ossus. Gnost-Dural and the other Jedi will be a huge help as the war heats up - I don't even want to think about how badly that would've gone without you.

I don't have any specific ops for you at the moment, but feel free to pitch in anywhere you see Republic forces in need. The more our people see you out there fighting on our side, the better morale is going to be.

With your help, I think we just might win this thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="383" id2="763171" version="1065353216">[Secure Message]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="384" id2="763171" version="1065353216">ALLIANCE DECRYPTION PROTOCOL: ENGAGED
MESSAGE READS:
I have told no one of your decision. I will continue to maintain absolute secrecy until you order otherwise. 

Should you wish to share the truth with anyone, I would ask only that you inform me of their identities so that I can include them as assets in future planning.

I would not advise telling the Alliance at large, as I do not believe we could maintain operational secrecy. This must remain a matter only for your most trusted agents.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="385" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Dazh Ranos</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="386" id2="763171" version="1065353216">An Open Mind</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="387" id2="763171" version="1065353216">I knew your past when I signed up, so rest assured, you won't have to hear any lectures from me. I go where the Force guides me, and right now, that's right here.

Just wanted to say that not all Jedi are as hard-headed and stubborn and narrowminded as the ones you might have dealt with. There are plenty who can be reasoned with. They don't all just march in lines, quoting the code with every breath.

Just keep that in mind, all right?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="388" id2="763171" version="1065353216">ERROR: Code J23-O9-N557-A59-S12</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="389" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Capitalize your future!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="390" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Great Work opportunities are waiting for you! Friendly management staff who don't focus on Losses. Minimal paperwork.

Pulling Your Punches at your current job? Well, no need here!

Further your career with Objectives that aren't Coming out of nowhere! Soon enough, you'll realize your dreams!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="391" id2="763171" version="1065353216">ENCRYPTED</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="392" id2="763171" version="1065353216">CODE KEY: ACCEPTED
IDENTITY: CONFIRMED
MESSAGE DECRYPTED:
You have served the Empire well and maintained your cover completely.
 
Our agents report that, while the Jedi are reunited with the Republic, there is much dissension on the matter given the Republic's failure to rescue several of the colony evacuation shuttles. Just the kind of subtle crack in morale that Sith Intelligence can exploit to great effect in the future.

Interrogations of the captured evacuees are ongoing, but I am confident that we will see valuable results soon.

Additionally, your efforts to merely maim our troops have been appreciated.

I will contact you with additional objectives soon.

Glory to the Empire,
NR-02</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="393" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Tau Idair</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="394" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Settling In</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="395" id2="763171" version="1065353216">I'm getting back into the old grind of life aboard a warship. Hot-swapping bunks and chowing on three Republic standard-issue rations a day, living the dream, you know? Probably doesn't sound like I'm thanking you, but I am; not sure any of us would have made it off Ossus without your help. 

Everyone on the crew seems surprised when they find out I know you. I guess you saved the entire galaxy while we were busy getting Zaryos's muja fruit to grow, so that's two I owe you.

Hey, how well do you know Daeruun, by the way? He asked if he could paint me the other day. Weird, right?

Anyway, long random message, the only kind I know how to write. Keep in touch.
-T</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="396" id2="763171" version="1065353216">You've brought the Jedi back</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="397" id2="763171" version="1065353216">My favorite sparring partner from Tython. A Gran I met in a trench on Karfeddion; we had shared our rations but not our names. Master Theenu, who always said my mind wandered too easily.

So many old friends I thought were lost years ago. It's enough to put a smile on the face of even the crustiest of lone wanderers. 

Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="398" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Darth Hexid</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="399" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Clarification</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="400" id2="763171" version="1065353216">I'm told you've recently saved a whole slew of Jedi from some boring planet or other. You may fear that this offends my Sith sensibilities, but I assure you, I couldn't care less. How you choose to spend your time is your affair, darling.

What I must make clear, however, is that if any of these Jedi or their refugee clingers-on are planning to move into the base here on Odessen, they will not be occupying even one square centimeter of my quarters. 

Darth Hexid shares nothing. Should anyone wish to challenge me for control of my space, they do so at their mortal peril. Please see that any incoming &quot;guests&quot; are made to understand this.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="401" id2="763171" version="1065353216">General A. D. Daeruun</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="402" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Deepest Appreciation</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="403" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Commander:

Having found a few spare moments, I would very much like to express again my heartfelt appreciation for your heroic actions on Ossus. It could have been a true disaster for the Republic, but thanks to your perseverance and skill, the Jedi live to fight another day.

With my fervent recommendation, the members of Republic Strategic Command have unanimously agreed to include you in our strategic planning for all major campaigns moving forward. The war is only just begun, but I already feel that a crucial victory has been won.

Someday, when we finally defeat the Sith once and for all, it will be with heroes like you leading the way.

Your Steadfast Ally,
Ardinondu Dipolus Daeruun</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="404" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Commander:

Having found a few spare moments, I would very much like to express again my heartfelt appreciation for your heroic actions on Ossus. It could have been a true disaster for the Republic, but thanks to your perseverance and skill, the Jedi live to fight another day.

There is a matter that I feel I must bring out into the open: after the events of Iokath, I'm sure you can imagine that there was some objection to my choice to call upon you for aid. There were those who believed you had abandoned the Republic. I knew in my heart that they were wrong.

The results of your intervention on Ossus speak for themselves. I am certain that the members of Republic Strategic Command will agree with my assessment that you should play an integral role in our strategic planning for all major campaigns moving forward. 

If we are to truly defeat the Sith, it will be with heroes like you leading the way.

Your Steadfast Ally,
Ardinondu Dipolus Daeruun</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="405" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Theron Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="406" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Checking In</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="407" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Heard you had an eventful mission! Sorry to have missed out on the fun, but it doesn't sound like you needed any help.

Crazy that you ran into Gnost-Dural, he's an old friend. We took down Darth Karrid together--I'll tell you all about it when I'm back. Trust me, it's a story I tell way better than he does.

See you back on Odessen soon,
Theron</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="408" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Major Anri</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="409" id2="763171" version="1065353216">I owe you!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="410" id2="763171" version="1065353216">I'm back aboard our old ship and I'm telling you, I have never been so popular. Can't walk a meter without someone wanting to hear the story of how I got to fight side-by-side with the Legendary Amazing Commander of Awesomeness. 

You've gotten me more free drinks than I can handle, and let me tell you, THAT is an accomplishment indeed.

Rest assured, I've put my secondhand celebrity to good use: got my little garden plot moved from the back corner of the deck fifteen locker room all the way to the center of the deck four officers' mess. Next thing I know, the shiny academy grads will be watering it for me so THEY can get a favor. Life is good.

You ever need Raven Squad for a mission, we're all yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="411" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Moff Pyron</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="412" id2="763171" version="1065353216">My Thanks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="413" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Commander,

Your actions in resolving the Ossus situation were impressive indeed. I'm told that you even intervened directly in the rescue of one of my soldiers-I am truly appreciative.

If I can ever be of service to you or your Alliance in the future, please do not hesitate to contact me.

Respectfully,
Moff Valion Pyron</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="414" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Dark Council?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="415" id2="763171" version="1065353216">I'm told you've recently been mingling with the Imperial elite, and that a seat on the Dark Council may have been opened in the process.

When I left the Empire to pursue my own campaign of terror against Zakuul, I left in a bit of a cloud-I'm simply no longer in contact with anyone of such stature.

Could you be a dear and pass along my resume to anyone who might be interested? I'm certain I could provide superior leadership as a member of that venerable body, just as I'm sure you'd love to see your close friend elevated to a mutually beneficial position within the Empire.

What do you say, darling?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="416" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Mourning a Friend</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="417" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Heard the news about Gnost-Dural-he was an old friend of mine. I should have been there. We could have worked something out, I'm sure of it.

If you could have just had time to talk, it would have been different. I'm sure Malgus didn't give you any opportunity.

Malgus. How is that old freak still alive?

Catch up soon,
Theron</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="418" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Gnost-Dural</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="419" id2="763171" version="1065353216">I want to thank you for making sure Gnost-Dural made it off Ossus alive-he's an old friend of mine. I don't like the idea of him in Imperial custody, but that's better than being dead. I'm sure that's what Malgus would have wanted you to do.

Malgus. How is that old freak still alive?

Catch up soon,
Theron</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="420" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Doc</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="421" id2="763171" version="1065353216">One last thing</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="422" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Got a little distracted during our chat earlier. Forgot something important.

I ran with Kira and Scourge for a while after you disappeared, but I haven't seen them in years. If you haven't found them either, with all your resources, I'm worried they might be in trouble.

The three of us were doing our thing, fighting evil and whatnot, and then Scourge just got weird. Obsessed. He wouldn't tell me anything, obviously, but he got Kira spun up in it too. We were going planet to planet, talking to weird people, looking for stuff they wouldn't show me. 

All I know is that it had to do with the Sith Emperor. Didn't you kill him? 

I have no idea what could have happened. But they had my back more than once, and I feel like telling you what I know means I've still got theirs.

That's it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="423" id2="763171" version="1065353216">A Pleasure As Always</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="424" id2="763171" version="1065353216">Commander,

Your resolution of the Ossus situation was as impressive as ever. It pleases me to see that the years have only seen your power and cunning increase. I'm told that you even intervened directly in the rescue of one of my soldiers-I am truly appreciative.

I shall look forward to our next opportunity to work together with great enthusiasm. If I can ever be of service to you or your Alliance in the future, please do not hesitate to contact me.

Respectfully,
Moff Valion Pyron</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
