<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>63</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/event.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="686119" version="1065353216">UNKNOWN SENDER</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="686119" version="1065353216">The Chevin Conglomerate</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="686119" version="1065353216">If you're taking part in the Grand Acquisitions Race, we should talk.

Look for a holotransmitter at the Dealer's Den cantina on Coruscant. Keep a low profile.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="686119" version="1065353216">UNKNOWN SENDER</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="686119" version="1065353216">The Chevin Conglomerate</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="686119" version="1065353216">You have accepted the list for the Grand Acquisitions Race, but perhaps you don't know all the facts.

Look for a holotransmitter at the Nexus Room on Dromund Kaas. I can speak to you there.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Agent Reeho</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="686119" version="1065353216">The Chevin items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="686119" version="1065353216">I promised to help you find those items. I keep my promises.

My intel suggests one of them, an Akar Kesh meditation mask, is on Coruscant. I couldn't narrow it farther than the district, so I did the next best thing--I dropped off a &quot;sniffer&quot; droid that should help you find it.

Just find the droid crate, use the codes attached to this message, and the little fellow will hunt that item down.

--Agent R.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Gyden Kall</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="686119" version="1065353216">The Chevin items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="686119" version="1065353216">One good turn deserves another; as promised, I've discovered the location of one of the items you seek: an &quot;Akar Kesh meditation mask.&quot;

I'd almost pinpointed its location on Dromund Kaas, but my search was interrupted. In the meantime, I've provided a &quot;sniffer&quot; droid that should help you track the item down.

The droid's operation is standard: find its crate, enter the codes I've provided and the droid will find a path to your prize.

G.K.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Agent Reeho</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Lead on Chevin items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Reeho here. I have another lead on one of those items you're looking for: the Black-and-Orange sphere. The bad news is it's in the hands of Sapaaga the Hutt. The good news is Sapaaga only cares about one thing: droid racing.

But Sapaaga's been on a losing streak. Maybe he'll make a generous offer. Try looking out for Sapaaga's observation droid at the race track on Nar Shaddaa. I'll keep working.

--Agent R.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Gyden Kall</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Progress finding Chevin items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Success. One of the items on your list, the Black-and-Orange sphere, is on Nar Shaddaa, in the possession of a Hutt named Sapaaga. He's a curious Hutt--no  interest in spice, credits or even the item he possesses. He only cares for droid racing, though he hasn't been successful lately.

Sapaaga keeps an observation droid at the track on Nar Shaddaa, and I suspect he may be getting desperate enough to give up the item, or its whereabouts. In the meantime, my investigation continues.

G.K.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Agent Reeho</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Another (possible) lead on Chevin items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="686119" version="1065353216">I wasn't sure whether to bother you with this, but I've got a very tentative lead for another item on Nar Shaddaa. One of them is some sort of plasma-sealed jar, yes?

Our report said something about it being connected with the infrastructure of Nar Shaddaa itself. I sent a slicing droid to investigate. By the time you check in with the droid, I should know what's up.

--Agent R.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Gyden Kall</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="686119" version="1065353216">More progress on Chevin items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="686119" version="1065353216">I have a potential lead on Nar Shaddaa for another of the items on your list; the plasma-sealed jar. Reports suggest it has some connection with the very infrastructure of Nar Shaddaa, but I'm having trouble getting confirmation.

I sent a slicing droid to Nar Shaddaa to investigate and gather more data. Rendezvous with the droid; hopefully it will have made some progress.

G.K.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Agent Reeho</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Re: The Chevin--READ IMMEDIATELY!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="686119" version="1065353216">I don't believe this. I finished compiling the information you gathered--thank you, by the way--and I think I know what was really behind the Grand Acquisitions Race. What the Chevins' talk of a &quot;fleet&quot; and those &quot;ideograms&quot; was all about.

It's the Gree. The Gree fleet is returning, along with all its tech and ancient artifacts.

I don't think anyone alive has seen a Gree in the flesh. Their civilization peaked before the Republic was even thought of; they've been absent from known space for millennia. Before they sent some droids to oversee reconstruction work on Coruscant, some of our reports said they were extinct. (Even our Coruscant data isn't that great--it keeps talking about black hexagons or something.) And now they're coming back?

That's what these curiosities are for: The Chevin want to buy the goodwill of the Gree when they arrive. Imagine the chaos if the Chevin get access to Gree artifacts and technology!

The SIS is holding emergency meetings on this--I'm already late for one, actually. But I wanted you to know the truth, and to be ready. If the Gree are coming, everything's going to change.

--Agent R.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Gyden Kall</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Re: The Chevin--TOP PRIORITY MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Forgive the rush. I've only just finished my investigation into the Chevin and their Grand Acquisitions Race, and my findings are... monumental. Your discoveries point at one inescapable truth.

The ancient Gree are returning. And they are bringing a fleet--all their knowledge, all their technology, everything.

The import of this can't be underestimated. The Gree are an ancient species; they predate the Infinite Empire. They had hyperspace travel while most sentient species were still banging sticks to make fire. There are scattered intelligence reports of Gree emissary droids on Coruscant, but obviously, confirmation was problematic. It seems we have that confirmation, now: the Gree are returning.

The Chevin knew; their contacts must have alerted them. All these curiosities were intended as a tribute to the Gree, to buy an alliance or some of their technology. If that happens, the Chevin could be a legitimate threat to the Empire. It's a sobering thought.

I will be reporting to Darth Marr and the Citadel. If the Gree are coming, we must be ready.

G.K.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="686119" version="1065353216">The Chevin Conglomerate</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Gratitude</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="686119" version="1065353216">From our homeworld Vinsoth, greetings.

All that was listed has been procured. Your provision for the Chevin Conglomerate has been noted, and your enrichment opportunity shall be fulfilled.

Rejoice in your profits and the fruits of collaboration. Know that your glory has been earned, and will not be forgotten.

End congratulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Agent Reeho</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Received the acquisitions safely</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="686119" version="1065353216">All the items you sent have been secured at SIS headquarters. (Some have been &quot;secured&quot; more than others--this stuff is strange.)

I don't know how well we can compensate you, but you did the right thing. The Chevin are ruthless and clever; if a Gree fleet really is coming, we can't afford to be second in a race for their allegiance.

Time to get ready.
 
--Agent Reeho</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Gyden Kall</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Chevin curiosities received</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Acknowledging receipt of the items you sent. They have been sent to the Citadel under heavy guard, for study at the Ministry of Logistics. Darth Marr will be overseeing the results himself.

Your help has been invaluable. If the Chevin are right about these items--if they can buy the goodwill of an ancient Gree fleet returning to our part of the galaxy--then they're worth any amount of credits. At the very least, they're out of criminal Chevin hands.

And we've got time to prepare.

G.K.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Claw</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="686119" version="1065353216">You're done for!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Are you really going to try and mess with me? Claw? The undisputed terror titan of House Frayus?

Matriarch Frayus has got no idea what I'm capable of. I'm not just some punk. I've got connections. I'm going places. What I've done to House Frayus is just a taste.

The local authorities have really started to bore me, so come find me if you want. Maybe you'll put up a little more of a fight.

~Claw~</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Samovan Bann</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Rank-and-File Futility</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="686119" version="1065353216">To Whom It May Concern,

Running a criminal enterprise is very much like running a successful corporation. In a corporation, however, one must abide by all manner of local, planetary, and galactic laws.

I will succeed in my mandate to lead Black Sun into a new era of prosperity; disquieted peasants with a couple spare credits and a hint of a backbone cannot stop me. Because of your interference, I will show them what I am capable of when left unburdened by oppressive rules and regulations.

Best regards,
Samovan Bann
Executive Architect</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Lord Trok</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Only I see the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="686119" version="1065353216">The Empire is governed by selfish hypocrites. They pursue their own passions while keeping the passions of others in check.

I am driven by passion, and allow others to do the same. That is pure.

I do not know how you learned of my operations, but I will not let you stop me from being that which I am.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Grov</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="686119" version="1065353216">My Destiny</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="686119" version="1065353216">It is true that I became what I am today on the backs and corpses of other Evocii. I did it to embolden my kind by showing them what one of us is capable of.

I call myself Destroyer because I aim to destroy the hold the Hutts have unjustly placed on this world. This world belongs to the Evocii. It is ours to plunder, not theirs. However many have to die to make this a reality is irrelevant.

Grov the Destroyer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Arkan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="686119" version="1065353216">You and Otheros</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Otheros thinks running a casino is all about accountants and playing by the rules and holding hands with deadbeats who owe you credits. Seems he's starting to learn just how wrong he is. Finally got the guts to come after me and my business. If he didn't hide behind some hired muscle to do it, I might actually respect the fuzzball.

You know how they say &quot;the house always wins&quot;? I'm the house. Take me on, and it will be the last thing you ever do.

Arkan
Supreme Executive Officer of the Lucky Runner</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Brogon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Reasons</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="686119" version="1065353216">I bet you've been hired by Ariavos. I also bet Ariavos didn't explain how he used to turn a blind eye to my activities until I came after his assets. How am I doing? Two for two?

If this is all about credits for you, I get it. But if it's for Ariavos or that bloated waste you call the Galactic Republic, I got no respect for you, and you deserve what's coming.

Either way, I WILL take you down.

--Brogon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Kreegan Ramar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="686119" version="1065353216">I don't believe it!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="686119" version="1065353216">You're really doing this? Coming after me over a measly pack of Jawas? I'm a merc for life, but even I got limits to what jobs I'll take!

Must be a lot of credits them runts are paying you. I shoulda been taking their coffers all this time instead of their inventory. Maybe even just killed them outright the first time.

I'll definitely have to pay that Meerko and his clan a special visit after I'm done with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Talosa, Eryn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="686119" version="1065353216">Do you see?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="686119" version="1065353216">I do admit that, when the Exchange essentially begged me to embark upon a new franchise on planet Voss, I was appalled by the idea; however, this placid orb with its naive inhabitants has revealed its true form to me--as a blank canvas upon which I can bestow any tableau I desire.

You are on my canvas. Get off.

Cordially,
Eryn Talosa</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
