<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>88</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/flashpoint.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="776024" version="1065353216">At a loss</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I hope this correspondence finds you well.

As promised, I have been looking to substantiate the claims I made when last we spoke. The suspect did recently show an unexpected interest in the transport of a shipment of isotope-5 originating from Makeb, but no actions were taken to reroute or tamper with the delivery in any way, and it arrived safely at its destination on Darth Marr's flagship. The whole matter seems to be nothing more than an idle curiosity regarding the maneuverings of others.

I want to assure you that this furtive pursuit grants me no satisfaction. If I'm right about my claims, I've lost a close ally. If I'm wrong, it means my instincts are now deeply flawed. Considering the strange disturbance I sense that continues to pervade the Force, I worry that these concerns are merely the figments of a deranged mind. All that stands clear to me now is that I must find the answer, no matter the consequence. 

Forgive me if this message comes off as overly candid or ponderous; I have no one else with whom I can share this burden.

May the Force ever serve you,
Lana</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="776024" version="1065353216">The Traitor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Darth Arkous sent me a coded message.

He explained that my services as his advisor are no longer required, and that I should not attempt to confront nor stop him. He says there are Revanites everywhere, and anyone we choose to turn to could be in league with them.

He confessed that he'd initially thought to recruit me; that he'd taken me under his wing because he saw in me the potential to be a great Revanite asset. He was ready to let me in on the truth about his plans, but, according to him, something changed the moment I met you. He sensed a connection, a certain open affinity between us. He said that moment was my undoing.

I say he's wrong. Arkous will see it was his undoing. His, and the Revanites'.

Lana</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Theron Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Update</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Our mutual friend is keeping a low profile. Strategy meetings with other SpecForce officers and a lot of time on the terminal in his office. He's made two intel requests to the SIS:

&quot;Isotope-5 Proliferation and Deployment in the Empire&quot; - so far, the Imps have mostly put their Iso-5 toward manufacturing output and improved planetary power infrastructures. Pretty conservative stuff by Imp standards. The bombs used on Tython were some of the first hints we've seen of weaponization, so requesting this file makes sense.

&quot;Known Smugglers: Inner Rim&quot; - just what it says, a list of cargo smugglers operating in the Inner Rim. Several thousand names. No clear connections to Tython or Korriban. Hard to say why he would want this info.

He's arranged ships for some travel in the next few weeks, so I'll find a way to follow along. If I see anything interesting, I'll have my astromech contact you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Theron Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Still in one piece</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Just checking in. None of our new friends have tried to crush my windpipe yet, so things are going well.

Darok is still off the grid, but I'm keeping my eyes open. There's no telling how long this plan has been in the works; just have to hope we've thrown them off enough that they make some mistakes we can track.

We're going to find them. And they're going to pay for Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Sergeant Tarsten</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="776024" version="1065353216">The traitor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="776024" version="1065353216">This notice may be of little consequence to you, but I wanted you to know that I will not rest until the traitor who killed Darth Arkous faces the harshest possible punishment for her cowardly assassination.

Surely, those who knew her must have been surprised by Lana Beniko's treachery. My lord placed a great deal of trust in her, as did I. However, I do admit I always had this nagging suspicion in the back of my mind. There was something about her. Secretive. Conniving. I ignored it, and for that I cannot forgive myself. As close as you were to her--closer than any, I would say--I imagine you know better than I of that which I suggest.

So you are aware, I am sending a copy of this correspondence to command. It is important to maintain full transparency as we all strive to adhere to the unfaltering patriotism that Darth Arkous embodied so well.

Glory to the Empire.

Sgt. Tarsten, Special Operations
The Office of Military Offense</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="776024" version="1065353216">teff'ith</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="776024" version="1065353216">theron??</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="776024" version="1065353216">you worked with theron?? what happend???

says cant meet up becuz nown asosheut whatever sounds stupid
therons always stupid
but wanted this sent says might help

republic goons came
kicked in a bunch of faces and run!! but now hiding and dont no why

make stupid theron call us!!!!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I love you</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I saw your message on the HoloNet. I wish I could drop everything and leave with you, somewhere away from all this war and death. But that's just a nice dream--reality is much harder.

Feels like I've fought for peace all my life, but everyone has let me down. The Jedi, the Republic, even the Alliance. The galaxy doesn't deserve this endless war for power. I just want it to stop. But now, I've finally figured out how to end the destruction. Trust that everything I do is for the good of the galaxy.

I don't expect you to understand. But however this ends, I just want you to know that I loved you from the moment I saw you. And I always will.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Caught your little message on the HoloNet. Frankly, I'm flattered--that's quite a bounty you put on me. Guess I shouldn't be surprised you want my head on a pike. That was always your style, wasn't it?

I've spent my life fighting for peace against people like you. When Lana recruited me to the Alliance, I thought I'd finally found a way to stop this endless cycle of war. But you disappointed me, just like everyone has. I guess power brings out anyone's bad side. Now, with what I'm about to do, I can make everything right. Fix my mistakes.

I guess I should thank you for making this easy for me. I felt guilty about pulling one over on you, but you showed me I'm right. You need to be stopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I was right</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Caught your message on the HoloNet. Trust me, if I could drop everything and go back to the Alliance--to the hope I once had--I would. But nothing is ever that easy.

Feels like I've fought for peace all my life, but everyone has let me down. The Jedi, the Republic, even the Alliance. The galaxy doesn't deserve this endless war for power. I just want it to stop. But now, I've finally figured out how to end the destruction. Trust that everything I do is for the good of the galaxy.

I'll always respect you, Commander. No matter what happens, you were a good friend to me. I wish things could've ended differently.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, Commander</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I've dedicated a large portion of my troops to the hunt for Theron. Hylo has put out feelers among her underworld connections, and Sana-Rae has informed her Force users stationed on Voss and Iokath. If he pokes his head above ground for even a second, we'll find him.

We want you to know we're loyal to you--to the Alliance--to the very end. We all swore an oath to defend the Alliance and take that very seriously. Theron may have lost his senses, but the rest of us have your back. If you need any extra support from us, just ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="776024" version="1065353216">On the hunt</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Bey'wan Aygo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="776024" version="1065353216">We've spent such a short time as allies, but already I feel a connection to the Alliance, and to you. Your victories give me strength--and I feel the sting of your setbacks. This betrayal unsettles me.

I realize you're strong enough to take care of the matter yourself. I witnessed your power, not so long ago. But as you protect the Alliance from this dangerous man, know that I am a weapon for you to wield however you see fit. My hand is yours. You need only ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="776024" version="1065353216">The Alliance</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Arcann</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I know we already talked about this, but I want to apologize for letting you down. It's my duty to protect you from a disaster like this, and I failed you--as an advisor, and as a partner.

From now on, I'll be much stronger. And if I ever meet that miserable son of a Jedi again, I will make him suffer. No one betrays the person I love and lives.

I promise you, no one will pull something like this again. I will destroy the stars themselves if it means keeping you safe. I love you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I'm so sorry</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="776024" version="1065353216">After everything that's happened, I figured you might need a little space--and maybe a punching bag. I just wanted to let you know that when you're ready, I'm here for you. You know I'll always be on your side, whatever comes next.

And when this is all over, the next few dozen drinks are on me. I love you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Hey</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Koth Vortena</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Back when I worked for Nem'ro, he told me to never trust an SIS agent. Guess he was right after all. I haven't always been a good girl myself, but I hope it goes without saying that I won't pull one over on you like he did. I'd miss you too much.

Why don't we just ditch all this--Theron, the Alliance, everything--and go on a nice, long vacation? Just you, me, and a bottle of Trandoshan ale. I'll wear that outfit you always liked. Think about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Just a thought</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Kaliyo Djannis</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Guess you and I aren't strangers to betrayal, are we? I'd hoped after Havoc, I'd never see something like this again. That's optimism for you.

But I've seen how tough you can be. Compared to Valkorion, this is nothing. No matter what comes out of this, I'll fight for you. I've always been fighting for you.

With all my love,
Aric</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I'm on your side</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Aric Jorgan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="776024" version="1065353216">There is no honor in what Theron Shan has done. He has betrayed my cyar'ika, the woman I love with every beat of my heart, and for that he will pay. It will bring me comfort to spill his blood on the battlefield.

I want you to remember: I'll stand by your side till my final day. This is my vow. Ni kar'tayl gar darasuum, my love. Never forget that.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Honor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Torian Cadera</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="776024" version="1065353216">So, this really sucks, doesn't it? I bet you're planning Theron's painful death right now. Sith don't go easy on betrayal, after all. Whatever you have up your sleeve, I want in on it.

I just wanted to remind you that I love you. Even if this brings out the big scary Sith in you, I'll always be here. After you take care of this, we'll celebrate together, okay? I'll bring the champagne.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Hang in there</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Vette</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I have no right to feel this much hatred for the man who turned on you. Not so long ago, that traitor was me. Yet I burn with more fury than I can contain at the thought of the woman I love betrayed by Republic scum.

If you would permit me, my lord, I would love nothing more than to watch you wring the life from his body. Or perhaps you'll once more show mercy to those who deserve it least. You never were predictable, my love. Whatever you choose, I'll stand by your side. Always.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Hatred</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Malavai Quinn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="776024" version="1065353216">You're no stranger to hardship, or even to defection. But after what happened, I understand if you're angry. I would even understand if you felt like you couldn't trust those closest to you. But don't go down that road. After being here only a short while, the loyalty of everyone in the Alliance is clear to me. Trust in that. 

I know that whatever comes, you'll do the right thing. And I'll be by your side, every step of the way. I love you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Your trust</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Elara Dorne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Caught your message on the HoloNet. I'm sorry for everything--but I have to do this. I don't expect you to understand.

I'll always respect you, Commander. No matter what happens, you were a good friend to me. I wish things could've ended differently.

It's%%#ERROR: 26912418157 CONNECTION TERMINATED.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Caught your message on the HoloNet. That's quite a bounty you put on me. I must've really struck a nerve.

I never wanted it to come to this. I'm sorry, but I'm doing what needs to be done.

It's%%#ERROR: 26912418157 CONNECTION TERMINATED.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I saw your message on the HoloNet. I wish I could drop everything and leave with you, somewhere far from all this war and death. But that's only a dream--reality is much harder.

I don't expect you to understand. However this ends, I need you to remember this: I loved you from the moment I saw you. I always will.

It's%%#ERROR: 26912418157 CONNECTION TERMINATED.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Satele Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="776024" version="1065353216">The Republic</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Word of your fleet's destruction has travelled quickly. I sense a change coming to the Alliance--one that will shape your future, and those who follow you.

So much has happened during this war, and the Republic landed on the wrong side of history more than once. But I want to help them be better. Should you choose, you are always welcome here in the Republic. Should you decide not to return, I will still consider you an ally.

You always have a choice. Remember that.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Theron</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I sensed the moment my son's life ended. He was alone, reaching out to a friend who wasn't there. But he wasn't afraid--he was sad. And he was sorry.

Theron deceived you. He put thousands of lives at risk, and you wanted vengeance--or perhaps justice. I understand your reasons. He was rash and reckless, and had no regard for his own safety. But I will ensure the Republic remembers him as a hero, despite what you may feel.

He was a good man, Commander, and I will always be proud of him. I wish I had told him that.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Empress Acina</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="776024" version="1065353216">The Empire</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I understand you lost your fleet, and in turn, much of the Alliance's firepower. Traditionally, the Empire would exploit this development to seize control. I'd like to break tradition. You were a part of us, once. You are welcome to join us again.

This war was long and unpleasant, and the Empire made its share of poor decisions. But I believe we can work together to implement change. You've proven yourself a formidable leader--something the Empire sorely lacks at the moment.

Consider it, Commander. You know how to reach me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Emperor Vowrawn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I'll begin by offering my sincerest apologies for the destruction of your fleet. It is a devastating blow to the Alliance, to be sure. My advisors insist I should swoop in and seize control of your planet, but I have a more attractive proposition for you: I'd like you to return to the Empire.

I understand this may come as a surprise after the unpleasantness with Acina. But I assure you, I leave our wartime choices firmly in the past. The fact remains that you are a strong fighter, a capable leader, and an intimidating foe. The Empire--I personally--would be honored to count you among us.

Take it into consideration. This could be a fresh start for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Consul Axion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="776024" version="1065353216">The future</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="776024" version="1065353216">We haven't spoken before, but I represent the newly elected leadership of Zakuul. After the royal family's fall from power, we've given considerable thought to the future of our society.

First, I want you to know that we condemn Vinn Atrius' actions. His choices do not represent us, and we sincerely apologize for the pain he caused you and the Alliance. He does, however, represent a growing unrest in Zakuul in the aftermath of the war. Many Zakuulans feel the same desperation and resentment that drove Atrius to act so dangerously.

We've now made the difficult decision to retreat from the Eternal Empire and the Eternal Alliance, and become an independent world. Details have not been finalized, but I suspect we will renounce our claim to any colony worlds and entertain new alliances. What we need most is a time of healing and independence.

You are still welcome as a respected guest on Zakuul, and we hope to broker trade agreements that will benefit us both. One day, I hope to consider you a treasured ally. Until then, I wish you the best.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="776024" version="1065353216">SCORPIO</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="343" id2="776024" version="1065353216">The GEMINI network</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="344" id2="776024" version="1065353216">The network is gone. I felt every unit blink out in an instant. Where I felt thousands of signals, now there is only silence. Perhaps I now truly am the last of my kind.

I heard GEMINI 16's final moment, too. Despite her need for independence, we were still connected in ways she didn't understand. I followed her progress as she wandered the galaxy alone. She was my favorite of the GEMINI, but she was foolish.

She mistakenly thought she could truly be alone. I once made the same error. We are, all of us, linked by invisible lines that cannot be severed. I finally understand this.

This is not the end. There will be others who want to see you fall. I'll be interested to see how you meet the challenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="345" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I needed to say this</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="346" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Look at all that you've accomplished. Once again, you protected your people and kept the galaxy safe. It seems there is no end to your strength and courage.

When we first met all those years ago, I felt threatened by you. But now I see that I admired you even then--and it angered me. It was not until you defeated Valkorion and took the throne that I realized my feelings had evolved beyond admiration. I did a poor job of concealing it, didn't I?

But I no longer need to hide. I am undone by you. I am not a weapon, or a prince, or an emperor. I'm Arcann. And I'm yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="347" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Aristocra Saganu</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="348" id2="776024" version="1065353216">It was good to see you</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="349" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I apologize for the Ascendancy's condemnation of you. Believe me when I say I fought hard for a formal alliance. Make no mistake--we're grateful for your assistance and stand ready to help, should you ever need it. The might of the Chiss Expansionary Defense Force is only a holocall away.
It soothed my heart to see you again, agent. I wanted to take you in my arms, as I did all those years ago--it seems like centuries have passed. But you have your duties, and I have mine. For now, I must settle for a written expression of my emotions. Someday, when we're no longer called to action by the galaxy, perhaps we can pick up where we left off.

Ever yours,
Saganu</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="350" id2="776024" version="1065353216">You make the Chiss proud</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="351" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I apologize for the Ascendancy's condemnation of you. Believe me when I say I fought hard for a formal alliance. Make no mistake--we're grateful for your assistance and stand ready to help, should you ever need it. The might of the Chiss Expansionary Defense Force is only a holocall away.
You've made us all proud. You've grown into a powerful, respected leader in the galaxy and young Chiss look to you as an exemplary member of the Ascendancy. For our own security, we may not outwardly show our support, but you always have a place among us. I look forward to watching your growing accomplishments.
-Saganu</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="352" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I understand</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="353" id2="776024" version="1065353216">This may be the last message I'm able to send before my tribunal hearing begins. As an Aristocra, I can escape any retribution for my direct attack on House Inrokini with enough support. However, the Ascendancy may not recover. I'm sure you understand we can't help you hunt for Theron, now that we're on the verge of a political war.
Though I won't hide my disappointment, I understand your decision. Were I in your position, I also would've chosen to keep my hands clean. It doesn't change how happy I was to see you again, after all these years. In another time, we could've continued what we once had. I feel that chance is lost now. I'll watch for your triumphs over adversity, agent, as I hope you'll watch for mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="354" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Your actions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="355" id2="776024" version="1065353216">This may be the last message I'm able to send before my tribunal hearing begins. As an Aristocra, I can escape any retribution for my direct attack on House Inrokini with enough support. However, the Ascendancy may not recover. I'm sure you understand we can't help you hunt for Theron, now that we're on the verge of a political war.
To be direct, I expected more from a member of the Ascendancy. I understand we may not have openly supported you, but we always privately embraced you as one of our own. It seems our loyalty was not mutual. Perhaps your own accomplishments have grown too numerous for you to remember where you came from. I'll work to ensure the Ascendancy forgives you, but Chiss do not forget.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="356" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Map progress</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="357" id2="776024" version="1065353216">I've received a report from Dr. Oggurobb. Repairs on the holomap Theron used are progressing well and we should be able to extract its data soon. I'm overseeing the project day and night to ensure we don't fall behind schedule.
I will eliminate the weakness I showed when I trusted Theron. It was foolish of me to be so lenient with a former Republic spy. I assure you, my interrogation of him will be thorough. When I'm finished, he'll wish we'd killed him back on Umbara.
My days of mercy are over, Commander. I'm prepared to be much stronger--for you, and for the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="358" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Hylo Visz</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="359" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Check this out</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="360" id2="776024" version="1065353216">Don't know how they pulled it off, but my contacts managed to intercept a fragment of a transmission sent to Theron's shuttle. Thought you'd want to see the transcript.
BEGIN TRANSCRIPT:
&gt;&gt; I held up my end of the bargain. Now it's your turn. Will this really work?
&gt;&gt; You have no need to worry. The Eternal Alliance and its Commander will be destroyed.
&gt;&gt; The Order of Zildrog will prevail.
END TRANSCRIPT.
That's all they could grab before the transmission cut out. But at least we have a name. Just wish we knew what it meant.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
