<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>117</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/jedi_consular.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Nadia Grell</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Dreams</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="575050" version="1065353216">My dreams are so much better. For so long, I kept dreaming about what happened to my father. And then it was about terrible things happening to you. But they've faded now. I think it's the training, and just knowing I have someone who cares for me. 

Now I keep seeing strange worlds instead. Battlefields and powerful enemies. Sometimes I'm surrounded by strangers, but it's like I should know them from somewhere. These dreams don't scare me like the others, though. I can always feel your presence somewhere close by, and I know there's no reason to be afraid.

Maybe they're prophetic? It's hard to remember the details. But if they are, it means we'll be facing these things together. That's a comforting thought. 

--Nadia</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Nadia Grell</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="575050" version="1065353216">A package from Sarkhai</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="575050" version="1065353216">This is a little embarrassing (please don't tell the others). One of my cousins back home sent me some... well, the Sarkhai term means &quot;gifts of bonding and happiness.&quot; They're usually given as wedding presents. I don't know how she found out about us, but I'm going to have some very searching questions for her later!

I suppose it was a nice thought. They're beautiful gifts, too. It's nice to see things that were created back home, and to know that my relatives are wishing me well. I've studied the Council's doctrine on attachment backwards and forwards since we've been together, but I still can't see anything wrong with being part of a family. Please share these with me; they're yours, too.

Except this bottle of thesum-bark syrup. It's my favorite, but I hear that if you're not from Sarkhai, it tastes a lot like medicine. 

--Nadia</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Nadia Grell</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Thinking</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="575050" version="1065353216">I've been meditating on something. If we marry and start a family--yes, I know things are hectic right now, and there's a lot of decisions to be made, but if we ever do--I wouldn't want to keep it a secret. 

Almost everything I've studied about the &quot;perils of love&quot; seems to be written by Jedi who've never experienced it themselves. They talk about &quot;uncontrolled passion&quot; and the &quot;fear of loss&quot; like they're poison. But these Jedi never discuss devotion, patience and compassion. Love's taught me more about those than the rest of my training combined. Those Jedi just dismiss love as &quot;obsession,&quot; when love's the opposite and they don't seem to know it.

If the Masters are going to claim that emotional attachment is flat-out wrong, I want to know that they've experienced it, and still think that way. Love can make a Jedi less selfish, more humble and more devoted. We're the proof. I wouldn't want to hide that from anyone.
 
--Nadia</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Felix Iresso</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="575050" version="1065353216">For you</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="575050" version="1065353216">I didn't really have much to say. I was just thinking of you, and I thought you might like this. I was going to say, think of me when you see it, but then it just goes in circles. (I'm kidding.)

Be safe, sweetheart.

F.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Felix Iresso</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Something to share</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="575050" version="1065353216">This is going to sound strange, but there was a holovid I was hoping to show you. I've been tracking down a copy for ages, and a Paaerduag on Coruscant traded me one along with some other bits and pieces. It's called &quot;Squad 223: Mission Zero,&quot; and I'm pretty sure it's the dumbest vid ever made. 

But when my family got turfed out in the war and we were sent to a refugee camp, it was the only thing they had for us kids to watch. And when you've just lost your home, a story about heroic soldiers kicking the teeth of the bad guys leaves an impression on you. It's a scary thought, but that stupid vid might actually be the reason I ended up in the army.

Anyway, once I've cleaned up the disc a bit, do you want to take a look? It's not much, but it's one of the few childhood things I've got. I was hoping to share it with you.

Love, 
F.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Felix Iresso</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="575050" version="1065353216">A message from Tython</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="575050" version="1065353216">I got a call from Tython; not someone from the Council, a Master I didn't know. He asked me a bunch of questions, about us. About you. He was polite enough and friendly, and it didn't get too personal. It was just a strange experience overall. I knew the Jedi Council would be curious about us, but I've never actually been, you know, interrogated about someone I was involved with.

It wasn't all bad. Talking to him made me really look at myself and how I feel about you. And you know what? I love you. And I can explain exactly why because I had to answer a point-by-point questionnaire laying it out. Everything feels more true to me now: you and me, us, our future.

I just thought, maybe that's the point of asking stuff like this? The Jedi get their answers, I get to know this is real and not just a passing fling, all in one go. Very crafty. But I guess the Jedi Order's had thousands of years to get this right.

With love, 
F.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Nalen Raloch</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Doing better</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="575050" version="1065353216">I don't know how to begin this. But you could have finished me off and you didn't. That deserves something.

I'm still healing up (that feint of yours isn't bad, if you keep your elbow in it might work better), but I'll be back on my feet soon. Bashenn and First Matriarch Kolovish came from the village to see me. They brought the first ripe candleberries of the season. It seems like forever since I tasted any food.

I feel like I'm waking up from a bad dream. I'm still the same person who did those things. I haven't made sense of everything yet. But I'm alive, and sane. So thank you.

Nalen R.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="575050" version="1065353216">First Matriarch Kolovish</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Nalen Raloch</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="575050" version="1065353216">You are the one who ended Nalen Raloch's life. I do not fault you for it. I am the dweller at Kalikori's highest stair; I look down the thousand steps to the village, and I feel the suffering of my people. Nalen's was keenest. He suffered not only for what he had to be, but what he could not become. All my counsel could not ease his pain.

Nalen lives now only in legend, and the memories of those who knew him. But take lessons from his life and death. The demands made of Nalen were small compared to those of a Jedi, but never give in to despair and hopelessness. The higher path is always there.

--Kolovish of Kalikori</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Master Yuon Par</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Recovering well</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="575050" version="1065353216">My dear student-- 

My mind grows clearer by the day. Syo told me about your deeds on Coruscant; this shielding technique came at a great cost to you and the Noetikons. It is a precious gift, but so is your life. Be careful not to overstress yourself.

I write because I gathered a number of materials to assist your training on Tython. My illness--and your unique circumstances--meant that they went unused. I send them now in the hope that they will be of use to you or Qyzen. Remember: Completing the trials marks a waypoint on your journey as a Jedi, not the end.

I must rest. Please be safe. My thoughts go with you both. 

--Yuon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Laria Taphoni</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="575050" version="1065353216">A friend on Taris</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="575050" version="1065353216">We didn't have time to meet properly, but I'm Laria, I was part of Master Tykan's expedition out on Taris. You saved my life and I'm never going to forget it. Doctor Edaine kept sulking about his holocron data until he joined up with a Jedi survey team, now all he needs is another big find and he'll be fine. 

Me and Tal are still working on the Taris restoration effort. It's slow but Governor Saresh is pulling more strings in the Senate, we should get more support and military protection. It's all working out though. The other day we found this new plant species growing on one of the collapsed pillars. All these tiny little blue flowers from nowhere. We might bring this planet back after all. 

Best, 
Laria</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Doctor Gatten Edaine</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Medical research</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="575050" version="1065353216">I hope that droid gave me the right frequency. If this is the Jedi who helped recover a case of medical holocrons on Taris, I have the right person. 

I wanted you to know that Laria didn't perish in vain. I've submitted the holocrons for study, and we've already made a number of startling discoveries. As we suspected, the Jedi at the Taris enclave had an extensive medical library, including notes on the rakghoul plague and its origins. We may even be looking at vaccines for the Iridian Plague and Knytix Pox within a lifetime. Worth the cost, perhaps.

Regards,
Doctor G. Edaine
Olaris Reclamation Base Medical Staff</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="575050" version="1065353216">CAUTION: UNKNOWN SENDER</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Funny stuff</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Slicing a jedis account is easy. Red Light Lancers can't be stopped!!

All that guiding hand stuff seems weird now. Gues I was going through a phase or something. The Hutt Cartel's off our backs anyway. Theyre throwing a lot of credz around. Someone bought them off seems like?

Everyone knows the Lancers have a jedi and Theren Cedrac on their side now. No one messes with us, well be taking the Duros secter next!!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Vorlo Stragen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Friendship</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Our thanks again for delivering the criminal Duras Fain. The Hutt Cartel appreciates your commitment to law and order on Nar Shaddaa.

Speaking of, we've encountered some illegal communications traffic coming from in-system. It could be Imperial, though who can say. But since the Republic's so law-abiding, we've passed the messages on to your SIS to investigate.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Rowan Delk</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="575050" version="1065353216">I'm a free man!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="575050" version="1065353216">M'um m'aloo, Jedi! It looks like the rot's finally cleared out, and I'm breathing good again. I convinced She Who Must Be Obeyed to lay off the steam-mask and towels and sign my release out of here.

If you come by Anchorhead, don't try looking me up. Those hours flat on my back brought on some thinking, and I'm finally going to do it, I'm going to hike the Krayt's Jaw range west of the Dune Sea. I've been thinking about it since I was seventeen, and it's about blasted time I got out there. If anyone tries to slap a steam-mask on me in the meanwhile, they're getting a black eye.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Master Ges-Su-Kai</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Eriz Vossan's research</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Greetings. Master Syo assigned me to examine Master Eriz Vossan's discoveries on Tatooine. His condition appears stable, by the way.

Though his notes have incoherent lapses, Master Vossan seems to identify three intertwined factors to the Sand People's success. One: a simple, sustainable culture, with low reliance on technology. Two: a harsh environment requiring constant adaptation to survive. Both of which lead to, three: a society that requires the immediate removal of the weak and sick, anyone who might endanger the tribe's success.

Given Master Vossan's plague madness, I'm hesitant to accept his work at face value, but the Republic military has expressed an interest in my final conclusions. Regardless, Master Vossan's research has advanced our understanding of the Sand People by decades; thank you for preserving it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Semphi Talen (Coruscant Security)</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="575050" version="1065353216">House Ulgo's accounts</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="575050" version="1065353216">I've been investigating a break-in at the First Bank of Coruscant. We caught two individuals trying to crack a safety deposit box belonging to the Alderaanian noble house Ulgo. All Ulgo accounts at the First Bank have been frozen after pressure from Teral and Organa investors. These fellows said they were Ulgo cousins, trying to reclaim &quot;valuable family heirlooms.&quot;

It turns out that the deposit box contained items smuggled from the Mid Rim; the Ulgos were probably planning to sell them on the black market and start raising more supporters. Between Alderaan seceding and the houses' Republic ties, this is a huge legal gray area, so the Senate's authorized us to place the deposit box in Jedi custody, until the succession's decided. I contacted the Council for suggestions and your name came up. 

Off the record: I'm glad these people aren't my headache.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Fasha Teral-Organa</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="575050" version="1065353216">To Our Emissary</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="575050" version="1065353216">I must thank you again for all you've done for my family, and for Alderaan herself. My father is well, and attempts at peace continue, though the negotiations are long and involved. (When people can carry a grudge over who said what about someone's husband at a party fifty years ago, it slows things down.) Without interference from Master Sidonie, though, I'm confident that this civil war will end quickly, once Ulgo's teeth are finally pulled.

Last: I'm so sorry protocol meant there were no wedding invitations available for you and your friends. Lew and I missed you greatly. However, I did keep these small tokens from the Organa reception; please accept them with our very best wishes.

Fasha</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Master Jaric Kaedan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Casualty List</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="575050" version="1065353216">My condolences again on the loss of Master Yuon. Reports have come in regarding the Masters whom Vivicar also infected. Unfortunately we've confirmed that they did, in fact, perish when Vivicar died. 

Master Alyos Sek-Shele (conducting biological research on Herdessa)
Master Ebebdian (negotiator assigned to Quas Killam)
Master Ye Tantari (both Padawans currently unaccounted for)
Master Rhana Hyss (assignment classified by order of the Council)
Master Tarben Jenoquan (studying at the Place of Enlightenment Through Knowledge on Romossobar)
Master Ssusk Uru (battle instructor to troops on Sennatt)
Master Hakkun Re Hanuther (Tetan Royal Palace, advisor-in-residence)

Page 1/12</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Parkanas Tark</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Coming Home</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="575050" version="1065353216">I have seen the Jedi Temple under the light of dawn. I have smelled Tython's air.

The Jedi Council has sought me out. I have nothing to say to them. After Morrhage's endless rage, I want silence.

Morrhage was such an ancient soul. His hatred of the Jedi, and the healer who first defeated his plague, was like a dark sun inside him. That anger cast the entire Malachor system under its shadow. Mine was the smallest of echoes beside it. But even that was enough to condemn me.

Do not make my mistakes. Do not succumb to rage, or let yourself be blinded, trustingly, by the light.

I will be free of the past. I will find peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="575050" version="1065353216">The Office of the Balmorran President</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Notification of Passing</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="575050" version="1065353216">To all concerned: 

I regret to inform you of the death of RETHEUS GALTHE, former President and High Commander of Balmorra. Having established no sign of foul play, the former president will be interred with full honors at a time to be designated herewith. My thoughts are with his loved ones at this difficult time.

President Tai Cordan

(Addendum: They found Galthe this morning. It looks like he just died in his sleep. It's understandable after being tortured so badly, but I wonder if this was part of Darth Lachris's game plan. It seems like her style. --Tai.)</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="575050" version="1065353216">The Office of the Balmorran President</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Droid Progress</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="575050" version="1065353216">I wanted to update you on the progress of the Republic's new droid army while I have a minute. We've got 20,000 units currently in production; 10,000 will be ready for delivery by next week. After that, it's just a question of getting enough material through.

It'll go faster once we reclaim the factories from the Imperials, but our workers are pretty demoralized. Between Darth Lachris and what happened to President Galthe, our people will be hurting for a long time. We're making sure to publicize Republic victories--especially yours!--but it's slow going.

Galthe himself is doing better, by the way. He's able to ask for food and dress himself. Maybe there's hope?

Tai Cordan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Researcher Tsuusha</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Attis Station discoveries!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="575050" version="1065353216">To the Master Barsen'thor of the Jedi, 

It is with pride that I report the recovery of the Attis Station facility on Quesh after your noble rescue. Though we lament those who sank to the depths, we carry their memory with us.

Regarding our medical research: The applications of Quesh venom in regenerative stims and kolto packs have exceeded our expectations. I wanted to share the very best of our work with you: Please see the enclosed package. I hope it was stored correctly in transit. A paper concerning our research will appear in next month's Coruscant Medical Review, if you are interested.

With regards from the Attis Station team.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Researcher Tsuusha</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Attis Station discoveries!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="575050" version="1065353216">To the Master Barsen'thor of the Jedi, 

It is with pride that I report the recovery of the Attis Station facility on Quesh after your noble rescue. Though we lament those who sank to the depths, we carry their memory with us.

As promised, we have focused Attis Station's output on military applications and armaments. Progress has been slow, but seeing current events on the HoloNet, we believe you might need every advantage you can get. Therefore I've sent our best prototypes with this message. Feel free to field test them to your satisfaction.

With regards from the Attis Station team.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Lahanna Dask</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Captain Valon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Master Jedi, 

It has come to my attention that the fugitive and pirate known as Captain Valon has finally been apprehended, and that you were directly instrumental in his capture.

My son, Sergeant Marren Dask, volunteered to join the Rift Alliance coalition and was killed in action against Valon's forces. Though nothing can heal the loss of my son, the knowledge that his killer will be imprisoned for life is a great comfort to me.

As CEO of Belazura Sensor Technologies, I have made arrangements to donate a portion of my salary annually to the Jedi Order. May you continue to bring justice to those who cannot find it themselves, whatever their resources.

--L. Dask</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="328" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Captain Valon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Dead Imperials</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Hey, boss. I hired 15 more guys on my last trip to Port Nowhere and finished off a rival outfit. Life's good.

Last job we hit an Imperial trade convoy. We ran off a frigate and took the freighters just fine. Sample inventory's attached. Your Rift Alliance pals will soon be getting their first delivery. 

This is working out. I should get my tail kicked by Jedi more often.

Valon (Captain)</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Galactic News Network: News Flash</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="575050" version="1065353216">SITH ATTACK AT DERALIA, REPUBLIC INVESTIGATING</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Dramatic scenes unfolded today over Deralia, as Sith forces launched a daring attack against a Republic diplomatic vessel. Several Senators and diplomatic representatives were killed before a Jedi strike team was able to reach the stricken vessel, the Fortitude, and restore order.

In a time of rising tensions between the Republic and the Empire, does this suggest the Republic may have difficulties securing its borders? In an exclusive interview, Representative Alauni of Saleucami says yes. &quot;This attack demonstrates the continued incompetence of Republic patrols and the mindless bureaucrats who manage them,&quot; she said.

When asked for comment, Imperial Ambassador and Coruscant attache Sammel Yane released a short statement, claiming the Empire has no operations in the Tammuz Sector. Ambassador Yane added that the Empire &quot;cannot be held responsible for the activities of rogue elements.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Galactic News Network: News Flash</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="575050" version="1065353216">DIPLOMATIC VESSEL COLLIDES WITH OUTER RIM MOON</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="575050" version="1065353216">A dramatic standoff in the Outer Rim ended in catastrophe today, as a Republic capital ship, the Fortitude, collided with Deralia's moon Aderalis. Many residents of Deralia's northern hemisphere claim to have seen the impact, describing it as a &quot;white flash.&quot; 

Reports indicate the Fortitude, currently assigned as a diplomatic vessel, was damaged after an assault by Sith forces. Survivors of the attack were successfully evacuated before the collision.

&quot;But realistically, the real disaster is about six months away,&quot; claimed Professor Temzin Eph-Emmas, head of astrography at Arkania's Arca Jeth University. &quot;There's already evidence of significant changes in Aderalis's gravitic profile and orbital distance. The impact on Deralia's oceans is certainly going to be noticed.&quot; Professor Eph-Emmas intends to issue recommendations to Deralia's ruling council to begin evacuations of low-lying coastal cities such as Dajasufer and Izmalay's Landing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Master Rou Cheryen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="575050" version="1065353216">How did you do it??</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Months of work putting those Noetikons back together from fragments, with the very cream of the Exploration Corps engineers to help me out, and we could never get them to say a single word! Then Master Syo tells me you just walked into the archives and started chatting to them? How?

Not that it truly matters. The Noetikons are starting to reactivate on request--if it's a polite request--and we're attempting to conduct audiences with the ancient Masters. I had the pleasure of a brief conversation with Noab Hulis before the replacement energy grid went into flux; we're trying to speak to them only sparingly until the grid's stabilized.

Vandar Tokare's memoirs of the Mandalorian Wars. Tharis Orne's inspired lightsaber designs. The mnemonic battle verses of Bastila Shan. They're all here, waiting to be rediscovered in time. However you did it, thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Commander Arteles Kol</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Peculiar Imperial Activity on Hoth</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Greetings, Master Jedi. Our records state you were recently on Hoth, and I hoped to bring a recent incident to your attention. An Imperial patrol was sighted entering a cave where they camped overnight. When they left, they went right into the canyons--in full view of our snipers--and apparently started an excavation. The Imperials only became hostile when we tried to arrest them; one soldier commented that they appeared mentally unbalanced.

After we eliminated the Imperials, we investigated both the &quot;excavation site&quot; and the cave in question, but we found only fragmented items and some old statuary, as well as the Imperials' possessions. I've sent you what evidence I have in case you have any insight. If not, I thank you for your time.

Commander A. Kol
Aurek Base, Hoth</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="343" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Administrator Komi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="344" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Is this yours?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="345" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Hey. I wanted to say first, the Belsavis crew appreciates your help. Geland had it coming after what he did. Big time.
 
Anyway, someone left a package near our security tower. They're lucky we didn't just implode the thing as a security risk. But there was a datapad with your name. The message said &quot;The other is gone, and the voice is safe. But I must return to sleep for a time. These, I trust to Jedi hands. A friend.&quot;

Everything passed screening, so I figured I'd just send it along. Do you have any idea what this means? 

Administrator Komi
Belsavis Republic Base Alpha

Caution! All transmissions are monitored and may be deleted without notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="346" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Administrator Komi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="347" id2="575050" version="1065353216">We Appreciate It</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="348" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Hey, Jedi. We heard that Geland finally got what was coming to him. Everyone on the Belsavis crew's going to lift a glass for you when the rioting dies down. That might not be for a while, though. We're finally getting control of some sectors, but it's rough out there.

The other problem is those gray aliens, the Eshukar or whatever they call themselves. We're getting reports that there's way, way more than we thought. A lot of them are even slipping past our patrols--those ones don't seem violent, but who knows what they're up to in the jungle?

But for now, we're on top of things and it's partly thanks to you. Take care of yourself out there!

Administrator Komi
Belsavis Republic Base Alpha

Caution! All transmissions are monitored and may be deleted without notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="349" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Lefry Kaonai</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="350" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Back to civilization</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="351" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Do you remember me? Lefry, from Doctor Kerrian's expedition on Voss? I suppose you wouldn't. I looked you up when I finally got home and wow! If I'd known who you were when we met, I'd have been more scared of you than the woods! (Maybe. Probably not.)

At least I got to salvage some of poor Doctor Kerrian's work. I'm back at the university on Rendili putting it all together. Did you know the ancient Voss may have actually invented a primitive form of energy manipulation using polished crystalline mirrors? It's true! I'm going to try recreating the apparatus for my thesis. I'm sure you'll want to see it when it's done!

Lefry</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="352" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Koten-Su</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="353" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Found</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="354" id2="575050" version="1065353216">A man wandered Voss-Ka. He stank of the Nightmare Lands. We took him away.

We sought answers. He screamed of horrors. Among them, your name. Therefore we speak to you of what is yours.

The healers came. He was sent deep into the shrine. His belongings, abandoned. We know no more.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="355" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Master Satele Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="356" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Syo Bakarn's final request</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="357" id2="575050" version="1065353216">I wanted you to know that the body of Master Syo Bakarn has been reclaimed from Corellia. According to his wishes, he was cremated at the temple without a ceremony, and the ashes scattered from the ancient Forge. Our search for the Children of the Emperor is already beginning; Syo's death will not be in vain.

Syo's standing request was that his possessions at the temple be passed on to you, and I have enclosed them with this message. I recognize some of them from our battles together, during the Great War. Syo's life always revolved around his colleagues: Bela Kiwiiks, Aryn Leneer, Jaric Kaedan, myself--and you, of course. I am glad to do him this last, small favor. 

--Master Satele</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="358" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Syo Bakarn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="359" id2="575050" version="1065353216">A Sanctuary</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="360" id2="575050" version="1065353216">The Council has found a place for me. I cannot say where, but trust that I am far from anyone I could possibly harm. I have my books and my thoughts. I am trying to study my condition from within. What strange places we come to.

I am doing my best to pinpoint the other Children of the Emperor on the Council's behalf. Besides keeping the First Son contained, it is the most difficult task of my life. There are so many. Most of them are unaware of the darkness within them, as I was. We must see if anything can be done. I know how it feels to have the Emperor's power grasping your mind, after all. I can show them that there is hope.

It saddens me that this will probably be my last message to you, but I hope you will understand--it is your understanding, after all, that saved me. I have asked that Satele keep me apprised of your career. We both have work ahead of us.

I am pleased to sign this with my true name:
Syo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="361" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Tai Cordan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="362" id2="575050" version="1065353216">On the State of Balmorra</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="363" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Barsen'thor,

I wish I could report that Balmorra is a haven; that the Empire has been sent packing and that the people are free to get back to living their lives. Sadly, I can't.

That said, there have been improvements, and some level of normalcy has been restored. Whole sectors are actually at peace, where factories have sputtered back to life as the efforts to rebuild continue.

It hasn't been easy. But every day I think of how hard you fought to help restore our government. I think about the stories I've heard of all you've done to help the people of Corellia and Makeb and on and on, and it pushes me to keep trudging forward, no matter how strong the headwinds.

We're landing on Manaan now to negotiate kolto rates. I'd ask you to wish me luck, but it took way more than that just to get a Selkath to talk to me! Be well, my friend. 

Tai Cordan
President of Balmorra</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="364" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Tai Cordan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="365" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Manaan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="366" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Barsen'thor,

Last time I wrote, I was landing on Manaan for my first meeting with the Selkath. I have to say, I was impressed by their Kolto Trade League's tenacity and intellect. After the drudgery of our protracted war, I can appreciate their isolationist stance--though I assure you Balmorra would never adopt such a policy.

I have remained in close contact with the Trade League, and they happened to mention your recent visits. Not knowing your agenda there, the citizens of Manaan seem at once honored and concerned that you have taken an interest in their planet. The leadership is consulting with something called the Order of Shasa to decide what to make of the whole thing. I wouldn't be surprised if you heard from Shuuru, either.

I told them that they should, of course, be honored; and that they should rest assured that you do not pose a threat to their way of life. I'm unsure if my diplomacy has had any effect, but they appear to like and respect me, so I hope it helps.

Tai Cordan
President of Balmorra</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="367" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Office of the Supreme Chancellor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="368" id2="575050" version="1065353216">On recent events</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="369" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Barsen'thor,

I am pleased to inform you that the Republic's relationship with the Rift Alliance continues apace. There was a setback for a short time when Shuuru claimed you were somehow involved in the collapse of a major undersea facility of some sort on Manaan. Naturally, when asked if our people could mount a thorough investigation of the facility to determine cause, he retracted his official complaint.

I was saddened to hear of the death of Colonel Darok. I knew the man well. Decisive, courageous, and quite smart. I know you worked with him on Korriban to send a bold message to the Empire. I am sure his loss is felt by you as well.

We should meet sometime. The Republic is strong, but there is always more that can be done to bolster our position even more. I would love to hear what you would have to say about it.

Leontyne Saresh
Supreme Chancellor of the Galactic Republic</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="370" id2="575050" version="1065353216">Gaden-Ko</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="371" id2="575050" version="1065353216">I saw you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="372" id2="575050" version="1065353216">I was reaching out. You were on a beautiful world. Late in the day. You were at a fire. You were at peace.

Then darkness fell. All the worlds trembled. I do not recall beyond that.

The Three say my mind lashed out. Say I shook the other Mystics. Say I went faint but was fine now.

I am not fine now. I am concerned. For you. For what is coming.

Tread with care.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
