<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>123</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/jedi_knight.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Kira Carsen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Juicy gossip</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Just overheard the wildest rumor about Master Satele and had to share. Did you know some people think she had a kid? I am NOT making this up. There are people who actually believe the Grand Master of the entire Jedi Order completely broke the rules and &quot;formed an attachment.&quot; There are all these wild conspiracy theories, too--it was a boy, he was raised in secret by one of her old teachers and now he's an SIS agent. Ridiculous, right?

On the other hand, if you and I ever get caught, maybe Master Satele will go easy on us.

--K</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Kira Carsen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Close call</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Some Master on Tython contacted me yesterday about moving back there to train Padawans. Apparently, that's something we're supposed to do after every few months spent fighting galactic wars. Who knew, right? I notice nobody's calling YOU about this stuff, so I suspect this has more to do with my past than any actual rules.

Anyway, I told the Master we were on a top secret mission and I wasn't available. But if he calls back and asks me again, I'll need to get more creative in my excuses. Sometimes I worry what'll happen to us when this war ends.

--K</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Kira Carsen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Robes</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Just came across an old security cam holo-image of us taken when we first teamed up on Coruscant. All I'm going to say is, Jedi robes are NOT flattering. My rear end looks like a Dantooinian sphere-fruit in that thing. You actually look pretty good, though. You always have.

I never told you, but I was already falling for you even then. Bad Jedi, I know. Never would've thought we had a chance, but that's me--Little Mistress Pessimist. Sometimes it's nice being wrong.

Looking forward to some alone time. Think there's any way we can convince the others to spend the night planetside for a change?

--K</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Doc</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Extra crew quarters</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="575048" version="1065353216">I know a guy on Nar Shaddaa who refits used space station escape pods into tugboats used for extra crew quarters on regular starships. They're detachable compartments, like hoverbike sidecars. I was thinking we should buy a couple and stick them to our hull. Don't you think Kira and the others would be a lot more comfortable not intruding on our love nest? Also, Rusk has this bad habit of sleepwalking. I caught him cleaning his blasters in the middle of the night with his eyes closed. That can't be healthy.

Think about it.

Love,
Me</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Doc</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Healthy teeth</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Just wanted you to know I deliberately left that piece of chasuka greens stuck in my teeth the other day. I realized when I was in the refresher later that I never told you about my stint practicing orthodontia on Rodia. Turns out one of the best ways to strengthen your teeth is by leaving a little bit of food in there. It stretches the gums and gives the teeth room to build enamel. Never forget Doc's taking care of himself.

Love,
Me

P.S. It only works for men, by the way. You should never try it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Doc</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Date night</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="575048" version="1065353216">I was just thinking how most of our time together involves combat zones and people shooting at us. I'm not saying that isn't fun, but Doc's a man who likes variety. I know some great restaurants on Ralltiir and Nar Shaddaa we could visit. There's also a great day spa on Ord Mantell, assuming it didn't get blown up during the Separatist War. I'm sure the Jedi Order can afford to give you a day off. It's not like they pay you.

Consider yourself reserved, beautiful.

Love,
Me</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Vistis</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Touching Base</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Hey there. Just wanted to thank you again for cutting me loose on Coruscant. Never would have taken the job if I knew I was stealing top secret military files. 

Just so you know, I didn't stick around. Hopped a shuttle to Nar Shaddaa and got myself a sweet new gig. I'll spare you the details, but I'm rolling in credits now. So, uh... just in case we ever cross paths again, here's a little &quot;contribution&quot; to the Jedi Order. Call it services rendered plus future considerations, if you catch my drift.

Vistis</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Coruscant Security Special Investigation Panel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Case File #1142-235-3721</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="575048" version="1065353216">An investigation into the above referenced case file, re: the wanted felon going by the street name &quot;Vistis,&quot; revealed evidence to indicate the subject was legally terminated by a member of the Jedi Order pursuing official Republic business, specifically the search for stolen top secret military research files. 

Given your recent activities on Coruscant, the investigatory panel has determined you to be the most likely individual responsible. As a result of your actions, the panel has deemed you eligible for the reward that was offered for the arrest of the above referenced criminal.

Thank you for your service.
Coruscant Security</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Doctor Godera</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Gratitude Long Overdue</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="575048" version="1065353216">When we last met, I was in a foul mood; being captured by Imperials has that effect. Now that I am more myself, I realize I never properly thanked you for saving me from Watcher One on Taris. I know Jedi do not seek such praise, but I owe you my life.

The Republic is starting to realize the true nature of our great enemy. The Senate is finally willing to do what we should have done many years ago, and I am ready to do my part. 

Without your help, none of this would have been possible. For this, you have my thanks.

Doctor Godera</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Watcher One</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="575048" version="1065353216">A New Life</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="575048" version="1065353216">I still don't understand why you spared me on Taris, but I have not betrayed your trust. I have taken a new name and created a new life for myself in the Republic. The skills of my former profession have proven quite useful in the corporate world, and to my surprise, I find my new life as compelling as my old.

This message is the last time I will ever use my old name: one final act of gratitude before Watcher One disappears forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="575048" version="1065353216">SIS Official Dispatch</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Commendation</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Field reports indicate Watcher One, a key member of Imperial Intelligence, has been neutralized by your hand on Taris. Though no recognition of this mission can be made publicly, the SIS appreciates and recognizes your efforts.

End Dispatch</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Lord Nefarid</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="575048" version="1065353216">A Job Well Done</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Congratulations on ending Lord Sadic's wretched existence on Nar Shaddaa--one less rival standing between me and Darth Angral's favor. I guess I owe you for that, and I always pay my debts.

Sadic was a fool to challenge you head-on. If our paths happen to cross, I don't intend to make the same mistake. Watch your back, Jedi!

Lord Nefarid</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Agent Galen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Status Update</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="575048" version="1065353216">When I left Nar Shaddaa, I wanted to die. I couldn't live with what Lord Sadic turned me into. But you refused to let me give up. 

Because of you, I've fought to come to terms with what I am. With the help of the SIS, I've learned to control my implants and bear the pain of my transformation. They're sending me on a special assignment deep behind Imperial lines, one specifically suited for someone with my &quot;affliction.&quot; 

I might not survive, but at least I'll strike one more blow against the Empire. You've given my life meaning again. Thank you.

Galen</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Special Agent Tander</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Status Update</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Something you might be interested in. Unofficially, of course.

SIS recovered the body of Agent Galen on Nar Shaddaa. What Lord Sadic did to him was horrible; he was more machine than man in the end. But by studying his remains, we've learned a lot about cybernetics  and the Power Guard Project. Stuff we can use against the Empire. Galen may be gone, but at least his death had some meaning.

S.A. Tander</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Lord Praven</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="575048" version="1065353216">A New Path</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Everything I believed about the Jedi was wrong. After you defeated me on Tatooine, I surrendered myself to your order as I promised, still not certain they would take me in. Yet they did, and I have begun my training as a servant of the light side of the Force.

I have cast aside the trappings of my Sith past, and been reborn as a Jedi Padawan. I cannot undo the horrors I unleashed on the innocent, but going forward, I swear to devote myself to halting the spread of darkness.

Your humble servant, 
Praven</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Fir Megsan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Lord Praven</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Heard through the grapevine that you fought and killed Lord Praven on Tatooine. Guess that makes me your new biggest fan, even though we never met.

My father was a Republic soldier; Lord Praven killed him during the Sacking of Coruscant. For years I had a bounty on that Sith scum's head, but everyone who tried to collect caught a serious case of corpse. Glad to see someone finally took that pompous butcher down.

Enjoy your reward. You earned it.

Fir</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Duke Horis Thul</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Aleyna Hark</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Congratulations on stopping Lord Nefarid, for both our sakes. The would-be assassin Aleyna Hark is still in my custody on Alderaan; despite all she's done, I'll honor my promise to you and keep her alive. Turns out she's more than happy to spill her guts over everything she knows about the Sith and the Empire. Her intel has been quite revealing--I've discovered she's not the only spy in my house.

I owe you my life, and House Thul does not forget its friends.

Stand. Endure. Prevail.

Duke Horis Thul</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Duke Horis Thul</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Lord Nefarid</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Congratulations on stopping Lord Nefarid, for both our sakes. Alderaan is in your debt, and I owe you my life. House Thul does not forget its friends.

I never thought I would have more in common with a Jedi than a Sith, but when you urged me to end the life of that traitorous spy Aleyna Hark as she lay unconscious at our feet, I realized we were cut from the same cloth.

Stand. Endure. Prevail.

Duke Horis Thul</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Captain Dal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Our &quot;Deal&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="575048" version="1065353216">I've been thinking a lot about those possible survivors on Uphrades, trapped on that world by Darth Angral's superweapon. It keeps me up at night. But there's nothing we could have done to help them, right? I know that. I hope you know that, too. 

We're not bad people. We're just realists. But just in case you're having second thoughts about leaving them behind, I figure it can't hurt to remind you we're both responsible. Wouldn't want an inquiry that makes us both look bad, right?

Captain Dal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Doctor Senessa</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="575048" version="1065353216">News from Uphrades</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="575048" version="1065353216">I would have sent this earlier, but we just now got communications back up; Uphrades is still suffering the effects of Darth Angral's superweapon. It's going to take some time before we can leave the surface, but we've stabilized the situation.

Turns out we were right--there were survivors on Uphrades! They were in rough shape, but most of them are going to make it thanks to the medical supplies on our ship. If you hadn't stepped in with Captain Dal, we might never have touched down to help; hundreds of people owe you their lives.

Sincerely, 
Doctor Senessa</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Colonel Finley</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Madel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Good call on taking that Imperial spy on Balmorra into Republic custody. Madel's been very, very helpful in providing information about the Empire and their activities in the area. Guess she wants to stay in our good books so we don't turn her over to the resistance. Smart girl.

Thanks to her info, we intercepted an Imperial shipment heading offworld. Found some stuff you might be interested in. Figured it's only fair, since you sent her our way.

Colonel Finley</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Madel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="575048" version="1065353216">A New Life</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="575048" version="1065353216">You saved my life on Balmorra. Nikollan would have killed me for betraying the resistance, even though I had no choice. I'm safely off Balmorra now and I'm not ever going back. The Republic has helped me start a new life. 

Colonel Finley warned me not to contact anyone from my past in case the resistance tries to find me, but I had to write you one last time. You gave me a second chance.

I know you don't want it, but I sent you something. Just take it. It'll make me feel better. Say &quot;hi&quot; to Doc for me.

Madel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="575048" version="1065353216">The Balmorran Resistance</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Madel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="575048" version="1065353216">The Balmorran resistance recognizes your service in surrendering Madel, a suspected traitor and spy, into our hands. I am happy to inform you that she was given a fair trial and convicted of treason against Balmorra, then executed for her crimes.

The goals of the Republic and the resistance are not always the same, even though we share a common enemy. However, we believe we must reward those actions that support our cause. Please accept this payment for helping to expose a spy in our midst.

The Balmorran Resistance</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Sajar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="575048" version="1065353216">A Second Chance</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="575048" version="1065353216">My fellow Jedi, 

After my fall to the dark side on Quesh, I once again find myself training on Tython to learn the ways of the Jedi, as you instructed. The Masters here accept and understand what I did. They do not condone it, but neither do they condemn it. They have taught me that guilt and remorse will only cause me to falter yet again; only through peace can I find the truth of what I must seek.

I walk a long and difficult path, but I welcome the journey. And I thank you for setting me on it.

May the Force be with you.
Sajar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="328" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Sajar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Silence and Secrets</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="575048" version="1065353216">My fellow Jedi, 

I have thought long and hard about what I did on Quesh, and I am even more convinced you were right to cover up my role in killing the Imperial prisoners. No good can come of telling Master Braga or the Council of my slip back to the dark side. The past cannot be undone, and I must focus on the future. We are at war with the Empire; death and slaughter are inevitable. You understand that; many of our fellow Jedi do not.

This is a difficult burden to bear, but it is made easier by the knowledge that I am not alone in how I feel.

May the Force be with you.

Sajar</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Pak Taldine</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="575048" version="1065353216">It's Official!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Good news from the Belsavis prison--Colonel Bartaph found a note from the old warden backing my story. She figured if he trusted me enough to make me an honorary guard despite my past crimes, she could do the same. Now I'm part of the Belsavis staff. She got me a uniform and everything!

Lucky for me you were there. She was just about to throw me in with the rest of the prisoners. Don't think I would've lasted too long.

Thanks for having my back.

Pak</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Colonel Bartaph</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Pak Taldine</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="575048" version="1065353216">I thought you might be interested to know that Pak Taldine is dead. He was killed by his fellow prisoners on Belsavis shortly after we returned him to the general population as you instructed. Identifying those responsible for his murder will be difficult; based on his reputation, there is no shortage of suspects. But I shed no tears for Pak Taldine--his past crimes proved him to be nothing but vile scum, and I believe justice has been served.

Colonel Bartaph</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Valen-Da</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Tala-Reh</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Outsiders rarely understand the Mystics. Tala-Reh's sacrifice was necessary. Tala-Reh did what was foreseen, as did you. You did not interfere; the vision is fulfilled. Yet there are other visions. Beyond Voss, we Mystics see little. Your destiny is too bright to ignore. Do what you must, outsider. Fulfill the vision. Remember Tala-Reh.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="575048" version="1065353216">The Three</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Valen-Da</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Voss mourns the death of the Mystic Valen-Da. This was not foreseen by the Three. The death of a Mystic must have purpose. It must fulfill a vision. Valen-Da's fate must now fall to another. This will not be forgotten, outsider. But in our visions, we have seen your fate. It looms near, and we must not interfere.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="343" id2="575048" version="1065353216">General Var Suthra</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="344" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Empire on the Run</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="345" id2="575048" version="1065353216">The battle for Corellia is all but over--the Empire doesn't have anyone who can stand up to the skill and courage of the Jedi troops you left in my charge. Even the Sith are running like cowards.

I don't know what your next mission holds. I'm just an old soldier who lacks the wisdom of you Jedi types. But even if I can't be there with you, I can still help out. We captured a lot of equipment and supplies from the Imperials. You might as well put it to good use.

General Var Suthra</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="346" id2="575048" version="1065353216">General Garza</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="347" id2="575048" version="1065353216">General Var Suthra</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="348" id2="575048" version="1065353216">General Var Suthra was laid to rest today with full military honors. I knew him for many years, and I could tell he thought very highly of you. There was a time when he had his reservations regarding the Jedi Order--most military personnel do. Yet you overcame this reservation, and he considered it an honor to serve with you.

In cataloging his personal effects, I came across something he would have wanted you to have. I know Jedi aren't supposed to have emotional attachments, but he considered you a friend. I hope you felt the same.

General Garza</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="349" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Ranna Tao'Ven</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="350" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Farewell</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="351" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Master Jedi, 

I was told you left Tython on an important mission. I'm sorry I could not bid you farewell personally, but please know that I have not wasted the second chance you gave me. Your fellow Jedi have been as compassionate to me as you were. They are helping me guide my fellow Pilgrims toward greater harmony with the order.

My offense to you and Master Orgus can never be forgiven, but I can at least ensure future Matriarchs do not make the same mistakes I did. Thank you for that chance.

Honor and respect,
Ranna Tao'Ven</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="352" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Warden Derrin Weller</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="353" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Report on Tython's Twi'lek Pilgrim population</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="354" id2="575048" version="1065353216">I have completed an investigation into the Twi'lek Pilgrims and their corrupt leaders who collaborated with the rogue Jedi Bengal Morr. After a brief period of governmental chaos following their former Matriarch's abrupt resignation, the Pilgrims' new leader appears willing to accept Jedi law and extend us their full cooperation. The order thanks you for your help resolving this situation favorably.

Master Satele wished me to forward you some gear she feels will be useful on your present mission. I trust it reaches you safely.

May the Force be with you,
Derrin Weller</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="355" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Ranna Tao'Ven</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="356" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Atonement</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="357" id2="575048" version="1065353216">I know you wished no further contact with me, but I felt it was important you understand that I am doing everything possible to honor the second chance I and my people were given. Our betrayal of you and Master Orgus can never be forgiven, but I am determined to guide my people toward greater understanding of and cooperation with the Jedi Order. Our future on Tython depends on it, and I am determined not to fail.

Please accept the attached display of our sincerity and commitment to peace with your people.

Ranna Tao'Ven, Pilgrim Matriarch</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="358" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Warden Derrin Weller</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="359" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Report on Tython's Twi'lek Pilgrim population</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="360" id2="575048" version="1065353216">I have completed an investigation into the Twi'lek Pilgrims and their corrupt leaders who collaborated with the rogue Jedi Bengal Morr. The Pilgrims have elected a new Matriarch to replace the one murdered by Flesh Raiders, and she is proving far more cooperative with us. I am uncertain exactly what motivated this abrupt change of attitude, but indications are your interactions with them were the deciding motivator. Well done.

Master Satele wished me to forward you some gear she feels will be useful on your present mission. I trust it reaches you safely.

May the Force be with you,
Derrin Weller</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="361" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Grand Master Satele Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="362" id2="575048" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="363" id2="575048" version="1065353216">As I feared, the Emperor's death has intensified the war by setting the enemy against itself with the remaining Sith vying for power. Now more than ever, the galaxy requires your courage and clear-mindedness to survive the coming battles.

I did not realize until composing this message how much I've come to rely upon you. Time and again you've proven yourself against impossible odds, and I can no longer imagine a Jedi Order without you in it.

Let us hope this war ends soon and our people return to our true mission: safeguarding the peace.

--Master Satele</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="364" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Supreme Chancellor Saresh</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="365" id2="575048" version="1065353216">With gratitude to a true patriot</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="366" id2="575048" version="1065353216">General, 

I regret not being present to celebrate your triumph over the Sith Emperor, but words cannot express my admiration for your accomplishment. It is my fervent hope destroying the enemy's vile leader will drive the Sith to extinction.

Though it would only endanger your future missions if we revealed your identity to the galaxy at large, know that you are regarded as one of the greatest heroes in our grand Republic's history. Let us now win this war and eradicate our enemies forever. Only then will peace be ours.

Sincerely,
Supreme Chancellor Leontyne Saresh of the Galactic Republic</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="373" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Satele Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="374" id2="575048" version="1065353216">The road ahead</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="375" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Every Jedi matters, but losing a member of the Jedi Council is especially hard.

In the Empire's despicable attack on our home, Master Oric Traless took his last breath. He is one with the Force now, and lives through us and our deeds. His defiance in the face of evil will never be forgotten.

I wish I had been there, as I am sure you do, but we cannot allow ourselves to become mired in regret. We must continue to strive for peace, both inward and out, and we must remain headstrong in our service to the Galactic Republic.

May the Force be with you. 

--Master Satele</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="376" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Satele Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="377" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Temple improvements</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="378" id2="575048" version="1065353216">If I haven't said so before: Thank you for your reclamation of the Jedi Temple from Imperial forces. You and Colonel Darok are to be commended for your swift action and unfaltering resolve.

Unsettling as the Empire's brief occupation was, what we've learned from the attack has allowed us to restore the temple with greater security than ever before. Should the enemy even reach the surface of Tython, they will have to contend with enhanced scanner arrays, slicer-proof turrets and reinforced blast doors. This will help prevent large-scale attacks as well as more subtle infiltrations, so items like the Rakata artifact that went missing during the recent commotion remain in our possession.

I have to go now. There is a faint yet growing disturbance in the Force I need to look into. If you happen to sense anything out of the ordinary, I hope you'll let me know. May the Force be with you.

--Master Satele</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="379" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Master Aharo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="380" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Without end?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="381" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Hero of Tython, I greet you.

I remain on Corellia. We fight the good fight, but it seems we cannot ever truly rid this world of the Empire's presence.

Sometimes I grow tired of it all. I did not choose the path of a Jedi to become embroiled in relentless combat. But I must endure, so I find remote spots to meditate whenever I can.

On a recent reprieve, I happened across a group of Republic and Imperial officers meeting in secret. They were making plans to abandon the theater of war and crash their war vessels into their own fleets' unsuspecting flagships. Something about internal discord and remapping hyperlanes. When I confronted the group, they activated their detonators. I could not stop them.

They chose the surety of death over the uncertain chaos of continued hostilities. But why did they feel the need to act in concert? Strange and unsettling, the ways in which war can alter one's perspective. I hope this conflict ends, and soon.

May the Force be with you.

--Unaw Aharo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="382" id2="575048" version="1065353216">Reiyo Barnes</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="383" id2="575048" version="1065353216">My thanks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="384" id2="575048" version="1065353216">I've been waiting in line to use this public terminal. The whole time I thought about what to write.

I was born here. Never left. Had multiple chances, even after me and my family lost our home in the Ravager Raids of my youth. We lost everything then, ended up living in the slums. It was terrifying for a while, but eventually it wasn't anymore.

I'm the only one in my family the fever didn't take. When I think of them, I don't picture them in our old house. I picture them at home--the home you helped.

You are far and away the kindest pirate I have ever met. It's hard to believe you're actually a cannibal. Thank you so much.

Reiyo</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
