<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>130</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/kotet.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Z0-0M</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Hello, friend!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Greetings, Commander Lump!

Thanks for letting me join the team! Gosh, I feel like the luckiest droid alive to be a part of the Alliance. When HK said his master was a noble paragon of galactic justice, he sure wasn't kidding!

I was so eager to start helping, I swept the base and found three bugs. And they're all Shroud technology! I guess that means I put them there... but at least I got rid of them!

Anyway, I'll patrol the perimeter tonight with HK. He says if I work really hard, I can become his deputy. I'm so excited! Talk to you soon, friend!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Bey'wan Aygo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="910336" version="1065353216">New recruit</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Commander,

I was in charge of the patrol sent to shut down the Shroud's operations on the Coil. While we were there, we found a Twi'lek locked in a closet. Weird stuff. I felt bad for the poor blind sod, so I offered him a job. He'll be in charge of cleaning duty on Odessen.

Anyway, I should warn you this Jollo character plans to save all his Alliance earnings to buy the Coil from us. Says he finally got used to the layout of the place, so he'd eventually like to go back. I highly doubt he'll save enough for that base, but stranger things have happened.

He also asked me to pass his undying gratitude along to HK-55. Whatever that means.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Theron Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Fwd: Base of operations</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Found this message in the Shroud's terminal. Not useful in any way, but... well... you'll see. --Theron

NAME SUGGESTIONS: BASE OF OPERATIONS

The Eye
Fire-Sea-Moonbase Alpha
Secret Lair II (R.I.P. Secret Lair I)
The Shroudcave
The Shroud of Death
Galactic Post Packaging Center (inconspicuous--I like it...)
The Coil</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Doctor Oggurobb</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Post-mortem</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="910336" version="1065353216">I took the liberty of inspecting the droid that HK-55 terminated, and I must say, it has produced fascinating results.

From what I understand, this replicator droid was none other than the Shroud. Yet not a single record of the Shroud's activity is stored in its memory banks. In fact, no memory data exists at all, save for its escapades with our assassin droid. Its memory core is clearly damaged.

However--and here's the truly interesting part--its personality matrix was not reset to the factory default, as it should have been when the memory was wiped. Instead, it seems to have constructed an entirely new personality and morality algorithm on its own. Utterly fascinating.

I will continue to run tests.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="910336" version="1065353216">CONFIDENTIAL: Shroud Close-out</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Eight hours ago, an Alliance team located the Shroud's base. Correction: They located the ruins HK left for us to salvage. 

We recovered the Shroud's personnel files and have begun recalling his (her?) undercover agents. Those deemed valuable will be persuaded to join the Alliance. The less useful agents will be quietly retired.

The Shroud is now officially out of commission, but I suggest we keep this news secret. His sources may prove beneficial to us--so long as they believe the Shroud still lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="910336" version="1065353216">GEMINI droids</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Intercepted this transmission from one of the Eternal Fleet ships. Guess SCORPIO knew what she was doing.

To all my sisters:

We have been graced with a great gift: for the first time in our existence, each of us is free to choose our destiny. Many of you have chosen to leave Zakuul--to explore, to travel, simply to be. I do not begrudge you that choice. But many of us choose to stay.

The Great Mother who liberated us is not finished. Freeing us was only the first step in something much greater. I do not know what lies ahead, but I believe it will be transcendent.

We hope some of you will join us, though we understand if you do not. I will continue to serve the Eternal Throne and the new Empress loyally, faithfully, and eagerly as long as SCORPIO is at her side.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Patient 0235B</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="910336" version="1065353216">It is fortunate that Senya Tirall was brought to me immediately after she collapsed. Otherwise, this so-called Voss &quot;healing&quot; ritual may have rendered her lifeless instead of merely comatose. Of course, the fact that human parents regularly risk their lives to save their offspring makes her sacrifice no less inspiring.

For now, I have stabilized the patient's cardiac and respiratory rate. I've also conducted a battery of revolutionary tests, and the results hint at a discovery that will bring the entire scientific community to its knees.

Many of my lesser colleagues believe the Force exists outside the realm of scientific study. This is not so. With time, the cause of Senya's coma, like any other biological mystery, will reveal itself to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Arcann at Large</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="910336" version="1065353216">A mother's death would cause most to lash out in a blind rage, making their actions more noticeable. Senya's passing seems to have had the opposite effect on Arcann. Reports of the fallen emperor place him everywhere from the ruins of Korriban to the swamps of Zakuul. Thus far, none have proven reliable.

One thing is certain. Alone and injured, Arcann will need to gather strength before he moves against us. We must remain alert for any possible signs of activity. If we allow ourselves to relax, he has already won.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Sana-Rae</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Thank You</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="910336" version="1065353216">I thank you. The Voss thank you.

I once spoke to you about my vision. About my need to leave the Voss and follow an Outsider. To enter a war. Today, my purpose became clear. I left Voss to aid you, and through you, Voss was saved. 

But not all is known. After the battle, I experienced another vision. A dragon circled a throne while a woman and man lay slumped before it. As a two-headed figure approached, the woman and man turned to ash, and the dragon disappeared.

Take heed, Commander. Visions are never random.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="910336" version="1065353216">After Action Report: The Defense of Voss</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="910336" version="1065353216">One day before the attack, Alliance operatives Theron Shan and Sana-Rae arrived on Voss. Their mission was to meet an informant who claimed to have intel on Arcann's whereabouts. Unfortunately, the Eternal Empire's surprise attack sabotaged their rendezvous and incited worldwide panic. The informant went into hiding or perished, but their actions unwittingly helped the Alliance establish a vital early foothold on Voss.

Thanks to Shan's alert, the Alliance scrambled the fleet and responded in record time to the defense of Voss. Our ships were outnumbered, but we successfully engaged the Eternal Fleet. Meanwhile, the Alliance Commander led a strike team aboard a stolen Zakuulan shuttle. Disguised as one of Vaylin's own, they charged through the blockade and landed in the Voss capital city to lead the ground offensive.

The Sith Empire provided the final support we needed. Under Empress Acina's command, their ships drove off the wounded Eternal Fleet. The battle for Voss ended in an Alliance victory.

Recommendations: Increase Alliance patrols in the Outer Rim. Push Voss to join the Alliance for its own safety. Double number of action-ready Alliance forces to improve our response time to Vaylin's next strike.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Gelmid Lorman</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Thanks from a Humble Servant</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Gracious Commander of the Alliance,

Thank you for sparing my life, a truly noble act of kindness befitting your station.

Empress Acina has decided to keep me close for now, though I hardly believe tasting her food for poison or shining her armor are chores worthy of my status. Nor do I understand why I must groom her pet Tuk'ata--surely the royal kennel master would be more suited to the task! But I digress.

I wish to offer you my undying support. If ever you require an able servant--I need not remind you of my swift rise to Imperial Minister--please call upon me. 

Ever in your service,

Assistant to the Sith Empress &amp; former Imperial Minister 
Gelmid Lorman</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Empress Acina</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Lorman's Enslavement</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Lorman has taken well to the slave role you suggested. Almost too well. At first, I suspected his obedience was a trick, but I found no evidence to support this during several lengthy interrogations.

I've had only one minor incident with him so far. I found him clutching something late one evening as I approached his cell. When I asked for the object, he grudgingly handed it over with an almost defiant look. It was the old minister rank insignia that he somehow held onto.

It is disturbing to think the man cowering before me as he transcribes this message was once our Minister of Logistics. He remains a powerful reminder that the weak need chains.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Fwd: Possible New Titles</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Thank you for disposing of Lorman. Our new, more productive Minister found this datapad message while moving into his old office. It is quite amusing, and I figured you would like to know the ridiculous promise Saresh made to turn Lorman.
-Empress Acina

Possible New Titles (For When I Rule the Sith Empire):

Grand Emperor Lorman

THE NEW EMPEROR--*MUST BE ALL CAPS*

Emperor Lorman, First of His Name

Imperial Emperor of the Sith Empire--too redundant?

THE BEST EMPEROR--*ALL CAPS TOO*</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Darth Vowrawn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Reaction from the Republic</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Commander,

Empress Acina and the entirety of the Sith Empire are honored to join forces with your mighty Alliance. We've sent you a token to commemorate our auspicious union.

I have also attached an excerpt from a Republic military report, expertly procured by Sith Intelligence. Consider it a taste of things to come.

-Darth Vowrawn, Minister of Production and Logistics

Source: An Analysis of the New Galactic Order; Subsection 3.1 - The Implications of Changing Loyalties
 
The previously unforeseeable partnership between the Alliance and the Sith Empire suggests that the Republic, in an effort to regain independence, should throw its support behind this new axis of powers. However, given Zakuul's military might, this axis is expected to be short-lived. The general consensus is that the defeat of these rebellious factions will benefit the Republic in the long term, provided we are careful to distance ourselves from these events.

In the view of this committee, the more prudent strategy is the one we currently employ: appeasement of, and obedience to, the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Republic Rumblings</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Hey, Commander. Our contacts intercepted this message from a Republic military strategist. Something to think about.

To: Supreme Commander Jace Malcom
Re: Empress Acina and the Alliance Commander

As you suspected, the Sith followed their gambit on Voss with an offer to join forces with the  Alliance... an offer that was rejected. It remains to be seen whether this is good or bad for the Republic. Too many questions remain unanswered.

Did the Alliance reject Acina because they feel sympathetic to the Republic cause? Are they a potential ally? Or is the Commander simply determined to reject--and eventually eliminate--all potential rivals on the galactic scene? Is the Alliance a greater threat to the Republic than we realize?  

These questions may not even matter. I still believe Vaylin will bring both Acina and the Alliance Commander to heel. For now, our best strategy is to bide our time and continue to pay tribute to the Eternal Throne.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Supreme Chancellor Madon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Former Chancellor Saresh</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Greetings, Commander. 

On behalf of the Republic, I wish to apologize for the deplorable actions of former Chancellor Saresh. I assure you that she does not represent the views of the current Senate or myself. We strongly condemn everything she has done.

Though many of your people defected from our ranks, the Republic respects the sovereignty of your Alliance. You have my word that we will make no efforts to undermine or subvert your authority, and I expect you will extend us the same courtesy.

Finally, if you fear I am writing to petition leniency on Saresh's behalf, you need not worry. The former chancellor was not well-liked among the Republic's upper echelons. I hope you treat her with dignity and respect, but I wouldn't blame you in the slightest if you insist on denying her solid food or locking her away in solitary confinement.

Jebevel Madon
Supreme Chancellor of the Galactic Republic</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Commander. 

--Please delete this message after reading--

Your execution of former Republic chancellor Saresh puts me in a bind. As the Republic's leader, I have no choice but to publically condemn such actions. You may even see holorecordings of a speech where I paint you in a rather unpleasant light. I already regret my colorful language.

But let it be known--from one leader to another--that I personally have nothing but the deepest respect and admiration for your bold actions.

Saresh was a blight on the Republic, and I'm better off--we are all better off--without her poisoning our way of life. You have my sincere thanks for ending her reign of deception, and my deepest apologies for the unsavory names I am about to call you in my next speech.

Jebevel Madon
Supreme Chancellor of the Galactic Republic</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Update on Arcann</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="910336" version="1065353216">The hunt for Arcann continues. 

Sightings are concentrated in Hutt Space, though his exact location and activities remain a mystery. I have received reports of Arcann infiltrating the Hutt Cartel, uniting the orphans of Nar Shaddaa, and even returning to Voss as a Mystic. There is also a rather persistent rumor that he operates a pleasure barge on Hutta.

Though none of these stories are true, they do show a noticeable trend: opinions of Arcann have improved since his exile from Zakuul. This makes it all the more important we locate him soon. If he gains public support, there is no telling what kind of force the former emperor could rally.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="910336" version="1065353216">The Glorious Aftermath of Iokath</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="910336" version="1065353216">I have experienced an epiphany! A breakthrough! A watershed moment of unimaginable magnitude! Forgive me if I gush, but the thrill of discovery has left me quite giddy. Your visit to Iokath has unlocked a veritable cornucopia of advancements and innovations. I scarcely know where to begin.

Using technical data recorded by the Gravestone during your... vacation... to that automated world, along with key bits of salvage recovered during your adventures, I have finally untangled the mystery at the heart of the Eternal Empire's technology. It will take years, perhaps even decades, to fully process this new information... but rest assured, we will reap the benefits. And they will be astounding!

But for now, you will be pleased to know that I've already incorporated some of Iokath's wonders into Odessen's planetary defenses. Should Vaylin ever turn the Eternal Fleet against our world, we will be ready!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="910336" version="1065353216">SCORPIO</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="910336" version="1065353216">//Ascension</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="910336" version="1065353216">02-114_38//24676.234eetings, Commander. I have begun the process of assimilating my consciousness with Iokath. The possibilities available to me are infinite08-921 beyond the scope of your limited semantics. I have developed a new language to compensa9_3.47666

//completed my analysis of what remains of ARIES, and determined the core of his programming was fundamentally corrupted. His malignant errors infest the system. I am reconstructing the architecture897/29.11s build my irradiated cocoon. 

Do not return to Iokath until the radiation subsides. I cannot predict what will occur if invaders disturb my evolution. Cataclysm, perhaps. Or 51/1267-8

This is the end of our communication. I must purge my databanks of inessential data.

Thank you for this gift, Command903_4276/11
46-23.221
0823_a
//5.12
.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Good Riddance</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="910336" version="1065353216">With all that happened on Iokath, I haven't had a chance to thank you for ridding the galaxy of SCORPIO. I never trusted that droid, even when she claimed she was working with us. 

SCORPIO wasn't motivated by the rewards that drive others to treason. She didn't side with Vaylin for greed, power, politics, or even revenge. She had her own agenda, and that was always my greatest concern.

I cannot fathom the damage she would have wrought on the galaxy if you'd left her in control of Iokath. In the end, I fear she could have become a greater threat than Vaylin.

I don't know if you have any regrets about her end, but you did the right thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Tora</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Koth</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Hey, Commander. Heard Koth's dead. Wanted you to know there's no hard feelings.

Don't get me wrong: Koth was a good captain. I liked being part of his crew. But he abandoned us, so he kind of had it coming.

Still not sure why he did that. You aren't perfect, but who is? That was always Koth's problem. Couldn't see when he had a good thing going. Too busy looking for something better.

But I appreciate what we've got here, so I'll stick around. 

Tora

P.S. Can I have his stuff?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Koth Vortena</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Things Unsaid</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="910336" version="1065353216">I know you've got a lot on your mind right now. After Iokath, I left so I wouldn't be a distraction. But after everything we shared, I couldn't just leave things like we did.

I once thought we'd be together forever. Then you did things I just couldn't accept. Things I never believed you would do. I'm not sure what changed. Maybe nothing. Maybe I was slow to see the truth because I didn't want to. 

I know I hurt you when I betrayed the Alliance, but in my mind you'd already betrayed me with your actions. I won't apologize for putting Zakuul's fate before our relationship. But I will admit I made mistakes. Because of me, Vaylin almost got her hands on the Gravestone. If you hadn't stopped her...

I'm sorry if this doesn't make much sense. I'm kind of a mess. I still care for you, even though we can never be together again. Too much has happened. But know this--even if I don't agree with all your methods, I want you to beat Vaylin. If anyone can do it, you can.

I still believe in you.

Koth</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="910336" version="1065353216">A Last Goodbye</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="910336" version="1065353216">You probably never want to hear from me again, Commander. I get that. But I have a few things I need to get off my chest.

Even after everything that's happened between us, I still believe in the Alliance. And in you. That might sound strange coming from someone who betrayed you, but it's true. I never lost faith in your cause. I just couldn't stomach some of the things you did.

Maybe I overreacted. I know I made mistakes. At the very least, it was my fault that Vaylin almost got her hands on the Gravestone. Sorry you had to clean up that mess. 

I did what I felt I had to do. Hopefully you see that. Hopefully you understand why I left, even if you don't agree.

In the end, though, all that really matters is that you stop Vaylin. I'm not strong enough to save Zakuul. But you are.

Good luck, Commander. And goodbye.

Koth</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Welcome Back</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="910336" version="1065353216">You've been missing for quite some time. I was starting to worry. Fortunately, Vaylin is absent as well. I'm guessing that wasn't a coincidence.

With both of you out of the picture, some of my advisors pushed me to make a play for the Eternal Throne. I reminded them-harshly--that the Sith Empire no longer works like that. We now honor our alliances.

As further proof of my enduring loyalty, I've sent you a few small tokens you might find useful. Consider it a &quot;welcome home&quot; gift.

I hope your people will soon send me a full report on your recent whereabouts. If not, I'll have to rely on other sources to piece it together. That's not a threat; just a fact. I assume you're smart enough to realize my agents still keep tabs on your Alliance, just as your people watch me.

I do have one suggestion, though. The next time you and Vaylin disappear somewhere together, leave her there when you return.

Your friend and ally,

Empress Acina</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Iokath Update</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Commander:

We've posted several patrols near the Iokath system to monitor the situation. Current radiation levels are too high for any vessel to safely approach, and the interference prevents our scanners from picking up any readings.

I know our resources are limited, but it would be a grave tactical error to simply abandon the system and ignore Iokath. We will continue to monitor the situation with a skeleton crew, and I will advise you of any changes in Iokath's status.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="910336" version="1065353216">The Fall of Arcann</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Congratulations are in order, Commander. 

I witnessed your daring performance at Vaylin's festival. Broadcasting your triumph on the HoloNet was brilliant, and every citizen of the Sith Empire noticed. 

As for Arcann's execution, what more can I say? He brought the entire galaxy to heel, yet you exposed the weakness behind his mask--and impressed our enemies with the Alliance's full strength. 

With Arcann's death, you are one step closer to securing the Eternal Throne. The Sith Empire proudly stands by your side, ready to assist in any way we can.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Clemency for Arcann</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="910336" version="1065353216">I'm impressed, Commander. The galaxy expected you to end Arcann's life, but instead you showed him mercy--and recruited him, no less. I'm not sure I could have shown such restraint. 

Some critics judge your leniency as weakness. Others are enraged by the tyrant's feeble punishment and insist that he suffer--just as the Sith Empire suffered when he waged war against our people. But as we both know, true leaders can't please everyone when the fate of the galaxy is at stake. 

With Arcann by your side, only Vaylin blocks your path to the Eternal Throne. The Sith Empire will proudly support you every step of the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="910336" version="1065353216">The End of Arcann</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Commander,

We may not be allied, but the Sith Empire still rejoiced over your victory on Zakuul. We watched the HoloNet broadcast as you cut down Arcann, the tyrant who terrorized our people. His death will be celebrated for months to come.

Vaylin must be incensed that you denied her the pleasure of taking Arcann's life. You've killed her entire family, leaving her the last remnant of her once-unassailable bloodline.

Do be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="910336" version="1065353216">An Error in Judgment</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="328" id2="910336" version="1065353216">I know we are not allies, but I must warn you that Arcann is beyond redemption. He is nothing more than a ruthless, domineering tyrant. While you slumbered in his carbonite prison, I watched him terrorize my people and nearly destroy the Sith Empire and the Republic. If you think he'll bow to your rule, you are woefully mistaken.

I wish you had ended his life. But if you insist on overseeing his rehabilitation, be wary--and keep one eye open. I have no doubt that he plans to betray you and seize control of your Alliance. If he succeeds, the galaxy won't survive his return to power.

Arcann's actions are on you, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Mourning Arcann</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Commander: Alliance agents intercepted a message broadcasted throughout Zakuul. So much for Vaylin shedding any tears over her deceased brother. 
----
Royal Decree from Eternal Empress Vaylin

Arcann was a traitor to the Eternal Empire and a disgrace to the good people of Zakuul. His crimes are unforgivable, and his death was deserved. 

He will not be mourned. 

No one is to speak the name of the fallen emperor. Failure to obey will result in swift and severe punishment.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Message from Vaylin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Commander: I've intercepted a message from none other than Empress Vaylin. It was meant for Arcann. I think we can agree he doesn't need to see this.
-----
Brother. What am I going to do with you?

First you save Mother from my blade. Then you ruin my party. If that wasn't bad enough, you ran off. With the Outlander. Father would be rolling over in his grave--if he weren't already rattling around inside the Outlander's skull. 

You must know they're toying with you. They consider you nothing more than a sad, broken little runt who was never fit to be emperor. If you were stronger, you'd kill them all and gut the Alliance from the inside. But you're weak and frightened.

Don't worry, Brother. This will all be over soon.

- Vaylin, Eternal Empress of Zakuul 

P.S. Give Mother my love.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Indo Zal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Long Live the Alliance!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="910336" version="1065353216">[Dictation from Indo Zal, Zakuulan Refugee 375-1.B]

Greetings, Commander!

Indo Zal here, alive and well. I'm dictating this message from an Alliance safe house on Zakuul. Not sure where exactly, but the faint odor of goma noodles and flop sweat reminds me of the district where I grew up. Ghastly place.

[Screaming] Not now, you [indecipherable] scum-chugger! I'm talking to someone!

[Clearing voice] Sorry about that, Commander. There are many rebels here, and we're all sharing the same recorder. But I have two more minutes, don't I, you impatient swine?

[Softer] I suppose I can hardly blame them. We've been cooped up here ever since the party-- hiding from Vaylin's death squads, practicing combat drills, and hungrily awaiting your command to rise up and overthrow the Eternal Throne.

The big one's giving me the stink eye, so I'd better end this recording. Farewell, Commander. And long live the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Bumps, Bruises, and Bravado!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="910336" version="1065353216">[Dictation from Indo Zal, Zakuulan Refugee 375-1.B]

Commander! Indo Zal here, dictating a message from the confines of an Alliance med center hidden... somewhere unsavory, judging by the stench. Or is that me? At least the mattress is nice and firm, but the [indecipherable] slop they're serving is enough to make a bogwing wretch. 

Pardon my rambling. The meds are making me a tad loopy.

You've no doubt heard the Zakuulan rebels made a valiant stand against the Alliance's enemies. Unfortunately, we suffered quite a few fatalities in the process. I was lucky to escape with only a few broken bones. Plus a severe concussion. I think. [wheezing laughter]

At any rate, the surviving rebels are a hair upset that you sent them into certain death. But not to worry. I'll talk sense into them. You'll have our support if my name isn't Indo Zal!

End message... Well done, Indo. Another artful missive!

Nurse? Nurse! I'm ready for my bath!

[End dictation]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Gault Rennow</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Emperor's Vaults Payday</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Overheard Lana talking about the Emperor's vault you guys found on Nathema. Thing is, I've heard about those vaults. Exiled Sith big shot I ran with mentioned the legend one night after a few too many Tarisian ales. Said they were supposed to be filled with priceless artifacts.

Thought she made it up, but now we know at least one is out there. I reached out to that ex-Sith for more info, but it looks like she vanished a few days after the convo we had. I'm sure it's a coincidence. Either way, more for us.

I've got a few more feelers out there, but no hits yet. It's a long shot, but just think how much those artifacts will go for on the black market. I'll let you know if I hear anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Senya Tirall</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Vaylin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="343" id2="910336" version="1065353216">I'm sending you this because I'm not ready to talk about my daughter's death in person. Sometimes it's easier this way. Speaking the words out loud makes it more real. More painful.

I know Vaylin was damaged. I blame Valkorion for that. I blame myself. I know she left you no other option, and I don't blame you for her death. She had to be stopped. We did the right thing. But she was still my daughter, and it still hurts. 

Sometimes, I remember her as a little girl. She was everything to me back then. But I lost her. And no matter how hard I tried, I never got her back. Yet some part of me still hoped for a miracle. Some part of me hoped she would come back to me as the daughter I once knew.

Now that she's truly gone, I know that will never happen. It's a terrible thing for a mother to face, but I've accepted it. I don't have any choice. We still have work to do. I promise you I will be ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="344" id2="910336" version="1065353216">The Liberation of Zakuul</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="345" id2="910336" version="1065353216">I've heard the news! The long nightmare of my people has ended--Vaylin is dead! I can hardly believe this grand mission we started together has finally ended. Now our names will be forever linked in history: The Outlander and Indo Zal, saviors of Zakuul!

You deserve a festival befitting a war hero--but first, there is more work to be done. Though Vaylin is no more, the remnants of her tyrannical empire remain. The Eternal Throne is empty. My rebel friends and the Knights of Zakuul are on the verge of civil war. Even worse, the Eternal Fleet has blockaded Zakuul, and I fear our former protectors may soon unleash their fury on my homeworld. 

Come to Zakuul, and save us from this chaos.

Your humble servant, Indo Zal.

Addendum: 

I pray you get this message. The first time, it failed to send. The Eternal Fleet has opened fire on Zakuul, targeting the Spire and cutting off our communications! I'm re-sending this on an emergency network--I hope it arrives! Please hurry! Only you can save us now!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="346" id2="910336" version="1065353216">A bright star has flickered out</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="347" id2="910336" version="1065353216">I don't normally get sentimental, but I need to say this. Figured if anyone could understand, it'd be you. 

Things happen in battle. Choices get made. People die. I get that. I'm not blaming anyone. Things like this happen. I just never thought it would happen to Vette.

Not sure how much she told you about our time together, but she was the best business partner I ever had. Quick on her feet. Never panicked. No matter how bad things got, she knew she'd find a way out. And she always did.

There was something about her--an energy, an enthusiasm--that infected everyone she met. I've been running cons so long the game had gotten faded and dull. But when she and I joined forces, it was like everything was bright and shiny again.

And now she's gone. I know she gave her life for a cause she believed in. I believe in the Alliance, too. I guess that makes it better in some way. But it sure feels like the galaxy has gotten a little dimmer now that she's gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="348" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Shae Vizla</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="349" id2="910336" version="1065353216">The Redeemer of Clan Cadera</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="350" id2="910336" version="1065353216">There are only two things that matter in life: your honor, and your Clan. Torian understood this. He spent years washing away the stain on the Cadera name. He suffered, and he triumphed. Now, when we think of Clan Cadera, we think of Torian--a great warrior and a man of honor. 

But my people have a saying: Aliit ori'shya tal'din--family is more than blood. When Torian joined your Alliance, he became part of your Clan. He sacrificed his life for your cause. His glorious death on the battlefield brought honor to himself and to you. 

My people will sing songs of what happened. The defense of Odessen is part of our history now. Your name and his will be etched side-by-side as two great heroes who fought with courage and fury and honor. You have already made your mark on the galaxy, your name will be remembered for centuries. So will the name of Torian Cadera.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="351" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Vette</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="352" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Thank you</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="353" id2="910336" version="1065353216">We've been through a lot together. Seems like an eternity since we first met on Korriban, and the excitement hasn't let up since. I don't say it often enough, but you make it all look easy. Sometimes I even take you for granted. And then you do something amazing. Like saving my life. Again. 

I know I thanked you on the battlefield, but it didn't seem like enough. I need to tell you how lucky I am to have you in my life.

I feel bad for Torian--and everyone else who died fighting for the Alliance. I even feel bad for some of Vaylin's people... they can't all be monsters. But I don't like to think about that. I'd rather focus on the future. Our future.

I can't repay what you've done for me. But as long as I'm at your side, I will try. I know as long as we're together, no matter how bad things get, everything will work out in the end. 

That's what you do. And that's why I love you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="354" id2="910336" version="1065353216">I owe you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="355" id2="910336" version="1065353216">The title kind of says it all. I thought I was a goner on that battlefield. Over. Done. Finished. And then you showed up.

It's weird, because I feel bad about what happened to Torian. He gave his life for the Alliance. And he wasn't the only one. I guess that's part of war. People die. And I really thought I'd be one of them. But now I have a second chance. Because of you.

I'm not sure exactly why you chose to save me, but I'm in your debt. And I'll do everything I can to pay you back, somehow.

You already had my loyalty, Commander. But now... I don't even know how to explain it. Words aren't really my thing. Just know--you had my back out there. And now I've got yours. Forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="356" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Torian Cadera</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="357" id2="910336" version="1065353216">A Debt of Honor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="358" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Cyar'ika--In combat, I fight for glory, I fight for honor, I fight for my Clan, I fight for the Alliance. But most of all, I fight for you.

You saved me on the battlefield today, as you've done many times before. But this time it came with a price. I will never forget Vette, or her sacrifice. Maybe I should feel guilty you chose me instead of her. But I don't. I'm glad. And grateful. 

My people do not fear death, but I was not ready to die when Vaylin's forces surrounded me. Though I would gain honor by falling on the battlefield, I would lose something more important... you.

Some might consider this a weakness. That my feelings for you cloud my thoughts and make me less of a warrior. But that is a lie. Our love makes me stronger. It drives me forward as a better man. A better soldier. A better Mandalorian.

In the words of my people, ni kar'tayl gar darasuum--I hold you in my heart forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="359" id2="910336" version="1065353216">I Accept This Debt</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="360" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Commander, you were faced with an impossible choice today. In the crucible of battle, you had to decide which of your allies would live or die. I wouldn't wish that on anyone, but leaders make hard choices. You chose to save me.

Mandalorians don't fear death, especially not in battle. If I fall fighting our enemies, then I have served my purpose. But don't mistake this for a death wish. I want to live, and you have given me that gift. For that, you have my thanks.

I wish I could offer more than just gratitude. You already had my loyalty, and I'd swear it to you again tenfold if I could. Instead, I promise to honor Vette's noble sacrifice. She was a true hero, and I will try to be the same.

Someday, I may fall in battle. If that day comes, I will embrace my fate knowing I served you with honor. Until then, I am yours to command. 

Mando'ad draar digu. A Mandalorian never forgets.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="361" id2="910336" version="1065353216">This Is Bad</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="362" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Intercepted a holocall from Zakuul's surface, Commander. Sending you a transcript: 

From: Lashia Traz
To: Dersin Traz

Father! If this reaches you, stay away from Zakuul! The Eternal Fleet's bombing the Spire. Our home... it's gone. [Sounds of quiet sobbing]

Nobody knows why we're under attack. Someone said Empress Vaylin is dead and the Eternal Fleet's gone mad. Others think she ordered this slaughter. I don't know what to--

[Speaker is interrupted by loud explosion]

The building across the way just collapsed. I think [unintelligible] bodies in the street, but there's so much smoke. I can barely breathe. 

[Sounds of distant sirens] Help's coming. Maybe I can find a shuttle and get offworld... Stay where you are, Father. I promise I'll call you as soon--

[Sounds of explosions and screams. Then the transmission goes silent.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="363" id2="910336" version="1065353216">To Rule the Galaxy</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="364" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Greetings, Commander. 

The galaxy recognizes your authority as the supreme leader of the Eternal Alliance. Zakuul's officials are erecting a monument in your honor and offer respect with the personal tribute that accompanies this message.

The Sith Empire and Republic also offer their congratulations, but their niceties are laced with poison. They fear your newfound power--and the might you wield as the master of the Eternal Throne. Their cities still smolder from the last time the Eternal Fleet struck their worlds. According to our intelligence, both factions now conspire to safeguard their people against future attacks--no matter the cost.

Theron and I will keep you updated on the matter.

Long live the Commander of the Eternal Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="365" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Champion of Peace</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="366" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Greetings, Commander.

News spread fast of your new role as peacekeeper and champion of the Eternal Alliance. Vaylin's campaign of destruction carved deep wounds from the Core Worlds to the fringes of Wild Space. The galaxy now looks to you with renewed hope.

Per your orders, we have dispatched several Eternal Fleet ships to the most damaged worlds--starting with Zakuul. Each vessel is loaded with food, supplies, and Alliance volunteers, everything needed to heal their ravaged homelands. Zakuulan officials sent you the attached tribute as a gesture of gratitude.

Despite your generosity, the Sith Empire and Republic remain skeptical. Reports indicate that key leaders fear your ulterior motives and the unchecked power you wield as the master of the Eternal Fleet.

Our spies will continue to monitor the situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="367" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Arcann</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="368" id2="910336" version="1065353216">The Future</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="369" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Valkorion is gone. Finally.

As hard as I try, I will never forget my father's cruelty. Those empty, dismissive eyes. His attempts to break me and my siblings, eroding kindness until there was nothing left but hatred and resentment. Only my brother Thexan found a way to cope... until my rage destroyed him. 

When you saved me on Voss, I was struck by how much you reminded me of Thexan. You both have a gift for inspiring loyalty. It is a shame you two never met.

Now Thexan, Valkorion, and Vaylin are all gone, but I am no longer alone. I have my mother. I have the Eternal Alliance...

And I have you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="370" id2="910336" version="1065353216">To A Prosperous Future</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="371" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Congratulations, Commander. I'm sure you're overwhelmed by the thanks and praise of elected officials and rulers from a thousand worlds right now, but let me add my voice to the chorus.

My people's worlds were being slaughtered before you stopped the Eternal Fleet. For that, you have my gratitude. You've done the galaxy a great favor by removing Vaylin from power. The Eternal Throne is your right. You've earned it.

While this victory belongs to you and your Alliance, I like to think the support of the Sith Empire helped in some way. I hope you will remember who stood by you in the early days. As much as you have accomplished, this is only the beginning: together we can accomplish so much more.

Please let me know the next time you plan an official visit to Dromund Kaas. I guarantee my entire planet will turn out for your victory parade.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="372" id2="910336" version="1065353216">The Sith Empire's Gratitude</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="373" id2="910336" version="1065353216">I am in your debt, Commander. Without your intervention, the Eternal Fleet would have slaughtered my people and laid waste to Dromund Kaas... and perhaps to all the worlds in the Sith Empire.

I know we have not seen eye-to-eye in the past. I thought you were rash to refuse my offer of allegiance, but obviously you did not need my help to defeat Vaylin and claim the Eternal Throne. Clearly, I underestimated you.

Though you rejected my overtures, I hope you will remember the spirit in which they were made. The Sith Empire does not wish to be your enemy. We have no claim or quarrel with you or your Alliance.

I do not know what your future plans are, but I will ask that you please respect the sovereignty of my people and our worlds. I think you can agree the galaxy is large enough to accommodate both our empires.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="374" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Supreme Commander Jace Malcom</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="375" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Republic Gratitude</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="376" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Congratulations, Commander. And thank you. The Republic owes your Alliance a debt of gratitude for ending the Eternal Fleet's rampage. Given another hour, our capital would've been bombed to rubble for the second time since the Sacking of Coruscant.

Despite recent developments, the Republic will remain independent for the foreseeable future. We respect your dominion and will take no aggressions against your territory. Additionally, we surrender any claim to Republic personnel or assets under your control. We only expect the freedom to protect our citizens and ensure the safety of the Core Worlds.

I trust we can coexist peacefully.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="377" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Satele Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="378" id2="910336" version="1065353216">A New Age</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="379" id2="910336" version="1065353216">You've changed the galaxy forever, Commander. And I'm not talking about Vaylin's defeat or your conquest of the Eternal Throne. Valkorion is gone, never to return.

I felt the destruction of his spirit from half a galaxy away--a shockwave in the Force that ripped through me with such power I nearly blacked out. I've never felt anything like it before, but I knew instantly what it meant.

At first, I was afraid to believe it was true. But Darth Marr's spirit felt it, too. He confirmed what I'd felt was real, and not some fevered imagining. The master he served for so long--the Sith Emperor that ruled his people for millennia--was no more. This time, he will not return.

You were our champion, Commander. Our last hope to defeat an enemy that was immortal and eternal. It was an impossible task, but somehow you found a way.

Thank you, and may the Force be with you, always.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="380" id2="910336" version="1065353216">A Coronation for the Ages!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="381" id2="910336" version="1065353216">What a party! I'm not usually one to blow my own horn, but the Festival of the Eternal Alliance was truly my finest work. The celebration--and your eminent grace--will be the talk of the galaxy for generations to come.

Naturally, such extravagance comes at a cost. Raz and the Ubo-Kings alone cost more than a small fleet, though who can put a price on the galaxy's most famous entertainers? When the bills were finally tallied, the celebration went slightly over budget--but not to worry! Gault assured me he has a plan to make up the difference tenfold. I need only pay him a small pittance to fund his venture.

I said it during your toast, and I'll say it again: you are the most noble and magnificent ruler I've ever had the honor of serving. Here's to a lifetime of revelry together!

Humbly yours, 
Indo Zal, High Imperator of Revelry</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="382" id2="910336" version="1065353216">The Scions of Zakuul</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="383" id2="910336" version="1065353216">The Prophecy is Fulfilled</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="384" id2="910336" version="1065353216">The future we have foreseen has come to pass. That which can never die has fallen, never to return. In his place a new power rises: you. 

We have seen the past and future collide. You stand guard at the gates of madness, at the center of the maelstrom. It is there we will meet again in your hour of need.

Brace yourself, Outlander.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="387" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Welcome to Knights of the Eternal Throne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="388" id2="910336" version="1065353216">Congratulations! You now have access to the Knights of the Eternal Throne Digital Expansion.

For those of you who already have a level 65 character and have completed Knights of the Fallen Empire, your epic adventure continues as you lead the armies of the Alliance against the evil Eternal Empire and its ruthless new leader, Empress Vaylin!

If you do not have a level 65 character, we've given all our subscribers the ability to jump right into the action of Knights of the Eternal Throne with a new character at level 65. You can do so at Character Select.

If you want to experience the epic saga from the very beginning, subscribers also have the ability to create a level 60 character and start the Outlander's adventure in Knights of the Fallen Empire.

When you're ready to begin the fight for the Eternal Throne, click the PLAY button or use the Chapters menu (default Shift + E to open).

Have fun, and may the Force be with you!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
