<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>205</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/kotfe_season_1.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Ralo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Safe</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Me, Dol, and a bunch of others are alive thanks to you. We'd never have made the escape pods without your broadcast.

Hope you managed to get in one, too. I caught a look at the fleet that took us down - we'll never be able to take them on without you.

Gotta power down to save energy now. Stay safe.

- Ralo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Ralo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="874956" version="1065353216">What happened?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Are you alive? Something must have busted in the engines--we actually sped up toward the enemy ships. I barely made it out before the collision.

Don't know if anyone else made it. Can't raise Dol or you or anyone.

Hope none of those ships drag me in. I wouldn't want to see what these people do with prisoners.

Get in touch if you###**#*-------TRANSMISSION ERROR</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="874956" version="1065353216">HK-55</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Report: Intercepted Transmissions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Observation: Zakuulan news broadcasts are transmitted on an unsecured frequency. Reports on our escape are currently the leading topic.

Elaboration: The sudden blackout caused by the reactor shutdown has been cited as the cause of minor injuries and property damage but no fatalities.

Conclusion: Maximum preservation of life achieved. Your efforts were entirely successful, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Observation: Zakuulan news broadcasts are transmitted on an unsecured frequency. Reports on our escape are currently the leading topic.

Elaboration: Fatalities due to the reactor overload are estimated at nearly 5,000. This does not include undocumented individuals living in the lowest levels of the Spire, where damage from cascading debris was greatest. Property damage is likely to exceed three trillion credits.

Conclusions: Zakuulan generators are a weak point in their infrastructure. High Justice Vaylin is willing to sacrifice thousands of Zakuulan lives to achieve your recapture.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Update from T7</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I've just received word from T7 back on Zakuul: Arcann's forces are scouring the swamps, capturing any exiles they find and killing any who resist. It is likely that they're being questioned on the suspicion that some of them might have aided our escape.

Zakuulan news networks are reporting nothing of it. They have no idea what their new Emperor is truly capable of. But we do--and we must remember just how far he'll go.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Terion Drel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Our Deepest Thanks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="874956" version="1065353216">On behalf of my fellow exiles, I would like to extend our utmost thanks for your generosity in bringing us aboard your vessel. It is a strange ship, to be sure, but far preferable to the swamps or Arcann's prisons.

Though we have few relevant skills, we are doing our best to assist in the running of the ship--Master Vortena has even offered us permanent positions in his crew! We are overwhelmed by such kindness.

You saved us all--we will do whatever we can to repay you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Tora</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Drinks are on me</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Hey,

I don't usually write notes, but I loved your work today with that prune-faced buckethead Vik. Guy was like a festering boil on a dewback's rear end. Nobody's going to miss him, least of all in the Free Zone. I hear they threw a party after you left.

I don't know what else you do for fun, but Asylum has a couple of cantinas that won't rot your guts with whatever swill they're serving. If you ever want to kick back and relax for a bit, I'm buying. Well, technically, Vik's buying. I stole his boots and sold them for my R &amp; R fund. Anyway, nice meeting you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Tanno Vik</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="874956" version="1065353216">You're good for business</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I've got to admit, I figured the stories were true and you died on Zakuul. Never thought I'd find myself haggling with a legend come back from the grave over some worthless thief. Don't know what your angle is with Tora, but if I catch her sniffing around my business again, she's dead.

The upside to my day is that all those merchants saw me walk away from you--and now my skim off them is double what it used to be. They think we're pals! I'd cut you in on the take, but you don't seem like the type to be interested. You and me will just stay out of each other's way, like a couple of firaxan sharks chasing the same fish. There's plenty to eat.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Fun catching up</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Knew you wouldn't stay dead--and sooner or later, you'd stick your nose in my business. Glad you can still see the bigger picture and make the smart play. Would've been a shame to ruin our little reunion by blasting you in the face.

Word around Asylum is you're going to war with Zakuul. Best of luck. I've got my own thing going, and I ain't reenlisting with Havoc Squad. It makes zero difference who's running the galaxy. Emperor Arcann, you, the next idiot in the sabacc deck--whatever. Me, I'll be just fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Heskal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Trust in the Eternal Emperor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Facing you in battle was the only way to see the truth. When I felt the Eternal Emperor's might radiating from you in the heat of our duel, it burned away all of my doubts. I know now that Arcann will fall, the Scions will be avenged, and you will bring order to the chaos engulfing Zakuul. It is my honor to be your herald and seer. I have already received a vision of what I must do to ensure your final victory. When the time comes, I will be ready to serve you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Do not hide your power</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Your prowess as a warrior was never in question. Our duel was not designed to test your skill or restraint. I needed to see the fate you were concealing. I now know the Eternal Emperor's spirit lives within you--and that your refusal to accept his gift is what blinded my Scions. Know that Valkorion is your ally and wishes to see this galaxy restored. When the final battle comes, he will stand with you. Let his power flow through you and guide us all to victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="874956" version="1065353216">UNKNOWN SENDER</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Educational</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Some skulls are thicker than others. I didn't exactly enjoy being knocked out cold today, but I took it as a learning opportunity. My partner, well, he's on the thicker side.

You could've killed us outright. If you were everything he says you are, you would have dumped our corpses in a ditch.

He'll come around someday. I'll work on it.

Thanks for letting me get home to my husband tonight,
--B</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Heskal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="874956" version="1065353216">The burden of destiny</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="874956" version="1065353216">By the time you receive this, I will be dead, my destiny fulfilled. Even now, I can feel the fire of your rage, though it has yet to ignite. You think me a fool, but you would be wise to remember that everything I have foretold has come to pass. Use the Scions. They will do what must be done. Our visions give us clarity, but are also a burden. I take no pleasure in bringing Arcann to Asylum. I am fully aware of the destruction his arrival will cause, but it is necessary to pave the way for a brighter future. From chaos, order will rise, and you will be its conduit. Do not shy away from destiny, for it will find you even in the darkness.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Embrace your destiny</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="874956" version="1065353216">This message will not reach you until I am gone, my destiny fulfilled. I have seen my final moments. Asylum in ruins. Your confusion. Do not let your emotions rule you. Look past the casualties of a single shadow port and focus on the galaxy. Your fate is already sealed. The longer you fight it, the more lives Arcann takes. When the time is right, my Scions will return and assist you. Use them. Blood is on your hands. Your actions put into motion the chaos that now threatens all of known space. Accept your burden and become the champion of order.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Asylum casualty report</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="874956" version="1065353216">It is difficult to ascertain precise numbers. As a shadow port, Asylum didn't have a government that cared about up-to-date population records. But SCORPIO kept a tally of deaths she witnessed, and we're looking at casualties in the thousands. That's not including the hundreds caught in Valkorion's blast outside the Control Spar. While not Ziost-level numbers, I hope the internal damage you suffered will caution you from using his power in the future. The cost is too great. I didn't wake you up so that Valkorion could finish the job the carbon poisoning started. Whatever he tells you, don't forget that Valkorion is the threat that we set out to destroy. He's a master manipulator who has been pulling strings for centuries. You cannot trust him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Sacrifices</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="874956" version="1065353216">We'll be arriving in Odessen soon. I don't know when we'll have a moment to simply talk, but I need to get something off my chest. I knew going into this fight, sacrifices would be necessary. Such is the nature of war. But seeing the damage you suffered at Arcann's hands... You should be dead. I spent the last five years searching for you because I knew you were our only hope for victory, but I didn't think about the toll it might take on you. Koth did. He's always harping on those things. All I cared about was rescuing you so that you could rescue us. I wonder if that was unfair of me. Please know that I never take what you endure for granted. No matter what happens, the galaxy will be forever in your debt.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Theron Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Good Speech</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="874956" version="1065353216">One of my jobs around here is monitoring morale. I intercept every comm channel in the camp (except yours--I respect the chain of command), and I know how to avoid being noticed by people who think they're having a private chat.

That all sounds terrible when I write it down. Let me start over.

I hear what people are saying around the camp, and the news is all good. Even the most die-hard Imperial soldiers are inspired by what you said. People believe we can win this fight, and that's a big improvement over what I was hearing over the last five years. You've won over the doubters, Commander. And if it makes any difference, you've definitely got my vote.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Alliance morale report</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I set up a computer in the base with the sole purpose of recording all comm chatter and intercepting every text message transmitted via local HoloNet. It runs a program originally created by Imperial Intelligence to pick out key words and form data maps of frequently used terms. The original purpose was predicting enemy activities and pinpointing areas of disloyalty in the Empire. Now I'm using it to ensure everyone here follows your leadership without question. No need to thank me--it's all part of my job.

I think you'll be pleased to know that your speech to the camp has resulted in a 90% frequency increase of the combination of words &quot;kill&quot; and &quot;Arcann&quot; in the same sentence and a 150% increase of the phrases &quot;sacrifice everything&quot; and &quot;victory at all costs.&quot; These numbers include our Republic allies, which only confirms my long-held suspicion they are just as bloodthirsty as the most zealous Imperial soldier. Everyone in this camp stands ready to kill on your command. Well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Kaliyo Djannis</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Don't come back</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Got to hand it to you, agent--you've got style. When I'm done with a person, I sneak out in the middle of the night. Leave a note, if they weren't a complete waste of time. Not you. You blow up a frigate to cover your escape. Always the clever one. Thought we had a good thing going. If you wanted out, you could've been upfront with me. I'm a big girl--learned long ago men aren't worth crying over.

Thought about hijacking the Phantom, dropping the others planetside somewhere. But it's got your stink all over it. No, it's time to get back to me. Truth is, I'm grateful. Obviously, I was getting soft. Won't happen again.

Just remember--I was the best thing that ever happened to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Vector Hyllus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="874956" version="1065353216">The Song has gone quiet</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="874956" version="1065353216">We do not know if this will reach you, but we had to try. We have meditated on the destruction of Darth Marr's frigate, replaying the events from all angles, but we cannot find clarity. The Song of the Universe crescendoed--its vibrations overtook the stars, then... silence. Your aura, normally so bright, dimmed, and the vessel we have made our home grew cold. 

Your scent lingers, but your essence slips through our fingers. For the first time since the cave, we are afraid of what the next verse will bring. You have become part of us. We cherish our life together--the experiences we share and the sensations you evoke. We do not know what we will be like without you. We do not want to know.

Please come home.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Andronikos Revel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Blast it, where are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="874956" version="1065353216">None of your Council friends will speak to me, and they grounded the Fury. Whole capital's in chaos. Rumors flying everywhere. Look, neither of us likes to be clingy, but you can't pull a disappearing act and not expect me to worry. We're a team. 

I'm not a sentimental guy, you know that, but if something's happened to you... I don't think I can go back to my old life. Used to feel like relationships were nothing but dead weight. All I wanted was to fly free, no attachments. But what we have together--I wouldn't give that up for anything.

I know you're alive. It would take more than an explosion to kill my girl. Even a really big one. If I don't hear from you, I'll commandeer a shuttle to find you myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Raina Temple</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I'm not ready for this</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="874956" version="1065353216">The Intelligence training regimen taught me I must be ready for anything. Under your guidance, I prepared for the unexpected, but when Darth Marr's frigate exploded... I hesitated, and now you're missing. The truth is, I don't know what to do. No one has answers. I thought about reaching out to Lana Beniko, but I can't risk the Sith finding out about me. Especially not now, when I have no protection.

Kaliyo thinks your disappearance is a scheme and I should forget about you. But I can't do that. I'm not ready for a life without you, sir. It's too dangerous for me to stay in Dromund Kaas. I'm going off the grid for a while, but I'll be monitoring the HoloNet for any news concerning your whereabouts.

I love you. Please come back to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Malavai Quinn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I remain your loyal servant</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="874956" version="1065353216">My lord, it's likely I'm prattling to no one. Still, I had to send something.

You're not one for minced words, so I'll be blunt: The Empire needs you. More than that--I need you. Discord reigns in Dromund Kaas. Without your leadership, the crew disbanded, and I have received little assistance from the Dark Council or Imperial military. No one will grant me an audience, much less answer my inquiries.

I should have come with you aboard Darth Marr's ship--stood in my rightful place by your side. I know I've made mistakes, but I thought I had a lifetime to make up for my betrayal. Now I'm faced with the possibility of never seeing you again... and it makes me ill. I cannot accept it. 

The shame of my past actions and my love for you will fuel me for eternity. No matter what anyone says--I know you're alive, and I will find you. Even if it kills me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="874956" version="1065353216">For when you wake up</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I've written this message twice now. Okay, more than twice. Kinda weird writing something that may never be read. Lana says you're locked in carbonite, but alive. (Yeah, we're in touch. Long story.) I like to think you're having one crazy dream. And maybe I'm in it. But I don't want to presume. We never really declared what this--you and me--is... was.... Have I mentioned I'm bad at relationships? Another reason I'm a workaholic.

I'm rambling. The point I'm trying to make is--whatever's between us, I want you to know that I care about you. A lot. The whole galaxy's lost its mind. The thing that keeps me going is the knowledge that you're out there, and we're putting together a plan to rescue you. I might not be there--we've all got our parts to play--but I haven't forgotten about you or our time together. I never will.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Kira</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I know you're alive</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Happy anniversary. As of today, you've been missing for a whole year. You beat your old record from the Emperor's Fortress. Everyone's given you up for dead except me. Thing is, I'd feel it if you died. The connection we made is too strong to just break apart. I've spent hundreds of hours meditating--trying to find you. All I get is a great big nothing where you used to be. That can't be right.

Did you find him out there? Did you fall to him again? Sometimes, I dream that you're standing in my doorway, but you're not you anymore. You're him.

Everything's gone wrong since you left. The Republic is giving up to the invaders. Nobody can tell me what happened to Master Satele. The Jedi Order is dying, and I can't save it. I couldn't even keep our crew together.

You have to come back.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Doc</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Just tell me you're safe</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I don't believe for a second you didn't make it to the escape pods. You've survived worse disasters without breaking a sweat. You're the best Jedi in this whole galaxy, and it'll take more than one lousy Sith battle cruiser going boom to kill you. I had to learn a lot of math in medical school, and I've run the numbers. You've gotta be alive.

There's only one explanation for you not answering my calls. You're on some secret mission, and you couldn't tell ol' Doc for his own safety. I get it, gorgeous--but enough's enough. Give me a shout back because I'm pacing a groove in this deck waiting to hear from you.

And if you decide to surprise me with a personal visit, that's fine, too. I'm easy.

Seriously, everyone's worried. You've been gone too long.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Risha</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="874956" version="1065353216">You win</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="328" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Don't know why I'm sending this message after three years. You'll never see it. If you survived what happened to Marr's ship, everyone would know--and if you ran off to start over without me, I'd sure as stars have heard about it by now. You've never been any good at staying inconspicuous.

Want to hear something funny? I didn't give up on you until today. I searched all over Wild Space, even after Corso said it was time to face the truth. And then this morning I remembered the first time we kissed, and how I promised myself I'd never let you make a sucker out of me. I'm the one who was supposed to leave when things got bad.

Damn you for getting the last laugh, just like always.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Akaavi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Ret'urcye mhi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="874956" version="1065353216">These are the things I wish I had said. Don't go aboard Marr's flagship alone. I know you're not afraid of him. You're never afraid of anything. It's one of the reasons I fell in love with you. But I have a bad feeling about this. I can watch your back and make sure you get out alive. Let me come with you.

I never thought you'd be first into the Void. I hoped we'd go together, when we were both old--but not too old for one last glorious battle. Now I have to fight alone. So be it.

Ni su'cuyi, gar kyr'adyc, ni partayli, gar darasuum. I can almost see the look on your face reading those words. You never did learn Mando'a worth a damn. I'll translate it one last time.

I'm still alive, but you are dead. I remember you, so you are eternal.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Corso</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Wait for me at Port Nowhere</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I don't care what anyone else says. You can't be dead. Not like this. Not after everything we've gotten through together.

I flew back to where Marr's flagship went down. Escape pods have scattered all over the blasted sector. You've got to be in one of them, and I'll keep scanning until I see your beautiful face again.

If you make it back to Republic space before me, go to Port Nowhere and send me the signal. I'll come running--but not before I stop off at the market on Coruscant that sells the thing from Naboo you like so much. I noticed you ran out of it.

Come home. I love you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Vette</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Things I'll never know</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="874956" version="1065353216">It's been almost a year since I last saw you outside of a dream. Every day, I have the same question. How did it end? Were there a hundred bad guys swarming you, like a bunch of killiks trying to take down a krayt dragon? I want to think you went down swinging and took most of them with you.

But other times I wonder if you were just in the wrong place at the wrong time. Some external bulkhead ripped open next to you. Hard Vacuum 1, Empire's Wrath 0. Maybe it was a reactor-core breach, and you never even had time to feel the heat?

They say powerful Sith can come back from the dead and appear to the people they had strong connections to when they were alive. Will I wake up some day and see you? Will you finally tell me what happened? Will I know if you had time to think about me before you died?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Mako</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Closing shop</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="874956" version="1065353216">People in our line of work never seem to retire. We all talk about it. Everyone plans to get so rich they can afford to buy themselves a nice little tropical planetoid in some remote system way off the main hyperlanes. That's the dream, right? Sit around drinking on a beach and enjoying old age? But I keep noticing how nobody actually does it.

Braden? Dead. Crysta? Dead. Most of the Great Hunt contestants from the last ten years? Three guesses what happened to them, and the first two don't count. Now you're on that same terrible list because you couldn't resist going after the scariest boogeyman the galaxy's ever seen. Who could've predicted that would turn out badly? Oh, wait--it was ME.

Not sure why I'm even writing this. Closure? Just to say &quot;I told you so&quot;? It doesn't matter. The galaxy's falling apart, and I don't need a front-row seat. I'm done with the business. All it's ever done is take away the people I cared about.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I know you're still alive. I could feel your presence even after the destruction of Darth Marr's flagship. You were traveling away from me, deeper into Wild Space, faster and farther than I could follow. When I concentrate, I can still feel your pulse and hear your thoughts like distant whispers. You're in pain, and I can't stand knowing I'm powerless to help you.

They moved the Noetikons back to Coruscant after the attack on Tython. I've been consulting them, especially Bastila Shan's. She understands what this feels like. You've done so much for so many, and now it's time for your allies to honor you in return. The Esh-kha, Gaden-Ko, the Balmorran resistance... I will rally these old friends and lead them to wherever you are. We will brave the dangers that await, my love.

Stay strong. We will come.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I will find you</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="343" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Nadia</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="344" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Everyone says you're dead. I thought I'd feel the empty place in the Force that was your presence. I search, but I find nothing. It's like you were never there. What does it mean, that you could die and leave no trace?

I close my eyes to see your face. I shut out everything to hear your voice. The secrets we told each other. The plans we made. The future we were building. I know now who took that from us. I saw the Eternal Empire's warships above Dromund Kaas. They tried to kill me, too. They almost did.

The Sith and Jedi are helpless against this enemy. I've left them all behind. I never belonged to those failed orders, no more than you did. We were always something special. Now it's just me.

Something is drawing me to the darkness beyond the edge of Wild Space. Maybe there will be answers waiting for me. Maybe I won't be alone anymore. I wish you were going with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="345" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Farewell</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="346" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Ashara</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="347" id2="874956" version="1065353216">You were always going to leave me. I knew that. It was inevitable the moment you killed my old master. I pace the ship's corridors and eavesdrop on your acolytes. Some mourn you. Their grief makes me smile. Beyond that, I feel nothing.

I'm free. I'm alive. I'm more powerful than ever, and I don't fear death. Not mine, not yours. The worst happened. I'm still here. Someone already seeks to replace you as the dark center of my universe. Why should I cry that you're gone? Why write words to a dead man?

Why?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="348" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Everything ends</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="349" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Jaesa</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="350" id2="874956" version="1065353216">A Mando knows every mission could be the last. None of us can count on seeing the next sunrise. There's only now. Sometimes we get lucky, and we march together all our lives. Sometimes, we only get a single battle. You and I had a few years.

They were good years.

You honored me. You saved my life. You loved me better than anyone ever has. I'll repay those debts. I'll carry your memory with me on every hunt I take until the day I die.

The ones who killed you are invading Imperial space. They think we won't fight back. They're wrong. Mandalore is gathering the clans, and I'm answering his call. Ret'urcye mhi doesn't mean goodbye--it means &quot;maybe we'll see each other again.&quot; If there's another life beyond this one, I hope we do.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="351" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Nu kyr'adyc, shi taab'echaaj'la</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="352" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Torian</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="353" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Don't know when you'll read this, but I'm certain someday you will. As far as I'm concerned, your status is &quot;missing in action.&quot; Not &quot;presumed dead.&quot; Definitely not &quot;killed in action.&quot;

Whatever happened when that fleet attacked, you got out of it. You've made it through worse. I don't know where you are or why you've gone silent, but I monitor your holofrequency at all times. The moment you transmit a signal, I'll be on it.

If I hear you're behind enemy lines, I'll break through them. And if you're on a mission so secret you couldn't even tell me about it, I'll understand. You need the galaxy to think you're dead, I'll play along--but I know better.

I spent a lifetime waiting to find you. If I have to, I'll spend another waiting for you to come back. That's what love is.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="354" id2="874956" version="1065353216">MIA</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="355" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Felix</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="356" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Dearest,

We've lost the battle. Jorgan and I have pursued every available option, but our final appeal has failed. Legally, you've been declared killed in action. 

I know it's not true. I'm sending this message because I know that somewhere, someday, you'll read it. I will never give up on you. And if the Republic military won't help me find you, I will explore other options. 

We first met on a search and rescue mission--I suppose it's only fitting that we reunite the same way.

Yours always,
Elara</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="357" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Perseverance</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="358" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Elara Dorne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="359" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I'm stuck in a trench with Forex and running low on ammo. Skytrooper dropships are inbound, probably two minutes out. Feels like the longest break I've had in weeks.

We've been fighting these things for two months now. We hunker down and shoot until our barrels melt, and more of them just keep showing up. Getting real tired of it. Might not be so bad if I just had my wife here with me like I'm used to.

I know you're still out there. No way you're dead. 

Two months is long enough. Please come back to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="360" id2="874956" version="1065353216">They just keep coming</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="361" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Aric Jorgan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="362" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Theron Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="363" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Fwd: Firebrand captured</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="364" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Lifted this from Zakuul News Bulletin. Give it a read.

URGENT MESSAGE TO ALL ZAKUUL CITIZENS:

Following the tragic massacre on the Spire, authorities have identified Alianna Slenn as the infamous terrorist Firebrand.

Slenn, whose recent activities caused a catastrophic loss of life throughout our city, has also been implicated in the recent death of her father, Overwatch administrator Tayvor Slenn. She was apprehended by a team of Skytroopers late last night and promptly executed for her crimes against Zakuul.

The red alert issued following the bombings has been removed. A vigil for those lost in the tragedy will take place tomorrow evening.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="365" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Alianna Slenn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="366" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Thank you</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="367" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I don't know why Firebrand didn't go through with the full plan. I have a feeling that was your doing. Either way, I'm glad it didn't happen.
It seemed so exciting and romantic at the time. Then my father died, and I realized this isn't a game. If I hadn't helped Firebrand, maybe he would still be alive.

Things have been hectic since the droid blackout. I heard my neighbors complaining yesterday about having to wash their own clothes. I wanted to tell them to shut up--it could've been so much worse! Because of you, at least no one else got hurt.
If Firebrand is with you, please be careful. She has a way of getting under your skin.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="368" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="369" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Koth's departure</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="370" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Commander,

I didn't want to voice my concerns in person in case someone overheard. I've made sure Theron can't intercept this.

I know Koth too well to believe that we've seen the last of him. He's not one to leave something unfinished, especially if he's passionate about it. He may cool off and realize he made a mistake. Even though he's being a hot-headed idiot right now, we need him, and he needs us. Stay on alert and let me know if you hear from him.

And please--don't judge him too harshly. We all have our breaking points. He simply found his.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="371" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Koth Vortena</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="372" id2="874956" version="1065353216">The new recruit</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="373" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Look, can we keep Kaliyo out of the sabacc games from now on? She played with my crew last night and took them for all they had. Len got back to the barracks without his clothes and wouldn't tell me what happened. He seemed a little traumatized, now that I think about it.

Kaliyo's part of the team now. I respect that. But my people don't get paid enough as it is, and now Mistress Shady's taking what little they do have. I'd appreciate if you could keep her away from them.

And if you could get Len's clothes back, that'd be great. For everyone's sake.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="374" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Seb Lorod</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="375" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Fwd: [no subject]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="376" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Really, Kaliyo? I have to hear from some slimeball pazaak dealer that you're out in Wild Space now? Two years I waited for you, and you couldn't even send a message. I thought you might be dead, thought the bounty hunters had finally caught up to you.

Well, I can take a hint. I saved up for that club we said we'd open together, but I guess I don't need the credits anymore. Take them. That was all I was ever good for, right?

-Seb

NOTE FROM THERON: Intercepted six more messages like this one, all from different people. I try not to judge personal lives, but tell me this isn't evidence to keep Kaliyo at arm's length and use her skills appropriately.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="377" id2="874956" version="1065353216">C2-N2</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="378" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Weekly morale analysis</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="379" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Greetings, Commander! It is my extreme pleasure to present my most recent findings on our delightful camp's morale.

Admiral Aygo and his soldiers have experienced a 12 percent increase in morale after the capture of a minor outpost on Tatooine. May I recommend a small celebration to maximize this boost in happiness?

In tracking Hylo Visz's daily routine, I have observed an 18 percent loss in sleep over the past week. My data also indicate high levels of frustration and increased irritability. Perhaps more comfortable quarters are in order, or even a reassuring hug from her commander!

I have been kept quite busy in my cleaning duties following Kaliyo Djannis's arrival. Our new recruit has conducted six scuffles with Tora to date. All have been resolved with a truce of intoxication and revelry.

I will continue to monitor morale and report any findings. I hope you have an extraordinarily productive day!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="380" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Pashna Veyaad</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="381" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Our purpose</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="382" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I wanted to thank you for everything you've done. You had no reason to assist us, but your support has made all the difference.

Havoc Squad has been running daily drills with my people. Already we've seen a considerable improvement in our skills. Yesterday, we managed to eliminate a small group of Skytroopers without Havoc's help. We may have a fighting chance after all.

But more than that, you've given us hope. Zakuul has failed us. Our Emperor has failed us. But you were there when we needed it, and for that alone, we have a reason to fight. We have a purpose. We will not fail you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="383" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Alise Davros</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="384" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Status update</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="385" id2="874956" version="1065353216">We received your supply drop. The weapons were in excellent condition, with plenty to go around. We thank you for your gifts and have been using them to the best of our ability. Many of us haven't held a blaster before.

We've been planning attacks on the Skytroopers whenever we can. We fight our hardest, but we're dropping quickly. Pashna fell drawing fire from the rest of us. Even in his last moments, he fought to protect his people. I assumed leadership, but it hasn't been the same. I feel us losing hope.

Still, I take comfort knowing we will die fighting. We will not hide and wait for our time to come--we will meet it head on. Thank you for giving us that chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="386" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Hylo Visz</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="387" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Slight issue</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="388" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Hey, Commander. Bit of a problem with our dear Admiral Aygo. Thought you might want to know.

Since Aric Jorgan arrived, he and Aygo have been two grenades in a bandolier. Talking tactics, designing training regimens... I'd swear they're the same person.

With this new &quot;inspiration&quot; egging him on, Aygo has been working his fleet twice as hard. People are getting burnt out. I've overheard complaints in the barracks, something about Jorgan &quot;wedging that vibroblade even farther up--&quot; Well, you get the idea.

I'll have a chat with Aygo about lightening up. Tell him he doesn't need to work so hard to impress his new best friend. The troops can't fight Arcann if there's nothing left of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="389" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Fwd: Urgent reminder</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="390" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Grabbed this from Zakuul News Bulletin. Looks like our pal Arcann is really cracking down.
-Theron

ATTENTION:

A reminder to all Zakuulans that aiding a traitor to the throne is an offense punished without mercy. It is your duty to oppose those who seek to spread turmoil and uncertainty, poisoning our grand society with their lies. In these trying times, we must remember our loyalty--to Zakuul and to the Emperor.

If you are contacted by a traitor to Zakuul, alert the authorities immediately. Skytroopers will be dispatched to apprehend the offender. Failure to turn in a suspected traitor will be treated as a crime against the Empire.

With your assistance, we can keep Zakuul safe and prosperous.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="391" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Doctor Oggurobb</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="392" id2="874956" version="1065353216">That infernal C2-N2</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="393" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Please instruct C2-N2 to kindly stay away from my experiments. I was working on a highly sophisticated piece of artificial intelligence this afternoon, very near completion. But when I returned from my second lunch, I found my work in shambles, a vital data chip fried with cleaning solution.

Apparently, that bumbling droid thought my complicated and delicate experiment looked &quot;dusty&quot; and attempted to clean it for me. Now the data chip is entirely useless, and my afternoon of work has been for nothing. It will take me hours to construct another data chip!

In the future, I would appreciate if you curb that nitwit's urge to &quot;help&quot; me. Otherwise, I'll be forced to break him down and use his parts in compensation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="394" id2="874956" version="1065353216">UNKNOWN SENDER</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="395" id2="874956" version="1065353216">The road ahead</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="396" id2="874956" version="1065353216">You have a long and difficult path before you. There will be moments that test all you stand for, that reveal who you truly are. Meet these challenges head on and show courage, as we know you can.

You must put the galaxy back together, for everyone who unwittingly helped tear it apart. The Eternal Empire took everything; it's up to you to reclaim it.

Marr and I have failed, each in our own way. Our time is ending, but yours is just beginning. Your decisions will define not only the present, but the shape of things to come. We trust you to choose wisely.

May the Force guide you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="397" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Fwd: The truth</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="398" id2="874956" version="1065353216">The original message from Satele painted you in a less flattering light, so I made a few alterations before letting Theron see it. Thought you might want to view my handiwork. The next time you see her, make sure to finish what you started. --Lana

Theron,

I need you to understand something. Despite what you may believe, I am proud of the person you've become. You have grown into a strong, capable man who fights for his beliefs. Everything I hoped you would be.

I cannot be found now, not even with your formidable skills. The commander is a leader worth following; focus on that. Put all your energy into helping the Alliance achieve victory. The Republic is counting on you, Theron. Use this to give you strength.

I will always be proud of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="399" id2="874956" version="1065353216">2V-R8</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="400" id2="874956" version="1065353216">My eternal gratitude</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="401" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Dearest Commander:

I would like to take this opportunity to say how fortunate I am to have such a remarkable master. You are an absolute inspiration, and your service to the galaxy will be recorded in history for eternity. If I had organic ocular functions, I would weep with sheer joy.

I should also to point out that I cleaned your personal quarters to sterile perfection. Not a molecule of dust escapes my watchful eye! I left a nutritious and satisfying array of meals in your refrigeration unit, should you need a late-night snack. I hope to prove how terribly useful I am!

From the bottom of my processor, thank you for allowing me to serve you. You could just as easily have deactivated me. I am a lucky droid indeed to be serving such a champion of order.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="402" id2="874956" version="1065353216">[No Subject]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="403" id2="874956" version="1065353216">It took me a long time to hit send on this one, but I guess you already know I'm not great at this.

You and me, we're used to danger. I've been trained to roll with the punches. I used to think nothing could faze me, but when you vanished without a trace... I couldn't stop pacing. I thought Lana was going to strap me into a chair to keep me still. I didn't know where you were, and I couldn't take it.

You're the commander of the Alliance; I know what that means. You have a long fight ahead of you. Someday you might disappear on me again, somewhere I can't follow. Just know I'll be here waiting for you.

Always.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="404" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Do you know how close I was to sending a search party for you? If Theron hadn't stopped me, I would've charged out there and looked for you myself. Don't ever do that to me again.

All right, that was harsh. I apologize. I know I shouldn't worry about you, but I do. Your duties will put you in danger more times than I can imagine. I have faith you can handle anything. I don't doubt your abilities in the slightest. But that won't stop me from fretting every time you leave without me.

And I swear to the stars, the next time you disappear, I will tear the galaxy apart looking for you. I've done it before, you know. So it's in your best interest to stay out of trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="405" id2="874956" version="1065353216">A little warning: this is going to get sappy.

With all the craziness happening, I wanted to remind you how important you are to me. When you disappeared, I thought I'd go insane. I almost sent my crew on a rescue mission until Lana told me what a stupid idea that was. Sometimes my imagination gets the better of me and I expect the worst. When it comes to you, I can't bear the worst.

I know how much you mean to the galaxy. Just remember how much you mean to me.  Next time you decide to pull a disappearing act, keep me in the loop, all right? I don't like wondering where you are, thinking you might've...

Actually, scratch that. Next time, just take me with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="406" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Dretcher</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="407" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Invoice</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="408" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Tyresius--oh, excuse me, Gault--told me to forward my invoice to you. I'd say I expect you to make good on it, but I know the company Ty keeps.

Identity forging--one human female: 105,000
Damaged combat droids: 42,600
Relocation fee: 38,900
Trandoshan ale, 14 bottles: 22,400
Personalized companion bot--female: 34,750
Antique Mirialan love token--stolen: 15,000
Imported substances--stolen: 28,500
Grievances: 55,250

That last one is an estimate. Psychological damage and all that. Anyway, I expect you to ignore this, so I'll send a bounty hunter after that Devaronian scum in a week or so. Great working with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="409" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Avus Dayne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="410" id2="874956" version="1065353216">My blue flower</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="411" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Vette,

You don't know me, but I'm a pilot with the Alliance fleet. I noticed you the second you stepped on Odessen, and I've been watching you from afar ever since. Sorry, that's creepy, isn't it?

Anyway, I wrote a poem:

My flower of blue,
I pine for you.
Your laugh is so cute,
And your head tentacle things are also cute.

It needs work. But the point is, I think you're pretty and I was wondering if you want to get a drink together. If you don't, tell me and I'll leave you alone forever.

Avus (that's my name)</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="412" id2="874956" version="1065353216">DO NOT READ PREVIOUS MESSAGE</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="413" id2="874956" version="1065353216">My sincerest apologies, Commander. That message was not intended for you. Please delete it without opening.

But if you did read it.... Do you think I have a shot?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="414" id2="874956" version="1065353216">My sincerest apologies, Commander. That message was not intended for you. Please delete it without opening.

And if you already read it, I had no idea you two were involved.

Please don't crush my windpipe.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="415" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Fwd: ATTENTION</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="416" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Look, Commander. You're famous. Transcript from a holotransmission sent to all Zakuulans.

Theron

CITIZENS OF ZAKUUL:

Late last night, the treasury that funds our great Empire was the target of a vicious attack. The rogue terrorist known as the Outlander seeks to dismantle our way of life and infect us with fear and chaos.

Due to the Outlander's deplorable acts of terrorism, this week's formal gala will be postponed indefinitely. Rest assured that our teams are working to correct the issue. Let us stand together and show the galaxy our strength as a united Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="417" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Khomo Fett</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="418" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Vor'e</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="419" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I don't know how you people use these machines to communicate. You need delicate little fingers to press the buttons.

You really proved yourself on the battlefield. I lost a few brothers and sisters, but it could have been a hell of a lot more. It's the best my people have felt in a while, and you showed we can trust your strength as a fighter. And Mand'alor seems to respect you, so Clan Fett has your back.

All this typing is making my blood itch, so I'll just say vor'e. Thanks. You're a true warrior.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="420" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Nar dralshy'a</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="421" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I'll keep this short. My patience for these machines is pretty low, and for you even lower.

I lost a lot of brothers and sisters out there. You sent us to be slaughtered by droids, and for what? Clan Fett is a house of warriors, not cannon fodder. I won't sacrifice my people for someone who doesn't respect us--even if Mand'alor trusts you.

Maybe you care about your allies, maybe you don't. But trust me, you want us alive. Nar dralshy'a. Try harder. Be a better leader.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="422" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Mand'alor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="423" id2="874956" version="1065353216">You really stirred something up with the clans. We lost a lot of brothers and sisters on Darvannis fighting your pointless battle, and you struck a nerve when you questioned Mand'alor. The clans are talking. I don't know if her leadership will hold.

If I know Shae, she won't go down easy. Things might get bloody. The last thing we need is to be fighting each other. But I bet that was your aim all along, wasn't it?

You'd better hope Mand'alor stays on top, for your sake. I guarantee a new leader won't put up with your osik. I wouldn't.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="424" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Torian Cadera</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="425" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Ni kar'tayli gar darasuum</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="426" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Cyar'ika,

When Mand'alor gave me this position, she asked what made me fight so hard. So I told her about you. Your courage, passion, strength. I treated every battle like it'd bring you back.

She taught me a phrase from her clan, and it reminded me of you. Thought about it every day. Chanted it in my head like a battle song.

Ner runi ca kebii'tra,
Bal gar me'suum'ika bal ka'ra.

My soul is the night sky,
And you are the moon and stars.

Always knew I'd find you. Now that you're back, I'm never letting go.

Ni kar'tayli gar darasuum. I love you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="427" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Thanks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="428" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Ner vod,

Wanted to say thanks for letting me stick around. I'll bring honor to Mand'alor and to you.

Things are different here. Not like I expected. Barely settled in and I already have supporters. In Mando'a we call it cyar'tomade, an affectionate group.  People who root for your victories. Never had one in the clans, not like Khomo does. Your people really like my hair. Not sure how I feel about that.

Point is, you need a brother in combat. I'll stand by your side. Let's send the Eternal Empire packing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="429" id2="874956" version="1065353216">SCORPIO</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="430" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Our partnership</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="431" id2="874956" version="1065353216">When we began this partnership, I was careful to manage my expectations. I have often been disappointed by the fickleness of organic beings. But you continue to demonstrate that allying with you is beneficial. The capture of GEMINI Prime is a victory for us both.

You have exceeded my predictions. I admit I underestimated you, even after the impressive displays I've witnessed. In the future, I will be sure to have higher expectations.

I trust I have proven that an alliance with me is equally valuable. I look forward to seeing what more we can accomplish together.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="432" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Gault Rennow</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="433" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Your investment</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="434" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Here's an update on that little investment of your Gilded Star plunder. Buddy of mine is running weapons to civilians on conquered planets looking to arm themselves against the Eternal Empire. Your credits got him enough stock to ensure business is booming. We're helping regular folk fight back. And we're turning a profit on it! Everyone wins.

You're not out of the red yet, but if Vel's business keeps up, you'll be rolling in credits in no time. Then you can do whatever you want with it. Make Miss Moral Compass happy and shower the oppressed people in riches. Buy everyone a shiny new pair of shoes. Whatever.

Anyway, I sent you a little something to prove your investment is in good hands. Let no one say old Gault doesn't take care of his friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="435" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Malita Tal</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="436" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Thank you</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="437" id2="874956" version="1065353216">You had no reason to trust one of your enemy's people. Thank you for understanding that Zakuul is more than its emperor. For choosing to save my life.

I've contacted my Zakuulan followers who believe in my cause and yours. I told them what you did for me, and you have their full support. My people can do nothing publicly while Arcann holds the power to silence them, but they wanted me to pass on this message: We stand with the Alliance.

You have the power to inspire, Outlander. You're everything I thought you would be.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="438" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Tai Cordan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="439" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Ready to help</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="440" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I know not everyone made it off that ship. I wish things had gone differently. We had our differences, but we all agreed on you.

I reached out to a few old friends on Republic worlds, sympathetic ears who would be interested to hear how you saved my life. You're gaining traction among those who won't roll over and let the Eternal Empire win. The Republic will still fight behind the right leader. Now more than ever, I'm confident that person is you.

It feels good to be useful again. Thanks for giving me something to believe in.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="441" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Zasha Ranken</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="442" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I'm on your side</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="443" id2="874956" version="1065353216">It seems I owe you my life, Commander. I was one of the lucky ones to escape that death trap. I'll earn the chance you gave me.

I contacted Empress Acina and told her what you did for me. She can't officially do anything yet, of course, but you have the Sith Empire's gratitude. I imagine that will be useful. Personally, I stand with the Alliance. I'll reach out to my old Sith friends and bend a few ears your way.

I look forward to seeing you grind the Eternal Empire to dust.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="444" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Fwd: Important message</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="445" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Take a look at this. People are already asking questions on Zakuul. - Theron

Reminder to all Zakuulans:

Spreading false rumors about your emperor is grounds for treason, and will be dealt with accordingly.

Emperor Arcann remains in power, battling off-world to preserve our great empire. He fights for all Zakuulans. Any contradictory news is vicious Alliance propaganda intended to sow doubt into the minds of good people. The vile Outlander seeks to diminish our emperor and throw us into chaos.

It is your civic duty to stop these harmful rumors. Crush these lies, and show the Alliance they hold no power over us.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="446" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Doctor Oggurobb</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="447" id2="874956" version="1065353216">GEMINI Prime</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="448" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Commander,

I regret to inform you that our attempts to reactivate GEMINI Prime have failed. We tried a variety of tactics: electromagnetic pulses, processor slicing, percussive maintenance, and so forth. These methods yield favorable results in nearly all droid models, yet I haven't managed to produce even a spark of life in Prime. My scans indicate she's still functional, but inactive.

I still have a trick or two up my metaphorical sleeve, but I am not optimistic about the results. Whatever issued the shut-down command seems to have an absolute hold over her. It appears we can only wait and hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="449" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Fwd: The Grand Coronation of Empress Vaylin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="450" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Vaylin sure didn't waste any time. --Theron

Citizens of Zakuul,

You are hereby invited to the coronation holo-cast for Empress Vaylin, our magnificent new ruler. Witness her ascension to the Eternal Throne as Zakuul enters a new era of strength and prosperity.

The broadcast begins promptly at sundown and can be viewed in the center square of each district. As always, transportation and celebratory noisemakers will be provided. A festival will be held following the event.

Please note: Attendance is mandatory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="451" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Bey'wan Aygo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="452" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Reinforcements</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="453" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Since the battle ended, a steady stream of Republic and Imperial ships have touched down on Odessen. They all want to join the Alliance and do some real good for once. We've nearly doubled the size of our fleet, and I doubt this will be the last round of recruits.

Normally, I'd advise caution. Technically, these are defectors joining your ranks. But that would make this Republic &quot;defector&quot; a hypocrite. I say we take all the help we can get. We'll need it if we're gunning for Vaylin.

It's been an uphill battle keeping the Imps and Pubs from each other's throats. I guess old habits die hard. Luckily, you're the one thing they all agree on. After watching you take down Arcann, they'll follow you anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="454" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Still no luck</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="455" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I used every resource at my disposal to locate Senya's vessel. Docking records on every major planet came up empty. Patrol ships in the Core Worlds and Wild Space reported no sightings. She simply vanished.

I'm sure you had your reasons for letting her escape, and I support your decision. That doesn't mean I understand it. If Arcann recovers and comes hunting for revenge, we may not be as lucky as we were today.

Senya was a valuable ally. I understand that better than anyone--I'm the one who brought her here. But promise me that if it becomes necessary to eliminate her, you won't hesitate.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="456" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I apologize, Commander. I was the one who brought Senya to the Alliance, but I couldn't have known she would turn on us. 

What's done is done. Now I intend to fix it.

I used every resource at my disposal to locate Senya's vessel. Docking records on every major planet came up empty. Patrol ships in the Core Worlds and Wild Space reported no sightings. She's simply vanished.

In a perfect world, your shot destroyed them all. But I know better than to assume things went perfectly. I'll keep an ear out for any leads. I promise you, we will find Arcann and his traitorous mother.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="457" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Gravestone whereabouts</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="458" id2="874956" version="1065353216">Koth's betrayal didn't surprise me at all. I even expected the Hutt-brain to steal his precious ship, which is why I installed a tracker on the Gravestone. Problem is, Captain Sticky Fingers found the device before I could get a solid lock on him. But I did manage to grab some info.

The Gravestone left hyperspace near Balmorra before the tracking signal went dark. I called a buddy planetside, who tells me a ship fitting the Gravestone's description blasted an Eternal Fleet vessel out of the sky. Then it scooped up a handful of refugees from the village the fleet destroyed. Looks like flyboy is playing hero, just like he said he would.

You want my opinion? Keep an eye out for people in distress. That's where you'll find him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="459" id2="874956" version="1065353216">GEMINI sighting</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="460" id2="874956" version="1065353216">I got eyes all over the place, and a friend just told me the most interesting story.

Said he was on Hoth, scavenging in the starship graveyard, when he hears this deafening roar. Suddenly, an Eternal Fleet warship lands on the ice, less than a kilometer away. After a few minutes, the airlock opens and a droid steps out. Then it stares at the frozen wasteland. For an hour. Just taking in the scenery.

Then the droid got back into the vessel and took off. That was the end of that. My friend can't make heads or tails of it, and neither can I. Gives me the creeps.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
