<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>102</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/sith_inquisitor.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="575047" version="1065353216">You have given the last Rakata hope, Sith. The Mother Machine recorded your pattern. We have dissected your power, analyzed it. Thanks to you, we have made breakthroughs unrivaled for a thousand years.

It may be many centuries yet, but I am now certain we will be able to replicate your power and restore our civilization and its wonders. On that day, the Rakata will be whole once more.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="575047" version="1065353216">The Rakata reborn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Warden Gorshaa</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Child, 

Belsavis is mine. My children are free, and for the first time in several millennia, my future is my own. 

Soon, I will birth a new species. These children will be of my own making, no longer constrained by the Rakata's vain attempt to save themselves.

Perhaps I will base them off you. A mother cannot help but be proud of all that you have become.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="575047" version="1065353216">New life</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Ashaa</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="575047" version="1065353216">My lord, I just received word of Darth Thanaton's cowardice. I may know little of the Kaggath, but I'm fairly certain that scampering off is NOT the path to victory.

Bad enough that Thanaton attempted to sabotage the Empire's war efforts for personal gain. Now he defiles his own traditions to save his skin. 

It's clear the Empire needs more Sith like you in positions of power. So please, my lord--crush him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="575047" version="1065353216">He RAN?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Moff Pyron</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="575047" version="1065353216">I just heard the news. Nomar is dead.

I can scarcely believe it. I've lived in the shadow of Nomar's rejection for twenty years now. After decades of heartbreak, I'm finally free of the man. 

I suppose I ought to thank you. But your presence on Alderaan reopened wounds I thought mended decades ago.

That said, do me a favor and never come back to Alderaan.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Moving on</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Rehanna Rist</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Destris is getting worse, my lord. His dedication to your cult has become fanatical and destructive. It's heartbreaking to watch.

He's actually started FORCING people to join the cult now. I've lost count of the number of times our recruitment talks have devolved into outright violence. His actions are perverting everything we try to do.

I'll have to talk to him, try to reason with him. I know he won't want to hear what I have to say, but I've known Destris for a long time. He may be in a bad place, but I'm certain I can bring him back.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Worried about Destris</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Rylee Dray</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="575047" version="1065353216">It took some investigating, but I finally figured out how you engineered that &quot;miracle&quot; of yours. Rigging explosives to simulate a groundquake? Clever, my lord.

I may have to resort to similar theatrics. One of the more powerful gangs on Nar Shaddaa is threatening to topple our glorious cult. 
	
You needn't worry, though. I've faced many would-be usurpers and I've crushed them all. 

Well, almost all, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="575047" version="1065353216">A threat to the cult</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Lord Paladius</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="575047" version="1065353216">You can rest easy, my lord. Your cult is back in order.

I finally spoke to Destris, explained how his violent behavior was destroying the cult. He denied it all, thought I was just making a power play. We nearly came to blows.
 
It wasn't until I compared him to Lord Paladius and pointed out the similarities that he finally caved and realized what he'd become. Honestly, it was like a dam had burst.

He's back on the path now and doing what he can to restore the cult's reputation. Wasn't easy, but I believe your cult will emerge from all this stronger than ever, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Settling affairs</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Rylee Dray</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="575047" version="1065353216">You'll be happy to know that the malefactors threatening your cult have been dealt with, my lord. All it took was a proper show of power.

I attempted to simulate a groundquake, as you did, and claimed that I was &quot;channeling the master's boundless power.&quot; However, I made a SLIGHT miscalculation--and leveled an entire neighborhood. 

Fortunately, most of the gang members were killed in the ensuing carnage. While that wasn't quite the intended effect, I believe the end result is satisfactory. 

I don't foresee anyone else opposing us for a long, long time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Miracle mishap</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Lord Paladius</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="575047" version="1065353216">My lord, 

Although you have my unwavering support, I would appreciate some discretion regarding my recent defection on Quesh. Traitors are rarely welcomed in civilized company, and I'd rather not find myself on the Dark Council's bad side should your bout with Darth Thanaton end in tragedy.

By the by, if you ever find yourself on Sullust, you simply MUST stop by Miep's Bistro. I tell you, it is THE gourmet experience in Brema Sector. Their brandy would shame Alderaan's finest vintage, and the waiters never leave your glass dry.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="575047" version="1065353216">A gentleman's recommendation</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Lord Cineratus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="575047" version="1065353216">know our business is done and you aint too interested in hearing more out of me, but I want to wish you good luck with andronikos. 

hes good people, real good. Just dont cross him huh? He doesnt deserve to go thru that again.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Good Luck</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Casey Rix</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="575047" version="1065353216">I apologize for sending you this message uninvited, my lord, but I do so only to fulfill my bargain with the hermit of the tomb--the one called Spindrall.

He said that I could only leave his sight alive if I passed along this, his &quot;final gift for the one who will shape fates both future and ancient.&quot;

Those were his words, his exact words. I had to be exact.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="575047" version="1065353216">The Gift of Spindrall</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Acolyte Shinos</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="575047" version="1065353216">My lord, 

We've examined the markings on Horak-Mul's sarcophagus. It's a nearly complete record of his achievements. It's all here: the Subjugation of the False Apprentice; Horak-Mul's great loyalty to Ludo Kressh; even the naval battle above Khar Delba, where Horak-Mul was killed by the Sadow'een. Amazing! And being buried on Yavin Four suggests he had followers in secret who survived the battle.

But we've found no trace of the ancient signs of his office. We know the Eye of Horak-Mul was seized by the Jedi centuries ago, but we were hoping to find the remains of his ceremonial robe or the tablets he created alongside Dor Gal-ram. At least we have the sarcophagus.

Your servant, 
Qualus Sorrel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Horak-Mul</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Engineer Sorrel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="575047" version="1065353216">I thought I was a dead man after I testified against Essor Kayin. Not many acolytes can rat out a Dark Council member's apprentice and live to tell about it. But I'm still breathing. I figure I have you to thank for that. 

I don't know what you said to Inquisitor Zyn, but it worked. He helped me lie low in the Academy until he could ship me off to Dromund Kaas. Now I'm apprenticing to some crotchety old Darth (sorry, no names!). She's a tyrant, but at least she's not trying to kill me. Yet.

Anyway, I owe you one.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Close one</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Acolyte Alif</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Inquisitor Zyn has informed me that it was you who uncovered Essor Kayin's hand in my apprentice's death. I suspected Essor--the fool has always been a nuisance--but I needed proof before acting. The acolyte's testimony will suffice.

As I am a man who settles his debts (a fact young Essor will soon learn), I'd like to extend my gratitude for your assistance in this matter. You've a sharp mind and a keen eye for details--no doubt you'd make a fine apprentice. 

A pity another already has her eye on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Debts paid</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Lord Necus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Local scuttlebutt is that some mechanical monstrosity of a Sith Lord was recently assassinated--I assume, then, that my cyber neutralizer worked as intended?

Don't worry, I won't say anything. I know better than to involve myself in Sith politics. Still, a craftsman can't help but take pride in his work.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Success!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Dorotsech</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Apprentice,

Consider yourself lucky I didn't ask for your help in clearing out Darth Skotia's chambers--the amount of sheer clutter in here is staggering. It'll take me at least a week to sort everything out. I daresay this is one of the less glamorous aspects of seizing a rival's powerbase.

There are plenty of treasures to be found here, however. Given your pivotal role in Skotia's demise, it's only fitting you receive some of the spoils. Enjoy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Tidying up</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Lord Zash</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Friends and associates,

It is with the utmost pride that I inform you all that, after a daring escape from Republic forces on Balmorra, my son, Hiran, successfully completed his first mission for Lord Esdras. I tell you, that boy will be a full-fledged Sith Lord before the year is out!

Unfortunately, important Sith business has kept Hiran from returning my calls, so if any of you see him, please give the lad his father's love.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Hiran's made it!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Major Bessiker</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="575047" version="1065353216">My lord, 

Just following up to make sure neither the Colicoid serum nor your exposure to toxic waste has resulted in any unpleasant side effects. Although I have nothing but the utmost faith in Doctor Tyrek's skills, I'd still recommend a full medical examination as soon as possible. Better safe than sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Feeling well?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Major Ilun</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="575047" version="1065353216">My lord,

I'm happy to report that your cult is positively thriving! People are still talking about that little &quot;display of power&quot; we rigged, and we're seeing a steady stream of new converts.

Destris is a natural leader: strong, willful, reassuring. Still, he can be a bit... overbearing at times. Seems awfully eager to flaunt his new authority. Let's hope he didn't pick up any bad habits from Lord Paladius.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="575047" version="1065353216">The Screaming Blade Cult</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Rylee Dray</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="575047" version="1065353216">You were wise to leave me in charge of your cult, my lord--our numbers have nearly doubled since you left.

We've had a few &quot;incidents&quot; with some of the local gangs, but the strength of our numbers and the righteousness of our cause have swayed their hearts time after time. Mark my words, we'll have the denizens of Nar Shaddaa chanting your name soon enough!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="575047" version="1065353216">The Screaming Blade cult</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Lord Paladius</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="575047" version="1065353216">I understand our &quot;attack&quot; on the Togruta Padawan went as scripted. I hope you found the results satisfactory.

Given that I have a reputation to maintain, I trust you'll keep our arrangement a secret. Planned or not, I don't want it getting out that my assassins failed to kill one measly Padawan.

Feel free to contact me if you require my services again. No more theatrics, though. My men were not trained to fail</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="575047" version="1065353216">A successful ambush</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Lord Anathemos</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Have you lost your senses? When I agreed to help you stage an ambush on that Jedi Padawan, I was NOT giving you permission to slaughter my men.

I will not forget this betrayal. I hope one Padawan pup was worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="575047" version="1065353216">You lying filth</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Lord Anathemos</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="575047" version="1065353216">I have found a new place for the Gormak. It is small, but away from the Voss. Away from mad Gormak king.

One day, I will return, guide other Gormak to the stars, guide them to peace. Maybe you come with us, dreaming one.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Among the stars</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Hadrik</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="575047" version="1065353216">It has come to my attention that a Gormak acquaintance of yours recently attempted to flee Voss. I don't know what possessed you to associate with such a creature, but I am relieved that you came to your senses and prevented the beast from leaving.

The Voss barely tolerate our presence as is, and I could certainly do without even more of their incessant whining. Thank you for sparing me that.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Diplomatic crisis averted</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Darth Serevin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="328" id2="575047" version="1065353216">I try not to think about the past anymore. It's done, loose ends tied off. Probably better that way.

Then I realize how long I've been with this crew, and I start thinking anyway. Trying to figure how we ended up together. How I started sharing nights with a Sith Lord--and not just for kicks, either.

Scares me that I don't have a clue. Guess I'm lucky, but you can't trust luck.

What I can do is fight. You make me want to fight for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Late Night, Too Sober</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Andronikos Revel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="575047" version="1065353216">It's not like I never got something for a girl before. Necklaces, fancy dresses, ex-boyfriends in stun-cuffs.

With you, I feel like a hunting dog dragging prey to his master. Not sure if he's done right, or if he'll be laughed at.

You don't like the gift, you got a choice. You tell me to my face, and I tell you how I got it. You're not impressed, blasters and lightsabers come out. Sparks fly. We have a good time.

Or you don't tell me, but I figure it out because I know you better than you want to think. And I try again.

However you want it, Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Something for you</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Andronikos Revel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Don't know if we'll always be crewmates. I like it here, but things change. I get restless, you get bored, who knows?

That ever happens, give it a few years. Doesn't matter how powerful you are, I'll be back with a whole fleet.

We're in each other's orbits until the stars go cold.

That's love, isn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Love and War</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Andronikos Revel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="575047" version="1065353216">I've been going through my daily meditations like always, but I can't seem to focus on the moment like I should.

I keep fixating on the past: looking back at our time together, at the patience you showed while I adapted to this life. I knew you were special then, but I don't think I realized how special.

The Force is trying to show me that this is where I'm meant to be, that I've found the person I'm meant to be with. I just know it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Meditations</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Ashara Zavros</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="575047" version="1065353216">I don't mean to make a big deal out of it or anything, but I got you something the last time you were out.

I'm so new to all of this--I really didn't have a clue what to get. I had to get Andronikos to help me. He even let me fly the ship!

But anyway, I really hope you like it. Even if you don't, though, just know that I really love you, okay? But I think you'll like it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="575047" version="1065353216">For You</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Ashara Zavros</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="343" id2="575047" version="1065353216">This war just keeps going. All of the violence, all of the hatred, all of the misunderstanding. People just won't open their eyes.

I think we're going to have to fight together for a long time before things change. But I'm ready.

With you, I know we'll bring the peace we've been hoping for.

I love you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="344" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Hoping for Peace</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="345" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Ashara Zavros</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="346" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Darth Marr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="347" id2="575047" version="1065353216">On Recent Events</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="348" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Dark Lord, 

The Sith Empire rises.

While the extraction of isotope-5 proceeds slowly, it proceeds all the same. And while our victory on Tython was short-lived, it proved to the galaxy that we are far from diminished.

We continue to press forward with Admiral Ranken's initiative in the Kuat system, and the rogue Czerka moon has become a symbol for Imperial resistance against the Republic's heightened aggressions.

Do not think for a moment that I am unaware of your contributions. Among the Dark Council, you have far and away played the most vital role in addressing these matters directly. For that, you have my gratitude.

Great days await us, but we must first endure the many trials that are sure to come.

Darth Marr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="349" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Darth Marr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="350" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Arkous and You</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="351" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Dark Lord, 

I recently had a chance to speak with our colleague Darth Arkous. He had much to say about you.

According to Arkous, the two of you have worked together a great deal since reclaiming Korriban, and you have built a strong rapport. In fact, he went so far as to describe your contribution as &quot;invaluable&quot;. The Dark Council could use more accord among its members; I hope your example serves as inspiration.

Arkous did not elaborate on what the two of you have been up to, though I can imagine many ways in which your knowledge of ancient secrets could be of assistance to Arkous's military strategies. I look forward to hearing more about it when next we meet.

Darth Marr</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="352" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Spindrall</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="353" id2="575047" version="1065353216">A vision</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="354" id2="575047" version="1065353216">With all who have passed through the catacombs in search of my wisdom, you might think I would forget a single acolyte. In truth, I remember every last one. I am not in the habit of corresponding with them, however--nor with anyone else, for that matter.

You have surely learned a great deal to have catapulted yourself into the Dark Council in so brief a span. But there is always more to learn.

The Force roils and convulses like never before. I reached out to study its peculiar activity, and in turn it showed me what is to come. You stand on a moon, defiantly, before one who is not one. You do not stand alone, but you fail all the same.

This fate appears unavoidable... but avoid it you must.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="355" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Moff Pyron</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="356" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Status Update</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="357" id2="575047" version="1065353216">Dark Lord,

Regretfully, I have indeed found agents of the Order of Revan within our ranks. Bunk searches conducted during surprise field missions provided the opportunity to identify several adherents. Of those, I chose one weak link to break. I'm going to wait until I feel he's given me everything I need to excise the remainder. I don't want a single mole left.

Speaking of which, my investigations also uncovered the unauthorized use of override transmission codes aboard the Doombringer. They were traced to an engineer we'd intended to question, but she fired herself out an airlock before we could arrest her. I believe she was in the employ of a particular freelance spy network.

I can only express my gross discontent in these matters, my lord. I will have security redouble their screening efforts in all future assignments to the fleet.

--Moff Pyron</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
