<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>120</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/sith_warrior.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="575046" version="1065353216">I know about the late Overseer Tremel. The acolytes whisper of his death at the hands of Darth Baras, but it was you who dealt the killing blow. 

Well done.

Overseer Tremel was not a true Sith, his bloodline muddied by slave breeding. But now that his tainted blood hardens in cold veins, I will see that his replacement is not so impure.

Heed your new master, and continue to honor the true Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Tremel's Retirement</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Lord Abaron</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Teeno and I thought we could kill Vemrin, and you talked us down. Now we owe you our lives.

I just watched that monster go toe-to-toe with six other acolytes. Vemrin toyed with them and laughed in their dying faces. He was still laughing when he fed them to a tuk'ata.

My hands are still shaking. That would have been us. I may never be as strong as you or Vemrin, but thanks to you I now know the limits of my strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Vemrin the Monster</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Phyne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="575046" version="1065353216">I've failed you, friend. The acolytes and I promised we'd eliminate Vemrin, but he proved too strong. Poor Teeno died instantly. I still hear his screams.

Vemrin got to me too. I only just woke from my coma, and the doctors say I won't walk for months. Lying here, I've learned to own my agony. 

I realize why you sent us after Vemrin. You knew he'd kill us or make us stronger. Teeno was weak, but I survived. And though I may be crippled for now, my hate gives me strength. For that, I thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="575046" version="1065353216">No Match for Vemrin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Phyne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="575046" version="1065353216">I never thought I'd say this to a Sith, but thank you. 

My wife and I have moved to Dromund Kaas. At first, Parvin hated it--these lightning storms play havoc with her nerves. But she's beginning to come around. As I tell her every day, at least we're alive.

Tomorrow we're to meet a Sith named Darth Baras for questioning. I hope he shares your good nature.

Whatever happens with Jaesa, please treat our daughter well. All we've ever wanted is her happiness.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="575046" version="1065353216">New life in the Empire</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Gregor Willsaam</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="575046" version="1065353216">My spies have intercepted a message intended for Nomen Karr. The Padawan anguishes over her parents' loss. Excellent work, apprentice.

To: Nomen Karr
From: Jaesa Willsaam
Subject: My parents

They're dead, master. I know it. I felt their final, painful moments.

My parents gave up everything for me. Now they're gone because of who I am, what I've become.

This has to stop.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="575046" version="1065353216">FW: My parents</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Darth Baras</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Your lenient ways have proven fruitful, my apprentice. But do not let this encourage further clemency.

To: Darth Baras
From: Commander Pritch
Subject: Slave Revolt

The slave captains have seen reason, my lord. Your apprentice preferred blackmail to bloodshed and secured proof that they're selling their own back into slavery. 

Fear of exposure has ensured the slave captains' silence. All blackmail threats against you have ceased. Furthermore, they have generously donated the profits of their slave trade to you. 

The slave revolt now rages without error. I will continue to monitor the situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="575046" version="1065353216">FW: Slave Revolt</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Darth Baras</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Your dedication to brutality is commendable, my apprentice. Study Commander Pritch's report and remember the value of aggression.

To: Darth Baras
From: Commander Pritch
Subject: Slave Captains

The slave captains are dead, my lord. Your apprentice exterminated every voice foolish enough to attempt blackmail against you.

The surviving slaves wage the revolt you designed with renewed strength. They now know the price of disappointing the great Darth Baras.

I will continue to monitor the insurgence. Thanks to your apprentice, the slaves' continued obedience is assured.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="575046" version="1065353216">FW: Slave Captains</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Darth Baras</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Our ploy has worked, acolyte. I escaped Korriban in disguise without arousing Darth Baras's suspicion.

Though free, I mustn't stop moving. I instructed thousands of Sith. If even one recognizes me, Baras will hunt me down and punish your treachery. For this reason I have left Imperial space.

Remember my teachings, and watch yourself. Darth Baras is a master tactician who will not suffer defiance.

May we meet again one day.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Beyond the Grave</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Overseer Tremel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="575046" version="1065353216">My lord, I have discovered an unexpected surprise. Per Imperial Ordinance 33-618, paragraph c, the Ministry of War issues incentives to married personnel in active service.

The reward just came through, along with a personal message from the Minister himself. He sends his respectful congratulations to my lord.

You are truly making waves within the Empire. I continue to count my luck at being your loyal captain and dutiful husband.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Marriage Incentives</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Malavai Quinn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="575046" version="1065353216">My lord, 

Pierce just slipped me a study that's been circulating around the Imperial military. It includes some grim claims about Sith and non-Sith relationships. No doubt Pierce's feeble attempt to drive a wedge between us.

According to this data, Sith partners are 210% more likely to commit adultery than &quot;normal people&quot;--their term. Non-Force users, on the other hand, have a 32% increased mortality rate after marrying a Sith.

Military conjecture and fabricated reports will never shake my feelings for you. If I must die young, I'd rather do it by your side on the front lines of battle than behind a desk on Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Sith Relationship Study</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Malavai Quinn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="575046" version="1065353216">My lord, 

In light of our close relations, I thought it prudent to compile an infant contingency report.

Bearing a child will temporarily sap your strength, creating a need for increased defenses. Once born, the infant will require constant guard against your many enemies. I also recommend Broonmark and Pierce be kept at a distance.

With our connections, entry into the Empire's top military academies shouldn't be an issue. If Force sensitive, the child will continue your legacy at the Sith Academy.

Merely something to consider, my lord. Should the matter arise, I will gladly nurture our offspring--without sacrificing work performance, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Infant Contingency Report</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Malavai Quinn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="575046" version="1065353216">I'm still thinking about last time, when we were alone. I hunger to indulge my appetite once more. But first, I want to share a dream with you--so you, too, can share my anticipation.

In this dream, I'm a frail, helpless Padawan struggling to forge my first lightsaber. My foolish Jedi Master stands over me, unaware that a mighty Sith approaches.

You cut my Master down with your lightsaber. I turn, horrified but in awe of your incredible power. You command me to bow, and I obey.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Anticipation</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Jaesa Willsaam</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="575046" version="1065353216">You're the most incredible, powerful, awe-inspiring Sith I've ever known. Naturally, I thought there was no way I alone could satisfy you.

That is why I planted a tracking device on you, to confirm my suspicions that I was one of many women in your life. 

But forgive me, my lord. I was wrong. You remained true. I will never lose faith in you again. Please accept this gift as my tribute to your superiority.

Oddly enough, I feel slightly disappointed. I was looking forward to hunting down your other female companions. Punishing them would have been such fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Question of faith</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Jaesa Willsaam</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Being your wife is a thrill, my lord. But what good is marriage if I can't rub it in the faces of my enemies? I couldn't resist sending word of our union to House Organa. The Jedi Council, too.

House Organa was not pleased, but their reactions paled to the despair the news elicited from the Jedi Council. Imagine, their prized Padawan is now wife to the most powerful Sith in the galaxy. Pity Nomen Karr wasn't able to attend the ceremony.

If I'd remained a Jedi, none of these pleasures would be mine. Thank you, my lord, my husband</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="575046" version="1065353216">The joys of marriage</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Jaesa Willsaam</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Do you know what today is? Exactly one week ago you removed my shock collar. Or was it six months? I'm bad with dates.

Anyway, I got you something special. It's stupid, I know, but I couldn't stop myself. If you don't like it, you can tell me. I don't want to be &quot;that&quot; wife.

Speaking of wife, I just remembered I never told you my dress size. In case, I don't know, you ever want to pick something up for me. Not that you have to, or anything.

P.S. On our next anniversary, we can celebrate again! Say, next week?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Anniversary</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Vette</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="575046" version="1065353216">This ship's cramped. I keep trying to make some alone time, just you and me, but every time I ask, Broonmark growls at me and Jaesa gets that look in her eye.

So I started thinking honeymoon. You know--vacation in paradise? I contacted a travel agent, found a few hot spots:

Star Cluster Suites, Nar Shaddaa (comped meals, generous casino credit)
Cloudside Resorts, Makeb (remote, five stars, dramatic views)
Whitecap Spa, Manaan (seafood, kolto peels, underwater suite)

Think about it. A little vacation would do wonders for that Sith complexion.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Alone time</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Vette</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="575046" version="1065353216">I know I'm getting ahead of myself with this baby thing, but hear me out.

Let's say we have a kid. Or we adopt, or whatever. Your ship's no place to raise anything short of a tuk'ata. Way too many sharp corners and Sithy things lying around.

Maybe we convert the medbay into a nursery. All it needs is a few lights, some decorations. Maybe Quinn could pull nanny duty. No kiddie leashes, though.

But seriously, no pressure or anything. I'm just planning for the future--now that you're stuck with me, we're in love, all that mushy stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Little ones</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Vette</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="575046" version="1065353216">The sands of Tatooine shift eternally, but they hide great truths. I know this thanks to your inspiration, my lord.

When you returned from Tatooine's Forbidden Pass, I found the strength to conquer my fears. I followed the ghosts of your footprints into the desert, to the home of Jedi Master Yonlach.

The Jedi lay dead, covered by a thin layer of sand. As your guide, I played a part in his death--and I couldn't face it. Now I've accepted the blame, and I'm not ashamed.

This is what I feared. Not the desert's mysteries, but the truth they would reveal about myself. Thank you for shattering my delusions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Taking responsibility</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Sharack Breev</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Since guiding you across Tatooine, I have learned much from tracking your path, my lord.

Your fading footprints accompanied me into the Forbidden Pass, a place I once feared. There I found the home of Jedi Master Yonlach and braced myself for the sight of a massacre. Thankfully, I was wrong.

Master Yonlach welcomed me and spoke of your unexpected kindness. I hid my role in your encounter as we exchanged stories from the wastes.

Thanks to you, cowardice no longer constrains me. I have conquered my fear of the Forbidden Pass, and I will not stop scouting these deserts until I have discovered every last secret they hold.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Desert pilgrimage</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Sharack Breev</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="575046" version="1065353216">It feels like years since I instructed you on Korriban. Ever since you defied Baras's orders to kill me, I've remained in hiding. My missing hand still itches for Baras's throat.

I followed your rise from acolyte to lord, mourned your death on Quesh. Imagine my surprise when Darth Vowrawn contacted me and claimed you still live.

I cannot hide any longer. When you stand against Darth Baras, I will stand with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="575046" version="1065353216">An Old Friend</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Overseer Tremel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="575046" version="1065353216">I knew this day would come, my lord. When you struck me down on Nar Shaddaa and bound me in service, I promised I would help you destroy Darth Baras.

Your new ally, Darth Vowrawn, knows of my intentions. I will meet you both when it is time to march against Baras.

For years I've hungered for the agony of your pompous former master. At last it's time to make him scream.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="575046" version="1065353216">The fall of Baras</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Lord Rathari</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="575046" version="1065353216">So you're the one who killed the Jedi Timmns. Twelve years I hunted that wily scum across half the galaxy. Then I lose the kill right when I've got him cornered on Belsavis.

Timmns and I had history. He captured my wife--wickedest Sith you've ever seen. She was one of Darth Baras's Sith infiltrators. She started naming names, and Baras made me silence her. All because of Master Timmns.

No way you could've known I was after Timmns. That's why I don't grudge you stealing my revenge. I just hope you made the green Jedi scream.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Revenge on Timmns</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Jorem Yange</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="575046" version="1065353216">I have had much to consider since our alliance on Belsavis. Darth Ekkage is one matter, but a Jedi cooperating with a Sith is unprecedented.

When I told the Jedi Council of our partnership, they couldn't believe it. For hours they debated, wondering how the Sith who hunted Jaesa Willsaam could show such restraint. Confusion and prejudice clouds their minds.

Your actions gave me hope. Though it may be decades before another Sith and Jedi join hands, I will ensure that our alliance serves as an example for all students of the Jedi Academy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="575046" version="1065353216">A Welcome Alliance</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Master Timmns</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="575046" version="1065353216">The false Voice silenced. Darth Baras exposed, broken and discarded. The Emperor is most pleased, Wrath.

The Hand applauds your actions and regrets its absence. We have been summoned home. This war no longer requires us on the front lines.

Know that the Emperor wishes to meet his Wrath, but present circumstances do not allow it. Instead, he offers this gift--a fitting reward for the Emperor's Wrath.

You remain the Wrath, enforcer of the Emperor's will. The Hand will contact you again, when the time is right.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="575046" version="1065353216">The Emperor's Thanks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Servant One of the Emperor's Hand</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="328" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Wrath, we have an important matter to discuss. It is time you knew the secret of the Emperor's absence.

While you silenced Darth Baras, the Jedi attempted the impossible feat of destroying the Emperor. Instead, they merely defeated the Emperor's true Voice. 

The unexpected blow was a shock. The Emperor's consciousness was wrenched from his Voice. He now slumbers, gathering his strength.

The Imperial Guard has moved the Emperor's body. As his Wrath, you will soon be called upon to rain fury on the Emperor's attackers.

Speak of this to no one. The Hand will contact you with further orders shortly. In the meantime, continue your service to the Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="575046" version="1065353216">The Emperor's Absence</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Servant One of the Emperor's Hand</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="575046" version="1065353216">The Emperor's recovery continues. But while he slumbers, his Wrath is needed more than ever.

The Empire echoes with whispered rumors of the Emperor's weakness. Baras was the first of many Sith to grow bold in our master's absence. Some even suspect the Emperor's death.

It is the duty of the Wrath to silence these rumors. 

Show the Empire your incredible strength. Devastate your enemies in the Emperor's name. Only then will the transgressors bow to you in awe and renew their devotion to our master.

The Emperor's return approaches. Prepare for his ascendance, Wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Unleashing the Wrath</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Servant One of the Emperor's Hand</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="575046" version="1065353216">You serve me well, apprentice. Lord Rathari's dying screams have sent shockwaves throughout the Sith Order. His death heralds my mounting influence.

I have seized Rathari's holdings, dissolved his power base and reduced his legacy to a forgotten nightmare. Only one scrap remains.

Enclosed you will find the last of Rathari's possessions--a prize for skewering the fool Sith. You have earned it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Remnants of Rathari</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Darth Baras</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="575046" version="1065353216">I have done as you asked, my lord. My power base has withdrawn from Nar Shaddaa. We now bow in supplication as your loyal servants.

No doubt Darth Baras still sniffs for my corpse. I will give him a whiff of my death to hide our deceit. But this only delays the inevitable.

Sooner or later you will earn Baras's disfavor. I will gather my strength in preparation for that day. And when my lord opposes Baras, I will stand by your side.

Until then, I remain your servant in the shadows.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Your faithful servant</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Lord Rathari</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="575046" version="1065353216">I have respected your terms of banishment. As far as the Empire is concerned, Lord Rathari is no more.

In solitude, my meditations are haunted by our last battle. I replay every feint and devastating strike, searching for an excuse for my defeat. There is only one answer: You are the superior Sith.

But strength can be a liability. Your master is bloated with paranoia and hatred for anyone he deems a threat. One false step and Baras will move against you. 

When that day comes, you'll beg for the mercy you showed me--but Baras will not grant it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Tribute</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Lord Rathari</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="343" id2="575046" version="1065353216">One of our bugs eavesdropped on Darth Baras. Enjoy.

[Begin recording]

Unidentified: My lord, Colonel Senks is gone. Your former apprentice--

Darth Baras: Impossible!

[Crashing sounds. Prolonged unintelligible yelling.]

Darth Baras: I am the Voice of the Emperor! Find that [muffled] cretin before I--

[Rest of conversation unintelligible.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="344" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Poor Baras</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="345" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Shadow</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="346" id2="575046" version="1065353216">My lord, I have cut all ties with Darth Baras. To express my gratitude, I recovered the file below for your perusal.

&quot;Voice of an Empire: The Memoirs of Darth Baras&quot;

Only the most powerful, well-respected and influential Sith stand a chance of becoming the Emperor's Voice. I was the perfect candidate. 

But when the Emperor chose me, my apprentice grew jealous. In a fit of heretical treason, my former apprentice challenged me to a duel.

Through me, the Emperor judged my apprentice unworthy. Humbled, my apprentice bowed to my superior power and accepted death.

The next day, the Dark Council recognized me as the Voice of the Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="347" id2="575046" version="1065353216">FW: Voice of an Empire: The Memoirs of Darth Baras</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="348" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Colonel Senks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="349" id2="575046" version="1065353216">The War Trust's failure is complete, my lord. Your execution of General Faraire signaled the collapse of Project Siantide. We followed your example and destroyed all evidence of their weapons research.

The Republic military is reeling from this loss. They were counting on Project Siantide to help them defend Taris. Now, they will be lucky to escape the burning wreckage.

I salvaged one piece of Project Siantide from the inferno. Please accept it as a reminder of your victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="350" id2="575046" version="1065353216">The War Trust</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="351" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Moff Hurdenn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="352" id2="575046" version="1065353216">We have had a breakthrough, my lord. Since you captured General Faraire, he has resisted our questioning on the subject of Project Siantide. Last night, however, we broke the stubborn general.

The secrets of Project Siantide now belong to the Empire. As you saw on Taris, the military benefits are boundless. 

Siantide prototypes have begun development. Thanks to your efforts, the Republic will soon feel the sting of their experimental weaponry.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="353" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Project Siantide</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="354" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Moff Hurdenn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="355" id2="575046" version="1065353216">The ambush was Master Karr's idea. I tried to hide our meeting, but he saw through my deception. 

Ulldin was a friend. When I heard what you did to him, I wanted to kill you myself. I've controlled my grief since then. But his sacrifice will haunt me forever.

There will be no more meetings--my Master watches my every move. Please, stop this madness. I can't bear it any longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="356" id2="575046" version="1065353216">The ambush</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="357" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Jaesa Willsaam</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="358" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Please believe me--the ambush wasn't my idea. Master Karr discovered our plan and sent his Jedi to kill you. 

I must admit, I felt relief when Master Karr found out. I hoped this would all be over. But when Ulldin returned with your message, I couldn't believe it.

I thought Sith killed their victims. Master Karr was surprised too. He insists sparing Ulldin was part of Baras's master plan, but I know better. Your actions were your own.

Thank you for showing Ulldin mercy. I only wish we'd met instead.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="359" id2="575046" version="1065353216">I'm sorry</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="360" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Jaesa Willsaam</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="361" id2="575046" version="1065353216">I never meant to betray you. I was preparing for our meeting when Master Karr detained me and sent his Jedi in my place. Now I have to answer for their fates.

Zylixx was always distant around me. He knew I could sense the darkness inside him. You saw it too. You brought his darkness to the surface.

I have so many questions for you, but Master Karr won't let me out of his sight. If only I'd had my way, this whole mess would be over by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="362" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Please forgive me</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="363" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Jaesa Willsaam</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="364" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Servant One of the Emperor's Hand</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="365" id2="575046" version="1065353216">The Emperor Lives</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="366" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Wrath, we have been remiss in our lack of correspondence. It is regrettable, but other matters have commanded our full attention of late.

Despite what you may have heard from Darth Marr and others, the Emperor is not dead. He slumbers still, preparing for his inevitable return.

It is to the Dark Council's advantage that you believe their lies. They fear your power, and with good reason. Absent the Emperor's Voice, you represent the truest embodiment of his will in the corporeal world.

We have foreseen that your allegiance to the Emperor will be tested. You must remain vigilant, and unleash your might upon those who would dare question the Emperor's reign.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="367" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Servant One of the Emperor's Hand</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="368" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Disturbance</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="369" id2="575046" version="1065353216">The Force moves through the Emperor's Hand in a manner that few others experience. For us, the Force is an intricate tapestry woven into our very essence.

That tapestry has become flawed.

I speak of a persistent disturbance. A cyst, dense and tangled and unpleasant. It began small and nearly imperceptible but has been growing ever larger.

Wrath, I have already impressed upon you the need for you to be wary of the Emperor's enemies and ruthless in their punishment, but the source of this basal disturbance is of the gravest concern to us and must therefore be subjected to the sheer vastness of your might.

Do not let the Emperor down.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="370" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Sharack Breev</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="371" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Word from Tatooine</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="372" id2="575046" version="1065353216">My lord,

When I learned that Darth Baras was no more and that you had ascended in his absence, I decided the allegiance I swore to Baras would pass over to you. I had nothing of value to offer at the time, which is why you have not heard from me until now.

I recently caught sight of someone distinctly out of place in the Dune Sea, apparently attempting to barter with a Jawa clan for lodging. When I closed in, I recognized her: it was the Sith wanted for the murder of Darth Arkous!

I shadowed her, hoping to see where she would ultimately find sanctuary. I am an excellent tracker, but she is Sith. She slipped away. I later learned that someone bearing her description departed the planet with the assistance of a Wookiee pilot. That is all I know, I'm afraid.

I hope my information has been helpful somehow, as I am sure she is a valuable target that you would like to bring to justice yourself. I will keep you informed if I learn anything further.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="373" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Darth Vowrawn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="374" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Farewell</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="375" id2="575046" version="1065353216">Wrath,

I am afraid I had to cut my visit to Rishi short, as anticipated. I do hope that you have learned who it is your watchers answer to, and that you use that information to your fullest advantage. It benefits us all when those we must depend upon are able to scrutinize their circumstances with full clarity, don't you agree?

Though it may be some time, I do hope our paths cross again. It has been a singular pleasure, as always.

--Vowrawn</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
