<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>129</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/smuggler.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Risha</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Engine tune-up</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Couldn't sleep last night, so I spent a few hours working on the engines. Found some carbon scoring around the fuel injectors to the sublight drives. I knew we weren't getting maximum thrust out of those things, but they're purring like a happy nexu now.

I know there's no chance of us getting into a line of work where the ship doesn't come under turbolaser fire every ten minutes, but maybe we can invest in better shields? The engines will thank you--and so will I (hint, hint).

Love,
Risha</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Risha</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Audila</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Got a short note from Audila. She and Juran settled down on Byllura to run a little frontier mercantile exchange. Guess she finally forgave me for that kidnapping thing on Tatooine, although I notice she didn't invite us to come visit. My old friends rarely do these days--unless it's to ask for favors.

The bigger you and this crew get in certain galactic circles, the more hangers-on we seem to attract. I'd be offended if I didn't see so many opportunities to take advantage. Who needs to rule a planet when the galaxy is this wide open to us?

--R</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Risha</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Dubrillion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Update on Dubrillion's civil war. Really glad we're not there.

HOLONET NEWS UPDATE - DISASTER ON DUBRILLION

Reports indicate the current ruler of Dubrillion, King Actavarus the Third, has destroyed six major cities on his planet to crush a rebellion. Initial casualty numbers are in the millions.

TAG THIS MESSAGE FOR UPDATES

Not to sound insensitive, but I'm wondering if there'll be anything left of Dubrillion to take over. Maybe we're better off conning our way into the monarchy of a less crazy planet. I'll start researching opportunities.

You'll always be my king,
Risha</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Akaavi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Guarding your name</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="575051" version="1065353216">I was informed that some fool of a besom was loudly slandering you at the last spaceport we visited. I paid him a call and gave him a chance to correct himself. He refused. Now he takes his meals in liquid form.

No one disrespects you without consequences.

--Akaavi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Akaavi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="575051" version="1065353216">The Mon Calamari</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="575051" version="1065353216">I try to respect your position as captain of this vessel, but Guss is testing my patience. Three times now, I have caught him staring at my body in an inappropriate way. Yesterday I confronted him in private and made it clear that I know how to remove a Mon Calamari's eyes without killing their owner. I believe he took my point.

I apologize if I have overstepped my authority, but I felt it important to deal with this issue personally.

--Akaavi

P.S. The gift was a peace offering from Guss. I have no use for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Akaavi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Vigilance</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="575051" version="1065353216">I do not often allow myself to relax or feel at peace--what we call &quot;udesiir.&quot; Lately, that has changed. There is a time every night after you fall asleep when the anger that has kept me alive fades, and I experience a moment of calm.

Do not be alarmed. I have already taken steps to correct this weakness. When we lower our guards, foes grow bold. Our enemies will never find me unprepared.

--Akaavi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Corso</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="575051" version="1065353216">For you</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Tried writing a poem, but I couldn't make all those short separate lines look right. So I just mashed them all together. Hope you still like it.

Your eyes are like a mountain sunset and your breath is the cool morning air. Your voice is a bird's call but you move like a wildcat through a jungle. When you fire a blaster it's a thunderclap I feel in my heart. Never stop shooting.

Love,
Corso</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Corso</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="575051" version="1065353216">People!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Just argued with some idiot on the HoloNet who was telling people plasma-based blasters have more stopping power than particle beam models. I'm betting this guy's never used his blaster on anything bigger than a gizka. Can you imagine surviving any of the things we have without particle beams?

That reminds me--I should give all our blasters a thorough cleaning. I saw a guy once who got his heter valve jammed up with dust. His face looked like one of those cheap Nar Shaddaa plasteel dolls of the Supreme Chancellor after it's been left out in the sun.

Love,
Corso</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Corso</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="575051" version="1065353216">A place to settle down?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Just saw a HoloNet real estate listing for this amazing homestead on Dantooine. It's over a thousand square kilometers! They've got farm AND ranch lands (with ronto herds!), plus a big estate house to live in. Have you ever seen a sunrise on that planet? They're gorgeous.

I know you're not in any hurry to give up your ship, but someday it'd be nice to have a permanent home. I don't know about you, but I like lots of wide open spaces and privacy. This place would suit me.

Love,
Corso</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Viidu</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="575051" version="1065353216">So long</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="575051" version="1065353216">If you're reading this, Captain, it means my luck ran out and yours didn't. This HoloNet message was set on a dead man's switch, so Rogun the Butcher or the separatists must have finally ended my horrible week.

Sorry I couldn't stick around to help you square things with Rogun, but Corso's a loyal kid. You can trust him to watch your back.

You don't owe me any favors, but I'd appreciate it if you looked after my girl Syreena. And I hope you kill Skavak in a truly painful way.

See you in the Void,
Viidu</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Syreena</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Watch your back</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Looks like Rogun the Butcher's thugs want to make an example out of everyone associated with Viidu--including me. I've had to move planets three times since Ord Mantell, but the bounty hunters keep coming.

If they're putting this much effort into finding me, you must be scraping off thugs every ten meters. I realize we aren't exactly friends, but I'm really hoping you'll live long enough to kill Rogun so I can stop looking over my shoulder.

Stay alive, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Skavak</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Thanks</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="575051" version="1065353216">I still have friends on Ord Mantell, and they told me you fried Syreena. Nice work, Captain. You're a real pal. Now I don't have to worry about running into her at my favorite cantinas. She was pretty enough, but way too clingy--and dumber than a load-lifter. Then again, aren't they all?

Skavak</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Darmas Pollaran</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Glad I could help</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Captain, 

My network just gave me the good news that you're back in business. I hope Skavak left your ship in good condition. Sorry that rascal escaped justice, but something tells me you'll get another shot at him.

It was a pleasure assisting you, and I do hope we cross paths again someday. I've just received an intriguing job offer from a Senator, so I may be out of pocket for the next little while--but my sabacc table will always have a seat for you.

Best wishes,
Darmas Pollaran</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Kixi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="575051" version="1065353216">My hero</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Hey!

Didn't take much digging to score your HoloNet ID, and I couldn't leave Coruscant without thanking you again. Not sure what would've happened to me if I'd stayed locked up with the Migrant Merchants' Guild, but I'm guessing &quot;good&quot; wouldn't describe it.

Think I've had enough of Republic space for now. I'm heading home to my family on Ryloth. Working for the Hutts is never easy, but at least they pay well. Good luck, Captain--hope you get your revenge, or whatever.

--Kixi</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Migrant Merchants' Guild</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Peace</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Captain, 

The Migrant Merchants' Guild regrets the recent unpleasantness and whatever miscommunication caused it. Your reputation from Ord Mantell was not known to the men at our headquarters who shot at you. All those who survived have been strongly reprimanded.

Clearly, your main interest in us was our slicer Kixi, and we appreciate you leaving her alive for our continued profit. Please accept the attached gift as a token of the guild's desire for less hostile interactions in the future.

High profits and smooth transactions,
The Migrant Merchants' Guild</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Sinistern3580</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Thanks for the assist</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="575051" version="1065353216">I admire your work. Consider me a fan.

That little schutta Kixi was a pain in my neck for years. She blocked even my best algorithms. With her dead, I've sliced right through the Migrant Merchants' Guild network--and found all of Kixi's back doors into the Republic's main databases. Too much fun.

Sent you something to show my appreciation. Don't bother tracing this message. You won't find me.

--Sinistern3580</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Agent Soganti</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Enjoy your freedom while it lasts</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="575051" version="1065353216">I was never fooled, Captain. Not once. Your diplomatic immunity was obviously forged, even if I couldn't prove it. Without that document, rest assured I would've seized and searched your vessel. I know I would've found enough contraband Taris artifacts to put you away for a good long while.

As for Thorne, she managed to escape Taris on a suspiciously quick schedule--but you already knew that, didn't you? Don't think for a second you've gotten away with anything. I know your kind. Someday you'll make a mistake, and I'll be there to see it.

Catch you later,
Agent Soganti</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Agent Soganti</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Beryl Thorne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Congratulations, Captain. Your cooperation resulted in Beryl Thorne's arrest on charges of smuggling and illegal contraband profiteering. Thorne is currently resting comfortably in a cell, but she had a few choice words to say about you. I won't bother repeating them--I'll just say that I'm sorry we didn't get to know each other better. I suspect we'd have a lot to talk about.

Enjoy your &quot;diplomatic immunity&quot; for however long it lasts. It's too bad I wasn't allowed to search your vessel, although I'm fairly certain I would've found the experience highly illuminating.

Catch you later,
Agent Soganti</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Lazhae</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Gratitude</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Captain, I must congratulate you one last time on your profound good sense and affinity for the scientific arts. Thanks to your non-interference, I am making great strides in my research of intelligent beast engineering.

I am domesticating a new pack of vrblthers and have acquired several new test subjects. How truly fortunate it is that so many lesser beings think Shadow Town is a tourist attraction--and that no one seems to notice their disappearance. It may be my prison, but Nar Shaddaa is a fine place to work.

For Science,
Lazhae</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Senator Wain Andrell</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Momi Andrell</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Captain, 

My security investigator informs me that you rescued my daughter Momi from a criminal research laboratory on Nar Shaddaa. Momi is now home and in stable condition despite the terrible ordeal she suffered. I have hired the best Republic scientists to find a permanent cure for her infections and am hopeful she will be restored to full health. Rest assured she will not resume her illegal activism when that day finally arrives.

Please forgive me for not delivering my gratitude in person, but my daughter's actions have caused me considerable political embarrassment. I'm sure you understand the need to keep things private and will accept my gift with the understanding that this matter never be discussed publicly.

Sincerely,
Senator Wain Andrell
Official Republic Representative of Ralltiir</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Guutroh Yon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Bounty on Momi Andrell</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Thanks for a nice payday, Captain. I'd been hunting Momi Andrell for weeks when I heard the shooting at Lazhae's lab. Poked my head in after you left and found my bounty gift wrapped.

Hosed down her cage and turned her in to her family. I'm a big believer in balancing the cosmic scales, so I figure it's only fair to extend a little professional courtesy your way. Enjoy.

--Guutroh Yon

P.S. I know Rogun the Butcher put a hefty bounty on your head, but I heard what you did to Zank Helrott. Figure I'll sit this one out.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Nariel Pridence</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="575051" version="1065353216">The Jedi Order thanks you</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Captain, 

I have filed a full report to my Jedi Council superiors regarding your cooperation on Tatooine. Grandmaster Satele Shan was especially impressed with your defeat of the Sith Lord Vaverone Zare and wishes to extend her personal gratitude. You showed great courage, and we are in your debt.

Although Jedi do not carry material possessions in the field, we do maintain a storehouse of items donated to us. Please accept the enclosed gift with our thanks. I hope we meet again someday. May the Force be with you.

--Nariel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Vaverone Zare</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Regards from the Empire</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Dearest Captain, 

I trust your business endeavors are meeting with great success. My own ambitions have blossomed thanks to your assistance recovering the artifact on Tatooine. I won't bore you with tedious details of Sith politics, but suffice it to say that my power is growing exponentially.

I often find myself reflecting on our fruitful collaboration and wishing the Empire was more welcoming of people like yourself. Perhaps when I am Empress I will see to it you have a place here. Do try to remain alive until that day.

Warmest wishes,
Vaverone Zare, now Darth Alluress (a trifle obvious, I'll admit--but you should see some of the other Darths' names)</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Hrenn Indiru</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Congratulations from the GFG</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Captain, 

After cross-checking numerous accounts of your recent exploits with a detailed report provided by Risha Drayen, the Galactic Finders Guild is pleased to formally record your name as the locator of Nok Drayen's lost fortune, aka Missing Wealth Collection #3263827.

On a personal note, I would like to offer my sincerest thanks for ridding the galaxy of Skavak. The man was a walking pustule of filth who repeatedly robbed the guild offices. He will not be missed.

Once again, congratulations on your find and best wishes in your future endeavors.

Sincerely,
Hrenn Indiru
Chief Secretary, Galactic Finders Guild</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="328" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Vance Garlint</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="575051" version="1065353216">You lying scum!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Just saw where the Galactic Finders Guild gave YOU credit for tracking down Nok Drayen's lost fortune. You're not even a professional treasure-hunter! I've put YEARS into searching for that payday, and I'll be rolled in bantha poodoo before I believe some no-talent freighter jockey beat me to the prize!

I don't know who you paid off at the GFG to discourage the rest of us from keeping up the search, but you haven't fooled me! I won't stop looking until I find the REAL fortune.

Drop dead!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Senator Bevera Dodonna</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="575051" version="1065353216">With gratitude from the Republic</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Captain, 

On behalf of the Republic, I thank you for securing the Nebula weapons shipment. I know the mission was both difficult and dangerous, but it was vital for the Republic's continued survival. Patriots like you are winning this war. We are grateful for your service.

General Var Suthra, the man who originally founded Project Nebula, asked me to also convey his personal thanks for ensuring the Empire did not gain an advantage that is rightfully ours. The attached gift is from him--he hopes it serves you well.

I look forward to our continued partnership.

Sincerely,
Senator Bevera Dodonna</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Darmas Pollaran</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Business is good</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="575051" version="1065353216">I'm pleased to report your products from Balmorra have been well received on the open market. Your entire stock is virtually depleted and what remains is the subject of heavy bidding from multiple interested parties. I do love it when inventory and buyers find each other so quickly.

I have attached your first batch of profits to this message. We'll have to celebrate the next time you're at Port Nowhere. As always, it's a pleasure working with you.

In friendship,
Darmas</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Alilia</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Greetings from Bespin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Those tibanna gas miners never knew what hit them! We raided a dozen mining ships and knocked over a refinery. I've only had one case of mutiny. That man took a permanent vacation to Bespin's core. I could get used to being a pirate queen.

This was a good shakedown cruise, but our next target needs to be more high profile. Maybe we'll hit one of those fatcat luxury liners? The security on them is tight, but the payoff would be worth it. Wish me luck.

--Alilia

P.S. Trick says hello. I think he's having fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Alilia</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Safe</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Thought you'd want to know the Republic got us off Hoth and all the way to Coruscant. The Jedi here are kinder than I was expecting. They're not treating Trick like some freak they can exploit. Neither of us misses the White Maw.

The Jedi have offered me a job assisting them with other people like Trick. They say I have a knack for it. At least I won't have to worry about keeping a roof over my head by sucking up to men like Shai Tenna.

Thanks for helping us out, Captain. Maybe we'll see you around.

--Alilia</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="343" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Raskurro</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="344" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Pleasure doing business with you</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="345" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Greetings, Captain. The Hutt Cartel wishes to extend its sincerest apologies for the recent situation with Rogun the Butcher's representative. Had we known the simpleton hostage was of value to you, we would have offered you the first option to acquire him.

The Cartel recognizes your stature within our enterprise sector and assures you that future business dealings will be approached with the proper respect. May we both profit handsomely from our association.

--Raskurro
Cartel Sub-administrator of Nar Shaddaa</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="346" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Torval Fregner</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="347" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Respect</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="348" id2="575051" version="1065353216">The Nar Shaddaa Exchange salutes you, Captain! We've had a hit out on Raskurro the Hutt for months now, but nobody was able to get anywhere near that sleemo until you did. The Cartel was blocking our expansion into organ trafficking, but now they're too busy arguing over Raskurro's replacement to mess with us. Business is booming.

We may have had our past differences, but know that you have friends in the Exchange--and we won't forget the favor you've done us. Feel free to keep blasting the Cartel to bits.

--Torval</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="349" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Scratch</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="350" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Fame pays</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="351" id2="575051" version="1065353216">You're getting to be a regular celebrity, Captain. You've been real good for my traffic on Voss. Word got out that we worked together, and now every spacer in the sector is dropping by to cut a deal. I've also had a few bantha-brained bounty hunters drop in looking for you, but they're not getting anything useful.

My bosses at the Exchange said I should cut you a piece of the extra action I'm getting. Appreciate the business--drop by anytime.

--Scratch</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="352" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Gormak Zak</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="353" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Business</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="354" id2="575051" version="1065353216">I contacted your representative. Our product goes to Port Nowhere. First payment is enclosed.

The Gormak offer thanks. When the final war comes and the Voss die, you will be remembered as our friend.

--Zak</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="355" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Bevera Dodonna</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="356" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Safe</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="357" id2="575051" version="1065353216">This will be the last time you hear from me. I made it off Corellia--barely--and got to my private starship just before it could be impounded by the authorities. I'm composing this message while sitting in deep space with my galaxy map open and having no idea where to go. I hear the Outer Rim has lots of empty planets to hide on, but I've never been good at roughing it.

Wherever I finally land, the luxuries of my old life won't be needed. Given our relationship, you're entitled to them.

Good luck, and goodbye.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="358" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Republic SIS</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="359" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Senator Dodonna</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="360" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Captain, 

In recognition of your service exposing and apprehending the traitor Senator Bevera Dodonna, the SIS offers you the attached compensation. The extent to which our entire war effort could have been compromised by such a high-ranking defector is incalculable. The Senator has been transferred to a special deep space interrogation facility while she awaits trial. Given the current war situation, we estimate she will be in our custody for some time. Your assistance in her capture has been recorded with the appropriate authorities.

Field Operations Director Korol Tander, Republic SIS</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="361" id2="575051" version="1065353216">A friend</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="362" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Senator Dodonna</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="363" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Captain, 

While I am not at liberty to reveal my identity, one of my many duties with Republic High Command is ensuring traitors are dealt with properly. It has come to my office's attention that you were the last person to see the treasonous Senator Dodonna alive. While some within our government might have preferred to interrogate her--or worse, make her the subject of a public trial--it is personally gratifying to me knowing that she died on her knees wearing an Imperial slave collar.

Please accept the attached gift with my compliments.

G.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="364" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Iceheart Carac</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="365" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Weirdest job I ever took</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="366" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Quite a day, Captain. I started out working for the Voidwolf to bomb the Republic shipyards and ended in a free-for-all against the Imperial fleet just because you said so.

In case you're curious, we slaughtered the Imps. Idiots were so overconfident, they were traveling without shields up. We took a few losses--Trizz'mal didn't make it--but the rest of us got out clean.

Tractored in some loot from the wreckage and figured I'd pass some along before you decided to come collect in person. I want no quarrel with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="367" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Master Sumalee</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="368" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Victory</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="369" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Reports indicate the Voidwolf's flagship self-destructed over Corellia and the Republic shipyards were spared from attack. I knew I could count on you, Captain.

Sorry I can't reward you in person, but the Voidwolf's pirate friends have decided to take advantage of the chaos and make life hard for everyone. I'm leading a picket defense force to intercept some of the more aggressive raiding parties before they storm our supply lines.

Take care of yourself. I hope we catch up with each other someday. I owe you a drink.

--Sumalee</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="370" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Iceheart Carac</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="371" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Easy pickings</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="372" id2="575051" version="1065353216">My boys and I went on a little raiding run through the Empire's supply lines after you cut us loose. Thanks to the Voidwolf, the Imps were still logging us as friendlies. We robbed them blind before they could call reinforcements.

Even though we already paid you off, I'm sending your share of the spoils. With the Voidwolf and Rogun out of the picture, everyone's saying it won't be long before you're running things--and I like to be on the winning side. Be seeing you, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="373" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Master Sumalee</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="374" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Been a while</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="375" id2="575051" version="1065353216">I'd ask what you've been up to, Captain, but I keep seeing your name pop up. Ilum. Makeb. Kuat. Even Oricon, if memory serves. And now this business on Korriban and Tython. You've kept yourself busy. Good.

As for me, Saresh has pretty much made me the standard bearer for Jedi taking a proactive stance against the Empire. Which is fine, but I'd rather be spending less time posing for the HoloNet and more time actually getting the job done. You know--like you.

Keep on doing what you do, but you'd better set aside some time in there somewhere to look me up. Pretty sure I owe you a drink.

--Sumalee</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="376" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Beryl Thorne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="377" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Manaan?!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="378" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Okay, so I've been trying for months to get the approval to receive an application for a landing permit on Manaan so I can negotiate a license to trade kolto... and I hear YOU just coast on in, and I can't believe it!

I've got a ship, the financial backing... getting a kolto license would secure my shot at the big time. But the Selkath limit those things, and now I bet you've got one--the one I should've gotten. Maybe if I spent more time sucking up to the Republic or rescuing people from doomed planets instead of being the best I can be at my chosen profession, that license would be mine, huh?

Yes, I'm bitter. And no, I'm NOT stalking you. In fact, I'm leaving for the Rishi Maze. Maybe there's some undiscovered kolto supply somewhere in there. Or just a limitless pile of cash. You can't possibly have ALL the luck.

See ya.

--Thorne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="379" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Master Sumalee</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="380" id2="575051" version="1065353216">A bad feeling</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="381" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Captain,

You've been on my mind a lot lately, and I wasn't quite sure why until recently. I'm sure you'd say it was due to your charm, but in all seriousness, I have become attuned to a strong and consistent sense that you're in terrible danger.

I feel that it has to do with this Theron Shan business. I know you worked with him during the invasion of Korriban. I thought, maybe, if he truly killed Colonel Darok as they're saying that you might be his next target.

But what I'm feeling is far more dire. It's not just your own life at stake, but those of many, and you stand at the center. I suggest you tread lightly for a time. Don't trust anyone. When you speak to the bird, it will be time.

--Sumalee</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="382" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Beryl Thorne</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="383" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Stupid Nova Blades</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="384" id2="575051" version="1065353216">Hey, Captain.

Don't know what's gotten into the Nova Blades, but word is they're raiding all over the place, jamming up hyperspace traffic. Not just on the juciest routes, either. I don't get it, but since the Blades have got their mitts all over Raider's Cove maybe you could knock on their door, tell them to give a girl a break? Haha.

I don't think I said so on Rishi, but it was good to see a familiar face. Don't be a complete stranger, okay?

--Thorne

(Haven't gotten those tickets sorted just yet, but don't worry, I've got some feelers out already.)</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
