<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>18</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/star_fortress.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="879182" version="1065353216">Apparently, your new Gormak friend hasn't mastered the art of composing HoloNet messages--or maybe he just doesn't think he's a very good writer. Either way, he asked me to formally convey his gratitude for destroying the Star Fortress at Voss. He says his people are already getting healthier and a lot of the ones who'd fallen sick are making full recoveries. Maybe there really was something to his whole conspiracy theory. I wouldn't put it past Arcann to poison the Gormak and keep them from becoming a problem for him.

--Theron</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="879182" version="1065353216">Message from Rokuss</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="879182" version="1065353216">Theron Shan</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="879182" version="1065353216">Just got off the holo with a friend on Tatooine. In the time since you put down that blasted Star Fortress, there have been two gang wars, a dozen raids on the Sand People and nobody-knows-how-many public duels and other disturbances of the peace. A whole lot of pent-up anger just got discharged, and now everything's quiet. For now, anyway.

It's like I always say--people need the freedom to misbehave. The Eternal Empire thought it could force peace down everyone's throats, and all they did was make it worse. You did a good thing, Commander. Don't let anybody tell you otherwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="879182" version="1065353216">Tatooine is safe for the not-nice people again</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="879182" version="1065353216">&quot;Deadeye&quot; Leyta</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="879182" version="1065353216">I don't know why the Cartel sent this to me instead of you, but here's their message:

&quot;To the Most Honored Commander of the Alliance Against Zakuul,

The glorious Hutt Cartel sends endless gratitude for your assistance in removing the blighted Star Fortress from its orbit around our precious moon of Nar Shaddaa! Once again, the great markets are open for business, offering wares to discerning buyers from across the galaxy. We are sure you will agree that commerce is truly the foundation of freedom. We raise our cups to freedom--and to you, Commander.

Most Sincerely,
Your Friends in the Cartel&quot;

Don't let it go to your head. Hutts will drink to anything. --V</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="879182" version="1065353216">FW: Thanks from the Hutt Cartel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="879182" version="1065353216">Veeroa Denz</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="879182" version="1065353216">We are so grateful for the opportunity to create the definitive public record of your war against the Eternal Empire. The Great Star Fortress Battle of Hoth will provide one of the finest chapters in our chronicles. We have conducted thorough interviews with all of your esteemed allies, and their accounts will ensure that we miss no details, however minor. Indeed, we have calculated to within fifty rounds how much ammunition was expended by members of the Alliance during this battle. We are disappointed that we cannot do the same for the enemy forces, but this is to be expected as there are no survivors to question. These are the sacrifices we must make in the war for truth.

We remain, as always, your official chronicler and comrade in arms.

Hemdil Tre
Esteemed Professor of Military Antiquity, Grand Nest of Cona</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="879182" version="1065353216">Chronicling the battle above Hoth</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="879182" version="1065353216">Hemdil Tre</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="879182" version="1065353216">I checked up on the prison now that the Star Fortress is just a bunch of pretty colors burning up in the atmosphere, and I'm glad to say the lower levels have stayed quiet and locked down. Haven't seen a shuttle from Zakuul heading in or out in days. Good riddance! I had to get professionally licensed as a recruiter. Those fools were strictly amateur.

Belsavis is still a festering minefield of escaped lunatics, ancient horrors and Imps and Pubs who don't know when to quit, but hey, nothing's perfect. They'll sort themselves out one way or another. In the meantime, I've heard some promising rumors about exciting new talent we might be able to recruit on a planet called Datho-something-or-other. I'll let you know if it's worth your time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="879182" version="1065353216">Belsavis is back to its old self</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="879182" version="1065353216">K'krohl</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="879182" version="1065353216">As a Jedi, I can never condone or celebrate the destruction of something like the Star Fortress above Alderaan. Many lives were lost within it, and those deaths diminish us all. But as a citizen of the Republic and a living being who seeks to end the suffering of all people, the Alliance's actions were necessary.

My contacts assure me that the campaign of terror perpetuating the chaos on Alderaan has ended thanks to you. It will be a long time before peace can take root there, but the Alliance has given it the chance it needs. Tempting as it is to interfere further, those people have suffered enough at the hands of outsiders with an agenda. Let us give the leaders of that world the opportunity to make what they will of your gift.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="879182" version="1065353216">Let us leave Alderaan to heal itself</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="879182" version="1065353216">Choza Raabat</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
