<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>24</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/strongholds.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Pargon Sisto</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Enjoy your new Stronghold!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Way to go!

By now I'm sure you've made good use of the essential furnishings provided when you purchased your Stronghold, but the place is probably still a little bare, right? That's why I've taken the liberty of setting you up with a personal vendor who specializes in Stronghold merchandise.

Maybe you're thinking, &quot;I've got the basics, Pargon--why would I need anything more?&quot; See, the more decorations and trophies you collect for your Stronghold, the greater its prestige will be. Earn enough prestige and you can have your Stronghold placed in the Public Listing! Let everyone know YOUR Stronghold is the best Stronghold. Rub it in their faces!

In case you're away from home, you can also make purchases with decoration vendors on Carrick Station. You'll find them near those helpful Crew Skill trainers. They've got some pretty nice stuff.

In buying a Stronghold, you may have just made the smartest move of your life. Now go make that Stronghold of yours the envy of all the galaxy!

-Pargon Sisto</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="798434" version="1065353216">ajolin</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="798434" version="1065353216">you own a Stronghold....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="798434" version="1065353216">you have done it. you have charted your own destiny by staking claim to a Stronghold. but what is next?

you have the basic essentials to furnish your new home, but that is not enough. you must have more if you want the prestige that will get you noticed. with enough prestige, your Stronghold can be entered into a Public Listing. EVERYONE WILL KNOW YOUR GREAT MIGHT.

to assist you in your journey of decadent excess, you are being provided your own private vendor. if that is not enough--and it should never be enough--you may also find Stronghold decoration vendors near the Crew Skill trainers on Vaiken Spacedock.

show them all. build an extravagant tribute to your greatness. make all who behold your Stronghold burn with the red-hot jealousy of a million stars....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Aesthetic Consultant K'torna</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Crafting decorations</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Hi,

I'm following up on your recent purchase of a Stronghold with some (hopefully) helpful pointers for making your own decorations. Have you heard of fabrication droids? They're able to quickly manufacture polished decorations from prefabs that you provide them.

There are two basic kinds of prefabs: Synthetic and Industrial. Synthetic Prefabs can be crafted by anyone proficient in Synthweaving, Biochem, and Artifice, while those familiar with Armormech, Armstech, and Cybertech can craft Industrial Prefabs. All you need is the proper schematic (which you can learn from a Crew Skill trainer) and the required quantity of crafting materials.

You can also combine the basic Synthetic and Industrial Prefabs into a Universal Prefab. Lots of decorations require a Universal Prefab, so it's a good idea to find another professional crafter to produce the parts you can't make yourself.

I've taken the liberty of shipping some fabricator droids to get you started. Happy crafting!

K'torna
Ultrastellar Aesthetic Consultancy
Nar Shaddaa</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Adornment Specialist Emmons</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="798434" version="1065353216">On the Fabrication of Decorative Elements</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Greetings.

After reviewing all pertinent documentation, I have confirmed that you are the purchaser and owner of a Stronghold as recognized under Imperial law. As such, I am now required to furnish you with a basic compliment of Stronghold fabrication droids.

Fabrication droids are designed to quickly and efficiently reconfigure prefab materials into finished items for your Stronghold. Two elements go into the creation of a prefab: knowledge of the proper schematic, which may be obtained from a Crew Skill vendor; and the correct quantity of crafting materials as described by the schematic.

Fabrication droids may work from one of three manners of prefab: Synthetic, Industrial, or Universal. Synthetic Prefabs may be assembled by way of Synthweaving, Biochem, or Artifice. Industrial Prefabs are the domain of Armormech, Armstech, and Cybertech. Universal Prefabs are compiled by combining Synthetic and Industrial Prefabs; therefore, it would serve you well to work with those who are proficient in skills in which you may be lacking.

This concludes my assistance in this matter; I bid you farewell.

E. E. Emmons
Adornment Specialist</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Fleet Admiral Aygo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Planetary Conquests</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Fleet Admiral Aygo here, reaching out from the Kuat system.

Word's come up from Pargon Sisto that you've got yourself a Stronghold. Good. The more you build that thing up, the better.

Think of your Stronghold as your power base for the Republic. The more you expand and build out your Stronghold, the more your contributions will count as we engage the enemy in Planetary Conquest events.

Your Conquest objectives will change periodically, as will the rewards. Keep an eye out for notifications in your official mission log, and keep fighting the good fight.

Bey'wan Aygo
First Fleet Adm.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Lord Krovos</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Planetary Conquests</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Greetings to you.

On behalf of the esteemed Admiral Ranken of Imperial Forward Command, I seek your cooperation. As the registrant of a new Stronghold, you're now capable of assisting the Empire in Planetary Conquest events. With each expansion to your Stronghold, you will be all the better suited to contribute to Conquests, and Imperial victory will be that much more certain.

See your official mission log for details on Conquest objectives and rewards, as both will change on a regular basis.

For the Empire.

-Lord Krovos</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Captain Darooga</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Guild Flagships</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Hello. It's an honor to be writing you.

Fleet Admiral Aygo asked me to pass along an important addendum to his previous message. As part of our ongoing effort to prevail in Planetary Conquests, guilds across the galaxy have been authorized to register a Flagship with the Republic. Guild Flagships will amplify contributions to Planetary Conquests and provide your guild with resource sharing and rapid deployment to a guildmate's position, among other benefits.

If you haven't joined a guild, I highly recommend you do so. And if you do enjoy guild membership already but your guild doesn't have a Flagship, we hope you work together to make it happen soon!

Thanks for your time.

Capt. Weni Darooga
Republic First Fleet</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Admiral Ranken</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="798434" version="1065353216">Guild Flagships</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="798434" version="1065353216">This is Admiral Ranken of Forward Command. I wanted to take a moment to impress upon you the importance of guild membership in our continued campaign to succeed in Planetary Conquests. 

The Dark Council has approved the registration of guild Flagships under Imperial law. Having a Flagship means your guild's efforts will be more effective. You'll also have the ability to quickly assemble your guild virtually anywhere in the galaxy and to share your resources with your guild.

Assuming you're the leader of a guild, I recommend registering a Flagship at your earliest opportunity. If you've not yet joined a guild, I strongly suggest you reconsider. The Empire is strong, but it can always be stronger.

-Ranken-</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
