<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>12</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/support_content.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="745106" version="1065353216">Your &quot;Admirer&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="745106" version="1065353216">A Special Gift</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="745106" version="1065353216">So you've employed my stolen EV2 Macrobinoculars to locate scores of my MCR-99s, thinking that will help you... find me? Stop me? Impress me somehow? Well, I am impressed with your tenacity, if nothing else. And, since you seem to be a fan of taking that which is mine, I offer you this in return for your diligence: my prototype for the more compact MCR-100.

I know what you're thinking: &quot;Won't he just have programmed the droid to spy on me, or even to destroy me?&quot; That would be such an obvious ploy, wouldn't it? On the other hand, that may be precisely what I want you to think. Such a conundrum.

Enjoy the MCR-100. Or don't. Either way, I'll see you around....

-S</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="745106" version="1065353216">Addalar Hyland</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="745106" version="1065353216">Introducing GSI</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="745106" version="1065353216">A special message from Addalar Hyland, founder and CEO of Galactic Solutions Industries:

Your history of high-profile combat victories and status as a major figure on the galactic stage qualifies you for a special offer from GSI, the leading developer of cutting-edge armaments. Ending a war that spans our entire galaxy and restoring peace and order will require the most advanced weapons technology, and GSI is committed to inventing and producing just that. However, we require your special assistance with our research and development efforts.

If, in your travels, you encounter any of GSI's friendly communications terminals, we sincerely hope you will read our alerts and aid our causes. Also, be sure to visit our corporate headquarters and vendor outlet on Nar Shaddaa's Promenade. We look forward to seeing you!

Best wishes,
Addalar Hyland
GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="745106" version="1065353216">Addalar Hyland</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="745106" version="1065353216">GSI Thanks You!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="745106" version="1065353216">Galactic Solutions Industries offers sincere thanks for your many efforts in helping us create the most state-of-the-art weapons technology. Please be sure to visit us at our corporate offices and vendor outlet on Nar Shaddaa. We look forward to working with you again in the future.

Best wishes,
Addalar Hyland
GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="745106" version="1065353216">GSI</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="745106" version="1065353216">Seeker Droid Instructions</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="745106" version="1065353216">Galactic Solutions Industries, the leading developer of cutting-edge military technologies, presents you with this handy guide to GSI's industrial-grade Seeker Droid. Originally created for the extraction of subsurface detonite mines, our Seeker Droids are now employed in a wide variety of applications--even in accessing such hard-to-reach areas as sea floors and mountaintops.

While in Orbital Standby Mode, your Seeker Droid will alert you whenever you arrive at a promising excavation zone. To activate your Seeker Droid, simply target an Area of Interest within the excavation zone. Your Seeker Droid will quickly arrive to scan the targeted area, digging up any item deemed valuable by its analysis parameters. Once an excavation zone is no longer viable, your Seeker Droid will notify you and return to Orbital Standby Mode.

Repeated scans of the same Area of Interest within a dig zone will not yield greater results; GSI recommends targeting a new Area of Interest instead. (For Seeker Droid accessories, see our vendors conveniently located near GSI terminals across the galaxy, or visit our corporate headquarters on Nar Shaddaa's Promenade.)

Please note that GSI is not responsible for the actions of any underground creatures disturbed by the Seeker Droid's activities.

One final note: you may use any high-grade model of Macrobinoculars to seek out special excavation zones predetermined by GSI to be of great potential value.

Good luck, and thank you for your patronage.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
