<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>29</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/misc/mail/system_messages.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="256" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Star Wars™: The Old Republic™</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Collector's Edition Items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Thank you for buying the Star Wars™: The Old Republic™ Collector's Edition.

Enclosed are the special in-game items to which your purchase entitles you. Use them to customize your character and show them off to other players!

Have fun, and may the Force™ be with you!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Star Wars™: The Old Republic™</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Digital Deluxe Edition Items</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Thank you for buying the Star Wars™: The Old Republic™ Digital Deluxe Edition.

Enclosed are the special in-game items to which your purchase entitles you. Use them to customize your character and show them off to other players!

Have fun, and may the Force™ be with you!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Star Wars™: The Old Republic™</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Thank you for pre-ordering Star Wars™: The Old Republic™.

Enclosed is the special color stone item to which your purchase entitles you. Use it to customize the color of your lightsaber or blaster!

Have fun, and may the Force™ be with you!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Pre-Order Item</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Star Wars™: The Old Republic™</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Changes to Free Trial Accounts</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Thank you for trying Star Wars™: The Old Republic™. Since you last played, we have made some changes to the permissions on Free Trial Accounts.

As a result, some items may now be unavailable and your maximum credits may have been limited. We apologize for any inconvenience that these changes have caused.

Have fun, and may the Force™ be with you!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Congratulations on reaching level 50!

The galaxy is fraught with danger, and epic adventures await you on distant worlds: Flashpoints, Operations, and more. You will need powerful equipment in order to face these challenges, so let's get you geared up!

Use this datapad to grant the Advanced Gear tutorial Mission, then follow the instructions to collect your new equipment.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Your equipment is already looking better! With a full set of Tionese gear (Rating 126), you should be ready to take on some of the toughest challenges in the galaxy!

You can queue up for Hard Mode Flashpoints or Story Mode Operations using the Group Finder tool, which is located just above your mini-map. This is a great way to earn Black Hole Commendations, which can be used to purchase some of the best equipment that is currently available (Rating 146).

For more information about gearing up, visit:
http://www.swtor.com/info/eldergame</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Priority: Flashpoints and Operations</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Priority: Advanced Gear</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="611766" version="1065353216">You are not eligible for the Advanced Gear Mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="611766" version="1065353216">You have already completed the Advanced Gear Mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="611766" version="1065353216">You are not eligible for the Introduction to Group Finder Mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="611766" version="1065353216">You have already completed the Introduction to Group Finder Mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="611766" version="1065353216">You have already started the Advanced Gear Mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="611766" version="1065353216">You have already started the Introduction to Group Finder Mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Ranked Warzone Arena Season Reward</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Greetings Combatant!

The PvP Season has come to a glorious conclusion! Giradda is very pleased with your performance and has graciously awarded you gifts to distinguish your entertaining efforts in the Ranked Warzone Arenas! Enjoy your rewards, show off to all those weaker than you but remember to pay homage to Giradda by participating in the next PvP Season for even greater rewards and glory! Now get in there and go berserk!

Deathmaster Baron Deathmark</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="611766" version="1065353216">PvP Ratings have reset for the new PvP Season!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="611766" version="1065353216">In preparation for the next PvP Season, Ranked Ratings have been reset on your character. Compete in the newest PvP Season for increased rewards and glory!

Thank you for playing Star Wars™: The Old Republic™.

Happy Hunting, and may the Force™ be with you!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Star Wars™: The Old Republic™</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Forged Alliances: Get Ready for the Next Major Story Expansion!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="611766" version="1065353216">Welcome to Game Update 2.10!

This release includes the final chapter of the Forged Alliances flashpoint series, a three-part storyline for level 55 characters that leads directly into the next major story expansion for Star Wars™: The Old Republic™--releasing later this year! While the flashpoints won't be required to take part in the expansion, if you want the full story experience, seek out T3-G2 on Carrick Station or A7-M1 on Vaiken Spacedock to get started.

May the Force™ be with you!

-The Star Wars: The Old Republic Team</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
