<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>30</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_04/scene_05_lana.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162215" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which side did Arcann attack first?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162216" id2="17" version="1065353216">Both. Ships from the Eternal Fleet struck at shipyards and rallying points for both sides simultaneously.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162218" id2="17" version="1065353216">They favored ambush tactics throughout the war. Zakuulan sensor technology has far greater range than our own, and their ships can fly much further on less resources.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only vessels retrofitted with isotope-5 could manage to outrun them. None could truly compete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162224" id2="17" version="1065353216">How long did the Republic and the Empire manage to hold out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162225" id2="17" version="1065353216">Within three months, the bulk of our naval forces were disabled or eliminated, and the Republic was in the same situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162227" id2="17" version="1065353216">With naval superiority, Arcann's forces could begin choking off supply lines, trade... any ship travel at all. The Eternal Fleet seemed to be everywhere at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162229" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coruscant and Dromund Kaas were blockaded by the end of the first year.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162231" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did it end?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chancellor Saresh also refused to discuss surrender, but the Republic Senate managed to overrule her. A cadre of Senators negotiated their own cease-fire terms.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162234" id2="17" version="1065353216">All of those Senators have since been disgraced or dismissed. I'm sure you can imagine the likely culprit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162235" id2="17" version="1065353216">The members of the Dark Council fought Arcann's invasion ruthlessly--and lost. The Empire's treaty was ultimately negotiated by the Minister of Logistics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162247" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the Mandalorians?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162250" id2="17" version="1065353216">So far, the treaties with Zakuul have held. But that will not last forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162251" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard rumors that they are still managing to fight somehow, but I've seen nothing concrete. I wish I could tell you more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165291" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the Jedi Order?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165292" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know that they suffered heavy losses, but that's the extent of my information. I've sent agents to find out more, but none have returned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165295" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about Sith Intelligence?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165296" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish I had more to tell you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165299" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no longer a part of the organization, but I know that most of its assets were wiped out in the fighting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1165301" id2="17" version="1065353216">From what I've heard, Empress Acina prefers to rely on technological surveillance rather than direct intervention. I'm not sure what, if any, reconstruction has taken place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176192" id2="17" version="1065353216">When Darth Marr and I faced Valkorion, we knew right away. He was the Sith Emperor, Lana.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176196" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know.... When he was struck down, it released ripples through the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176198" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone who had felt the Sith Emperor's presence in the past... on Ziost, on Yavin Four... we all sensed what had happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176200" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arcann invaded soon after, claiming that an &quot;Outlander&quot; had assassinated his father, the &quot;Immortal Emperor&quot;. It didn't take long for us to unravel the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176208" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about Republic Special Forces? Is Havoc Squad still operational?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176209" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe so, but they've gone dark--top secret operations only. I haven't been able to determine their current roster, let alone make contact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176212" id2="17" version="1065353216">What of my power base? Moff Pyron? The Silencers?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176213" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many of the vessels equipped with the Silencers were lost in the initial fighting. The rest disappeared along with Pyron somewhere in the far Outer Rim.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176215" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is presumed that they were ambushed by the Eternal Fleet, but no wreckage has been found. We must carry on without them.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
