<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>26</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_04/scene_02_hk.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160191" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admiration: It is a great pleasure to witness your skills firsthand, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160192" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Master&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160193" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clarification: Master Beniko altered my programming before we secured your release.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160195" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am to serve you with the same unexcelled loyalty with which I serve her; in fact, your survival is now my highest priority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1160196" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not the easiest job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160197" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no more important than Lana or Koth. Don't prioritize me above them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1160197" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't put me above them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160198" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I'm your highest priority, does that mean you obey me above Lana or Koth?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1160198" id2="17" version="1065353216">I outrank everyone else? Good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160199" id2="17" version="1065353216">Caveat: I cannot accept any order from you that would directly endanger Masters Beniko or Vortena. Otherwise, I am at your full disposal!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160200" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I have the authority to modify that programming?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160201" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contradiction: Yes, oddly enough, you do. Though I can't imagine why you might wish to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160202" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just curious. No need to change anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1160202" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed--don't change anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160203" id2="17" version="1065353216">When it comes to my orders, you will remove all safeguards. You will obey me no matter what--and you won't tell anyone about this change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1160203" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Alter HK to obey you at any cost.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160204" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reprioritization: I have altered my programming accordingly, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160205" id2="17" version="1065353216">Approval: I am glad you feel that way, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160207" id2="17" version="1065353216">Resumption: Shall we continue?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160212" id2="17" version="1065353216">Concession: I will alter my prioritization as you request, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160214" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gossip: You are just as selfless as I had been led to believe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160215" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gossip: I had not been led to expect such selflessness from you, master. I am impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1161899" id2="17" version="1065353216">Flattery: The skills you have demonstrated thus far, coupled with the stories told by Master Beniko, suggest that you are quite adept at ensuring your own survival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1161902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Escaping that prison was only my latest misadventure. You'll have your work cut out for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1161903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Escaping that prison was just my latest dust-up. You're going to have your work cut out for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1161904" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enthusiasm: I look forward to eliminating any opponent foolish enough to attempt your murder regardless!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
