<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>94</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_04/scene_06_lana_hk.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162002" id2="17" version="1065353216">A freshwater spring. It should be safe for drinking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162003" id2="17" version="1065353216">So the Eternal Fleet overwhelmed both the Republic and the Empire. What was the result?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Both sides are forced to pay a heavy tribute to Zakuul, mainly raw materials and resources. They are also held under an arms limitation statute.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162006" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire and the Republic are both breaking it, of course, but they're still incapable of challenging the Throne directly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who's in charge of the Republic now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Saresh reached the end of her term limits recently, but her replacement is a carefully-selected puppet. She still runs things, even if she isn't officially the Chancellor anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162009" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the Empire?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only one member of the Dark Council remained after the chaos: Darth Acina. She now rules as Empress of the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who rules the Empire now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Acina was the only Dark Council member left standing; all others died or disappeared in the chaos. Without opposition, she declared herself Empress of the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162014" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Saresh remains in power, though she no longer holds the title of Chancellor. The Republic has limits to their rulers' terms, but her replacement is a mere puppet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Both sides see this only as an opportunity to eliminate one another at a time of weakness instead of combining what strength they have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arcann does nothing to prevent violence between them so long as their tribute is paid and no one challenges Zakuul's superiority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162020" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised Arcann didn't try to destroy both governments. He obviously had the firepower.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1162020" id2="17" version="1065353216">He could've destroyed both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162021" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think Arcann feels any desire to actually govern our portion of the galaxy; for now, he sees it as a backwater, useful only for resources.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162023" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does Arcann use the tribute for? Zakuul doesn't seem to need much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1162023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where does the tribute go?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162024" id2="17" version="1065353216">A question no one else seems to ask or answer--not in any detail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zakuul's empire spans a sizeable portion of Wild Space, but not enough to consume the resources they're acquiring. I've been working to learn the answer myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even after all of this time, Saresh is ruining the Republic. Something needs to be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1162028" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe Saresh is still around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Saresh and her lackeys aren't our most urgent concern. Their resources can't help us--not yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Acina cannot stand against me. Take me back to the Empire and I'll hold the throne in a matter of hours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1162031" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is my chance to rule.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162032" id2="17" version="1065353216">Neither Empress Acina nor the Republic are our most pressing concern. We cannot make use of their resources yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162034" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith Empire would be better off if someone other than the Sith ran things. That should be obvious by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1162034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith shouldn't rule.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our entire society is based on Sith rule, and it has accomplished much. We don't necessarily need different leaders--they just need different priorities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Powerful Zakuulan battle stations have been placed in orbit around key worlds to watch for possible uprisings, but there are no ongoing planetary occupations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162039" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ships of the Eternal Fleet simply patrol at random, while the tribute paid to Zakuul gradually chokes all economic potential.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162040" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about my team? My ship?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162041" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have allies looking for them as we speak. With all of the chaos of the last few years, though, it will take time to find them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162043" id2="17" version="1065353216">For now, we make do with ourselves, Koth, and HK.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162044" id2="17" version="1065353216">You obviously put a lot of thought into getting me out--did you think about what would come after?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1162044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have a plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162045" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course--though I admittedly didn't plan on being stranded in this swamp. For now, let's take things one step at a time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162046" id2="17" version="1065353216">As long as you're here, there's nothing we can't handle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1162046" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] You're all I need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162047" id2="17" version="1065353216">The feeling is mutual. It truly is a relief to see you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that why you went to so much trouble to rescue me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speaking of Koth, you two seem to have a lot of history. Personal history.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1162049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's talk about you and Koth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162050" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's been an invaluable ally. Koth is a Zakuul native, a veteran officer of their military--one of the few who hadn't been replaced by a droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162052" id2="17" version="1065353216">He and his crew were part of the occupation of the planet Denon. When ordered to do things they weren't comfortable with, Koth took his ship and crew and went rogue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162053" id2="17" version="1065353216">What exactly were they ordered to do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162054" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's for Koth to say. But I trust him with my life, as I trust you. I'm confident that you'll learn to trust one another just as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162055" id2="17" version="1065353216">So why me? You clearly went to a lot of trouble to get me out of carbonite.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162056" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before you were captured, you accomplished things no one else dared to attempt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162058" id2="17" version="1065353216">You changed the galaxy more than once--and if things have ever needed to change, now is the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162060" id2="17" version="1065353216">But... there is something else. I've felt it since the moment I found you in carbonite. There's a power in you, something new... it's elusive, but I know it's there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162061" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you're right, Lana. I think the Emperor--Valkorion--is in my mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1162061" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor is in my mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162062" id2="17" version="1065353216">What?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162063" id2="17" version="1065353216">After he died, there was a storm of energy... I barely even remember being thrown into the carbon freezing chamber.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162065" id2="17" version="1065353216">And then, while I was frozen, I saw things... dreamed about him, about everything that happened while I was gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162066" id2="17" version="1065353216">It can't be. If he were controlling you, I'd know it. I certainly saw enough of it on Ziost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162067" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think he's trying to control me... not directly, anyway. He was trying to convince me to work with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1162067" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is different.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever he's doing, we can be sure that he is always trying to deceive us somehow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162070" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't heard his voice since you revived me, but... is there really any way I could know for sure that he isn't controlling me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1162070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe it was just a dream.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162071" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose not. But we have to try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162073" id2="17" version="1065353216">He doesn't control me--he's not strong enough. All of his power is just an illusion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1162073" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not afraid of him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deception is his greatest tool, yes, but... we shouldn't discount his influence so quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162076" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe in you. And I appreciate your honesty--I'll remain watchful for any influence he might have over you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162078" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the time being, though, we have no choice but to proceed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162079" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the others?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162080" id2="17" version="1065353216">They wouldn't understand--and like you said, we really don't know anything for sure yet. Let's keep the matter between us for now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162081" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know what you're talking about, Lana. I'm the same now as I was when they froze me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1162081" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] I haven't changed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something is different--I'm sure of it. But for now, I'm just relieved to have you back with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162084" id2="17" version="1065353216">The water was our last necessity--shall we return?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Request: Please rendezvous at my current coordinates at your earliest convenience, masters. I require assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162090" id2="17" version="1065353216">Salutation: It is a pleasure to see you again so soon, masters. I have encountered minimal resistance in my patrol.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162092" id2="17" version="1065353216">How &quot;minimal&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162094" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reassurance: Only one Skytrooper and three local predators with poor survival instincts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162096" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our position appears to be secure at this time, but I would still advise caution on your return trip, masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162097" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep up the good work, HK.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1162097" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162098" id2="17" version="1065353216">Appreciation: It will be my pleasure to do so, master!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162099" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you've already spotted enemy scouts, more are bound to be coming. Keep patrolling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1162099" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get back to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162100" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reassurance: I will annihilate any potential threat that approaches the Gravestone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162308" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's been an invaluable ally. Did he tell you that he was a former officer in the Zakuulan navy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162309" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. He said that he deserted with his crew.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162310" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right. I've come to trust Koth with my life, just as I trust you. I'm confident that you'll learn to trust one another just as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1162312" id2="17" version="1065353216">Strange... we should hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176218" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you end up working together with Koth?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1176218" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about Koth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176219" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew I'd never find you alone. Recruiting assets with firsthand knowledge of Zakuul was my top priority for years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176221" id2="17" version="1065353216">Koth was on the run, pursued by the deadliest of the Zakuul Knights. I... resolved... the situation, and we've worked together ever since.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
