<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>32</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_04/scene_04_arcann_lana_koth.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160305" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Endless Swamp. After the damage you inflicted, they couldn't have made a safe landing anywhere else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160307" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if they didn't make a safe landing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160309" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll know soon enough. Skytroopers: sweep the area. Focus on regions with high metallic sensor readings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160311" id2="17" version="1065353216">I oversaw security in the carbonite prison. I... I humbly submit myself to answer for this failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sister?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160315" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't like his answer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160318" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this ship has been here for... a thousand years? More?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right. It's amazing that it's in such good condition, considering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Judging by the damage I've seen, the stories are true: whoever built the Gravestone scuttled it themselves after the Eternal Fleet was defeated. It wasn't shot down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160375" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Fleet was defeated, but not destroyed--Valkorion brought it back, under his own control, more than a century ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160377" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly. The Eternal Fleet is totally automated--nobody knows who first built it, and every theory is crazier than the last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160379" id2="17" version="1065353216">Renegades left behind after a successful droid revolution... representatives of an entire race of droids from somewhere beyond the edge of the known galaxy....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160381" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like I said: crazy stuff. But no matter where it came from, the Eternal Fleet is practically unstoppable, and Arcann controls every single ship from the Throne.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160384" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Valkorion has had this unstoppable fleet for more than a century, why didn't he use it to help the Sith Empire defeat the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1160384" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why didn't Valkorion use the Fleet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160385" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can only theorize. If the war was just part of a ritual to make the Emperor truly immortal, perhaps using the Fleet would have interfered somehow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160387" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regardless, we have many other things to discuss. I owe you five years' worth of explanations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160389" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I'm going to need some parts to get this thing moving again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Locating supplies and fresh water would also be wise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160392" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll help you find what we need, Lana.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1160392" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Help Lana find supplies first]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get those parts first. Might take a while to install them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1160393" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Help Koth find parts first]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah. Ship this old, there's no telling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160398" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assertion: I will begin a patrol pattern to ensure that no enemy forces report our position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160924" id2="17" version="1065353216">So if we defeat Arcann, the Eternal Fleet isn't a problem anymore?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1160924" id2="17" version="1065353216">So Arcann is our target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160925" id2="17" version="1065353216">So against this giant, unstoppable fleet, we have... ourselves, and an ancient wreck that may never fly again?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1160925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't say I like those odds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160933" id2="17" version="1065353216">So long as the Throne goes to someone other than his sister, yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1160935" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you put it that way, how could we lose?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
