<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>130</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197390" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know what you're thinking, but don't worry, I'm not going to say it's cold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197391" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sense a lot of apathy and disgruntlement. The morale of Imperial forces here is as low as the temperature.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197392" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm betting spilled blood freezes before it hits the ice here. I look forward to finding out firsthand.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197393" id2="17" version="1065353216">The cold does not affect me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197394" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing but snow for kilometers either way, and I already can't feel my toes. Whose idea was it to come here again?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197395" id2="17" version="1065353216">And to think, I used to love snow. Just one look out here, and I've already had enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197396" id2="17" version="1065353216">You brought us to the wrong planet, agent. There's nothing here worth having.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Breathe deeply, here. There is great beauty on this world... along with keen discomfort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197398" id2="17" version="1065353216">What exceptionally bracing weather this planet has. The fresh air will be good for both of us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Brrr. I knew it'd be cold, but I lost feeling in my feet just on the shuttle down....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just so we're clear, frostbite still counts as death and dismemberment so far as our work agreement goes... knew I should have worn a thicker coat....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197401" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cold. Didn't join up to let the weather do me in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197404" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I ever tell you I have a fear of freezing to death?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197405" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have reinforcements ready if we need them, my lord. Just say the word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thinking of throwing a grenade just to warm things up a bit.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197407" id2="17" version="1065353216">All your industry won't prolong your lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197408" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a little warmer by the pipes, I think. Looks like someone's pumping geothermal energy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197409" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remember seeing a pipeline like this as a child on my homeworld. We used it to pump geothermal energy to the surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got a ways to go before we hit the next shelter. Hope you're ready for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197411" id2="17" version="1065353216">How long before these structures are buried in the snow? The Empire is strong--but planets are strong, as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197412" id2="17" version="1065353216">The monthly maintenance required by this equipment could support a small moon. The military is taking this push seriously.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197413" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't imagine trying to build something like that out here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197414" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're trying to pump heat from under the ice. Go figure, I'd have thought this place was frozen to the core.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good landmark, should keep our bearings. Get lost out here, that's it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197418" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at the size of that place! Who built that thing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm, clearly man-made structure. Fanatics of some kind to build that out of ice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at that thing. Crazy to be out there stacking ice. It doesn't even have a roof!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197421" id2="17" version="1065353216">A tower of ice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave it to the brotherhood to open shop in the biggest hunk of ice on the planet. Subtlety never was their thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197423" id2="17" version="1065353216">So that's the brotherhood ice fortress. I wonder how these outcroppings are formed. I doubt the pirates built them themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197424" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sort of freaks build a fortress out of ice? Listen to me--pirates like cash and comfort, they don't do this....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197425" id2="17" version="1065353216">A palace, crafted from ice. Perhaps we're too quick to judge these pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197426" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think that structure was built by the Republic. But I'm surprised pirates would be so enterprising.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197427" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would you look at that glacial peak? It's like a--like a big tooth or something. I don't think that's natural.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get a load of that peak. It's a little too even, like somebody shaped it. I've heard of ice sculpting, but that's taking it a bit far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197429" id2="17" version="1065353216">See that? The spike, in the distance. Some kind of ice fortress. Wonder who made it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197432" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pirate vault. This is what I've been waiting for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197433" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suspect there will be more dangers ahead, my lord. The pirates will doubtlessly have defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rest is for the weak. Think we're past the worst of it. Let's press on.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come out of your hiding places, little pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197436" id2="17" version="1065353216">These guys call themselves pirates. They should be out in space, cut free. Not hiding in ice caves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you think these are friends of Andronikos? I can imagine him living in a cave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197438" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've gone through a lot of garbage to get here. Now it's payday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Storybook characters raid pirate vaults. Now, so do we.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197440" id2="17" version="1065353216">The White Maw is very serious about their security. I advise caution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197441" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know they're shut down, but these droids are giving me the creeps. I feel like we're being watched.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197442" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, that's not suspicious. Look, I don't exactly see a security network, but I'm not taking my chances.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't like the look of this. Got &quot;trap&quot; written all over it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197446" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, that's it, I tried not to say anything, but bantha poo, it's freezing!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197447" id2="17" version="1065353216">All ships, no matter how big and powerful, eventually fall. A lesson for us all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197448" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is one bantha of a ship carcass. Bet the impact when it crashed was an amazing sight.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197449" id2="17" version="1065353216">The carcass of a great ship. Death claims all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197450" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star of Coruscant. Always wondered what happened to her. Spent a week in her brig once. Wish I'd been the one to shoot her down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197451" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star of Coruscant. So this is what happened to it. It had a crew of over a thousand. I'd be surprised if any survived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197452" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's one big ship, I'll give you that. Probably crack a planet with that thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197453" id2="17" version="1065353216">It must have been massive. No surprise the Republic wants it back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197454" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remember the reports coming in from Hoth during the war. I was at headquarters when the Republic superdreadnaught went down... the whole room cheered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197455" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, wow. That has to be the dreadnaught... look at the size of it. It must be covering a few kilometers of the planet's surface!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197456" id2="17" version="1065353216">There she is. The Star of Coruscant. I'm surprised there's so much intact. Can you imagine what it took to bring that baby down?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Phew. Ship worth fighting for alright. Never fly again though, couldn't... could it?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197462" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = regretting not upgrading anti-freeze systems</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197463" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you mashed Hoth together with Tatooine, would it make a decent planet with nice weather?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197464" id2="17" version="1065353216">I left Balmorra for this frozen wasteland? What was I thinking?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Must endure cold, for Herald and hunt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197466" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? No sip of brandy before we set out into the cold?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quiet. Stark. Beautiful. Whole planet is an empty page.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cold air feels good on Bowdaar's fur.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197469" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're sure you need me in the frozen wasteland? I could do so much more from the ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hoth. Beautiful desolation. A fitting test of a warrior's survival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be sure to take all precautions against hypothermia outlined in Service Manual chapter four.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197472" id2="17" version="1065353216">These desolate conditions do nothing to dampen my resolve! Lead on, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ice and snow, as far as you can see. I can't tell you how glad I am to be here, boss.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Frozen geysers = evidence of underground hot zones // Jedi + T7 = find them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197477" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, Hoth isn't all bad. This area right here? Kinda pretty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hot geysers, frozen solid. That's how you know a planet's too cold.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha. Hoth has teeth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197480" id2="17" version="1065353216">These ice formations inspired Gerrut's theory of tertiary volition. Obvious, now that I see them in person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197481" id2="17" version="1065353216">Frozen geysers. Beauty from chaos. Always where you least expect it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow, look at that. The geysers froze mid-burst. Isn't that something?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Frozen geysers. That's something you don't see often. Thankfully.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive. Nature itself is no match for Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. Frozen geysers would be my guess. Quite a sight out here in the middle of nowhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Formations resulting from the flash-freezing of surface geysers. No tactical significance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice. Looks like shrapnel from a big, icy grenade.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197490" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = requesting hot oil bath post-mission</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just when you think you've seen every form of ice on Hoth, somebody has to go and build a fortress out of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197492" id2="17" version="1065353216">You see that giant tower out there? That can't be a natural formation.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is strange formation there. Or, was built.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of all the things to build your castle from. Ice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197495" id2="17" version="1065353216">There. Someone's stronghold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197496" id2="17" version="1065353216">That ice tower looks man-made. What lunatics had the time for that project?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197497" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me guess: We're going to wind up at the ice fortress? Knowing you, it's inevitable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197498" id2="17" version="1065353216">That tower in the distance is an invitation to battle. We should answer the call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197499" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think that buildup is a natural formation, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197500" id2="17" version="1065353216">The feature in front of us did not occur naturally!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197501" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is that supposed to be? Looks like a building.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pirates = clever hiding place // Jedi + T7 = more clever</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197505" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hoth. If the cold doesn't kill you, the pointy landscape will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197506" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could be worse. This cave could be full of man-eating wampas. It's not, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have seen ice stalactites cut men in half.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197508" id2="17" version="1065353216">When we get back, I'm finding those designs for a centrally heated coat. If you insist on trekking across this snowball, I can at least be comfortable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful. Ice stalactites might come loose. Sharp as razors.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bowdaar smells many pirates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197511" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am officially tired of all this ice. Think I'll take out my anger on the local pirate population.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197512" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pirates are cowards for hiding in these holes. They will learn the error of their ways.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197513" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no telling what kind of defenses the pirates might have built in here--watch for blind corners and ambushes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pirates, Imperials--anyone who strikes at the Republic will face swift justice!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Charging into a pirate base instead of an Imp base--should be a nice change of pace.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197518" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 + Jedi = need a vacation // Location = anyplace warm</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at the size of that thing. No wonder everyone's fighting over it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197520" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's one monster of a starship. Too bad it's a wreck.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="197521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ship could hold every clan ever hatched, and every prey they hunted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoever built that ship wasn't shy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic hubris. Always overbuilding their ships.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that a starship, or did someone break off a piece of Coruscant?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wouldn't you love to salvage that thing? Has to be worth a fortune.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197526" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should upgrade your starship to one like that--preferably a version that flies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197527" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star of Coruscant. One of the most powerful ships the Republic ever designed. They just don't build 'em like they used to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197528" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star of Coruscant. I never thought I'd actually see it in person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197529" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star of Coruscant. A landmark of Republic engineering--such a waste!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023233" id2="17" version="1065353216">Praise: You are wise to bring me, master. Unlike soft organics, I am not intimidated by cold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023236" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rumination: This geothermal station could provide enough heat to melt this ice shelf, if improperly directed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023239" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alert: Be cautious, master. Any undesirable who would sculpt a fortress like that is likely insane.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023242" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insult: A pirate vault. How quaint. Perhaps we will find rare treasures and make it worth the effort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023245" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reverie: Oh, to command such a vessel, master. Think of the potential liquidations. Whole planets, wiped clean for the Maker.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reassurance: Fear not, master--sub-freezing temperatures do not impair my functionality.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observation: Impressive natural structures--highly useful for pinning down troublemakers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reflection: Consider the insanity that drove troublemakers to build such a place. I look forward to deleting them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Announcement: I am composing an opera, master. I call it &quot;Deleting Pirates Under the Ice.&quot; It's a tragedy--for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1023485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Truism: Your Republic must remember to keep its dreadnaughts in space where they belong.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
