<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>80</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/the_colicoid_war_game/republic/master_satele_shan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="513442" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513444" id2="17" version="1065353216">The competition is over, Master Satele. We won.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your safe return is cause enough for celebration, but preventing the Empire from gaining new weapons is a significant victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513447" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoids have already begun shipping technology to our forces. You've bought us some much-needed breathing room.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anytime, Master Satele. You can always count on me and my allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513449" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've proven that on more occasions than I can count.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513451" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made it sound like these weapons were our ticket to victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that all?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Weapons are only one factor in this conflict. Nothing is ever certain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513454" id2="17" version="1065353216">From what I saw, the Colicoids are just as bad as the Empire. When this war's over, we'll be fighting those insects.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513454" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoids are a threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513455" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sincerely hope that is not true--but I will communicate your observation to Republic High Command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513457" id2="17" version="1065353216">This unfortunate business is behind us, but the war goes on--as do your personal missions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do what you can to hold the line out there. Give our people time to regroup. May the Force be with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="513461" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Opening priority channel &quot;indigo seven.&quot; I'm receiving your transmission. It's good to see you, but I'm afraid I don't have pleasant news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513464" id2="17" version="1065353216">The war is not going well for Republic forces. We've sustained heavy losses on multiple fronts. The Empire is too well-equipped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513466" id2="17" version="1065353216">And unless we take immediate action, they could gain a decisive advantage that will overwhelm us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513467" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've fought too hard to let the Empire beat us. I assume you have a plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Failure is not an option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a plan--a surprise opportunity from an unexpected source.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513470" id2="17" version="1065353216">From what I've seen, the Republic is kicking the Empire's back side. What happened?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513470" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I thought we were winning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513471" id2="17" version="1065353216">This war spans dozens of systems. For every one where the Republic emerges victorious, there are three where we don't. But there is hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe our troops need better leaders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time for new leadership.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513474" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're facing practical realities. Troop numbers. Technology. We need more of both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513476" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoids are an insectoid species who have remained neutral in the war. They're weapon merchants, selling to both sides.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513478" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've developed devastating new weapon designs. The Republic must secure the Colicoids' technology to survive the Empire's onslaught.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513479" id2="17" version="1065353216">It isn't enough to get these weapons for ourselves. We have to stop the Empire from acquiring them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513479" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's only half the solution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Correct. You were not summoned to negotiate an arms deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513482" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised to find you advocating an escalation of this destructive war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attacking is not the Jedi way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless the Republic defends itself, this war will end all too quickly for us. It is a difficult truth we cannot ignore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513485" id2="17" version="1065353216">The better the weapon, the better the soldier. If we want to send the Empire packing, we need all the firepower we can get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513485" id2="17" version="1065353216">No arguments here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513486" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish it weren't so, but our battlefield casualty reports don't lie.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513488" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get it. You want me to meet with these Colicoids--work out a deal. Piece of flatcake, your Masterfulness. Leave it to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513488" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need a negotiator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513489" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoids have made their terms quite clear. Negotiation is not an option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513491" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fought some of these beasts on Balmorra. They didn't know the business end of a hydrospanner, much less how to design advanced weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513491" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are smart Colicoids?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513492" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoids on Balmorra are genetically engineered drones. True Colicoids are highly intelligent beings--and far more dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513494" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of weapons are we talking about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Describe the Colicoid tech.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513495" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a broad array: everything from orbital torpedo pods and droid tanks to advanced infantry shields.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513497" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoids have issued a challenge to both Republic and Empire. We are invited to a contest of military might.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513499" id2="17" version="1065353216">The winner receives an exclusive contract to purchase the Colicoids' weapons. The loser gets nothing. The Empire has already accepted and sent forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513500" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would the Colicoids make an exclusive offer? Wouldn't they profit more from selling to both of us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513500" id2="17" version="1065353216">An odd bargain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colicoids are shrewd merchants. They know that both Republic and Empire will pay dearly for an advantage the other side cannot possess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513503" id2="17" version="1065353216">What exactly is this contest? How do we win--best two out of three?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513503" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are the rules?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513504" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are no rules. It is simply war on a battlefield created for commerce.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513506" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would the Republic participate in the Colicoids' sick game?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513506" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Colicoids are insane.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513507" id2="17" version="1065353216">We sought a more peaceful negotiation, but the Empire's agreement to their terms forced our hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513509" id2="17" version="1065353216">A small strike team must enter a remote asteroid base on the Outer Rim. The Colicoids will test our battle-worthiness there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513511" id2="17" version="1065353216">I find the entire scenario barbaric and wasteful, but we cannot allow the Empire to acquire the Colicoid weapons unopposed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513512" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I've learned anything from this war, it's that the enemy won't rest until we're all dead. I'll fight this battle, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513512" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll do what we must.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Again and again, I ask too much of you. And yet you never fail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Using their weapons to stop the Empire can only benefit the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our efforts won't be wasted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513516" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope when this war finally ends we'll have no further need of such terrible devices.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad handles details like this every day, Master Satele. If there's a battle to fight, we're there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513518" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's all you had to say.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every day? I regret so many sacrifices are required of you, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never let your competitor steal a deal. Besides, I assume the players in this little chess match get paid--right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513521" id2="17" version="1065353216">That wouldn't be sporting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513522" id2="17" version="1065353216">In addition to whatever Colicoid technology you obtain during the competition, you'll be amply rewarded by the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it too late to back out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like it or not, you rank among the Republic's greatest warriors. If you cannot win this competition, no one can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513527" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Twenty years ago, I would be answering the challenge. But I am no longer the warrior you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be aware: The Colicoids will participate in their own contest. Killing you elevates their individual clans. They won't exercise restraint.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your shuttle is waiting nearby--hurry. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="513534" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This holoterminal is offline.]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
