<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>27</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/operation/rishi/the_ravagers/intro/ruugar.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141671" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mark of the Ravagers. Bloodiest, meanest crew of killers in the Rim.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Used to be my crew. Had some class, when I was running things. Even let people surrender sometimes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your crew? You were their captain?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, till I took a blade in the back. Few other places, too. Can thank my second-in-command for that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coratanni. She calls herself captain, now--hah! &quot;Kill everyone, steal everything.&quot; Real complex strategy, there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141679" id2="17" version="1065353216">What I wouldn't do to get my crew back from her backstabbing hands....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141680" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would you go legit?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Huh? What are you talking about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141682" id2="17" version="1065353216">I help you get your crew back, you all become privateers for the Republic. What do you say?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141683" id2="17" version="1065353216">I say aye! Better a captain for you than nothing at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141685" id2="17" version="1065353216">They run junkers to our old hideout all the time. You can stow away on one and nobody will be the wiser.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141687" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know that place like the back... hm. What I mean is, I can talk you through once you're inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just be sure you take some friends along--the Ravagers didn't earn their reputation for nothing, and Coratanni's the toughest of them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revenge will be sweet....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141695" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, that takes me back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141697" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Ravagers. Terrors of sea and sky. They got a motto: &quot;Why leave 'em alive when you can kill 'em?&quot; Not the cleverest, granted, but it is appropriate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you talking to me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141699" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seen you around here. Seen what you can do. I got a proposal, like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141701" id2="17" version="1065353216">Used to be the Ravagers' captain till I got double-crossed by my first mate. Coratanni. Cut me up good, left me for dead. Took my hand for a trophy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141703" id2="17" version="1065353216">She doesn't deserve to call herself captain. Sure, she stuck one into my back okay, but she doesn't know from killing or looting--not like me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141704" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what do you propose?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141705" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get rid of Coratanni. Get me my crew back. Do that, and the Empire's got itself a major player on Rishi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ravagers got a nice little hideout. It's remote, hard to get to, but they make junk runs all the time. Stow away on a scow and you're in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141708" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds easy enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141709" id2="17" version="1065353216">Might want to take some, ah, associates with you. Even with Coratanni at the helm, the Ravagers ain't nothing to mess with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141711" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep in touch along the way. Lend you a hand, so to speak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1141713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Haha... revenge, revenge, revenge. Here it comes, Cora....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
