<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>12</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/class/smuggler/skavak.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="686143" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, well. The jackal of the stars himself pays me a visit. Long time no see, Skavak. You must really need my help, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="686145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Urbax, buddy, you're such a cynical guy. Can't I just be paying an old friend a visit?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="686147" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;You&quot; and &quot;friends&quot; is the funniest thing I've heard all year. Get to the point before I stop laughing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="686149" id2="17" version="1065353216">A lawman from the Outer Rim is sticking to me like a mynock on a power coupling. I need somebody to scrape him off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="686151" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lawman, huh? Sounds like that'll cost double.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="686153" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever it takes. I'm in a rush to wrap up other business here. Besides, finding work for my friends makes me feel good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="686155" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice. So, where is this little parasite you want me to remove?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="686157" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's at a docking bay in the spaceport, and he's alone. I'm sure he won't give a burly scrapper like you much trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="686159" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guarantee he won't. Oh, and I'll be wanting my payment in advance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="686161" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't have it any other way, Urbax. You enjoy yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="686163" id2="17" version="1065353216">It might be this lawman knows how to find Skavak. We'd better try to save him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="686165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's go bust up that party at the spaceport, Captain.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
