<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>43</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/world/firestar/captain_neddis.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713973" id2="17" version="1065353216">The war proceeds well, thanks to your help with Firestar.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713974" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard the reports. Lasers raining down from the sky, shield generators in flames... Operation Firestar is a reality now, thanks to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713976" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've opened up new strategies for us. I hope support from the Empire's elite becomes more common on Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713977" id2="17" version="1065353216">We all serve the same cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="713977" id2="17" version="1065353216">It should.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713978" id2="17" version="1065353216">A cause we're now closer to achieving. You're a credit to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="713979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't presume.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713980" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand. I won't presume to ask again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="713981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are we done here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. I won't ask for any more of your time, but you'll have my gratitude forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713984" id2="17" version="1065353216">Operation Firestar consists of two phases: The targets must be painted, and the satellites must be fired.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Generators targeted. Weapons locked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aerial Assault Commander Neddis, my lord, at your service. One moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aerial Assault Commander Neddis, sir. I'll be with you in a moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713993" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be with you in a moment. We've an aerial attack underway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fire when ready, Hawk Leader.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Proton bombs away... generators show no damage. Should we come around for another run?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="713999" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the use? Return to base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714001" id2="17" version="1065353216">There you have it--the resistance shield generators are well-nigh invulnerable. Too entrenched for our bombers, too well-armored for ground assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714002" id2="17" version="1065353216">I take it you're in charge of the bombing runs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714002" id2="17" version="1065353216">You command the air attacks?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714003" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right. Just promoted... and not long for the position, unless we resolve the generator situation. Pity our &quot;solution&quot; is so troublesome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714006" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's another failed strike against the resistance... and our only &quot;solution&quot; is troublesome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714008" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not here to save you. If you can't fight this war, you can be replaced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you've failed us, fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714009" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear the Empire doesn't take kindly to failures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your bosses won't like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen to me. We haven't lost this. There's... a solution, of sorts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714012" id2="17" version="1065353216">This planet is orbited by laser defense satellites. Most were destroyed in the invasion, but a few still function.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714014" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we took over the laser satellites via their control tower, we could aim them at the planet and destroy the shield generators. My predecessor called it &quot;Operation Firestar.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714015" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you have a plan, why is it up for discussion?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then what's the problem?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714016" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds like something worth seeing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714016" id2="17" version="1065353216">A laser from the sky, eh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714017" id2="17" version="1065353216">It would be. Unfortunately, it hasn't happened yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="714019" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Firestar was scrapped. With the resistance blasting us every step of the way, taking the control tower is impossible. And we have no alternative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714022" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Operation Firestar stays iced, the aerial campaign is doomed. But perhaps... you can do what a squad of soldiers can't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714023" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Operation Firestar stays iced, the aerial campaign is doomed. But perhaps... a Sith's wrath can do what a squad of soldiers can't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714024" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Operation Firestar stays iced, the aerial campaign is doomed. But perhaps... you can go where a squad of soldiers can't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714025" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a mercenary. Make the impossible possible... and we'll see you compensated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="714027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Neddis to Hawk Squadron... engage maneuver X-16....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
