<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>57</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/world/republic/speaking_their_language/officer_serik.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sessar? Madoon, come in! Is anyone there? Blast!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522697" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't thank you enough. Fifty-one's spreading the word, and pretty soon all the guards will know how to stop the Rattataki.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522698" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've studied the jungle noise and found a number of non-indigenous bird calls that increase before an attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522700" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Rattataki are imitating bird calls?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522702" id2="17" version="1065353216">My programming enables me to replicate these calls. I can teach the remaining guards to recognize them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get right on that, Fifty-one. Thanks for protecting him out there--with this info, we can finally avoid their attacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522705" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll be nice to see the Rattataki on the defensive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="522705" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to turn the tables.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522706" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll say. Thanks for everything. We couldn't have cracked their codes without your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="522707" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not that big a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522708" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've helped even the playing field in this sector. I think that deserves some recognition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522710" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll be a lot safer knowing when the Rattataki are going to attack. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="522711" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for wasting my skills.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522712" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care if you're offended or not. We're safer. That's all that matters to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522714" id2="17" version="1065353216">How's it going out there? Getting the information you need?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522716" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you fight a ghost, Master Jedi?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522718" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major, I've never faced a foe this crafty before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522720" id2="17" version="1065353216">By now, the Rattataki prisoners control more guard towers than we do; they certainly control the jungle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522721" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your people are armed and trained. How are prisoners gaining the upper hand?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="522721" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can they overcome guards?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522722" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Rattataki are fearsome hunters--and twice as deadly now that they're free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522724" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been around, but I've never heard of the Rattataki before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="522724" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know the Rattataki.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522725" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're white as death, and nearly as quiet. The Rattataki were the most vicious of the prisoners, and getting free only whet their appetite.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="522727" id2="17" version="1065353216">So... tell your superiors?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look around. The Rattataki are killing guards left, right and center, and you're the only one still standing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522730" id2="17" version="1065353216">The worst are called the Blood of Talath. They've turned the jungle into a slaughterhouse. Traps are everywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522732" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're communicating somehow--they spring, fall back and regroup with military precision. But they don't have comms or computers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522733" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to figure out how they're operating.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="522733" id2="17" version="1065353216">Communications can be broken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522734" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was thinking the same thing. Let me introduce you to someone. Fifty-one? Come over here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522736" id2="17" version="1065353216">They have to be getting the information from somewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="522736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you've got a leak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522737" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no mole--there's no one left to squeal. It's like they figured out we're there and gathered an army to fight back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="522739" id2="17" version="1065353216">They sound pretty nasty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522740" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're great at parties--assuming you want the guests brutally murdered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, if we can figure out how they're talking, I have an idea how we can disrupt it. Fifty-one? Come over here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, I am C-5D1. Officer Serik believes I can uncover how the Rattataki communicate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Protocol droid--built to translate new languages, right? Give him enough time in the jungle, he'll hear whatever we're missing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522748" id2="17" version="1065353216">Problem is, the Rattataki are going to be suspicious of random droids. He won't last thirty seconds unescorted. Any chance you could help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522749" id2="17" version="1065353216">He will be safe with me, I assure you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="522749" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can escort your droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522750" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force will protect us from their attacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="522750" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can escort your droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522751" id2="17" version="1065353216">If he can follow orders, I'll keep him safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="522751" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can escort your droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522752" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got a knack for slipping things past blockades, or so I'm told.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="522752" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can escort your droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. Just keep the Rattataki off of Fifty-one, and he'll let you know when he's ready to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522755" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will it take long to break their communications code?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="522755" id2="17" version="1065353216">How much time will he need?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure. Fifty-one will let you know when he's got all the data he needs. When he's done, get him back here safely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522758" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll also need to listen from several points within the jungle, to rule out ambient sounds. I apologize for the trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get in too deep--we've lost enough people already.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="522762" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're kidding. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522763" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should have known better. We were self-reliant before the Sith showed up, so getting by without you is no problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="522765" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still haven't heard back from a patrol I sent out this morning. Tell me if you see anything out there, will you?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
