<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>34</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tatooine/bronze/imperial/rogue_processes/ensign_rosha.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616418" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to know the Exchange won't be reporting on my every message home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616420" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Exchange won't be spying on you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Probably untrue, but at least they won't be able to use the same tricks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616427" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616431" id2="17" version="1065353216">According to the tracer you planted, it's Hutts paying for information against us. High Command will have a lot to say about that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616433" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope this covers any expenses you may have incurred.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616436" id2="17" version="1065353216">The coordinates for the uplink towers should be in your datapad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah! And I thought they weren't taking my reports seriously.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616439" id2="17" version="1065353216">But here they are, sending a group of the Empire's most storied defenders....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616441" id2="17" version="1065353216">But here they are, sending me a Sith Lord to handle the problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616443" id2="17" version="1065353216">But here they are, teaming me up with one of the Intelligence Minister's best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616445" id2="17" version="1065353216">But here they are, hiring one of the galaxy's top bounty hunters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616447" id2="17" version="1065353216">But here they are, sending me one of the Empire's best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616449" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess the Exchange spying on us really gets High Command's regulation briefs in a twist, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616450" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid I don't understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't High Command brief you? I told them I needed advanced operatives capable of targeting strikes against Exchange spies in public locales.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody sent me here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616454" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't been hired.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616455" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop talking nonsense!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you... weren't sent by High Command? I requested advanced operatives who could perform targeted strikes against Exchange spies in public locations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616458" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're using satellite uplinks to get into our databases. Advanced stuff for them. We're guessing the Republic or someone is backing them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616460" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to get the codes they're using, sabotage their connections and find out who they're forwarding the intel to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616461" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll deal with this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616462" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you offering?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616463" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can arrange a payment, yes. Does that mean you'll take the job?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spell out what you need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616466" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Exchange has taken over a number of satellite uplink towers. I'll transmit a file with which ones.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616468" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need to get the codes for the uplink towers from their people on-site, then use them to sabotage the links.</text>
		<text bitflag="5441" id1="616470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best-case scenario, you also plant this tracer so our techs can track who the information is being fed to. Thanks for helping us out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616473" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not needed. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616474" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess I should send a second alert....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our goals here would be better accomplished had we wiped out the native life before landing....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
