<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_14/scene_06_shae_torian_khomo.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183842" id2="17" version="1065353216">They level a thousand guns against us, and still we endure. Ha!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183844" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done, all of you. We'll head into the factory within the hour.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183845" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a droid--GEMINI Prime--linked to its machinery somewhere. It's key to beating the Eternal Fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take your droid--so long as we claim the weapons. Imagine: the clans rearmed with the spoils of Darvannis, led by a new Mandalore...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183848" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll break the siege of our homeworlds and smash Zakuul like in the days of the Neo-Crusaders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183850" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Mandalorian Neo-Crusaders were beaten by the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183852" id2="17" version="1065353216">But they left scars. And they survived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dream of glory another time. Go! Prepare the clans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183856" id2="17" version="1065353216">One commander to another? Half the time, I feel like I'm making calls just to keep my people together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183857" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone can plan a war or negotiate a treaty. Not anyone can hold an army together while doing it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1183857" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what leadership means.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183858" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. Not anyone can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183860" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least all your troops are Mandalorians. I'm dealing with a more... diverse coalition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1183860" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the feeling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183861" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're funny. Didn't think you'd be funny.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess this is what happens when they put loners in charge. Come on--I'll show you the battle plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183864" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're Mandalore now. If you're incapable of winning this battle, I'll handle the attack myself. As for the clans...</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1183864" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can't handle it, leave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough. Mandalore the Avenger isn't stepping down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me show you the battle plan we've got. You want to add anything, now's the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183869" id2="17" version="1065353216">...Torian can stay with you, get you to your droid while we smash the defenses and loot the armories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wish we had more detailed scans, though. In those tight corridors, it could easily end up a slaughter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1183872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here. My people sent intel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183874" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's not a lot of trust between the Mandalorians and the rest of the galaxy. Maybe this will help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1183874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here. As a show of good faith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183875" id2="17" version="1065353216">What?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183876" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of my agents sent factory schematics a short while ago. It should give your troops an edge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183877" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a blasted lot better than nothing. All right, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183878" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no time to gather more data. We need to commit our full force to have a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1183878" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a pity. [Withhold information]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183879" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better be worth it. You're right, though. We've come this far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mandalorians! Prepare for battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ret'urcye mhi, hunter. To the killing grounds with both of us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183884" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may not be one of us. But today, the vanguard is yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1186948" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no vengeance to be found today. No droid is worth an honor-killing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1186950" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we fight because we're promised a shot at the enemy fleet. We fight to claim weapons for our war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1186952" id2="17" version="1065353216">Today we march. We bleed, exhaust ourselves, and die. Because our true destination will be a battle worth winning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1186954" id2="17" version="1065353216">Follow this outsider who fights among us, and seize victory!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
