<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>23</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_14/scene_05_lana.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183813" id2="17" version="1065353216">You shut down the sensors. I'll watch your back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana. What is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183817" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a surprise: schematics for the Darvannis factory, procured by Theron.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183819" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're patchy, but they should help you and the Mandalorians concoct a battle plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183820" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. I should have GEMINI Prime soon. Anything else?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183821" id2="17" version="1065353216">One delicate matter. The Mandalorians make fierce allies, but I have certain concerns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your people have never prioritized pacts and treaties above their love of war. I fear our arrangement can't last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mandalore and I have an understanding. I've earned the clans' respect. My brothers and sisters can help defeat Zakuul.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1183824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry about the clans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183825" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're talking about my family. Be very careful what you say next.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1183825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch your tone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183826" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've always had my respect. But you must think of the galaxy, not just your people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Despite their code of honor, the clans have always had... animalistic tendencies toward violence. I fear our arrangement may not last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183829" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know how you think, Lana. If you want something done, tell me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1183829" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you propose?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Treat the Mandalorians with respect, you'll get respect in return. I've spent enough time with them to see that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1183830" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think they're trustworthy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183831" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't mean to say they'll plot against us. But in the long term?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mandalorians want a challenge more than anything else. They don't like staying on the winning side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1183833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. They're dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183834" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're in agreement, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183836" id2="17" version="1065353216">The clans have opposed both Republic and Empire in the past. Raided planets for sport. Now imagine them free after Zakuul is beaten.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Predators are beautiful, but they mustn't overrun an ecosystem. I trust you'll do what's right to hold our friends in check.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
