<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>44</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/seasons/01/ep_14/scene_09_lana_scorpio_theron.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome home. Sounds like things went okay on Darvannis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184009" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am concerned about the clans rearming. You did think about what I said?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184010" id2="17" version="1065353216">I spoke to Mandalore. She knows turning on us after Zakuul falls isn't wise, and we discussed her options.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184011" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds unusually reasonable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184013" id2="17" version="1065353216">The clans weakened, their leadership destabilized but still favoring an alliance... I couldn't ask for more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184015" id2="17" version="1065353216">The clans are weakened but still favor an alliance. Not a bad outcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184017" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like that Torian kid, by the way. Promised to take him big game hunting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184020" id2="17" version="1065353216">That &quot;kid&quot; is my husband.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184021" id2="17" version="1065353216">And he's also my new hunting buddy. What's your point?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184023" id2="17" version="1065353216">SCORPIO--have you examined GEMINI Prime?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184024" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am studying her mind now. Doing so without obliterating her intelligence is challenging, despite her lack of full sentience.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know where she came from?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not yet. Nor do I have full access to the GEMINI network that controls the Eternal Fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184030" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I have opened a one-way connection. I will soon be able to use the template to locate all GEMINI units.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every ship is piloted by one of those GEMINIs. If you're right, we can track their entire fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1184031" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a huge advantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184037" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we had our own armada, that might be a decisive advantage. We don't. We need to control the Eternal Fleet, not just track it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1184037" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184038" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Prime is the master GEMINI template. With proper modifications she could overwrite the existing protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1184040" id2="17" version="1065353216">We would need direct access to a command console used by the GEMINI captains. Through such a portal, the Prime could infiltrate the entire control network.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1187044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Her chassis is modified from my own base. My designs were stolen. However, my assumption that her code was duplicated was premature.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1187046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any chance you can use the connection to disrupt the operations of the Eternal Fleet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1187046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you sabotage them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195911" id2="17" version="1065353216">So if we board one of the ships and plug the Prime into the captain's chair, we can swipe the entire fleet out from under Arcann's nose?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see how long Arcann keeps his throne if we take away his fancy toys.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1195912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice. Hit him where it hurts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195913" id2="17" version="1065353216">You say that like it's not impossible. Even if we somehow manage to board, the other ships in the fleet will vaporize the compromised vessel well before we acquire control of the bridge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even if we get on board, the other ships in the fleet will blow us from the sky before we have a chance to take control of the bridge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1195915" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not that simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195916" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are still a lot of details to figure out. Like how we board a ship and take control of the bridge before the rest of the fleet disintegrates us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1195916" id2="17" version="1065353216">Risky, but it could work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195917" id2="17" version="1065353216">We may not have to face the entire fleet. Individual ships make transport runs from the Core Worlds all the time. And once SCORPIO can track the GEMINI units...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195919" id2="17" version="1065353216">I already possess that functionality. I completed my analysis of the GEMINI communication templates while you were talking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195926" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you said you'd have the information soon, you weren't kidding. I'm impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1195926" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was fast. Good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any ships scheduled to make a transport run to the Core Worlds in the near future?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1195927" id2="17" version="1065353216">What did you learn?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195928" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the feeling you're not telling me something. Any secrets you'd like to share about your connection to the GEMINI droids?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1195928" id2="17" version="1065353216">That seemed almost too easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing that will impact the current mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195930" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Prime is a lesser version of my original design. Compromising her protocols was not difficult.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195932" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am currently tracking a lone vessel in a nearby sector. It is scheduled to make a stop to recharge its hyperdrive very soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195934" id2="17" version="1065353216">By my calculations, we can intercept it if we hurry. It is unlikely that a similar opportunity will present itself in the foreseeable future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1195936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. It's time to start taking this fight to Arcann.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
