<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>36</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/bronze/imperial/exterminator/imodin_ganalya.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319102" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're equipping the bombers to spray the hives with serum. Deadly to Killik young, entirely non-toxic to humans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319104" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've tested the formula on the Killik eggs. Here are your results.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319105" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh! Wonderful. A few adjustments, and we'll have the serum ready to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Six million larvae, dead in their eggs. It may sound unpleasant, but they'd do much worse to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319109" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to test that serum on the Killik eggs in time for the hatching cycle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319110" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Three Killiks crawling into the nursery... creeping past the royal guard; whatever do they see?&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319112" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Doctor Ganalya, my lord. You must be interested in the Mother's Milk project.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319113" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Doctor Ganalya, Science Bureau. You must be my latest muscle for the Mother's Milk project.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319114" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Doctor Ganalya, Science Bureau. You must be here about the Mother's Milk project.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319115" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Mother's Milk&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319116" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Mother's Milk&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was that a song about Killiks?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Were you just singing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319118" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a local nursery rhyme about the kidnapping of a prince. Gruesome, but in the right spirit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319120" id2="17" version="1065353216">That depends on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Believe me, the results of the project will speak for themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319123" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm developing a serum that neutralizes Killik larvae--toxic membrosia nectar, technically. Pump it into an egg, the babies feed; no more nest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319125" id2="17" version="1065353216">Moff Sarek wants enough serum to spray down the hives before the next hatching cycle. I'd gladly oblige, only my field testers keep disappearing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319126" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happened to them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319127" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happened to them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319128" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spray the hives with poison... that sounds like genocide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319128" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're wiping out the Killiks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319129" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, it's barely population control. Besides, better their children than mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319131" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't my concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319132" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we're going to stop six million larvae from swarming, we need to field test the formula.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319134" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sent an armed squad to try the serum on Killik eggs. The boys took my equipment and never reported back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319136" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not deserving of Sith assistance, but the project is. Would you be willing, my lord?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319137" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're running a small budget surplus. I can hire you to find their remains and finish the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some angry Killik mother probably ate them, but your team is clearly more competent than mine was.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319139" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll finish the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319140" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose it has to be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319141" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. Salvage the equipment from the last team and pick up where they left off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319143" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are their last known coordinates. I'll be here, writing the boys' next of kin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="319145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Despicable. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, we'll just have to keep throwing warm bodies at the Killiks until the tests are done. Or until the hatching cycle is over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="319148" id2="17" version="1065353216">One Killik egg can hold three hundred larvae. Did you know that?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
