<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>17</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/uprisings/space/crimson/transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217072" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got something you might want to look into, Commander. A group of pirates called the Crimson Fang have taken over Port Nowhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess when you were on ice for five years, the station decided you weren't in charge anymore. Might be time to remind them you're still around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure if you know the place. Port Nowhere's a popular smuggler's hideout--an old Hutt dreadnaught that got converted into a space station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217078" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still gathering intel on the Crimson Fang leaders, but word is they've got a major weapons haul stashed in the cargo hold. Keep you updated as more info comes in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice work, Commander. The Crimson Fang is nothing but a memory thanks to you, and Port Nowhere is firmly under Alliance control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217084" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really made the scum on that station pay. Guess they deserved it for turning their backs on you. Remind me to stay on your good side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gonna take a while to clean out all the bodies you left behind. Remind me to stay on your good side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217088" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sends a message to my underworld contacts, though. Makes 'em think twice before double crossing the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217090" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice work, Commander. The Crimson Fang has collapsed, and Port Nowhere has thrown in with the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217092" id2="17" version="1065353216">Must feel good knowing you're the only person in galactic history to take over that station twice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217094" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must have made an impression. The scum on that station normally won't side with anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217096" id2="17" version="1065353216">And with Port Nowhere in our corner, my underworld pals will cut us a deal on future trades. I call that a win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander, just got a message from an old friend... a Twi'lek gunslinger named &quot;Whisper.&quot; He's on Port Nowhere, and he isn't happy about the Crimson Fang taking over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217106" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whisper doesn't say much. The Hutts cut his tongue out when he was a kid. Now he lets his blaster do the talking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217108" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're coming up on his location now. He's in a bit of a jam, but if you help him survive the fight, he'll help you take down the Crimson Fang leader.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217111" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and Whisper will make a good team, Commander. Don't expect him to stick around after the battle, though. He likes to work alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never thought I'd see Whisper lose a fight, but at least he went down blasters blazing. Shame. Would've been nice to have him on our side.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
