<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>16</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/uprisings/space/trial_and_error/barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217366" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll monitor your progress, Commander. Watch your step in there. Doctor Semhess runs a tight ship. Her eyes never leave her work for long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217368" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unauthorized visitors detected. Engaging laboratory security protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to the X7-Cratus. Your timing is perfect. Our troops are just about to start real-world testing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217379" id2="17" version="1065353216">RS-33 turns ordinary soldiers into devastating killing machines. And it turns elite warriors like Marlon Fenn here into, well, you'll see for yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217380" id2="17" version="1065353216">Containment systems damaged. Traces of RAK-5 detected in social quarters. Initiating Vital Personnel Quarantine Safeguards. Please proceed to designated safe zones immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217383" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careless, clumsy fools! You've put this entire facility at risk. There will be consequences!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful, Commander. I'm picking up traces of an unknown airborne chemical in the base. Looks like it could cause extreme mutagenic biological reactions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217402" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our work is too important to let you interfere! Icarr, Nyris, eradicate this contaminant!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217404" id2="17" version="1065353216">Critical overload of Vital Personnel Quarantine Safeguards detected. Airborne RAK-5 levels rising. Initiating purge protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have any idea what you've done? The RAK-5 serum isn't stable! We've all been exposed!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217408" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did this! You turned us into these... monsters!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thrash and gnash! Tear them to pieces!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pierce flesh! Crush! Smash!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217411" id2="17" version="1065353216">Argh!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217412" id2="17" version="1065353216">Noooo!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217414" id2="17" version="1065353216">Purge protocols complete. Airborne RAK-5 levels now stable.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
