<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>13</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/uprisings/space/trial_and_error/transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander--just picked up some critical intel on a small group of rogue Republic scientists led by Doctor Alirra Semhess. They're working on a new adrenal called RS-33.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217324" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice work, Commander. Wasn't looking forward to fighting a galactic war against Doctor Semhess and her army of scientific abominations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217325" id2="17" version="1065353216">And don't worry about anyone else using RS-33, or continuing her experiments. Your assault on the lab destroyed all her research.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217336" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's still in the experimental stages, but rumors suggest it enhances strength and speed at the cost of mental faculties. Makes the users hyper-violent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217338" id2="17" version="1065353216">We tracked Doctor Semhess to a secret lab inside a Republic space station. We need to stop them before they create an army of unstoppable, mindless super soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217340" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if you're wondering about using RS-33 on our own troops, forget it. Your assault on the lab destroyed her research.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217344" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the record, I think that's a good thing. If you ask me, the galaxy already has more than enough unstoppable, hyper-violent monsters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217350" id2="17" version="1065353216">After months of stalled development on RS-33, Doctor Rahser Poth has made a major breakthrough by synthesizing the RAK-5 serum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217352" id2="17" version="1065353216">RAK-5 isolates the rakghoul plague's genetic mutation in a stable form. Exposure to RAK-5 causes major, but temporary, physical transformations in all subjects.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Initial testing indicates we could replicate similar bio-chemical markers in RS-33 while suppressing the undesirable transformative properties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217358" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once RS-33 is perfected, the Republic will command an army of unstoppable super-soldiers. We will reclaim our rightful place as the dominant power in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217360" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given the unorthodox--and unsavory--origins of the serum, there are considerable risks. However, the benefits--increased strength, agility, and aggression--more than compensate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217362" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have reached the final testing stages on the RS-33 adrenal. Volatility has been minimized, and soon we will be able to produce it in mass quantities.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
