<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>26</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/advanced_class/jedi_knight/master_nimi.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220947" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember: A Jedi never stops learning. Even our wisest Masters continue to study and train in the ways of the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220948" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Cassa is waiting for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Orgus speaks highly of you. He says you are the finest Padawan he has ever trained.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220951" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force flows through you. It gives you strength. You have the potential to be a great champion of our order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220953" id2="17" version="1065353216">But first, you must learn to focus your ability. You must choose which path you will walk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220955" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi are defenders of the Republic. In this role, we must accept a harsh truth: To preserve peace, we must often be warriors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some warriors become scourges of evil, living weapons who serve the light. Others become stalwart defenders, guardians who protect and shield others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220958" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you recommend for me, Master Nimi?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="220958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which one is best?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Each style has merit. Sometimes we must strike hard and fast; other times, indomitable resistance serves our needs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Transforming myself into a living weapon sounds like the path for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="220961" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer strength in combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Striking hard and fast is one way to defeat our enemies. Yet sometimes, indomitable resistance has value as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220964" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see myself as a protector of others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="220964" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer to defend others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220965" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indomitable resistance is often an effective strategy. Yet sometimes there is more value in striking hard and fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220969" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is a time for speech. A time for action. Even a time for quiet meditation... like now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220972" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure I follow, Master Nimi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="220972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Path? I don't understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220973" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sense you have great wisdom to share with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="220973" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready to learn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Orgus mentioned your superior martial skills. However, he neglected to mention your admirable hunger for knowledge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220976" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not a Padawan anymore. My training ended on Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="220976" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've chosen my path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="220977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knowledge is not finite. We must learn from birth until we become one with the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="221017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider this decision carefully, for it will forever alter your destiny.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
