<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>42</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/jedi_knight/chapter_3/doomsday/doc.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639725" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who needs to be a Jedi Master? You can be my general anytime, beautiful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tough break not getting promoted to Jedi Master. You need to talk about it, let me know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639727" id2="17" version="1065353216">They promoted you to general, huh? Does that make me a colonel?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who says you can't have it all? You can be a Jedi Master and still have me on the side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639730" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that you're a Jedi Master and all, maybe you can finally give me the time of day. What do you think?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639731" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi Master. Sounds good on you. Me, I prefer one-word titles. Snappier. Easier to remember.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for sending the droid. It was almost like you really cared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639737" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess you figured a droid could do what I couldn't, huh? Sure, I understand....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639739" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand why you didn't come. You like an independent man who can take care of himself. Fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639740" id2="17" version="1065353216">I realize you admire my skill, but next time, don't leave me fighting half the Imperial army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad we can't stay. I was warming up to this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639743" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm calling this party officially over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before you go, let me memorize how gorgeous you look. Okay, got it. Go kick the Emperor's tail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639747" id2="17" version="1065353216">You go save the galaxy. I'll handle the rest of these chumps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teeseven said you were in danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639750" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have I ever mentioned how gorgeous you look while you're rescuing me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639752" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you just had to come check. I'm flattered, sweetheart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639754" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had everything under control. I was luring these Imperials into a trap... somewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639756" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate you taking time out of your busy schedule. I know how all-consuming saving the galaxy can be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639757" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on my way to face the Emperor. Be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="639757" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay safe, Doc.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639758" id2="17" version="1065353216">I always have time for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="639758" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] No problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get ready to clear your schedule, sweetheart. I'm planning a long vacation for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639761" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need something to do when this is all over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="639761" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] You can't die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639762" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's about time you got here. Staging this thing to get your attention was a lot of work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639764" id2="17" version="1065353216">When this is over, drinks at the cantina are on me, Doc.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="639764" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what friends are for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639765" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's good, 'cause I'm broke. This is a great job, but it pays lousy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639767" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you just pretended to barely tolerate me all this time? You're alright.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639769" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get in over your head again. I won't be there to pull you back out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="639769" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're on your own now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639770" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get it--you've got a date with destiny. But after that, you've got a date with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639772" id2="17" version="1065353216">No problem. I can hold my breath a long time. I'll show you sometime.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639774" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, come on--what else could go wrong?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry about me. I'll keep the Imperials running in circles 'til you're done. Tell the Emperor I said goodbye.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639778" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been to some unfriendly towns, but this one takes the prize.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639779" id2="17" version="1065353216">No turning back now. We're in this up to our necks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wish we had time for a private consultation. I'd make sure all your vaccinations are up to date.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639783" id2="17" version="1065353216">We might not come back from this alive. You sure you don't want to surrender to my charms while you still can?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639784" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to survive this. Think of all the free drinks we'll get at the cantina.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
