<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>39</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/jedi_knight/chapter_3/doomsday/kira_carsen.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639830" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is my fault. I shouldn't have let things go so far between us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639831" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you're probably mad about not getting promoted, but look at this as a challenge to improve yourself. You like challenges.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639832" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you don't want to hear this, but Master Satele is right. You need to get serious about being a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639834" id2="17" version="1065353216">You earned this. We'll celebrate in private later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations, Master. Blast... I have to start calling you that again, don't I? I was just getting used to &quot;hey you with the lightsaber.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations, Master. Keep this up, and they'll put you on the Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Poor little Teeseven had no business running to the rescue. That's a Jedi's job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639842" id2="17" version="1065353216">You take your Jedi Code pretty seriously. Would it have killed you to feel a little attachment here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639843" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm gonna guess they cover you in medals for this. Not that a Jedi cares about that sort of thing....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639844" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was close, but we all made it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639847" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was fun. Now go punch the Emperor back to deep space.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for coming for me. I promise you won't need to come back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639850" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teeseven said you were about to be killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639851" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a little melodramatic--but accurate. Thanks for dropping by.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639853" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many times have you saved my neck? I stopped counting when the number got embarrassing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639855" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is exactly why the Council says we shouldn't form attachments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639857" id2="17" version="1065353216">I distracted you from your mission. I hope that doesn't cost you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to see you didn't buy Lord Grouchy's &quot;we're all expendable&quot; speech.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry I dragged you away from your mission. I hope this little detour doesn't hurt you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639861" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor is my problem, Kira. Keeping out of trouble is yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="639861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me worry about that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639862" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't face the Emperor knowing I'd abandoned you here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="639862" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your death would be worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639863" id2="17" version="1065353216">In case I haven't mentioned it lately... you're the best friend I've ever had.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639865" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wasn't sure you cared. Amazing what a little brush with death can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639867" id2="17" version="1065353216">How about a kiss for luck before I go?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="639867" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Make it up to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639870" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wanted to do that on the ship, but everyone was staring. You'd better get moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kira, I'd walk across Tatooine barefoot for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="639872" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] I had to come.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639873" id2="17" version="1065353216">When we get home, I'm filing a formal complaint with the Council about their stupid &quot;no attachments&quot; policy....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639875" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should've thought of that before you got yourself in this mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="639875" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's too late for &quot;sorry.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Point made. Lesson learned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since the direct approach got me nowhere, I'll focus on leading the Imperials away from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639880" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be alright. Go finish this. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639882" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if we pretend we're going to a costume party dressed as Jedi? Think they'd buy it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't take the Empire long to realize we're here. Better move fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="639884" id2="17" version="1065353216">The six of us against a whole planet. I almost feel sorry for them.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
