<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>104</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/yavin_4/dashade/dashade.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too weak... too weak! I am freed only to be delivered greater indignity!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187109" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will suffer it. Take what you want of me but my life. That I cannot give until my purpose is complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187110" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is your name, monster?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187111" id2="17" version="1065353216">As a Shadow Killer, you are honor-bound to serve me, are you not?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187112" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is honor to the dead?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your purpose now is to devour my enemies. You will not go hungry.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187115" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is acceptable. I will need my strength for what is to come.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187118" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can start with an apology for trying to eat me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187119" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sort of creature seeks respect from the vanquished? As you will: I am sorry I could not kill you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187121" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you have to offer me in exchange for your life?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187122" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before the destruction of my homeworld, I was its most feared Shadow Killer.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187124" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was Ak'ghal Usar. Last lord of Urkupp, the lost dominion of Cron, and subjugator of the Kon'me. All that remains is my vengeance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187126" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I am avenged, I will have no other purpose than to serve your whims. Not before.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187127" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you seeking retribution against those who imprisoned you here?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187128" id2="17" version="1065353216">The one who delayed my awakening will suffer, but he is not who brought me to this world.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187130" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your servitude isn't required, but I may take your help. Tell me what happened to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187131" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have time to indulge your personal vendetta.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187132" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have waited centuries for this moment. I will have it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187134" id2="17" version="1065353216">My home world was burned and shattered by the ambition of Exar Kun. Millions of Dashade turned to ash in the wake of an atrocity not even meant for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187142" id2="17" version="1065353216">I followed him here. I came to consume his very being for what he had done. I was too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187143" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Say nothing]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187144" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kun was already dead?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187145" id2="17" version="1065353216">So it seemed.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187147" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such a pointless loss of life. I'm sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187148" id2="17" version="1065353216">I care nothing for pity.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187150" id2="17" version="1065353216">The means to cause such a cataclysm, does it still exist?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187151" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is whatever he used to cause that still out there?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187152" id2="17" version="1065353216">The weapon and its wielder were annihilated by the Dark Lord's design.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187154" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found this moon a smoldering ruin. Months, I scoured for a sign. My worst fears were confirmed by his Massassi worshipers.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187156" id2="17" version="1065353216">The stragglers I found all spoke of the Dark Lord's ascendance into an immortal spirit. Beyond my reach and my wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187157" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why stay then?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187158" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would not be denied so easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187160" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised you got the Massassi to speak to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187161" id2="17" version="1065353216">They had lost the only thing they could fear more than me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187163" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're saying he destroyed this place to become immortal? Sounds familiar.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187168" id2="17" version="1065353216">He sacrificed countless Massassi, but it was the Jedi that burned this world to stop him.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187170" id2="17" version="1065353216">Buried here among the secrets of the ancient Sith, I found the means to restore Exar Kun to life.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187176" id2="17" version="1065353216">The life of this moon was meant to fuel the mechanism, and it had nothing left to give. Until today.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187177" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Temple of Sacrifice was destroyed when someone else tried to use it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187178" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would never let you use the temple even if it were still possible to do so.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187179" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is nothing here worth more than my retribution!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explain yourself!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187186" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've waited a long time for disappointment. That device is in ruin.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187187" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? No! No!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187189" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exar Kun's fetid soul is forever beyond my reach!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187191" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is his fault! The black-eyed Sith! He turned this place into my prison instead of my salvation!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187192" id2="17" version="1065353216">This black-eyed Sith, do you know who he was?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187193" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not know his name. Only his dead eyes and his power.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187195" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you know he's responsible?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187196" id2="17" version="1065353216">He was the first to wake me, so long ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187198" id2="17" version="1065353216">After all this insanity has cost you, you still need someone to blame.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187199" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone must suffer for it!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187201" id2="17" version="1065353216">He took this place as his own and locked me away to protect his precious temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187202" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith Emperor. I know your enemy. I've fought him for a long time now.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187203" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's as dead as anyone strongly connected to the Force can be. His son has conquered much of the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187204" id2="17" version="1065353216">A son. A tyrant. He shall inherit the crimes of his ancestor. Of all Sith who have wronged me!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187206" id2="17" version="1065353216">His body is dead, but he still lingers. You won't be able to exact your punishment against him directly, but I know how to hurt him.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187207" id2="17" version="1065353216">To never taste the anguish of these men leaves me hollow. I crave anything to satiate my rage.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187209" id2="17" version="1065353216">So long as you mean harm to my enemies, I shall serve you willingly.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187211" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show me redemption, little Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187212" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show me redemption, little Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187213" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show me redemption, little whelp.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187217" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ahh, the seal is broken, and this tomb breathes once more. As do I.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187219" id2="17" version="1065353216">How long since I tasted this air?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187221" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, not as I remember. This place has the richness of life, not the acrid tang of devastation.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187237" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are not the jailer who trapped me. Speak your purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187238" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have come to reclaim the treasures of the ancient Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187239" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are no Sith I have seen, but you reek of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187241" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you another servant of Tulak Hord? Or an enemy?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187242" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not answer your questions, creature. You answer mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187243" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wanted to see what was contained here and if it could help me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187244" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did not stumble here. You were guided.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187246" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jailer? You were kept prisoner here?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187247" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think to play tricks on my mind in this weakened state. I am not fooled.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187249" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's none of your business.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187250" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunger gnaws at my patience. You can appease it or my curiosity.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187252" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me: are you a servant of Exar Kun or the black-eyed Sith?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187253" id2="17" version="1065353216">Neither.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187254" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know their fates?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187255" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's your interest in them?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187256" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have had my fill of your talk. My other cravings are of more interest.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exar Kun died long ago, and I don't know any black-eyed Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187259" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I have much to do, and I shall need my strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187261" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't, no.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are these people you're speaking of?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ignorant empty vessel. At least I may find you filling.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187265" id2="17" version="1065353216">My loyalty is to Exar Kun.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187266" id2="17" version="1065353216">I serve the black-eyed Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187267" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you shall whet my appetite for the feast to come.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187269" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have not consumed power such as yours in longer than I can remember. I shall savor it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187271" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will make a meager repast, but ageless hunger will sweeten your demise.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187273" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Attack] I've heard enough of your demands and threats. Time to learn your place.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1187274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wretched morsel! Come and be devoured!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1188148" id2="17" version="1065353216">For all his claims of immortality, his interest in the temple betrays those lies. If it was destroyed, he may be dead, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188149" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may join my Alliance. Keep your word, and you'll find things a lot more comfortable than here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188150" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, you certainly came to accept the order of things more quickly than Khem Val.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1188151" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not insult the legacy of such a Shadow Killer. Khem Val honored Tulak Hord's victory with unwavering loyalty. Few shared his renown.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1188153" id2="17" version="1065353216">My service to you will pale to it in every way, but the dead have no right to complain.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188155" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Reject companion] I don't know that you're the kind of company I want to keep. Enjoy your freedom.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1188156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enjoy? I can never have what I crave, but I will find something to sate the pangs. This I swear.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1188158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not cross me, and I will not cross you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188160" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Reject companion] Waking you was an accident and a mistake. You're too dangerous to leave this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1188161" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am denied so much, but I will not be denied your pain!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
