<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>131</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/trooper/chapter_2/finale/general_garza.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain! Fantastic work--the Imperial Ministry of War is a firestorm over the Gauntlet's destruction. The SIS says that heads will roll over this--quite literally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633664" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Imperials are busy fighting over blame, this is the perfect time for more strikes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633664" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should take advantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633665" id2="17" version="1065353216">A good thought, actually--I'll have the SIS work up a priority listing of targets of opportunity right away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633667" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to know our work paid off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633667" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad we've had an effect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad has accomplished a great deal under your command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I get anything for all of this hard work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633670" id2="17" version="1065353216">How about a reward?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633671" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your leadership and skill in conducting this ongoing operation have been exemplary. I'm promoting you to the rank of major, effective immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commensurate promotions will be issued to your squad members as well. Congratulations--Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633674" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm honored to accept this promotion, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you very much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Serving in Havoc Squad has its benefits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633675" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm moving up in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633676" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've earned it. When presented with extraordinary circumstances, you have delivered extraordinary results.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633678" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm grateful for the promotion, General, but don't my actions deserve more?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633678" id2="17" version="1065353216">No medal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633679" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pushy, Major. But accurate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633681" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm also recommending you for the Silver Crescent, in honor of the extraordinary valor you demonstrated in the attack on the Gauntlet superweapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633683" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aric Jorgan and Elara Dorne will each be recommended for a Mark of Dedication, for the injuries they sustained and their heroism in ensuring each other's survival. Do you approve?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dorne nearly got herself killed treating Jorgan's wounds, and Jorgan risked his life to get her out of there. They deserve higher commendations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633684" id2="17" version="1065353216">They should get more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. With your recommendation on top of mine, we'll try for two Medals of Valor instead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633687" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jorgan and Dorne did their jobs. If you want to give them medals for it, fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633687" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't really care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633688" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're just as deserving as you are, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633690" id2="17" version="1065353216">In recognition of injuries sustained in the line of duty, I've recommended Aric Jorgan for the Mark of Dedication. Assuming you approve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jorgan was just doing his job. If that gets him a medal, fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633691" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't really care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633692" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jorgan's work more than qualifies for commendation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633694" id2="17" version="1065353216">In recognition of the injuries she suffered in the action against the enemy, I've recommended Elara Dorne for the Mark of Dedication. That is, if you approve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633695" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't think of anyone more deserving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633695" id2="17" version="1065353216">I approve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633696" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. I'll submit the necessary forms right away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633698" id2="17" version="1065353216">M1-4X risked himself to save the life of a squad-mate. Doesn't he deserve something for that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633698" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about Forex?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633699" id2="17" version="1065353216">Droids serving in the Republic military are classified as equipment, not personnel. There is no precedent for granting a droid any sort of commendation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633701" id2="17" version="1065353216">But, if you feel strongly on the matter, I can see about having his contributions recognized appropriately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Elara did her duty as a member of Havoc Squad. If you want to give her a medal for it, fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633703" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't really care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dorne's actions are more than worthy of recognition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now--I'm afraid that not all of our news is positive. We received the following holotransmission not long after the Gauntlet was destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633708" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic Command. I am General Rakton of the Imperial Ministry of War.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633710" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have made a grave error. By destroying the Gauntlet, you have destroyed a weapon of peace--and the final hope your people had.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633711" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me everything we've got on this man, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633711" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need intel on Rakton.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633712" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have a dossier sent immediately. In short, Rakton is the Empire's top commander--the mastermind behind their military campaigns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633714" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must have really hit a nerve with this guy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633714" id2="17" version="1065353216">He sounds very upset.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633715" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is serious, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633717" id2="17" version="1065353216">A &quot;weapon of peace&quot;? That's ridiculous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633717" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a joke, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633718" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is only the beginning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633720" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had hoped a device that removed the possibility of resistance would allow the Empire to achieve its great works without further bloodshed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633722" id2="17" version="1065353216">But your actions have destroyed any hope for peace. I am forced to launch a campaign unlike any the galaxy has seen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633724" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your soldiers will be slaughtered. Your planets will burn. And your people will embrace the light of the Emperor's will at last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633727" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not scared of Rakton or any other Imperial scum. Havoc can handle him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let him come.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't underestimate this man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633730" id2="17" version="1065353216">For years, General Rakton has outmaneuvered and outwitted every Republic force that has stood in his way--including mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633732" id2="17" version="1065353216">The SIS is watching for any sign of Rakton's new campaign. Until we have solid data, Havoc Squad is relieved. Rest, recuperate and be ready for my call. Dismissed, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can Rakton back up these claims?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633738" id2="17" version="1065353216">How serious is this threat?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633739" id2="17" version="1065353216">He can, and I have little doubt that he will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633741" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Empire is about to begin a full-scale campaign against us, our forces need to be ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633741" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd better prepare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633742" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're putting all outposts and units on alert immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, come in. You may stand at ease.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633746" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand you've succeeded in bringing Havoc Squad up to full strength, Captain. Congratulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633747" id2="17" version="1065353216">My squad and I are very proud to be a part of this operation, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633748" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I speak for everyone when I say that we're glad to have Havoc involved. General Garza, why don't you begin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633750" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad can take down whatever the Empire throws at us, Commander, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633750" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're ready for anything now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633751" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what we were hoping for. General Garza? Care to begin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633753" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're here to destroy the Gauntlet, not to make small talk, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Skip the chitchat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633754" id2="17" version="1065353216">So we are. General Garza, why don't you get us started?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Certainly. As you know, Captain, the Gauntlet superweapon allows the Empire to target and destroy any ship traveling through hyperspace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633758" id2="17" version="1065353216">This capability, if put to use, would give the Empire an insurmountable advantage. It also makes an attack on the Gauntlet itself extremely difficult.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633760" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fortunately, the technical data you helped retrieve allowed us to determine a safe approach pattern that will get our forces within striking range.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you explain this approach pattern, sir?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633761" id2="17" version="1065353216">How will it work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633762" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to know the attack won't end before it begins.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633762" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's great news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633763" id2="17" version="1065353216">The plan is not without its dangers. Commander Rans can explain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633765" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Gauntlet gets a bead on us, this will be the shortest offensive in history.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633765" id2="17" version="1065353216">This approach better be good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633766" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've run the numbers from the Imperials' readouts and determined the Gauntlet's minimum time to acquire and lock onto a target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your ship, and those of my battle group, will approach the Gauntlet by making numerous short hyperjumps, always remaining below the minimum lock-on time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633770" id2="17" version="1065353216">Short, repeated hyperjumps are very inefficient--once we're in, our warships won't have enough fuel to return. Total victory will be our only option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633771" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is my squad's objective once we're in the target area?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633771" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the battle plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Failure has never been an option, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633772" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would never accept less.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quite right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633775" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happens if the Imperials have increased their defenses, or if the Gauntlet can acquire targets faster than you think?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your plan sounds risky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633776" id2="17" version="1065353216">We adapt and succeed. That is our only choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633778" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the attack begins, Lieutenant Coria's Safecrackers will immediately disable the planetary shield generator that protects the Gauntlet, allowing Havoc Squad to board it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633780" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you're aboard, begin the demolition operation. Sergeant Yuun will help you bypass the security seals on the weapon's inner core.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Specialist Vik will then go into the core with you and plant explosives at key weak points, ensuring the Gauntlet's total destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633783" id2="17" version="1065353216">How should I deploy my other squad members?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633783" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the rest of Havoc?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633784" id2="17" version="1065353216">First I work with Yuun, then with Vik. Got it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds straightforward to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you issuing all orders, or will I actually command my squad?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I get to have any input?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Certain portions of the plan must proceed as we order them. Other details have been left to your judgment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633788" id2="17" version="1065353216">During your demolition operations, two Havoc Squad members of your choice will assault the Gauntlet's bridge and download all data from the weapon's computers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633790" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unassigned squad members will provide mobile backup to the rest of the team as needed. As soon as your objectives are complete, evacuate the Gauntlet immediately. Understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633791" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll assign the bridge assault team before the attack begins.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Affirmative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633792" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need a review.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633793" id2="17" version="1065353216">After boarding the Gauntlet, Sergeant Yuun will help you gain access to the inner core, then you and Specialist Vik will plant explosives within.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meanwhile, two Havoc Squad members will assault the bridge, with the remaining squad members providing mobile support as necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633797" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to get this op started!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633797" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get going!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well. The briefing is complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633800" id2="17" version="1065353216">We cannot overemphasize the importance of this mission, Captain. The future security of the Galactic Republic hinges on the destruction of this single weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633802" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and your team are no strangers to situations like this. You've faced incredible odds before, and overcome them with skill and determination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633804" id2="17" version="1065353216">If anyone can lead the charge in this battle and see us through to victory, it's Havoc Squad. Your Republic is counting on you--move out!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's do this!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's go ruin the Emperor's day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time for some fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633807" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll blast that piece of junk before the Imps can blink.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Start organizing the parade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="755172" id2="17" version="1065353216">I approve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="758624" id2="17" version="1065353216">I approve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="758626" id2="17" version="1065353216">I approve.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
