<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>9</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x2/daily/corellia/republic/corellia_rising/bounty_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036009" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE OPERATIONAL UPDATE / SIS ADDENDUM

Monitoring devices: deployed and active. Republic forces already act on this intel to strike at Councillor Torvix's forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036010" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE OPERATIONAL UPDATE / SIS ADDENDUM

Dispatch from the Strategic Information Service is as follows:

SIS agents were dispatched in the Black Hole to deploy monitoring devices and gather intel on Councillor Torvix and his underworld forces. No agents have returned.

The SIS has cleared select individuals to resume this vital mission. Plant any monitoring devices behind enemy lines, and the Republic can effectively break Councilor Torvix's defenses. A stealthy infiltration is recommended.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036011" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE OPERATIONAL UPDATE

Prototype weapons received. All armaments accounted for.

The Republic thanks you. Our forces will soon wield new armaments in our fight for the Black Hole.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036012" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE OPERATIONAL UPDATE

Councillor Torvix's criminal agents have acquired dangerous new armaments.

Supreme Chancellor Saresh recently committed heavy Republic firepower to our fight. Prototype weaponry meant for Republic soldiers arrived on-site only to be stolen by Torvix's army of criminals.

Recovery of this prototype weaponry is the Republic's top priority. Claim the weapons from our enemy, before we lose our only advantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036013" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE OPERATIONAL UPDATE

The Drall refugees are grateful for their freedom. Their expertise will aid the Republic's overthrow of Councillor Torvix.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036014" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE OPERATIONAL UPDATE

The Republic has received a distress call from within the Black Hole.

Drall engineers are trapped in the hypermatter refineries. Councillor Torvix is holding them in cages and forcing the Drall to operate his factories. Such abuses will not stand with the Republic.

Supreme Chancellor Saresh calls for an emergency rescue operation. Free the Drall, and signal the liberation of the Black Hole!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036015" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE OPERATIONAL UPDATE

Radiation levels have returned to acceptable range. The Black Hole is safe once more.

Supreme Chancellor Saresh sends thanks for your selfless victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036016" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE OPERATIONAL UPDATE

Criminals working for Councillor Torvix have begun a campaign of sabotage to slow our progress in the Black Hole.

Torvix's agents have damaged radiation control stations at key locations, causing the hypermatter refineries to poison our forces. Already, dozens of lives have been lost to radiation sickness.

Hazard pay is available for neutralizing the saboteurs and repairing our radiation control stations. Recommend seizing anti-radiation serums from the enemy to prevent nausea and internal bleeding.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1045511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Republic by completing the following daily missions in the Black Hole district of Corellia:

[HEROIC] Chasing Shadows
[AREA] Criminal Crackdown
[DAILY] Counter Eco-Terrorism
[DAILY] Eyes and Ears
[DAILY] Forced Labor
[DAILY] Stolen Victory</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
