<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>32</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x2/daily/corellia/republic/corellia_rising/sal_dakron.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia is worth fighting for. I just wish the Empire and Councillor Torvix didn't feel the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005531" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not soldiers, Dakron. CorSec can't handle heavy artillery or stealthed attacks. We need more backup from the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every man I have is either out in the field or in the infirmary. Who knows what'll sink us first--Torvix, the Empire or the radiation poisoning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005535" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll tell you what'll sink us: all the excuses. Look at us! Losing to some ex-politician and his band of Corona scum--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005537" id2="17" version="1065353216">What now? Have we lost another sector? Run out of supplies? Looking for your pet gizka?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005538" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're looking for Sal Dakron. Agent Carhart sent us to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005539" id2="17" version="1065353216">A whole squad, huh? Looks like he understands the situation, at least.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005541" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm looking for Sal Dakron. Agent Carhart sent me to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, let's hope you're tough. We've lost too many Green Jedi already.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005544" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're in luck, Dakron. Havoc Squad's worth a thousand of my men.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005546" id2="17" version="1065353216">A privateer. Wonderful. At least you're working for us and not Torvix.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to the Black Hole. We're low on power cells, rations and just about everything else. I needed reinforcements yesterday, but better late than never.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005549" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not leaving until the Black Hole belongs to the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005549" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm here to win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not leaving alive, anyway. But I'm glad to hear it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005552" id2="17" version="1065353216">As long as we remain focused on our goal, we cannot fail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005552" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just stay positive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right. Focus. I'll try to work on that, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005555" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess that takes care of the status report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005555" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's bad, I get it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's just say you're a sight for sore eyes, Major. And sore bodies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005558" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're going to pop a blood vessel if you keep this up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005558" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm down, buddy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005559" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're probably right. I feel ten years older already.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005561" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're in command. Just tell me where I'm needed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005561" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where do I start?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005562" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're needed everywhere. Between Torvix at our front and the Empire at our backs, we've got our hands full just holding the area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show a little respect, or your reinforcements are leaving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005564" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005565" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry. I'm glad you've come. Really. We need the help now more than ever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005567" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take a look around, see who's calling for volunteers. Blast anyone who's not CorSec or Republic, and avoid the radiation. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005569" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do I look like, a tour guide? Get in the field or get out of my way.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
