<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>24</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/ilum/bronze/republic/darkness_on_ilum/master_moran.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you again. I can't wait for this war to end.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179080" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no doubt of that. I'm sorry to hear that the Sith would not surrender. But in war, we all do what we must.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, once more, for your invaluable service.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179084" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck smoking out those Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Friend. We long for peace, but the Sith press us to war once more.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179089" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major. It's good to have you and Havoc Squad here on Ilum.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179091" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain. You are a credit to free-traders everywhere. The Republic needs more enterprising citizens in its ranks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179093" id2="17" version="1065353216">Friend, citizen of the Republic. The dark side looms heavily over Ilum.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179095" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire has struck at our non-human forces because they hate and fear the Republic's diversity. They know it is our strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179097" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Lords of the Sith murdered our Kaleesh, Rodian and Talz commandos, and took over their forward camp. They showed no mercy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179099" id2="17" version="1065353216">They leave us no choice. I need volunteers to smoke the Sith Lords out of the buildings and if they do not surrender, take them down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179100" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will do my duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179101" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds simple enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179102" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would not celebrate the deaths of so many, even if they are our enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179104" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm honored to have your help. Smoke the Sith Lords out and prepare for the worst.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179106" id2="17" version="1065353216">There must be a better way.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179107" id2="17" version="1065353216">I, too, would rather find a more peaceful solution, but the Sith have shown us on Coruscant, on Taris, on Corellia, that they only know violence.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179109" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith Lords must be stopped before they overrun another camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179110" id2="17" version="1065353216">In that case, I'll help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179111" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179112" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope Ilum is the last of this disgusting conflict.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="179114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not interested. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179115" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please reconsider. The Sith strike with abandon because they do not think we'll strike back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="179117" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry. I'm too busy to talk right now.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
