<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>42</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/bronze/ravaged_reconstruction/veldo_balesh.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119502" id2="17" version="1065353216">Taris deserves at least one beautiful thing. That base will be it, if we get the workers.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Y--you're back. That must mean--the Mandalorians must be gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119504" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can restart work on the construction site whenever you like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, the base is safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119505" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not without a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119506" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew those Mandalorian scum wouldn't trouble someone like you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119508" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that base is so precious, the site should have guards. I don't want to be troubled with this again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Next time, get some security.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are you yelling at me? I wasn't the foreman. But, you make a good point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119511" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I'd like compensation.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119512" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? Oh, yes, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here. I know this isn't much in return. But I'll make sure that new base has something in it named after you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember: Use the power cells to get the elevator running. That'll get you to the upper levels, where the Mandalorians and their droids are.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, Master Jedi, do something! They killed everyone, I'm the only one left!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119521" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a soldier, aren't you? You have to do something! They killed everyone, I'm the only one left!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please! You've got to help me! They killed everyone, I'm the only one left!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119525" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were working on the Reconstruction Authority's new base. It'll be so beautiful....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119527" id2="17" version="1065353216">But, yesterday, they came from nowhere. Mandalorian mercenaries! Those murderers slaughtered everyone; someone's hired them to destroy the construction site!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Preying on unarmed workers is low, even for mercenaries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Despicable.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119529" id2="17" version="1065353216">We had tools; we tried to fight back. Didn't do any good. Those Mandalorians know their business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mandalorian or not, mercenaries are ruthless. How did you get away from them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119531" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you escaped.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119532" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... I played dead. I had to listen while they killed my friends, planned to destroy everything we'd made!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119534" id2="17" version="1065353216">So someone gave them orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Probably some Imperial. The Reconstruction Authority's &quot;investigating,&quot; but what good will that do? The site's in danger right now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hiring Mandalorians to destroy a building is like using a blaster to clean your fingernails.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119537" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's overkill.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone wants the new base gone, probably some Imperial, and I can see why.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119541" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's true! They brought demolition droids--why else would Mandalorians care about a building?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119543" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's only a construction site.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119544" id2="17" version="1065353216">That new base symbolizes the reconstruction effort. Reclaiming Taris, making something worthwhile from this chaos.... It has to be saved!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119546" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Mandalorians and their demolition droids are on the upper levels right now, planting bombs and cutting into the superstructure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119547" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119549" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have to deactivate the Mandalorian bombs to save the building. Our ion dischargers can do that--and you can find them by the generator, if you hurry!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119551" id2="17" version="1065353216">We kept ion dischargers by the generator, in case there was an overload... you could use one to deactivate the Mandalorians' bombs and save the building! Please!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show that Mando scum that the Republic doesn't give up without a fight!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119555" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, no. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119556" id2="17" version="1065353216">But with that base destroyed--forget it. You obviously don't care about Taris, or her future!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119558" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're killers, all of them!</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="944358" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ion what?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
