<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>45</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/multi/chancellor_saresh_holo.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046498" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a great honor to speak with the warrior who struck down the Emperor. The Republic needs your strong arm once again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi are strongest when defending others, Madame Chancellor, but I'll help however I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046499" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer peace to war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046500" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sadly, protecting the innocent often means striking down the guilty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046502" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's about time you contacted me. With the Emperor out of the way, the Sith are primed for a fall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046502" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ready to destroy the Sith?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046503" id2="17" version="1065353216">I regret our greatest foe must wait while we deal with a new enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046505" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm honored to speak with you again, Master Jedi. Your victory over the Sith infiltrators saved the Republic, but we face new threats to our security.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046506" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eliminating one foe often exposes the presence of others, Chancellor. Lasting peace of mind is difficult to obtain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046506" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am always ready to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be that as it may, lasting peace and security are my goals. We must remain vigilant and primed to strike.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046509" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am not your personal stalking hound, Madame Chancellor. I pursue my own path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not presume to use me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046510" id2="17" version="1065353216">We both desire peace and security to pursue our agendas. A foe has risen who must be defeated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046512" id2="17" version="1065353216">I apologize for contacting you outside normal channels, Major, but I need Havoc Squad immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046513" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're prepared to handle anything you need, Madame Chancellor. It'll be good to get back in the fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046513" id2="17" version="1065353216">My team stands ready to serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046514" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the spirit we'll need to triumph over our foes--and it appears we have a new one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046516" id2="17" version="1065353216">With all due respect, Chancellor, you don't have military authority. I won't jump when you bark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046516" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't take orders from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046517" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Garza has authorized this call. To be clear, I'm not requesting a favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, congratulations again on your defeat of the Voidwolf. I require a moment of your time to discuss matters of galactic security.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046520" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this is about missing valuables or some kind of illegal enterprise operating in Republic space, I have no idea why you're calling me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046520" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't do it, I swear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your knowledge of shadow economies is the asset I seek. I require expert help with a particular breed of criminal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046523" id2="17" version="1065353216">It isn't every day the leader of the free galaxy calls. How can I help you, Madame Chancellor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046523" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a rare honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't matter if I'm talking or blasting--I charge a flat fee. Can you afford it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046524" id2="17" version="1065353216">My time costs credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046525" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm prepared to negotiate for your special expertise. We're facing a foe I believe you can provide special insight into.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046527" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutt Cartel has invaded Republic space and seized the planet Makeb. We will respond to this unprovoked act of aggression in full force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046529" id2="17" version="1065353216">My war council will be convening on Keylander Station in the Makeb system. I ask that you join us immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046530" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're in luck. I just landed at the station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046530" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm already at Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046531" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people will be arriving at the conference chamber shortly. We'll meet you there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046532" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll set a course for the Makeb system right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046532" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on my way to Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know why the Hutts have invaded Makeb?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you tell me anything more?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Supreme Commander Jace Malcom and Jedi Grand Master Satele Shan are gathering intelligence on the situation. I promise a full briefing as soon as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046536" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's there to discuss? The Hutts have crossed the line. We'll make them pay for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1046536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's just smash the Hutts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046537" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid the situation's more complex than either of us would like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Proceed to the conference chamber on Keylander Station. I'll meet you there. Please hurry--we must act quickly and decisively against the Hutts' aggression.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1046734" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please stand by for a priority communication from Supreme Chancellor Leontyne Saresh of the Galactic Republic.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
