<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>173</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/multi/zan_3l0.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021812" id2="17" version="1065353216">It has been my honor to serve you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most cordial greetings. I am Zan Threelow, Republic protocol officer. Welcome to Makeb and Keylander Station.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please hold all questions. Supreme Chancellor Saresh and her delegation are arriving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assembled friends... the Republic owes its continued survival to this brave Jedi. Entire worlds would be smoldering ruins if not for this hero's courage and sacrifice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021822" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was in the right places at the right times. Anyone in this room would have done the same, given the chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021822" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no one special.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps, but would they have succeeded? You carry burdens that would break others--and we have need of that strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021825" id2="17" version="1065353216">My friends, this wise Jedi Master has protected the Republic from dangers without and within time and again. I can think of no greater guardian of our security.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Protecting the Republic takes more than a lone Jedi. It requires the vigilance and strength of everyone safekeeping our society.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021826" id2="17" version="1065353216">I share that duty with all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Astute words--and especially fitting here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone... this brave soldier assumed command of Havoc Squad in its darkest hour and led it to many victories. I regret that such heroism must remain classified.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad doesn't ask for fame, Madame Chancellor. It's enough for us to know the Republic is safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021830" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're just humble soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021833" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want the galaxy to know you're a hero. People need them--especially now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021835" id2="17" version="1065353216">I ask everyone here with me to honor this brave captain, who thwarted an attack on the Republic by no less than an Imperial Grand Admiral.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021836" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you were throwing me a surprise party. Not that I'll turn down another job... but I wouldn't mind a little blowout bash once in a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021836" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expected a parade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me for placing business ahead of pleasure. Hazard of the office.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for coming. I'm a great admirer of your victories in service to the Republic. Whenever I require someone who will not fail us, you always come to mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1021840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always a pleasure, Chancellor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021841" id2="17" version="1065353216">The honor is ours--and rest assured, I would not call you here without good reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021843" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's always a privilege to stand before the Republic's greatest heroes. Time and again, you have not only saved us from the enemy but brought us closer to ultimate triumph.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I may have deprived the Empire of its leader, but I won't rest until the worlds the Sith have taken are free once more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've only begun to fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021845" id2="17" version="1065353216">Liberation is precisely what brings us here today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021847" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor's Children may be gone, but if I've learned anything about Sith, there are more hidden threats awaiting us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021847" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our foe isn't easily beaten.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unwelcome surprises are exactly what bring us here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021850" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still getting used to people calling me &quot;Major.&quot; Wasn't that long ago I was a lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021850" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explains all these promotions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to your defeat of General Rakton and impressive victories on Corellia, military recruitment has surged. We'll need those soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not to brag, but I took down an Imperial Grand Admiral and his flagship. You wouldn't believe how much ammo that took.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021853" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's putting it lightly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021854" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should consider enlisting in the Republic military, Captain. The ammunition there is free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021856" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt all these people came just to hear you flatter me, Chancellor. The situation on Makeb must be bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021856" id2="17" version="1065353216">I take it things are serious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021857" id2="17" version="1065353216">The crisis we face is unexpected and severe. I require my best advisors--and most able problem-solvers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021859" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know better than to sweet-talk me, Chancellor. There's trouble--what do you need me to do about it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Flattery doesn't interest me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021860" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to see success and fame haven't changed you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victory over the Empire lies within our grasp. But first, we must face a cowardly act of unwarranted aggression. Supreme Commander Malcolm?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thirteen days ago, the Hutt Cartel violated Republic space and seized the planet Makeb. They've blockaded the system with thirty Ajuur-class heavy cruisers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb's citizens have formally pledged to join the Republic if we respond to their crisis. We will not abandon them to the Hutts' brutality.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021881" id2="17" version="1065353216">The planet must have something of value if the Hutts are risking outright war for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hutts only attack for profit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021882" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care what motivates them. I want their blight removed from our space.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021884" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galaxy has suffered upheaval, but the Hutts haven't been interested in galactic conquest for fifteen thousand years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021884" id2="17" version="1065353216">A strange attack by the Hutts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021885" id2="17" version="1065353216">This war has created opportunities for the greedy and unscrupulous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021887" id2="17" version="1065353216">Invading a planet is way beyond casinos and spice smuggling. The slugs have upped their game.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021887" id2="17" version="1065353216">A bold move by the Hutts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021888" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts haven't organized a military operation of this scale for millennia--and I want it to stay that way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021890" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate to suggest my way out of a job, but everyone has a price. Make the Cartel a generous offer, and they'll go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Buy off the Hutts. They'll go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021891" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't negotiate with despots who take planets hostage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021893" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we're willing to fight the Hutt Cartel for control of a planet that's been neutral up until now, we must have good reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb must be quite a world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb is a paradise. Quality of living standards significantly above the galactic average. Thriving mining and tourism industries. A world worth saving--and having.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021896" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Hutts want trouble, they just bought more than they can handle. I'll stomp those slugs into jelly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's crush the Cartel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our response to this attack must be unequivocal. I will not see us defeat the Empire only to war with a parade of aggressors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021899" id2="17" version="1065353216">Severe atmospheric conditions on Makeb make large-scale troop landings impossible. We need help from local resistance forces to pull this off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021901" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of Makeb's business leaders, Shalim Avesta, is awaiting you on the surface. I want you working closely with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021902" id2="17" version="1065353216">We couldn't have freed Balmorra or Corellia without help from the locals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Native support is invaluable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shalim is a patriot who led his people to embrace the Republic. We mustn't desert him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021905" id2="17" version="1065353216">If he's bold enough to stand up to the Hutts, he'll be worth listening to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021905" id2="17" version="1065353216">I look forward to our meeting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shalim would sooner accept a live grenade than Hutt rule.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we count on all the locals for backup, or is Shalim the exception?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021908" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope he's not all we've got.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021909" id2="17" version="1065353216">The citizens are ill-equipped for armed assistance. They'll mostly provide enemy intelligence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021911" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want this done right, let me handle it my way. I'll only take this job if I don't have to salute anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021911" id2="17" version="1065353216">I work best alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021912" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one's asking you to compromise your ideals, Captain. Shalim is a resource--use him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021914" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised the planet's army didn't put up a fight. Or did the Hutts defeat them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't Makeb have a military?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb's entire military strength came from hired mercenaries. The Hutts simply bought them off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021917" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Shalim sounds like he belongs in a boardroom, not on a battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021917" id2="17" version="1065353216">Businessmen are useless to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021918" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll need local expertise for this mission. Shalim and his forces can provide that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021920" id2="17" version="1065353216">Liberating Makeb is your top priority--but I want the Hutts' ambitions ended permanently. Grand Master Satele Shan has insight regarding our enemy's future plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021922" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi Council has meditated on the Cartel's actions. We believe that Makeb is a staging point for a larger attack on the entire galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021924" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts will not be allowed to expand their dominion at our expense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021925" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's always an honor to face down the enemies of the Republic, Madame Chancellor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021925" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be proud to stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021926" id2="17" version="1065353216">When our enemy realizes who they're facing, I predict a hasty retreat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021928" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Republic cuts a deal with the Cartel, we could team up and take down the Empire together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could Hutts be good allies?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021929" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there's to be any negotiation, I intend for it to be entirely one-sided.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021931" id2="17" version="1065353216">No planet deserves Hutt rule. I'll see the galaxy safe from their kind if I have to kick every last one straight into the Void myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1021931" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're a plague. I'm a cure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021932" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll settle for a crippling strike that reminds them of their place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021934" id2="17" version="1065353216">A shuttle will transport you to Shalim Avesta's encampment on the surface. Go now, and show the galaxy the Republic is not to be trifled with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1021940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings. I am Zan Threelow, Republic protocol officer of Keylander Station. I am currently unable to assist you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022016" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Supreme Chancellor requested a meeting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back! I was informed that you survived a terrifying ordeal. You have my deepest admiration. Ah, here they are....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022019" id2="17" version="1065353216">We had no idea the planet was that unstable. Our offer was made in good faith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022021" id2="17" version="1065353216">Millions of hungry mouths to feed and nothing to show for it. You pledged Makeb to us, Shalim--and you knew it was doomed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022023" id2="17" version="1065353216">You knew the groundquakes were getting worse. You used the Republic, knowing we'd be obligated to help your people even if you had nothing to offer in return.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022024" id2="17" version="1065353216">They didn't know Makeb was doomed--only that the groundquakes were increasing after the Hutts took over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1022024" id2="17" version="1065353216">It wasn't that simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022026" id2="17" version="1065353216">They didn't voice all of their suspicions, but they were trying to save lives. Would we have acted any different?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022027" id2="17" version="1065353216">That hardly matters now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022029" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's done is done. We have a vessel filled with millions of refugees who need food, water and medical treatment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1022029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regardless, people need help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022030" id2="17" version="1065353216">And a home. My people can't live on that ark forever. They're packed in like cargo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022032" id2="17" version="1065353216">We got those people off Makeb. What happens next is their problem, not ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1022032" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have no obligation to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022033" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't just abandon us. Planet or not, we're Republic citizens now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022035" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a debacle. We came here seeking resources to defeat the Sith Empire. Instead, we're walking away with debts and obligations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022037" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the Hutt leaders? You negotiated a peace agreement with them, didn't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022038" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's right. The Cartel leaders have promised to support the Republic wholeheartedly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1022038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, we've made them allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022039" id2="17" version="1065353216">So we have a worthless ally and a broken one. Still... the Hutts possess considerable wealth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hutt promises aren't worth the time it takes to hear them lie. They're all scum--we can never trust them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1022041" id2="17" version="1065353216">That deal is mostly worthless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022042" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no intention of trusting them--but I'll exploit their fear of you for all it's worth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022044" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I recall, you wanted to abandon the Cartel leaders on Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1022044" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were against that deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022045" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cooler heads prevailed. My point is, the Republic did benefit from rescuing us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only the Cartel leaders who needed rescuing agreed to this alliance. Fortunately, they possess most of the wealth and power. They'll neutralize any holdouts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1022048" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts can provide aid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022050" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can hold their warships in reserve and use them to protect vulnerable systems. Meanwhile, the Hutts will build a colony for Makeb's people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022051" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had to twist your arm to call the Republic. Glad you finally swallowed that &quot;spirit of independence&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022053" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to speak with my operative in private. Please excuse us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022054" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time for the Republic to wipe the Empire from the galaxy. Everyone who has chosen our side will play a role.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1022054" id2="17" version="1065353216">Draft them all for the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022056" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutt Cartel will place its warships under our command, and the people of Makeb will find new homes in our armies and factories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022057" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never thought.... How can you treat us like this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022059" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's better than the alternative--and you should be more appreciative. Dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022061" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've made the best of an unfortunate situation. Well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022063" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts want to be on the winning side of this war, and you've shown them who that is. We have you alone to thank for this alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022064" id2="17" version="1065353216">All Jedi are taught that our power should be used to bring people together for peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1022064" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was about helping others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022065" id2="17" version="1065353216">A great many have seen your example and responded--and I need that beacon in the darkness more than ever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope what we achieved here will ripple across the galaxy and rally more forces to our cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1022067" id2="17" version="1065353216">We made a powerful example.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022068" id2="17" version="1065353216">This victory has already been noted by several independent factions. Our diplomats will be quite busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad isn't one man or woman. I'm always part of a team--and we're with you all the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1022070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not just me--my team, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022071" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish I could offer you some much-deserved rest, Major--but the war has other plans for us both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022073" id2="17" version="1065353216">People are naturally drawn to me. I think it's because I exude confidence and power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1022073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always bet on a winner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022074" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one could ever doubt your audacity, Captain--which is why I must continue to request your services.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022076" id2="17" version="1065353216">We still have plenty of fighting to do. The Empire isn't falling anytime soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1022076" id2="17" version="1065353216">The war isn't over yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed--which brings me to my next point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022079" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's wise of you to recognize my importance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1022079" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm your greatest asset.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022080" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic wouldn't be nearly as close to victory if not for you--a fact I intend to rely upon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1022082" id2="17" version="1065353216">For too long, the Republic has wasted time reacting to the enemy. We must fight this war to win by going on the offensive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1029386" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts destroyed Makeb. It seems only fair they should pay the cost of caring for its refugees.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1029388" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic needs to establish a haven for war victims. I can't think of anyone more deserving than the people of Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1029390" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts have plenty of credits to fund the construction of new homes--and we can use their fleet to protect them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050201" id2="17" version="1065353216">My uncle is a businessman, Chancellor--but in this case he's telling the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050210" id2="17" version="1065353216">With our new friends' wealth and warships, we've gained a substantial advantage over the Empire. That doesn't address the problem of Makeb's people, however. I need a solution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050374" id2="17" version="1065353216">After everything we've been through, to receive such generosity... thank you all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050375" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people of Makeb need someone guiding them to their new home. I think you're the right person for that job, Shalim.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1050375" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be a good leader.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050376" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm... not. But you've shown me what a true leader looks like. I'll follow that example.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1050381" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] This was for Lemda.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050382" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. You win. Here's my holofrequency--call it often.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050384" id2="17" version="1065353216">You got your people through this mess--but I don't think you're the leader Makeb needs anymore. It's better if businessmen like you retire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1050384" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time you stepped down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050385" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't step down. My people need leadership.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050387" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic government will see to Makeb's citizens. If we require your services, we'll contact you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050389" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish to speak with my agents privately. Excuse us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050390" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said the Republic would help us--not make us indentured servants!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1050393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Savor this victory. Return to the war's front lines and press our advantage. Together, we will be triumphant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1051679" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did it for a snappish woman who deserves a new home. I'll miss you, Lemda.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1051680" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make sure the Hutts build you a nice place, Lemda. You deserve the best.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
