<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>50</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/world/a_cure_for_a_planet/cb_08_4.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623485" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are alive, and our business is concluded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, I see your infection is progressing. Hold still, I will take samples for analysis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623488" id2="17" version="1065353216">While I transmit the data to Doctor Cel, there are some questions I should ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have any of the following symptoms: dizziness, fever, shortness of breath or an inexhaustible hunger for sentient flesh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you do anything about these cuts? I'm losing blood, here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623491" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, but I got clawed up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623492" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, my core function is in analysis, not trauma care. Ah, here's Doctor Cel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623493" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could go for a nerf-burger. That doesn't count, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that you mention it....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623494" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will note it on your chart. Ah, here's Doctor Cel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623495" id2="17" version="1065353216">None of your business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623496" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should warn you: Evasiveness and hostility are the first symptoms of the brain degeneration process. Ah, here's Doctor Cel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good news. Your antibody count is off the charts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623500" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll start work on a vaccine immediately. You are remarkably brave. Our progress has just jumped forward by years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623502" id2="17" version="1065353216">While you recuperate, I'm going to transmit the usual secrecy agreements. Just use your thumbprint to sign on the sensor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623503" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean &quot;usual&quot; secrecy agreements?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623503" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since when do we do this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623504" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623505" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is standard procedure when the Republic develops biotech with significant earnings potential.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623507" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not signing anything until I know what it is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623507" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think so. Slow down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, no, no. This is perfectly normal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623510" id2="17" version="1065353216">We develop the vaccine for Republic soldiers first, and when it's proven, sell it to colonists. Until then, it's under wraps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623512" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't want the Exchange or the Sith funding some horrible operation with an underground version.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lives will be lost while this profit is being made.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623513" id2="17" version="1065353216">The vaccine should go to all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me something I don't know. Every week we hear another rakghoul horror story.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623516" id2="17" version="1065353216">But every colonist on the planet is going to want this vaccine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623518" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do I tell my superiors we gave up that kind of money?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623519" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you get a sample to the Jedi, I bet they'd find someone to make it fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go around them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623520" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep that in mind. We'll get this cure out one way or another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623522" id2="17" version="1065353216">An entire planet succumbed to this plague. Are you a doctor or a patent office?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grow a spine!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623523" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a doctor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623525" id2="17" version="1065353216">And this cure will get made, even if I have to build the manufacturing plant or hand-synthesize every macrophage....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, I think she's angry. But from past experience, may I say that usually motivates her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623529" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it means anything coming from a droid, sir, congratulations on your research and also, your remarkable survival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell them I'm already selling my blood elsewhere to start up a competing cure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623530" id2="17" version="1065353216">So lie a little.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623531" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know... that's not bad. It ought to light a fire under them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for putting yourself on the line for this. It would have taken years to do it the safe way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623535" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know if Taris will ever be what it was, but now, at least, there's hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623537" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess that makes sense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure, important people first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for soldiering up. I'll see you get a donor fee, but I can't promise a cut of the profits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623540" id2="17" version="1065353216">The amount of money we're talking about is staggering. I could make a career out of a vaccine like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623542" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you put yourself on the line to make it happen. I won't forget.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Cel has informed me of your experiment. Be certain to seek treatment here before any loss of consciousness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our team is observing rakghoul populations. Be advised it is not safe here.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
