<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>142</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/trooper/chapter_3/finale/general_garza.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632207" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major, welcome back! General, the major is here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632209" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a moment too soon. Come with me, Major. We were supposed to be in the Supreme Chancellor's office ten minutes ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632210" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, I didn't realize we'd been summoned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632210" id2="17" version="1065353216">My apologies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632211" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to apologize. Just come along.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632213" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the situation, General?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632213" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is something wrong?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632214" id2="17" version="1065353216">The situation is that the Supreme Chancellor of the Republic is waiting for us. Come along.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632216" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm really not in the mood to chat with bureaucrats, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632216" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not more politics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632217" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody is interested in your mood, Major. When the Supreme Chancellor calls, you answer. Come on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632219" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Garza, hello! Please, come in, make yourself comfortable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632221" id2="17" version="1065353216">And Major, so good to see you again. It seems I can't blink without you winning yet another incredible victory for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632222" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to see you too, Your Excellency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632222" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632223" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not easy being so incredible, believe me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632223" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know, I'm amazing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632224" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you must be the commander of Havoc Squad. I've been hearing a lot about you recently--it's a pleasure to finally meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632225" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm very pleased to meet you, Your Excellency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632225" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is an honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632226" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never thought I'd actually meet the Supreme Chancellor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632226" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632227" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no more impressive than any other servant of the Republic. I've certainly never achieved anything comparable to your victory on Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632229" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to tell me why I'm here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632229" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get to the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632230" id2="17" version="1065353216">I only wanted to congratulate you on your victory. Defeating General Rakton was no small task.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632232" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't become fully aware of Havoc Squad's achievements until I took office. Your service to the Republic has been truly remarkable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632234" id2="17" version="1065353216">For your exemplary service in the defense of the Republic, you are hereby awarded the Chancellor's Service Medal. Congratulations, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632235" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm truly honored, Your Excellency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632235" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you very much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632236" id2="17" version="1065353216">I only wish I could do more to recognize the work you've done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will the other members of Havoc Squad be recognized as well?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632238" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about my squad?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632239" id2="17" version="1065353216">Each of your squad-mates will be awarded Silver Crescents to recognize their contributions to your defeat of General Rakton.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632241" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally, some real recognition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632241" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's about time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632242" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you haven't felt slighted up until now--the Republic certainly appreciates your work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632244" id2="17" version="1065353216">With Rakton gone, the Imperial military is weaker than ever. For the first time in many years, we have the advantage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632245" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been a long, hard fight, but we've come out on top.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632245" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've come a long way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632246" id2="17" version="1065353216">For now, yes--but we must be cautious to maintain what we've fought so hard to gain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you think the Empire might give up the fight?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will they surrender?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632249" id2="17" version="1065353216">At best, we'll drive them back to the fringes of the galaxy and spend decades hunting them across obscure Rim worlds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632251" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the people of the Republic will be safe from their assaults, and that is what our work is all about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632253" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I have to hunt down every last Imp myself, I will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632253" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soon we'll destroy them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632254" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even disadvantaged, the Empire is not done yet. Much work remains before the galaxy is safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632256" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're all fortunate to have defenders as skilled and clever as yourselves. Meeting with you has been a very great pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632258" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish you good fortune in all your future missions, and know that the Republic is proud of everything you've achieved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632260" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you very much for your time, Your Excellency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632262" id2="17" version="1065353216">General, Major, welcome back! How did your meeting go?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even better than expected. I'm proud that you stood up to the Chancellor, Major--I had almost resigned myself to the idea of hunting Rakton down all over again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632265" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you approve, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632266" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you've saved a great many lives by changing her mind on the matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632268" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wasn't sure speaking up would do any good, but I had to try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632268" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just glad she listened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632269" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you did. There's no telling how many lives you've saved by changing Saresh's mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632271" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe our own Supreme Chancellor would want to do something so stupid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632271" id2="17" version="1065353216">That woman was a fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632272" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very few people are prepared to make the kinds of choices we make on a daily basis. We're just fortunate she listened to reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well. The Supreme Chancellor was impressed with the major's accomplishments. You really have gone above and beyond the call of duty, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632275" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just proud to do my part, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you very much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632276" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do far more than just your part. No matter how much is asked of you, you always deliver.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have another mission lined up for us, General?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632278" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's next?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not at the moment, but that's likely to change soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632281" id2="17" version="1065353216">A trinket and a &quot;thank you&quot;--that's my reward?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632281" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that all I get?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632282" id2="17" version="1065353216">If one of the highest awards in the Republic and the personal thanks of the Supreme Chancellor aren't enough, then you're out of luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632284" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I said, our work doesn't end here. Imperial forces are already regrouping on Ilum and elsewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632286" id2="17" version="1065353216">And though you were honored today, the killing of Senator Zian hasn't been forgotten. It's best if you keep a low profile for the time being.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632288" id2="17" version="1065353216">It won't be long before your team is called back to the front lines. You should take this time to get what rest you can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632290" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what's the plan? Where do we go from here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632291" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are your plans, Major? What will we do now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632292" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd say we've all earned some away time, wouldn't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Vacation for everyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="632293" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun hopes that we can find a temporary peace proportional to the chaotic path we've walked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632295" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy doesn't take time off, so neither do we. Let's get back out there, people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632295" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's find another fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632296" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will fight until the last Imperial lies dying at our feet!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632298" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd say it's time to find out who wants to buy the heroes some drinks. Who's in?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632298" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm hitting the cantina.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632299" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know you can always count on me, boss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632301" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose I could join in, just this once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Somebody's got to keep you from getting into too much trouble. I'll go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632305" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just be sure to keep your holo close by, Major. When the next crisis comes, Havoc Squad will get the first call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632307" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Supreme Chancellor is trading Rakton back to the Empire, alive and well. I can't begin to imagine how difficult it will be to capture him again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632308" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have a duty to uphold the Supreme Chancellor's decisions, no matter what.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632308" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was her call, not ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632309" id2="17" version="1065353216">Upholding her decisions and approving of them are very different things. What a mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632311" id2="17" version="1065353216">We captured Rakton once. We can do it again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632311" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing is impossible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632312" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope so. We have no other choice, now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632314" id2="17" version="1065353216">How could anyone be stupid enough to set Rakton free?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632314" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe it either.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Obviously, the lure of an easy solution was too much for her. Bureaucrats.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even without this setback, our war against the Empire is far from over. Their forces are already regrouping on Ilum and elsewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632319" id2="17" version="1065353216">For your meritorious actions and unequaled valor in service of the Republic, you are hereby awarded our highest honor--the Cross of Glory. Congratulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632320" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm honored to accept this award, Your Excellency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you very much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632321" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've more than earned it, Major. The people of the Republic owe you a debt that can never fully be repaid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will my team be recognized for their work as well?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632323" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about my squad?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632324" id2="17" version="1065353216">The other members of Havoc Squad will each receive Gold Crescents for their contributions to the capture of General Rakton.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to know my work is finally being appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632326" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's about time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, if you've felt slighted in the past, I certainly apologize. The Republic is very fortunate to have such a skilled defender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632329" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's hard to believe we actually have the Empire's greatest general in our custody. He's the best bargaining chip we've ever laid hands on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me, Your Excellency, but what do you mean exactly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632333" id2="17" version="1065353216">A trade. In return for Rakton, the Empire is willing to release thousands of Republic prisoners. It's an incredible opportunity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632334" id2="17" version="1065353216">With respect, wouldn't it be extremely dangerous to release Rakton ?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure that's wise?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632335" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe the risk is more than outweighed by the reward. We've beaten him once--we can beat him again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632337" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm impressed that the Empire would offer so much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632337" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is a great opportunity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently, Rakton is still very important to them, even in his current condition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632340" id2="17" version="1065353216">With respect, Supreme Chancellor, this seems like an incredibly reckless proposition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632342" id2="17" version="1065353216">After everything we've been through to capture Rakton, you want to let him go?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632342" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't send Rakton back!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632343" id2="17" version="1065353216">He doesn't do us any good rotting in a cell, does he?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think of the countless families reunited--thousands of husbands and wives, parents and children, all brought home at last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632347" id2="17" version="1065353216">And what of the many thousands more killed by Rakton in his campaigns, Your Excellency? Don't they deserve some kind of justice?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632349" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't help the dead, General. But we can help the living, and we have a duty to do so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632350" id2="17" version="1065353216">As Supreme Chancellor, the choice is yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632350" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is your decision.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632351" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes--and the correct choice seems obvious to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632353" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have a chance to save thousands of Republic lives. We should take it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632353" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632354" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you agree, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632356" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be proud--your actions have freed thousands of soldiers from enemy custody, and proven that we can defeat the Empire's greatest general.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632358" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been a pleasure, Major. Good luck in your future missions, and know that the Republic appreciates your many sacrifices.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632360" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good day, Your Excellency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632362" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you send Rakton back to the Empire, then this medal will be meaningless, along with the deaths of countless good soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="632362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let Rakton go and I quit!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632364" id2="17" version="1065353216">We might get thousands of our people back, but with Rakton's help, the Empire can kill twice that number in a day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632366" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't stand for this, Chancellor. I won't watch you hand the Empire's deadliest weapon back to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632367" id2="17" version="1065353216">You... you won't have to, Major. You're absolutely right--Rakton must remain in our custody.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632369" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate hearing your thoughts on the matter--it's been a pleasure meeting with you. Unfortunately, other matters press, please excuse me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632371" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, Your Excellency. Good day.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
