<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>20</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/trooper/chapter_3/finale/radio_transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Team Two to command--all ambushers neutralized. We are regrouping and advancing to sweep any remaining infantry. Dorne out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jorgan here--Rakton's flank team is history. We're going to move up and sweep for any leftovers--see you inside. Out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Team Two reporting--all Imps are down here. Time to move up and clean up--see you soon. Jorgan out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632680" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Team Two--enemy ambushers neutralized. We will regroup and advance with caution. Dorne out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="632684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unit Four is down! Units One and Five, move to cover them--keep firing!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="632686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anti-armor teams spotted! All units, focus fire!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="632688" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fifty-third reporting. Initial blast results positive, advancing and preparing second blast. Estimate seven total blasts needed, will update shortly. Lesher out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632692" id2="17" version="1065353216">Focus your fire! Bring it down! Team Two, advance!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632694" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're through! Go, go, go! Team Three, you're next--show me those charges!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632696" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coria here. Progress is slow, but we're clear so far. Hope the rest of you are having fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Team Two in position. Enemy speeders approaching now--we will advise if any forces escape our ambush. Dorne out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Team Two in position. Rakton's flanking team is right on time--welcome party is prepared. Will advise of any runners--Jorgan out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Team Two in position. Welcome party is staged, and Rakton's flankers have been confirmed. Will advise if anyone escapes--Jorgan out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Team Two in position. Enemy forces incoming, as predicted--proceeding with ambush as planned. Dorne out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="632710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fifty-third reporting. Enemy contact established--moving into weapon range now. For the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="632712" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fifty-third reporting. Enemy infantry positions spotted--advancing to weapon range now. For the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="632714" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fifty-third reporting. Automated defenses and mines detected as reported. Charging main guns for area blast--will update shortly. Lesher out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632718" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coria here. Enemy armor spotted--they're big, but we brought the big toys. Moving into position now--out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coria here. Approaching enemy infantry positions now. Explosive charges and entry weapons prepped and ready. They don't know what they're in for--out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="632722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coria here. Automated defenses and mines are confirmed--we're proceeding with caution. Out.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
