<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>55</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world/republic/unstable/gawash_family.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, last building. Come on, everyone. Single-file, not too fast. Not too slow, either.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get your hands off me! Blasted Republic interlopers... I know my rights! I'm not going anywhere!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020643" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, I'll be a Wookiee's uncle. I knew we'd find your building sooner or later. It's Roop, isn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Roop and his family are old friends. They send the Protectors strongly worded holomessages before every Makeb evac.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems the Hutts promised them bonus pay if they stayed inside. Roop here thinks we're trying to cheat him out of his credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020650" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Protectors are an official Republic unit. They perform evacuations like this all the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020650" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the real thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020651" id2="17" version="1065353216">The perfect front for a gang of looters and thieves!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020653" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's got you there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020655" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jedi has no interest in material wealth. I can vouch for all these people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020655" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can trust me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shame on you, bringing a Jedi into your scam!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020658" id2="17" version="1065353216">What, you think Jedi aren't desperate, too? Look at what they wear!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020660" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm the commander of Havoc Squad. That comes with a pretty high pay grade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020660" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020661" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure does, when you're stealing it from the locals like a common thug!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, that's uncalled for. There's nothing common about us!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020665" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, buddy, I'll do a lot of things for credits, but this isn't one of them. Probably.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020665" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not my style.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scamming honest, hard-working folk--you're no better than Shalim!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020668" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rich guy bankrolling this fight? We should all be that terrible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020670" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do the Hutts gain by making their workers stay in dangerous areas?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why pay them to stay inside?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020671" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our combined weight helps maintain the structural integrity, or something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020673" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could name ten things wrong with that sentence. Half of them aren't even engineering-related.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020675" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not getting a bonus. Your idiot employers have drilled Makeb into an early grave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020675" id2="17" version="1065353216">News flash, morons....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone knows the groundquakes are entirely natural. Have been for months.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020678" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't even make any--fine. They're natural. A building is still no place to be during one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020680" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rest of you can cut and run if you like, but me and mine are staying right here. It's quadruple overtime, people!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020682" id2="17" version="1065353216">Need you outside, sir. One of the speeders blew a hoverpad on the way back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talk them down, will you? Or bribe them--we're good for it. Meet you back at base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020686" id2="17" version="1065353216">You show me an order from Vice Commandant Grevin, my foreman or Toborro himself. Otherwise, I'm not moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020687" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no more time to argue about this. What will it take to make you leave this building?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020687" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to leave now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020688" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want my bonus. Unless you've raided the Hutt treasury, I know you don't have it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020689" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic will compensate you for your lost bonus pay. Whatever percentage you want.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020689" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have our own credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020690" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. How about a little now to prove it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020692" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow. You weren't kidding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't matter to me where the creds come from. Point me towards the exit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020695" id2="17" version="1065353216">They didn't want me to tell you this, but the Republic's already cleared the vaults.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020695" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] Actually, we did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020696" id2="17" version="1065353216">But... how are they going to pay us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020698" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're not. I knew I should have volunteered for the militia!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020700" id2="17" version="1065353216">No point in sticking around here. At least you're providing transport after robbing us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020701" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can leave by your own two feet, or I can drag you out one by one. Your choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020701" id2="17" version="1065353216">Move or I hit you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, okay, we're going! Just take it easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020703" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can see you're not fools. But I came here for credits, and I'm not leaving without them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Split the credits with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020704" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mean Roop was right? You're actually robbing us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't I tell you? Blasted parasites.... Better give 'em what you've got.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020708" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was my last month's pay, you rotten scab. Now get out of here and leave us alone!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why? Going to steal my identity, too?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
