<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>101</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world/republic/unstable/tefani.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020502" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for the assist. Those civs would be under a pile of rubble now if not for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020505" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tefani. Looks like your reinforcements are back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020507" id2="17" version="1065353216">There they are! The Supreme Chancellor's well-oiled machine. I see why you all keep together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020511" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a performance, Master Jedi! If we had ten more of you, the war would be over tomorrow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020513" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a pleasure watching you work, Major. Makes me wish Havoc Squad needed an engineer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020515" id2="17" version="1065353216">One hired gun, a few dead mercs, and here we all are. We're lucky you're not on the Hutts' side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020517" id2="17" version="1065353216">One hundred percent of the building's occupants were rescued and accounted for. That's what I call a good day at the office.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020523" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a pleasure to work with, Tefani. The Protectors can call on me anytime.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad I could help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020524" id2="17" version="1065353216">No point in doing anything unless you're having fun, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020526" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts had those people brainwashed. It took some doing to get them to leave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020526" id2="17" version="1065353216">It almost wasn't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020527" id2="17" version="1065353216">No kidding? Glad you stuck with it. Fear makes people do crazy things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there anyone else to evacuate on this mesa, or are the Protectors moving on?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020529" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happens now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020530" id2="17" version="1065353216">We lost fifteen percent of the occupants when the building's interior collapsed, though. Roop Gawash and friends, I'm guessing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Roop and his family wouldn't listen to reason. I couldn't waste any more time on them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing I could do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020532" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need to work on your people skills. Plenty of ways to lure a scared cat out of a trash compactor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Roop took off inside the building, and his family followed. There was nothing I could do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020534" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] They ran away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chased 'em, maybe. But then we might have lost you, too. Wouldn't want the heat for that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those idiots deserved to stay behind. Better hope for the next generation without them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too stupid to live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ouch. Sorry I asked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talaos City should be pretty well cleared in a few hours, thanks to you. I had Cash put a little something together to show our appreciation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better get back to it. Next evac means repairing a light bridge. A bridge made of light! What'll they come up with next?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020548" id2="17" version="1065353216">The numbers aren't getting better. You've got to get those civs out before that building comes down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, I've asked Chief Hurkwill three times. They can't spare anyone. Will you please come back now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020553" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nah, it's practically cozy out here. So Hurkwill's men aren't an option. There's got to be someone else back there with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020555" id2="17" version="1065353216">Or a lot of someones. That's the Supreme Chancellor's squad. Over here, you guys!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020557" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use your eyes, Cash. There's a Jedi, right there. Master Jedi! Can we have a minute?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on, you're letting the commander of Havoc Squad get away. This way, Major!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020561" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, an independent contractor, just looking for a job. Hey, you! Credits over here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cash Zarrin, Logistics Specialist Tefani. We're with the Protectors--Republic MedCorps, Second Battalion. Official evacuation forces for frightened civilians everywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to see a friendly face in this chaos. How can I help you, Tefani?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020565" id2="17" version="1065353216">And everyone says Jedi are cold! For starters, we could use that lightsaber of yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020567" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people of the Republic need a group dedicated to their safety.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020567" id2="17" version="1065353216">A fine mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020568" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sound like my captain. But he's right--being a hero ain't a bad way to make a living.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020570" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been with the military a long time, but I've never heard of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020570" id2="17" version="1065353216">Must be a new unit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain doesn't like a lot of press. Me, I wouldn't mind a few medals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Between the mercs and the groundquakes, Makeb's kept you busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good place for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020574" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're free as birds right now. How'd you like to put us back to work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020585" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume you didn't come up with that title yourselves?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020585" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're named &quot;the Protectors&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nah, some orphaned kids from Corellia started it. Just kind of stuck after that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020588" id2="17" version="1065353216">You look like you need an evacuation, yourselves. Why aren't you armed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not much of a force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020589" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're non-combat, staffed by civilians and ex-military volunteers. Worked out fine--until now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Big seismic event coming up. We're talking big enough to devour Talaos City. Got to get these people out now if we're going to beat the clock.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Problem is, Talaos City's on lockdown. The Hutts have turned all the keys and put the Regulators on street patrol. I think one of 'em's eyeing me now....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your head down and don't engage. I'll be there as quick as I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay put, I'm coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020595" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, no, I'm fine. Me and a couple scouts got ourselves a nice piece of cover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020597" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you need someone to take on the Regulators while the Protectors escape?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020597" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need a rescue?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020598" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you talking to me for? Run back to camp before he sees you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then get out of there, fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020601" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Regulators aren't a problem for me, they're a problem for our evac. They're sitting guard on some buildings at the corner of Groundquake and Epicenter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020603" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the quake hits while the buildings are still full... well, it'll definitely lower the property values. We need the mercs out of our way so we can evacuate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just point me towards the buildings, and those mercs will be history.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020604" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can handle that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020605" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got a very strange way of saying things, Tefani.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020605" id2="17" version="1065353216">Property values?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020608" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take &quot;strange.&quot; Not the worst thing I've been called.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020610" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're out there already. Pick up a blaster and start shooting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do it yourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020613" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm an engineer. I could try calculating them to death, but they'd need to stand still first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020615" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll transmit you coordinates, soon as this seismic scan is done... uh-oh. Better hang on to something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020617" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was a warning, and we're not getting another. Cash, get the speeders ready. Our reinforcements will clear the mercs and get inside the buildings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you're in, hit the emergency alarm. The civs will run out, the speeders will pick them up, and we all meet back here to shake hands. Sound good?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020620" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm usually on the front lines. It's rare I get to rescue civilians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020620" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm excited, actually.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain's always looking for new recruits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020622" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can see why the Protectors made you their logistics specialist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020622" id2="17" version="1065353216">An excellent plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aww, don't make me blush, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take down the mercs, move out the civs. Easy enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Affirmative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020625" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like your attitude, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020626" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should hit the cantina, play a few hands of pazaak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why stop there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020627" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have to take a groundquake check on that one, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shaking hands is a little impersonal for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020628" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Could be better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad I'm married. Cash here might kiss you, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020630" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got plenty to do on this planet before it falls apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1020630" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's make it fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't we all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here are the coordinates. Speeders are fueled up and ready to go. We'll be in position when you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1020635" id2="17" version="1065353216">No good. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1020636" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're in the middle of an evac here. Talk to Chief Hurkwill if you need information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1057850" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another building emptied. Can we keep you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1057851" id2="17" version="1065353216">All clear here. Head on down to the next one!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1057852" id2="17" version="1065353216">First building's evacuated. Keep those mercs busy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1057853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Almost done. We've got to be setting some kind of record.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
