<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>162</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/trooper/chapter_2/intro/general_garza.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, Captain, you've arrived. This is Fleet Admiral Numinn, head of the Republic Navy's Fifth Assault Fleet, and Supreme Commander Rans, overall head of the Republic Armed Forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633260" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633262" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've both heard a great deal about you, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given our present circumstances, Fleet Admiral Numinn and Supreme Commander Rans have come here to plan a full-scale joint operation to deal with the Gauntlet superweapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633265" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm honored to meet you both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633265" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633266" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's unfortunate that we couldn't meet under better circumstances. As you know, the situation is dire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633268" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's our strategy for dealing with the Gauntlet, General?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633268" id2="17" version="1065353216">How are we proceeding?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633269" id2="17" version="1065353216">Plans are still being developed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't feel like you were bossing me around enough on your own, General?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great, more oversight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633272" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is no time for insubordinate jokes. You know the situation we're in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633274" id2="17" version="1065353216">A single operational Gauntlet device gives the Empire a decisive military advantage, but Agent Garn's report has revealed the enemy's true plan: mass production.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633276" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Gauntlet prototype is completed and the Empire succeeds in producing more of them, we're doomed. The entire Republic would be conquered in a matter of weeks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633277" id2="17" version="1065353216">There must be something we can do to stop this thing, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633277" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let that happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633278" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand that the Gauntlet is a dangerous weapon, but is it really that game ending, sir?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633278" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are we really that bad off?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any fleets sent within range of a Gauntlet superweapon are forfeit. Reinforcing battles, retaking lost positions, assaulting new ones--all become impossible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633281" id2="17" version="1065353216">How could we not have discovered this earlier?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633281" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633282" id2="17" version="1065353216">We know about it now--that's all that matters. Assigning blame will only waste time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633284" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroying the Gauntlet will require a coordinated naval and infantry strike of unprecedented scale. Our forces must begin preparing now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633286" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the midst of the assault we're planning, a single commando team will board the Gauntlet and sabotage it from within. We've chosen Havoc Squad to carry out this task.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633287" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad will be proud to end this threat to the Republic, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633287" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633288" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're the best of the best, General. Consider it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who else would you pick?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633289" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's not get ahead of ourselves, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633291" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we get anywhere near the thing, let alone board it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633291" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like suicide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633292" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will find a way to get your ship close to the Gauntlet. You need only worry about destroying it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633294" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your team will need to be expanded. You'll need a technical specialist and an explosives expert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633296" id2="17" version="1065353216">The general and I have scoured the entire Republic personnel database to locate the two most highly qualified specialists available.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633298" id2="17" version="1065353216">Both men are engaged in active operations--the first on Balmorra. Extract him and return here as quickly as possible. Understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633299" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I have your leave, I'll get started immediately, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633300" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely, Captain. The sooner Havoc Squad is at full strength, the sooner we can begin the assault on the Gauntlet. Dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633301" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I'm adding these people to my squad, I'd like to know about them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633301" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you tell me about them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633302" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have full reports on each new recruit. You'll receive the relevant details when you arrive in each mission zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc doesn't need anyone else to pull this mission off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633304" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a waste of time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633305" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is not a matter for discussion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633307" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now move out, Captain. We need Havoc Squad at full strength by the time our other preparations are complete, so that the assault on the Gauntlet can begin. Dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633309" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have your orders, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant, welcome. Stand at ease. We have a lot to discuss, and not much time to do it in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633312" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please ignore my other visitors. Tavus's testimony at trial has created a great deal of interest in my day-to-day affairs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tavus had a right to trial. I never intended it to lead to anything like this, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633313" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry about all this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633314" id2="17" version="1065353216">No apology necessary. Let's just get on with our work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you being investigated for some kind of crime?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633316" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633317" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senate fears I'm withholding information, so they've sent observers to waste my time. But we have more pressing concerns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633319" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you have nothing to hide, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nervous?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let the investigators worry about that. You and I have more important matters to discuss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633322" id2="17" version="1065353216">First, for demonstrating exceptional discretion in the capture of numerous key enemy personnel, you are being awarded the Bronze Crescent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633324" id2="17" version="1065353216">First, for your courageous actions against superior enemy forces, you are being awarded the Republic Mark of Victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633326" id2="17" version="1065353216">In addition, due to your exemplary leadership under the most dire of circumstances, you are hereby promoted to the rank of captain, effective immediately. Congratulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you very much, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633327" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm honored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633328" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've more than earned it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633330" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? I don't get a ceremony?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633330" id2="17" version="1065353216">No big show?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633331" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no time for pageantry at the moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633334" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've called the other members of Havoc Squad here so you can designate one of them as your executive officer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your XO will serve as your second-in-command and be promoted to the rank of lieutenant. As droids cannot hold rank, your choice is between sergeants Jorgan and Dorne.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aric Jorgan, I'm promoting you to the rank of lieutenant, effective immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jorgan will be my XO.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Elara Dorne, I hereby promote you to the rank of lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633338" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want Dorne for the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's start with you, Jorgan--why should I give you this promotion?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me talk to them, first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you serious? I was a lieutenant when you met me. I was an operations officer on Ord Mantell for more than three years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633342" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Tavus hadn't left the lazy jerks upstairs hungry for a scapegoat, I'd still be a lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633344" id2="17" version="1065353216">Besides--you've seen my results in the field. I'm obviously the most qualified for executive officer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633345" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll think about what you've said, Jorgan. That will be all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633345" id2="17" version="1065353216">You make a good case.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Dorne has done a lot for this squad, Jorgan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Elara's pretty sharp, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, she's a great medic, and she knows the regs--but she doesn't have the training or the experience that I have, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633350" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and I don't always get along, Jorgan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633350" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get your hopes up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633351" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, sir, but you don't need to like me for me to do a good job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633353" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for hearing me out. Sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me what makes you the best choice for the job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633354" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about you, Dorne?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633355" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe my service record speaks for itself, sir. In spite of my short time in the Republic Army, I have received multiple commendations and glowing performance reviews.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633357" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you've seen firsthand, I carry out my duties professionally and precisely at all times.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally, I have extensive personal knowledge of the tactics and training of our enemy--more so, perhaps, than any other soldier in the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633360" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take all of this into consideration, Dorne. That will be all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633360" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a good point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood. Thank you for your time, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633362" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Jorgan already has a lot of command experience.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633362" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about Jorgan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633363" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, sir, but I think you'll agree that Sergeant Jorgan's combative demeanor is not a recommended quality for a position of authority.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633365" id2="17" version="1065353216">Memorizing regulations doesn't put the bad guys in body bags.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633365" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're too focused on rules.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633366" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe in regulations, sir. Because if we do not hold ourselves to our own ideals, we are no better than our enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633368" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for allowing me to speak, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633369" id2="17" version="1065353216">Elara Dorne, I hereby promote you to the rank of lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633369" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be my XO, Dorne.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633370" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you very much, Captain. I will endeavor to serve well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aric Jorgan, you are hereby promoted to the rank of lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633372" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd prefer Jorgan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633373" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're both good candidates, General. I'll go with your recommendation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633373" id2="17" version="1065353216">You decide, General--I can't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633374" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aric Jorgan, I hereby promote you to lieutenant, effective immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633374" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sold--Jorgan's in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633375" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally back where I started. Thanks, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633377" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't choose between them, General--I'll go with your recommendation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633377" id2="17" version="1065353216">You pick, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633378" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's what you want. Jorgan, you're hereby promoted to the rank of lieutenant. Congratulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633380" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, General. I appreciate your confidence in me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633382" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, let's discuss the reason you were called here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633384" id2="17" version="1065353216">An SIS agent working undercover in the Imperial military has made a critical discovery. The Empire is constructing an experimental new superweapon, code-named &quot;Gauntlet.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633385" id2="17" version="1065353216">How dangerous is this thing, General?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633385" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are its capabilities?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633386" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're short on details, unfortunately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633388" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just give me the coordinates and plenty of thermal detonators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633388" id2="17" version="1065353216">So let's blast the thing!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633389" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can only hope the situation ends up being so simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633391" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the SIS found it, the SIS should handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633391" id2="17" version="1065353216">How is this our problem?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633392" id2="17" version="1065353216">The spies have played their part. But a threat of this scale calls for the best military team available.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633394" id2="17" version="1065353216">The agent is in too deep to risk transmitting any further information. Our only option is a rapid extraction--that's where Havoc comes in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633395" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll pull the agent out immediately, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633395" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Easy as could be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633397" id2="17" version="1065353216">This situation is serious. Please try to treat it that way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633399" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds messy to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633400" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's risky, but if there were any other way to get this information, we'd do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633402" id2="17" version="1065353216">The extraction will take place on Tatooine. An SIS agent will meet you there with the full details of the operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633404" id2="17" version="1065353216">Failure is not an option, Captain. We have to learn what the Gauntlet is and what it's capable of, no matter the cost. Dismissed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633408" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come in, Lieutenant. This is General Garza. I'm afraid your leave will have to be cut short.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633410" id2="17" version="1065353216">A critical situation has just been brought to High Command's attention. Havoc Squad is needed--immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633412" id2="17" version="1065353216">Report to my office on Coruscant right away. We'll discuss things further when you arrive. Garza out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633414" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. If High Command is worked up, this can't be good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's move out, people!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633415" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd better get going.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like we're back on the job. Are all of you ready for this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone ready for more work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633418" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ready and able, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our degraded enemies have rested in reprieve too long! Let's set out right away!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633423" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I want your opinion, Sergeant, I'll let you know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stow the attitude, Jorgan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633424" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood. Sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633431" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come in, Lieutenant. This is General Garza. Excellent work on Valence Station--few could have handled the situation so well, on such short notice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633432" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm always ready to do my duty, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633432" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad I could help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just what I was hoping to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pretty exciting end to my vacation, I'll give it that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633435" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've had worse missions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633436" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid your work is just beginning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633438" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe I cut my leave short for that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="633438" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a waste of time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="633439" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid any further leave will have to be postponed as well.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
