<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>19</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/world/republic/survivors/captain_quarn.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Healing the minds of the Killik slaves will take time, and possibly Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surprising turn of events here. It's good to make your acquaintance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our mutual friend Elz says you found and freed the prisoners who have been coming in today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, he smeared them in thranta dung and dragged them through a river to throw Killiks off the scent, but that's Elz for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720599" id2="17" version="1065353216">How are the prisoners?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are the prisoners okay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not good. The Killiks made them ingest a mind-affecting ooze of some kind. It will take time to wean them off it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720602" id2="17" version="1065353216">But their families wanted you to have a little something. I said I'd pass it on to you--or you'd have been mobbed by grateful people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720604" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did all right out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720605" id2="17" version="1065353216">How valuable were these lives to the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720605" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I get paid for this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720606" id2="17" version="1065353216">That remains to be seen--many of them are unstable. But House Organa doesn't label one life valuable and another cheap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720608" id2="17" version="1065353216">As such, they did not want to see you unrewarded. You have served their old vassal house, and Organa by extension. Congratulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just how long has he been alone in those mountains?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="720609" id2="17" version="1065353216">He did seem a bit odd.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720610" id2="17" version="1065353216">A year or more. Long enough to choose a pet name for each Killik he tracked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720612" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I wouldn't mock his habits. He got every captive through the Killik lines alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without the two of you, these people would still be digging ditches and eating that foul Killik ooze. I must pass on their gratitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="720616" id2="17" version="1065353216">I handle prisoner exchanges. You are not one of them.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
