<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>42</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/world/republic/survivors/elz_organa.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513219" id2="17" version="1065353216">The captives are free and clear. I'm watching for more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just give the captives the opportunity to run. I'll take it from there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513221" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you doing here? I didn't think anyone could escape from the minders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513223" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait... you're armed. You're not a Killik prisoner at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513224" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Killiks have prisoners?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513224" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should I be?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513225" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I've been telling people, but no one listens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513227" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513228" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Elz. House Organa sent me out here when House Syrush fell to the Killiks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513230" id2="17" version="1065353216">A year ago, these things swarmed all over, and we presumed all captives were dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513232" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I found they've still got human prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513233" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you doing this close to man-eating bugs?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513233" id2="17" version="1065353216">How have you survived here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513234" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watching and waiting. House Syrush has been gone a year, but the Killiks who took over their estate are busy, busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513236" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't get too close, but you can tell who's got four limbs and who's got six.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513238" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's how I know the Killiks still have human captives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513239" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can put an end to that right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513239" id2="17" version="1065353216">That needs to be stopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513240" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll do it together. You get them free. I'll get them home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513242" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513243" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been out here for a year, hiding my tracks, my smell, burying spoor, burying Killik bodies. I know Killiks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513245" id2="17" version="1065353216">But there aren't spies or soldiers to spare if you don't have a last name of Ulgo or Thul.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513247" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure the Organas can spare a few people to rescue the prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513247" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Organas can help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513248" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Organa assumes they're dead. My reports get buried under a mountain of Thul and Ulgo data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513250" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, it's Crazy Elz still holding out hope, they say.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513252" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I don't keep hope alive, where does it put the prisoners? They need to believe, and they need a way out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513253" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show me where the prisoners are, and we'll get them free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513253" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll do it together, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513254" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not much good in a fight, but I can handle getting a shocked prisoner home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513256" id2="17" version="1065353216">You take out the Killik guards at the estate and send the prisoners running to me. I'll mask their smell and get them to the Republic outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Quarn takes care of former prisoners there. Make sure they all make it to him. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513259" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd need to be paid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513260" id2="17" version="1065353216">That can be handled. Now, let's coordinate this--you be the muscle and I'll be the getaway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513262" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought Jedi were supposed to--never mind. Captain Quarn at the Republic outpost can take care of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Quarn at the Republic outpost handles that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513266" id2="17" version="1065353216">You just have to remove the Killiks at the estates and get the captives clear. I'll mask their scent and get them to the outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Check in with Captain Quarn to make sure they all made it, and you'll have your reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513270" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no way we can escort someone through an alerted hive of Killiks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="513270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't do it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513271" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you don't think so, get out of my hiding spot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="513273" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can smell you. Stay away.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
