<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>6</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/support/alderaan/shared/bb_group_1_board_1.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1111403" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
WEATHER TOWER ANALYSIS

Sensitive instruments used in Alderaan's weather towers contain a proprietary technology to which the rights are in dispute. However, our Natural Weapons Division requires the technology to build a proposed &quot;Weather Dominator&quot; prototype.

If you provide us with detailed scans of the weather towers in action, our crack team can reverse engineer the technology and create a new weapon for your faction to employ.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1111404" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
SURVEILLANCE DATA RECOVERY

The giant red thranta of Alderaan: majestic, aerial and endangered. We've fitted several thrantas with GSI technology to gather data on area troop deployments. This allows us to better determine military needs without any preconceived biases--or bureaucratic hindrances.

The one downside is that the compiled data must be retrieved manually from the rare thrantas. Our research and development teams would greatly appreciate your assistance in this matter.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1111405" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI ACTION ALERT:
SABOTEUR AT LARGE

Someone has managed to infiltrate our databanks, absconding with proprietary GSI weapons technology. We believe the perpetrator works for a freelance spy named &quot;the Shroud&quot; and is using one of the Great Houses of Alderaan to transmit the data offworld without their knowledge or consent.

Please monitor the Great Houses' communications networks to track down and defeat this saboteur. Our Recovery Division will take care of the rest.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1111406" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
HAZARDOUS MATERIALS

Long ago, Czerka employees commonly eschewed proper disposal protocols, burying vast amounts of radioactive waste on Alderaan. Orbital scans indicate the waste could be a powerful fuel source. However, the Killik hives that have developed over waste sites make extraction a chore.

Look for glowing, irradiated plants at the dump sites to better locate the buried waste barrels. Obtain these barrels for GSI and our Starfighter Division can get to work on building more powerful warships.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1111408" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI REQUISITION ALERT:
WEAPONS TESTING

The Killiks have assimilated a great many cultures into their hive mind over the centuries. These couplings often led to hybrid weapons of a highly unique nature--weapons which the Killiks have buried under their civilization's ruins on Alderaan to honor their past. At GSI, we believe the weapons would be far more useful above ground.

We would like for you to recover and test some of these weapons so that we can determine their potential efficacy in future applications.

GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1112011" id2="17" version="1065353216">GSI OPPORTUNITY: VALUED PARTNER INITIATIVE

At Galactic Solutions Industries, we're always looking for ways to grow our partnerships. By accepting and completing multiple GSI assignments, you may qualify for GSI's Valued Partner Initiative. The VPI rewards your hard work with reputation above and beyond what you've earned for each individual commission.

Thank you for your consideration in becoming one of our most valued partners.

Addalar Hyland, founder and CEO
GSI - We stay neutral, so you don't have to.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
