<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>90</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/yavin_4/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135699" id2="17" version="1065353216">Update: I am activating internal dehumidification systems to compensate for the environment. Please inform me if we are to remain here for over a month.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135700" id2="17" version="1065353216">From the stars, I thought this might be my homeworld. My world looks much the same. But I think I am not sad. Much more to explore here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135701" id2="17" version="1065353216">No fighting, no gambling, no contraband. This isn't an army base--it's a prison camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you feel it? The gravity of the gas giant urges us skyward, as if we could spread wings and ascend. This world is more than it appears.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135703" id2="17" version="1065353216">I tried a HoloNet search on Yavin before we came here. Lots of urban legends and ghost stories. The first few were fun, but... it's not fun anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clean air. Cleaner than Taris. Strange smells, though. Can't trust your senses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135705" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rishi was more my speed--raiders and pirates, and not a temple or ancient relic in sight. Guess you like Yavin better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135706" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi never talked to me about Yavin. There were stories, and I asked about them, but I was always told I wasn't ready. Am I ready now, my lord?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135707" id2="17" version="1065353216">The circumstances may be dire, but in truth, my lord, it's good to be among our forces again. There is nothing on Yavin that can stop us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135708" id2="17" version="1065353216">I feel like if we take one wrong step, this truce'll break. I also feel like this planet--moon, whatever--is going to eat us. Can we go yet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135709" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yavin Four, huh? Place is kind of pretty from here. Don't think I want to go any farther, but we can at least say we made the trip.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135710" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're surrounded by Sith on a Sith planet. Are you as uncomfortable with this as I am? Because if you are, we're doomed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135711" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch your hydration here, Jedi. In this heat, you'll sweat out a liter before you know it. Can't have you wither on my watch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135712" id2="17" version="1065353216">The heat, the moisture--I feel like I'm going to wilt. Is it like this for your species?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Normally I enjoy an empty world, Captain--trees and greenery far as you can see. This place, though? Really makes me miss Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135714" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even before the Empire returned, the worst criminals in the galaxy wouldn't hide on Yavin Four. There are reasons no one goes here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135715" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch your back--alliance or not, I bet there's more than a few Imps here who'd like to drop Havoc Squad's commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135716" id2="17" version="1065353216">Part of me is glad to see we can put aside our differences with the Empire if need be. But I also fear how this will end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recalibration: Apologies master, but I am receiving excessive targeting data from the plethora of small mammals and invertebrates; deprioritizing them now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good trees, good dirt, good place for battles endless. I will lead, Chief. I know forests well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135721" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stupid jungle. What am I stepping in? If it were Hutt filth, at least I'd know there was something fun around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135722" id2="17" version="1065353216">The aura of life here is blinding, but its sound is cacophanous. The jungle struggles for its spirit as each bud and insect struggles for survival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Promise me one thing on your honor: If we live through this--if we get through this squishy, stinky jungle--you will buy me new boots.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135724" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thick growth, high canopy. New environment to learn. Perfect place to hunt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135725" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's something mean here, Sith. I'm not a fan of nature walks, but this jungle doesn't seem right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135726" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dark side is powerful here. It's like the trees are on fire with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135727" id2="17" version="1065353216">I trained in the jungles of Dromund Kaas, but those were a garden compared to this. Be wary and watch your footing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135728" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lekku are dripping from the humidity and I swear I smell something rotting. Dromund Kaas was scary, but there's something really wrong here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knew an infectious disease expert who specialized in natural cures--plant extracts, that kind of thing. Me, I just wonder how the jungle will try to kill me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135730" id2="17" version="1065353216">The dark side is strong here. It's not the jungle itself--it's like the jungle is flooded with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135731" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jungle warfare. Don't think I've done this since Felucia. Didn't like it much then, either.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135732" id2="17" version="1065353216">My world is a place of dangerous forests--very like this jungle, and very different. The beasts will make me homesick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135733" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got enough supply packs for a few days in this jungle, but let's try not to need 'em. Meaning we should be quick--not, you know, die real fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135734" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm better with cities than with jungles, but even I know this place isn't friendly to strangers. Let's be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135735" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heat like this makes you feel the weight of your armor. Stay focused. Fatigue makes you fight stupid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135736" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll both need full bioscans when we get back to the ship--General Medical Order 627-A. This jungle is designated a hostile biome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135739" id2="17" version="1065353216">Offer: I possess numerous training programs of my own, master. If desired, I can hunt any of your associates through this environment for a positive learning experience.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135740" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are hunted by many, Chief. This is good. Tomorrow we make trophy flags from their cloaks!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guardsmen! I am the Emperor! I have possessed this awesome body! Strip and kneel before me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135742" id2="17" version="1065353216">We always thought the Imperial Guard were noble--dedicated to an ideal of service above all. Our Empire loses itself by the day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135743" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one can say the Imperial Guard isn't brave. You have to be brave to wear bright red on a planet like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enemy training grounds. Nowhere more dangerous. Didn't save the Guard. Careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135745" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Revanites, the Imperial Guard... they're all dupes, worshiping one Force-using maniac or another. No offense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135746" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperial Guard--the servants of the galaxy's greatest evil, already brought to ruin. What are we facing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135747" id2="17" version="1065353216">As a child, I idolized the Guard. To serve the Emperor as they did was the greatest honor a non-Sith could achieve. Now... look at them. Look at us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135748" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperial Guard really lives here? What do you think that does to your head?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you imagine training in a place like this? Hard to picture anyone coming out with their head on straight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135750" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like this place. There's something familiar about it. I haven't been here, but I've seen it before... It belongs to the Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lot of stories about the Imperial Guard back in the army. They scared us more than Sith--ordinary people who could take out a full platoon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135752" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we could stop the fighting, I'd walk through these ruins for days. Look at them... and yet the Empire uses them to train.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Real guerilla warfare is bad enough. Faking it on a training facility using live ammo? Just a little bit worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135754" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire says one Imperial Guardsman is worth a hundred ordinary troops. Looks like the Revanites got a discount.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135755" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Guardsmen must know every meter of these ruins. Didn't save them from the Revanites. Stay alert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135756" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you'd told me as a little girl I'd one day visit the Imperial Guard training grounds, I'd have expected it to be the highlight of my life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis: The structural integrity of Massassi is far superior to that of the baseline Sith species, master, but well within my favored target parameters.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135760" id2="17" version="1065353216">My tribe builds better villages. My tribe builds better defenses. But my people are much smaller. Maybe size and strength make creatures stupid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Massassi. One more of those things looks at me, and I will wear its tentacles around my fist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could all the Empire have become like the Massassi, if things had gone differently? Could we still become this way?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't wander off, okay? I would sort of rather not be left alone with the Massassi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135764" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad we're in a hurry. I'd like to watch these Massassi. See them live in the jungle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never thought much about becoming a human sacrifice before. Not something I had to worry about before we came here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135766" id2="17" version="1065353216">The creatures here--I want to hate them, but I can't. They were bred to be savage, raised in this culture. I pity them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135767" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are carvings of the Massassi in the Heritage Museum in Kaas City. Their savagery is great, but their blood is far purer than mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135768" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I have bad dreams about Korriban and scary monsters coming for me in jail? Those scary monsters pretty much look like Massassi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135769" id2="17" version="1065353216">After careful consideration, when it comes to getting to know the locals? I think I liked the Rishii better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135770" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is what you get when you're as obsessed with blood purity as the Empire. Kind of feel sorry for these guys.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135771" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Massassi--they're like Sith Purebloods, right? Guess we should feel lucky they're not all Force sensitive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135772" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you suppose the Massassi would do if they had ships and technology like us? Could they ever join the Republic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makes me feel a little better to think we'll never see these guys again after Yavin Four. We won't--right, Captain?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135774" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen friendlier welcomes from Trandoshan hunting parties. Let's not stick around too long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let these guys get close. They're strong enough to peel us out of our armor if we let 'em.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Evolutionarily speaking, the Massassi are fascinating. They were genetically altered from Sith, then naturally adapted to the jungle. Pity they won't consent to a study.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warning: The nearby temple is difficult to penetrate with sensors, master. I advise extreme caution.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1135800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great darkness is in the temple, Chief. I know this. You know this too. We go together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Old. Ugly. Smells like death. I'm sick of temples that remind me of growing up. What'll it take to blow it up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135802" id2="17" version="1065353216">The temple--we don't have the words for it. It crawls with shadow. It lives like night.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135803" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know, between Dromund Kaas and Oricon and Voss... I just can't look at a temple anymore without getting chills. Maybe this one's a nice temple?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135804" id2="17" version="1065353216">Temple looks old. But check the tracks. Lots of movement. Be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Few tonnes of detonite would do that place good. Assuming it even scratched the surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135806" id2="17" version="1065353216">The statue--I recognize Naga Sadow from my studies. He was a Dark Lord from the time of the Emperor. There must be power here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at that temple. Note the construction, the outer layout. It was built as more than a monument--it was built as a stronghold.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, I know that temple! I mean, I haven't been here before, but I swear I've stolen Sith-y things with pictures of it. Neat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoever that statue's of, I've got this weird feeling he wouldn't want us here. At least not without us tied up and turned on a spit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135810" id2="17" version="1065353216">That temple--it reminds me a lot of Korriban. But it's quieter. Just as old, but... not awake yet. Not completely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135811" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you could tell me the history of that temple, Jedi, but I'm going to stop you right now. I really don't want to know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135812" id2="17" version="1065353216">That temple--it gives me a terrible feeling. I don't think you should go in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135813" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd think someone would have looted that statue by now, all the centuries it's been there. Really worries me it looks good as new.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135814" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's something wrong with that temple, Captain. I can't explain what or how I know--it's just wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135815" id2="17" version="1065353216">That temple's a death trap. Funnel invaders right in and slaughter them. Who was expecting a war on Yavin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1135816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, I find I'm slightly hyperventilating when I look at that statue. It may be a cultural fear response. If so, I apologize.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
