<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>36</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/bronze/republic/a_lesson_is_learned/doctor_everis.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289432" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once my clearance goes through, I'll be leaving. I'll tell everyone what you did--thank you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your colleagues are safe. They're on their way back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289435" id2="17" version="1065353216">They survived? Thank you, Master Jedi, thank you!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, so much--I see why they call you the Republic's finest.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289439" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're alive? I--I can't believe it. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289441" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you. All of you. I--I don't know what else to say.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289443" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once I've seen the others, I should... leave Belsavis. Tell someone what I did here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take this. I made it to keep myself safe. At least one of my designs should do some good in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you find my colleagues yet? They might not have much time!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis is a place of retribution and justice, isn't it? Finding ways to make things right....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you see those horrific experiments in the main wing? Forcing sentient beings to fight one another? I designed those experiments. Me!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289452" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was told they were in the name of science. I believed the lie. And now my colleagues are the ones suffering for my foolishness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you were deceived, but you must have known this was wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289453" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're still responsible.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing is achieved without sacrifice. I kept telling myself that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our actions are dependent on the truths we're given.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lies give rise to mistakes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289457" id2="17" version="1065353216">If your team is in trouble, come up with a plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then make it right.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289458" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I can think is that it should have been me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whenever something's done &quot;in the name of science,&quot; it always means trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never trust scientists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289461" id2="17" version="1065353216">What did you do, exactly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289462" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're hysterical.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289463" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Senator ordered it. Run combat tests among the prisoners, gather data.... Turned out to be a sadistic whim of his.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those who survived the &quot;Noble Focus&quot; experiments--that I devised!--were never the same. A group of Gand was driven utterly insane.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289467" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gand broke out yesterday, hunting the one responsible. I--I would have accepted their punishment, but they took my colleagues instead! Please--someone has to help them!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289468" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="289469" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's hundreds of soldiers here, couldn't they mount a rescue?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289469" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about Republic support?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289470" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the prison break and the Empire to handle? They can't. I tried.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289472" id2="17" version="1065353216">The security footage shows those Gand dragging my friends to one of those old vaults. Down to the lower levels, I think.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, save them. Stop the Gand. Don't let anyone else suffer because of my stupidity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="289476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not me. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289477" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many more have to die because of my stupidity?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="289479" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's all my fault. Why do I never think?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
