<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>14</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/uprisings/makeb/destroyer_of_worlds/transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trouble on Makeb, Commander. A Jedi Master named Adelade dug up some kind of monstrosity buried deep inside the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217671" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Makeb crisis has been contained. Good work, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217701" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oggurobb will examine what's left of the &quot;Gethul&quot; abomination. If it corrupted Adelade's mind, we need to figure out how to guard against it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Either way, you did what was necessary. The Jedi had to be neutralized. Thanks to you, Makeb is safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217704" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're approaching the dig site. Protect the payload, and bury that monster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217705" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful. Adelade's followers will stop at nothing to destroy the payload.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Secure the payload and deliver the explosives to Adelade's monstrosity. Makeb is counting on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217709" id2="17" version="1065353216">More importantly, you exterminated the Jedi and blasted his abomination into a puddle of soup. Decisive victories like this make the galaxy fear the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217722" id2="17" version="1065353216">They call this abomination &quot;Gethul.&quot; We're talking giant tentacles, blaster-proof skin, and enough strength to destabilize the planet's core. We've never seen anything like it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217724" id2="17" version="1065353216">Adelade and his followers are trying to wake Gethul. You need to stop them. Deliver an explosive payload into the jaws of the beast--and blow it sky high.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217934" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see you, interlopers. Gethul sees you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Engineer Penzaren has stopped the interlopers! Gethul sings his praise!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Skurr! Velloc! Fill the interlopers with light.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1217953" id2="17" version="1065353216">His song fills us with light and calls for this world's demise. You can't stop his awakening. No one can.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
