<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>42</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x2/raid/explosive_conflict/republic/av9r.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005851" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am pleased to report the technician has failed to permanently deactivate me. Also, congratulations on your successful mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1005854" id2="17" version="1065353216">As the Supreme Chancellor indicated in her message, your presence is required immediately at the main fleet. I'll deal with this electronic butcher.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005857" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ow! Don't touch that! Do you even know the difference between a servomotor and a vocabulator?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive my outburst. It appears I am suffering a mobility impairment. This &quot;technician&quot; has been sent to repair me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005861" id2="17" version="1065353216">But my personal health is no burden for a renowned Jedi hero. Stand by for a coded priority message from Supreme Chancellor Saresh....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005862" id2="17" version="1065353216">But my troubles are not yours, honored Jedi Council member. I have a priority coded message to you from Supreme Chancellor Saresh....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005863" id2="17" version="1065353216">But that is not your concern, Major. Supreme Chancellor Saresh has authorized me to display a coded priority message for you. Initiating....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005864" id2="17" version="1065353216">But my personal misfortunes do not concern a licensed privateer. Please stand by for a coded priority message from Supreme Chancellor Saresh....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005865" id2="17" version="1065353216">But my malfunctions should not trouble heroes of the Republic. Please stand by for a coded priority message from Supreme Chancellor Saresh....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005866" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've fixed droids before--and not always with my lightsaber. Want me to take a look?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005866" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could try to repair you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005867" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could never impose on you for such a trivial task. I will have to trust this fat-fingered fool to not deactivate me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005868" id2="17" version="1065353216">We all suffer glitches now and again. Carrying on despite them is the mark of a dedicated droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005868" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admire your professionalism.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005869" id2="17" version="1065353216">You flatter me, Master Jedi. I am saving this moment to my permanent data records.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005870" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not gonna malfunction and go on a rampage, are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005870" id2="17" version="1065353216">As long as you don't blow up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005871" id2="17" version="1065353216">I certainly hope not. That would be a horrific breach of protocol.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005872" id2="17" version="1065353216">No rush--I can wait until you're fully repaired. I'm charging by the hour.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take your time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005873" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Supreme Chancellor was quite adamant that her message be delivered promptly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shouldn't a top secret message have a bit more privacy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should the technician hear it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005875" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can assure you this so-called gentlebeing does not comprehend a single word of Basic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thing the Republic can afford top-of-the-line protocol droids for its most sensitive communications.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get on with it, pile of junk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005877" id2="17" version="1065353216">I may not be able to walk, but my sarcasm filters are fully functional.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005879" id2="17" version="1065353216">As one of the Republic's most reliable operatives, your presence is required at our main fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005881" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have been betrayed by our own forces on Denova. Resources critical to our war effort have been seized by mercenaries collaborating with Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005883" id2="17" version="1065353216">The situation demands a retaliatory response. Captain Exteen of the battle cruiser Vanguard's Blade will brief you on Denova and the traitors occupying it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005884" id2="17" version="1065353216">What makes this planet important enough the Supreme Chancellor wants me to go in?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005884" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about Denova.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005885" id2="17" version="1065353216">The planet's crust contains vast deposits of a substance used in the manufacture of high explosives. A vital strategic resource.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005886" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are we going up against here? Who betrayed us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are these traitors?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005887" id2="17" version="1065353216">That information is above my security clearance, but if you're being called to action, the enemy must be quite powerful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005888" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it's payback the Supreme Chancellor wants, I'll get it for her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Retaliation is my specialty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005889" id2="17" version="1065353216">Considering your past record, I have no doubt of that statement.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1005891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ow! You fool, you've adjusted the wrong setting! Listen to me--I sound like a Hutt breathing underwater!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1005893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please accept my most profound apologies. Rendezvous with the main fleet and meet Captain Exteen immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please do not distract my technician. He is incompetent enough as it is. Ow! Stop that!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
