<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>158</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x2/raid/explosive_conflict/republic/captain_exteen.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005900" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been an honor serving with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005904" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain... Supreme Chancellor... Kephess is dead and his army is broken. Denova is back under Republic control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005905" id2="17" version="1065353216">You delivered a message to everyone who thinks they can defy us without consequence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005907" id2="17" version="1065353216">We monitored the battle transmissions. Kephess kept referring to his &quot;masters.&quot; Any clue who he was talking about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoever these &quot;masters&quot; are, they weren't on Denova.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005908" id2="17" version="1065353216">None.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005909" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have intel on forces invading Hutt Space. Could this be related?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Follow a puppet's strings far enough and there's usually a Sith holding them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could this be a Sith plot?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005911" id2="17" version="1065353216">It would explain a great deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005912" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't take his ranting too seriously. For all we know, he was just hearing voices in his head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005912" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Trandoshan was insane.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regardless, you've done us a great service by eliminating him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Empty victories, celebrated by dead heroes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005917" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic mistakes nightfall for dawn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005919" id2="17" version="1065353216">The six herald rebirth. Of power... order... domination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Submit, and be spared. Resist, and be swept aside. Choose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005922" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi will never submit--and we won't be swept aside. We will defend the Republic to our dying breath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005922" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've picked the wrong fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your air grows thin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your negotiating skills leave much to be desired. May I offer you some instruction?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005924" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's no choice at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your taunts ring hollow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005926" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad never backs down from a fight--and those robes look plenty flammable. I'd say the choice is yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005926" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not going to happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Empty-headed threats do not amuse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005928" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;We will crush you,&quot; blah, blah, blah. Don't you Sith ever get sick of hearing yourselves talk?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better idea: You shut up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cries in the darkness, mistaken for bravery. Fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005930" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you get in here? Identify yourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005931" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are fear. Horror. Doom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005932" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you put it like that, there's only one response.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005932" id2="17" version="1065353216">Choose this. [Attack]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005935" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are prisoners no more. Free of the Republic. Free of the Empire. Both will fall before the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1005937" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will find you again, Republic children. Next time, you will die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005939" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never felt fear like that before, not even as a Padawan. Who were those people? How is Kephess alive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005941" id2="17" version="1065353216">They appeared in my Senate chamber, as well. Security systems didn't register their presence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005943" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we know their names. The Dread Masters were powerful Sith serving the Emperor. They laid waste to whole fleets during the last war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005945" id2="17" version="1065353216">We imprisoned them on Belsavis. When the Empire stormed our maximum security wing, the Dread Masters broke free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005946" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're no longer serving the Empire. They want the galaxy all for themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005946" id2="17" version="1065353216">But now they're on their own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005947" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't have this. I want them dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Escaping their cells is one thing--how did they get off the planet? We had ships in orbit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005949" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did they get away?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005950" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you just experienced, these aren't ordinary Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005952" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imprisonment is no longer an option. Time to kill that scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005952" id2="17" version="1065353216">This time, we execute them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005953" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't agree more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005955" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm calling an emergency meeting of High Command. When the Dread Masters resurface, we'll be ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until then, remain vigilant. I will contact you when we know more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005959" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should go. I'll coordinate our forces landing on Denova. We're going to need that baradium.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005963" id2="17" version="1065353216">The shuttle to Denova is standing by. We'll monitor your progress as best we can. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Exteen, Jedi Knight and commanding officer of the Vanguard's Blade. Welcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005968" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a genuine honor. I flew bombing runs on Darth Angral's battle cruiser when he attacked Tython. That's a fight I'll never forget.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005969" id2="17" version="1065353216">There were far too few Jedi starfighters in the sky that day. The Force was with you to survive against those odds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to meet a fellow veteran.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005970" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you boarded his ship, Darth Angral didn't stand a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005972" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was far from Tython when that battle occurred. When this mission is over, perhaps you two can tell me about it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005972" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to hear about this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005973" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd be honored, Master. I'd just arrived for my final trials the day you saved Tython's ancient Forge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005975" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did a Jedi fighter pilot wind up in charge of a Republic cruiser? Did you even go through officer training school?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting career you've had.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Piloting a chair strapped to a bunch of bombs... that takes a special kind of crazy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fighter jockeys amuse me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005977" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was much worse than it sounds, Captain--and it's a pleasure to meet you. Master Sumalee praised your actions on Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, it's an honor. I'd just arrived on Tython when you saved the ancient Forge from Nalen Raloch. Your trials inspired all the Padawans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005980" id2="17" version="1065353216">So much has happened since those days. My battle with Nalen Raloch feels like another life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005980" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was a long time ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Masters at the temple still talk about what you did then--and everything since.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005983" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's hard to believe the Jedi trials were ever our biggest worry. Of course, neither of ours were exactly by the book....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005983" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've all come a long way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005984" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surrounded by heroes. I flew bombing runs on Darth Angral's battle cruiser over Tython. Quite a day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005986" id2="17" version="1065353216">You Jedi have all the luck. For my first mission, my CO sold me out to the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your trials sound easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005987" id2="17" version="1065353216">You remade Havoc Squad into the greatest special ops team in the Republic, Major. I've tried to follow your example.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005989" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know what half those words meant, but you sure make them sound fancy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005989" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose I'm impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, it's a pleasure. Master Sumalee told me about your heroism on Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major, it's an honor to serve Havoc Squad. When I assumed command, I learned everything about military service by studying your career.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Datapads won't teach you how to be a soldier. You only learn that in the field.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you didn't learn much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, sir. That's why I logged two hundred deep recon missions before accepting this promotion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005996" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's rare to see a Jedi focused on the art of war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005996" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seem right at home here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005997" id2="17" version="1065353216">I flew bombing runs on Darth Angral's cruiser when he attacked Tython. Your victory over him inspired me to follow this path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005999" id2="17" version="1065353216">The major is impressive, but I hope we won't need his expertise. Peace should always be a Jedi's first path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005999" id2="17" version="1065353216">War is never our best choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006000" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you learned saving the ancient Forge, peace is only possible when both sides pursue it. I'm honored to meet you, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006002" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's great, kid--but there's more to this galaxy than uniforms and salutes. I'll show you how to retire a rich man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now learn from me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unnecessary, Captain--but it's a pleasure. I heard of your heroism on Corellia from Master Sumalee.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006005" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're becoming a celebrity even in Jedi circles, Captain. Master Sumalee can't stop talking about you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006006" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew she had a thing for me. Even Jedi women find me irresistible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admit it. She thinks I'm cute.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006007" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd have to take that up with her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006009" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should call her. She still owes me a drink for what I did on Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006009" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's my kind of Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006010" id2="17" version="1065353216">She mentioned that, too. Master Sumalee is... unconventional.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gaining a Jedi Master's respect is no small feat, Captain. I trust you achieved that through legitimate means?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive, if true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006013" id2="17" version="1065353216">The hero of Tython. I flew bombing runs against Darth Angral's cruiser when he attacked our homeworld. Never thought I'd meet you in person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let the flattery go to your head, Captain. Jedi are above hero worship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi don't have celebrities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006016" id2="17" version="1065353216">That isn't entirely true. I was a Padawan when you saved the ancient Forge on Tython, Master--and I'm truly honored to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006018" id2="17" version="1065353216">I love going on missions with celebrities. They're great at drawing fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006018" id2="17" version="1065353216">The captain can take point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major, it's an honor to meet you in person. Your mission records were required reading when I joined the military.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006021" id2="17" version="1065353216">When High Command said special reinforcements were coming, I wasn't expecting anyone so high profile. Your accomplishments are legendary to my troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006022" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just doing what I can to win this war. Becoming a celebrity wasn't part of the plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006022" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to flatter me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regardless, it'll be an honor to see you in action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006025" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's an honor just to serve. We're all heroes in this war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006025" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to flatter me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006026" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know how you maintain that humility, considering all you've done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006028" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't realize Jedi were serving in the Republic military these days. How does that work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006028" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a Jedi soldier?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006029" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm part of a new program initiated by Chancellor Saresh to integrate the Jedi Order and Republic military.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006031" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not here to reminisce. What's the situation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006031" id2="17" version="1065353216">No time for pleasantries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006032" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stand by. We're making the jump to hyperspace. I'll continue your briefing on arrival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Launch delta wing. Initiate aerial reconnaissance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006036" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Denova. Republic scouts discovered it last year. An unremarkable planet, except for its vast deposits of baradium--a key component in high-yield explosives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three months ago, the Empire discovered Denova's location, learned of the baradium deposits, and invaded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006039" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assume this substance we're fighting over is rare enough to warrant a major assault?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Baradium must be worth a lot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our stockpile of rockets and torpedoes is running out. We can't resupply our ground and space forces without more baradium. Neither can the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006042" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't see any Imperial warships in orbit. If the enemy is still on Denova, they must have landed some heavy forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the invaders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006043" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire lacks enough ships to control the airspace--so they landed an entire armored battalion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006045" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Supreme Chancellor took her sweet time sending reinforcements. Why the holdup?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006045" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're late to the party.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until last week, we had defenders holding off the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006048" id2="17" version="1065353216">We couldn't spare our own forces to secure Denova, so we contracted a Trandoshan mercenary army: the Warstalkers. Tough warriors. Never lost a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006050" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Warstalkers' leader, Kephess, has honored every contract he's taken--he's no Imperial sympathizer. His betrayal caught us completely off guard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006051" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mercenaries work for the highest bidder. Obviously, the Empire offered Kephess more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006051" id2="17" version="1065353216">It shouldn't have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006052" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Warstalkers aren't working for the Empire. They've gone rogue--and taken our enemies with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006054" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was there anything in Kephess's background to suggest he'd turn against us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006054" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do we know about Kephess?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006055" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic doesn't normally hire mercenaries to defend its territory, but Kephess had a reputation for loyalty. We don't know what changed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006057" id2="17" version="1065353216">None of those details matter. Kephess stabbed us in the back, and his Warstalkers will pay the price with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006057" id2="17" version="1065353216">All traitors will die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006058" id2="17" version="1065353216">We aren't just facing traitorous mercenaries down there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kephess convinced the Imperial forces to desert the Empire and side with him. They've combined armies and declared Denova independent territory.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1006062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic children... you could not hold Denova--and Imperial fools will not take it. My masters gave me all I need to destroy you. Stay away, or die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like Kephess isn't as trustworthy as he was cracked up to be--and he's taking orders from someone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006063" id2="17" version="1065353216">So much for loyalty to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006064" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the strangest part. We've monitored Denova's communications since the invasion. This was the only transmission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006065" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who does Kephess serve? The Empire? The Hutts?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006065" id2="17" version="1065353216">His masters?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006066" id2="17" version="1065353216">No idea. We initially thought he was referring to the Trandoshan &quot;Scorekeeper&quot; deity, but this is something else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006067" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've met some overconfident fools in my time, but he is by far the ugliest. I'll enjoy putting him out of the galaxy's misery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't count on it, freak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006068" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think that's the reaction High Command was hoping for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006070" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Supreme Chancellor's orders are clear: Take down Kephess and neutralize his army. The Republic needs Denova and its baradium stores.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006072" id2="17" version="1065353216">A strike shuttle's waiting for you. This vessel and its fighters will provide support. May the Force be with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006076" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm overseeing a delicate op. Excuse me.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
