<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>16</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x2/raid/explosive_conflict/republic/transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025303" id2="17" version="1065353216">The walkers will secure a landing zone on the beach--you push ahead towards Kephess's camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025305" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Captain Dennik. Picking up some drouks moving in your direction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025307" id2="17" version="1065353216">The main force is engaging Kephess's troops in the valley. See if you can find an alternate route through the mines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025309" id2="17" version="1065353216">Double check your targets. Those baradium deposits pack a major punch!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025311" id2="17" version="1065353216">The baradium is on the move. Probably heading for Kephess's base camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Dennik here. Enemy reinforcements closing on your position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kephess has set up a major baradium processing operation. Could be stocking up for a major galactic offensive!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025317" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperial defectors set up camp near the strip mines. Expect them to be heavily armed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025319" id2="17" version="1065353216">The defectors have set up defensive fortifications in your area. Watch for land mines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025321" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kephess is targeting your position with heavy artillery! We'll try to draw some of the fire with a frontal assault on his camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take out the Imperial commander! If you can get to his shuttle it'll take you right to Kephess's camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025325" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're keeping the pressure on Kephess at the main front. See if you can find an alternate route to get to his camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Picking up heavy static in your area. Losing your signal. If you keep going you're on your own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025329" id2="17" version="1065353216">We thought we'd lost you--good to see you back on the grid! See if you can flank Kephess's camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone needs to take out that shield generator!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1025333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Orbital bombardment is under way--clear out while you still can!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
