<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>18</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/taris/multi/shared/data_recordings.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197644" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Sannus Lorrick: log entry 12-46. Progress on the enhanced strain of the rakghoul virus is slow, but I will not be daunted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197646" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have spent too long in exile. I will return to the worlds I once called home as a conqueror and a hero!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197648" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those who cast me out will bow down before me. They will cry for mercy, and be rewarded with death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197652" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Sannus Lorrick: log entry 13-22. I've modified the rakghoul virus to cross the species barrier--a monumental breakthrough!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197654" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mutative properties have been enhanced as well. The newly transformed creatures are stronger and more powerful than previous generations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even with their increased strength and aggression, they remain responsive to my commands. My work is nearing completion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Addy Ingrol, log entry 13-44. I and the other assistants have noticed some disturbing results.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Current test subjects show very different characteristics than those originally captured on Taris. It's almost as if someone has been tampering with the specimens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197664" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Lorrick believes the changes are due to the virus's natural adaptability. If he's right, our efforts to find a cure will be even harder than we thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Sannus Lorrick: log entry 14-08. The modified virus is ready for field testing in the Tion Hegemony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197670" id2="17" version="1065353216">The first few worlds will be wiped out. Their populations will become rakghouls under my control, swelling the ranks of my armies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197672" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the hegemony secured, I will spread my campaign world by world until I sweep away the war-torn tatters of both the Republic and the Empire!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Sannus Lorrick: log entry 14-11. Preliminary results from the hegemony have exceeded even my expectations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197678" id2="17" version="1065353216">The success has led me to re-evaluate the virus. I understand now that it is neither a disease, nor a weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197680" id2="17" version="1065353216">The exposed become bigger, faster, stronger--genetically improved in every way! The virus is evolution perfected; it must be spread across the entire galaxy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Addy Ingrol, supplemental log update. Doctor Lorrick has gone completely mad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197686" id2="17" version="1065353216">We realize now he was never working on a cure for the virus. His work is an abomination; we have to stop him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197688" id2="17" version="1065353216">After I delete his files, we will try to take him into custody. I fear he may oppose us with violence, but we have no other choice.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
