<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>121</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/flashpoint/shared/taris/multi/shared/pilot.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197976" id2="17" version="1065353216">You almost done here? Sooner I can get off Kaon, the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197978" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not trying to be pushy or anything, but I'm ready to leave whenever you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197984" id2="17" version="1065353216">About time the cavalry showed up. Been hiding out here in the spaceport for days. Name's Melarra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197986" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're probably going to check the records and see it was my ship that brought the rakghouls here. But it wasn't my fault!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197988" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had no idea those things were in my cargo hold. I'm as much a victim as anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't you feel bad about all the suffering you caused? Did you even try to help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197989" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't sound very sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Helping others is your thing, Jedi, not mine. Besides, this wasn't my fault. Blame the man who hired me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197992" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fact that you survived when everyone else died suggests you were anticipating something like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197992" id2="17" version="1065353216">You had to suspect something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not like this. But I admit my guard was up. Always a good idea when you're working for someone who carries a grudge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only an idiot would take a commission without knowing what she's carrying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not much of a pilot, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Times are tough. I take whatever work I can get, and the man who hired me doesn't like questions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197998" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have some secret strategy for dealing with the rakghouls?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="197998" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm impressed you survived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="197999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find a good place to hide while they're chomping on someone else. You want more than that, ask the man who hired me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your actions resulted in millions of deaths! Why shouldn't I execute you on the spot?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198001" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should kill you right now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kill me and you'll never know what happened here. So simmer down and listen to my side of the story.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198004" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't judge you without giving you a chance to explain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, I'm listening....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198005" id2="17" version="1065353216">You heard of Doctor Lorrick? He's a member of the Thirty-seven Families from Deservo. Bitter rivals of the Tion ruling family.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lorrick instructed me to fly to Kaon. Rakghouls burst out of my cargo hold the second I touched down. Blood and bodies everywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198008" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were still inside your shuttle. You could have just taken off when the attack began.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why didn't you fly away?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Figured Lorrick was expecting that. Thought he might have booby-trapped the shuttle. So I slipped out and hid in the spaceport.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kaon isn't the only planet to be overrun by this plague. Did you land anywhere else first?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Other worlds were infected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198012" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wasn't the only pilot he hired. He sent a bunch of us out. Probably figured none of us would make it back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most rakghouls are little more than beasts. This plan required patience and timing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakghouls aren't that smart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198015" id2="17" version="1065353216">They didn't attack like wild animals. Seemed like they had a plan. Like they were following orders... and searching for me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198017" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last thing Lorrick wanted was for me to survive. Because I can tell you where to find him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198018" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're going to help me stop him to make amends for your role in this tragedy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198018" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you do feel guilty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198019" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? No! This is about revenge. Lorrick double-crossed me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198021" id2="17" version="1065353216">How much is this info going to cost me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198021" id2="17" version="1065353216">In exchange for what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a thing. Look, I'm in trouble here. I figure if I come clean, maybe I can earn some goodwill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me his location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where is he?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198025" id2="17" version="1065353216">The shuttle departed from a remote island on Ord Mantell. Lorrick has a secret base there. But that's all I know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, I came clean. Told you what I know in good faith. So you going to get me out of here now, or what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198028" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were nothing but a pawn in Lorrick's scheme. And you did provide valuable information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198028" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess we can help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad we're on the same page. Tell you what--just drop me off at the nearest uninfected planet, and I'll figure it out from there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198030" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to verify you're not carrying the plague, first. A shuttle will pick you up when I'm done here and take you for testing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198030" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if you're infected?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. Poked and prodded by medical droids. Beats the alternative, I guess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic SIS needs to know everything you can tell them about Doctor Lorrick. A shuttle will pick you up when I'm done here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198033" id2="17" version="1065353216">We still need to question you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic custody, huh? Guess it's better than the alternative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198036" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll send a shuttle to pick you up when I'm done here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just do me a favor--don't wait too long to come and get me. I've spent more than enough time on this rock.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198039" id2="17" version="1065353216">You knew Lorrick was dangerous when you agreed to work for him. Now millions are dead. Their blood is on your hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198039" id2="17" version="1065353216">You deserve death. [Kill her]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198040" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I didn't... I was just... no!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hold on, hold on, hold on. Don't shoot. Not a rakghoul. Just a harmless shuttle pilot. Name's Melarra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, I need to get off this world. And I know how this whole rakghoul outbreak started. So maybe we can swing a deal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only a fool tries to bargain with the Emperor's Wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198049" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're playing a deadly game.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198050" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bargain? Who said anything about a bargain? My info's a gift! A gift to show my deep and sincere respect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198052" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's easy to make promises. Even easier to break them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198052" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're far too trusting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, I know how that goes. But I'm out of options here. I gotta trust you, or I'm done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198055" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't make deals. I make corpses. Understand?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198055" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me or you die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198056" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh. Okay. New plan: I tell you everything I know and nobody gets hurt. Especially me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Either give me the info now, or I set up a little session with the Imperial interrogators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198058" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can force you to talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198059" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interrogators? What? No. We don't need them. I'll just tell you what I know. Friend to friend, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me what you know, and I'll make sure you get off of Kaon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. Okay. Yeah. I knew we could work this out. We're all reasonable folk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198064" id2="17" version="1065353216">I already had one person I met on this world turn into a rakghoul right in front of me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you infected?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198065" id2="17" version="1065353216">N-n-n-n-no way. I'm clean. So don't get all nervous and take me out if I sneeze, okay? Just listen to what I have to say.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198067" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, uh... these rakghouls? Yeah. I brought them. On my shuttle. But I didn't know what I was doing!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198069" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just a pilot. I was hired to fly here. My boss is the one you want, not me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why didn't the rakghouls kill you along with everybody else? Do you have some kind of protection?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198070" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you survive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198071" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just better at hiding, I guess. Boss probably figured the rakghouls would get me, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198073" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're basically responsible for millions of deaths. Doesn't that bother you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198073" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't seem too upset.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure. I mean, better them than me. But it's not like I'm a monster. My boss, on the other hand....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your boss's name. Now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who do you work for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198077" id2="17" version="1065353216">You heard of Doctor Lorrick? He's a member of the Thirty-seven families, the main political rivals of the royal family.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198079" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hired me to make a delivery to Kaon. Soon as I touched down, the rakghouls came pouring out. It was ugly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198080" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were still inside your shuttle. Why didn't you just take off?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198080" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why didn't you fly away?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198081" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pretty obvious Lorrick wanted me dead. Figured he booby-trapped the shuttle, so I jumped out of the cockpit and hid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198083" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rakghouls waited patiently until you landed. Doctor Lorrick must have found a way to make them follow orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those rakghouls were trained.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198084" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could be right. They weren't acting like mindless beasts during the attack. Seemed like they had a purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Lorrick obviously didn't want anyone to survive the attack. He's trying to cover his tracks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198086" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're lucky to be alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad for him I got a heightened survival sense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198089" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lorrick double-crossed me. Now I get to return the favor. He's hiding out at a secret base on Ord Mantell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198091" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, uh... that's about all I know. Now, you ready to get me off this rock?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198092" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've outlived your usefulness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198092" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather you die. [Kill her]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198093" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I told you everything I--ah. Now I see the problem. Damn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198097" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your information was quite valuable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198097" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've earned it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198098" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad we're on the same page. Tell you what--just drop me off at the nearest uninfected planet, and I'll figure it out from there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198099" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to verify you're not carrying the plague, first. A shuttle will pick you up when I'm done here and take you for testing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198099" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if you're infected?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198100" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. Poked and prodded by medical droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess it's better than being left here with the rakghouls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198104" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire needs to know everything you can tell them about Doctor Lorrick. A shuttle will pick you up when I'm done here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198104" id2="17" version="1065353216">We still need to question you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198105" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't realize an Imperial interrogation was part of the deal. Guess I'll have to tell my story again, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just--tell them to go easy on me. I've already told you everything I know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198109" id2="17" version="1065353216">And make sure they let me go when they're done. I don't want to &quot;disappear,&quot; if you catch my drift.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198111" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll send a shuttle to pick you up when I'm done here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="198111" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198112" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay. Great. Wasn't sure you'd keep up your end of the deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="198114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to know the Empire can be trusted. I'll keep that in mind if I'm ever looking for work.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
