<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>24</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_1/hitting_the_hutts/fingers_holoterminal.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shalim, come in. The Regulators' weapon caches are all destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011239" id2="17" version="1065353216">Outstanding! I hope you're ready for more--we've detected an army of war droids massing for an attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011241" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hutt engineers just installed a light bridge to access the ark construction site. The path leads directly through my plantation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011243" id2="17" version="1065353216">If those war droids make it across that bridge, they'll slaughter everyone in their path--including us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011244" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Hutts can set up a light bridge, we can take it down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1011244" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'll disable the bridge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011245" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had something slightly more destructive in mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011247" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said the war droids are already in place. Why haven't they moved in?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1011247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why haven't they attacked?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011248" id2="17" version="1065353216">We think they're awaiting orders from the Regulator Command center. We're still hunting for that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011250" id2="17" version="1065353216">Giant portable platforms for moving huge numbers? I can't think of anyone who might need something like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1011250" id2="17" version="1065353216">Light bridges sound useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011251" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were planning to set up light bridges to evacuate our citizens to the ark. The Hutts beat us to the idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011253" id2="17" version="1065353216">The war droids are holding position for now, but you could lure them out by transmitting false orders from the mercenary army's comm towers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011255" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once the droids are halfway across the light bridge, you could deactivate it. Drop the whole army into the depths.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011256" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those droids will spend the rest of this fight seven kilometers down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1011256" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011257" id2="17" version="1065353216">At the rate the planet's collapsing, they won't have time to rust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011259" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a waste of perfectly good droids. Is there any way to reprogram them to fight for us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1011259" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't we just reprogram them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011260" id2="17" version="1065353216">The master control is out of our reach. There simply isn't time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Droids make hilarious noises when they're destroyed. Too bad we won't be able to hear them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1011262" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm going to enjoy this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1011263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Slice into the mercenary comm towers, transmit the false marching orders and deactivate the light bridge at the perfect moment. Good luck!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
