<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>32</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_1/hitting_the_hutts/light_bridge_controls.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012825" id2="17" version="1065353216">The war droid army is gone for good. The Regulators will think twice before setting foot on that light bridge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012826" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the cost per unit of those war droids. Between them and the weapons you destroyed, the Regulators are over three hundred million credits in the red.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012827" id2="17" version="1065353216">They need to learn that working for the Hutts will always be a losing proposition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1012827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Serves them right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's drive the point home, shall we?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012830" id2="17" version="1065353216">If all they care about is money, there has to be a credit figure where retreat becomes the better option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1012830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe they'll finally give up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012831" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our foes appear determined to throw good money after bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012833" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't be happy until we make the billion mark. What else can we blow up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1012833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hit them again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012834" id2="17" version="1065353216">We finally tracked down the main mercenary base: a floating battle platform called the Storm Carrier. Vice Commandant Grevin, the mercenary leader, is gathering troops there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012836" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't let Grevin's forces reach the ark. The only way to stop the Storm Carrier is by overloading its power reactors to meltdown.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012837" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we eliminate the Storm Carrier and its commander, the remaining Regulators will have to abandon their attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1012837" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll force a surrender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Strike hard enough, and even their Hutt masters will feel the sting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012840" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Storm Carrier would make a powerful defense against the Hutts. Is there no way to preserve it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1012840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destruction seems wasteful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012841" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know Grevin. He'll destroy the Storm Carrier himself before letting it be captured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Neutralize every merc in our way and neutralize their battle platform. Standard Havoc op.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1012843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sabotage and cripple. Easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have yet to see anything you don't do well, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012846" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could sure use a floating battle platform. Too bad Regulator stink never washes out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1012846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pity to waste a good ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012847" id2="17" version="1065353216">Honestly, it's a hideous-looking thing. You deserve something far more stylish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should we eliminate Vice Commandant Grevin, or is he worth more as a prisoner?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1012849" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do we do about Grevin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012850" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grevin knows the Hutts won't tolerate failure. I doubt he'll let himself be captured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you checked in with Foreman Tiero? Is the ark secure?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1012852" id2="17" version="1065353216">How's the ark holding up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Safe for now, but only if you hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sending you the Storm Carrier's coordinates. Our scouts report there's a Regulator shuttle near your position. You can fly it directly to the enemy and take them completely by surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1012860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything's riding on this. May fortune smile on us all.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
