<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>58</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/world/loudest_bait/foreman_meropta.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our crews will be on it, as soon as they've sobered up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546431" id2="17" version="1065353216">The lake team said they heard you at work. Given the size of those blasts, I'm surprised we didn't down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any problems detonating those bombs?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546434" id2="17" version="1065353216">No trouble. It's more fun than trying to defuse them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546434" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546435" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't know. Sounds like your life is a bit more exciting than mine. But there's good news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546437" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's done. I need payment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, hey, no problem. I just wanted to give the good news first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546440" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I got bit by the filthiest mouth this side of Nar Shaddaa.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546440" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still hurt from the bites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546441" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, you'll want to disinfect that before the rotting starts. But there's good news!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546443" id2="17" version="1065353216">I told the Republic the swamp is clear, and they instantly gave the go. No more bureaucratic boondoggle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, we'll double-time it until the pipeline is done. Those colonists are going to feel a lot better when they can afford to shower.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember, those demolition charges won't kill the tremor maws, but that doesn't mean you can stand next to one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546448" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're here from Republic Command, don't worry, we got the message. It's too dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546450" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if you're from the union, same thing. None of my men are working as long as those tremor maws are in the lake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546451" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know what a tremor maw is, but it doesn't sound good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tremor maw?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Swamp lizards the size of a speeder. We tried to build a pipeline to the lake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546454" id2="17" version="1065353216">You try and get the colonists a little fresh water and what happens? Deaths, dismemberments and your project shut down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546456" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not involved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546457" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess so. You wouldn't believe how many people they've sent to check on us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546459" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the lake got to do with this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546459" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't see a lake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some colonies and survey camps are running out of fresh water, so we were building a pipeline from the north lake down to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546462" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the machinery attracted tremor maws. One minute we're enjoying the scenery, and the next, screaming and death and the project shut down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546464" id2="17" version="1065353216">We exploded a few demolition charges to scare the maws off, but it just makes them want to fight. Our blasts were more like bait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you need me to get you back on track?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546465" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you need me, I'm there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546466" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you think you can kill these things, you're welcome to try. The demolition charges are still set up in the lake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546468" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic outpost has soldiers. Can they spare a few to kill these things?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't the army kill them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546469" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd think, but they're the ones who told us to wait. They're exploring options. Flying water in, filters, moisture vaporators, it's nonsense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546471" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pipeline's our only long-term bet. Everything else, colonists can't afford. They'll start deserting soon. No money, no colony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546473" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's frustrating because the charges were already laid. You could flush out every tremor maw in that lake if you wanted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546474" id2="17" version="1065353216">How long can the colonists last without fresh water?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will the colonists be okay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546475" id2="17" version="1065353216">No colonist can afford water that's flown in for long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546477" id2="17" version="1065353216">And it's become a pattern--the money dries up, people leave and rakghouls move into the ghost town.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546479" id2="17" version="1065353216">What I wouldn't give for someone to just shoot those lizards. It's not like we ever removed the bait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546480" id2="17" version="1065353216">This colony won't fail on my watch. I'll let you put down that pipe safely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546480" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll remove the tremor maws.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546481" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wanted to say that up-front, but I didn't want to put pressure on a Jedi. It just ain't classy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546483" id2="17" version="1065353216">The demolition charges are in the lake. Set them to go and get way, way back. The blast will be big.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546485" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've dealt with more reptiles than I care to remember. I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha! That's what I like. The demolition charges should be easy to spot when you get to the lake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546488" id2="17" version="1065353216">You show me where these monsters live, and I'll show you where they die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Point me at them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that's how it's done! Head to the lake. We've got demolition charges in the water up there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546491" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could do it, but I have to work for a living, too. Understand?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546491" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll need compensation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you kidding? I learned budgeting on Hutta. We'll take care of you. Just get up to the lake where the demolition charges are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Obviously, when you key them in to blow, don't walk--run out of the blast radius. That stuff is construction-grade detonite.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then get ready for the fight of your life. Maws can bite through a gripper crane, let alone humanoids like us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="546498" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who am I going to get to kill these things, my union boys? Not likely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="546501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, we're not working. Tell me something I don't know.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
