<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>17</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/raid/shared/eternity_vault/eternity_vault_transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121710" id2="17" version="1065353216">They will not! I command them to know fear, to raise me to my throne! They cannot!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121713" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have waited twenty thousand years, but I will wait no longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121716" id2="17" version="1065353216">The blood of a lesser species.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your forces are lost!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Know now the face of my slaves. Know the army that was buried alongside me, to serve me unto death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121724" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you fall, it is they who will march upon the stars. They will reclaim my galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121727" id2="17" version="1065353216">They come marching, believing themselves equal to the army of ancients that chained me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121729" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I am not of their time. Their ancestors called me Soa, wrath and power, and knew fear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121731" id2="17" version="1065353216">For I ruled a thousand worlds, and Korriban was my crown, Korriban my cradle and my testing ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121734" id2="17" version="1065353216">My finest creation, machine of machines, metal enemies welded together and allied toward destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Silentior lived to obliterate the Rakata who opposed me, who did not realize I had risen above them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121738" id2="17" version="1065353216">It decimated armies, and it lives for destruction still.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hear it howl, for it was bred to scream, blood and fibers woven into a devouring beast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121743" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was Gharj whose claws scored the canals of Seylott; Gharj who consumed the natives of Alzoc, and was worshiped for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gharj whom the alchemists of a younger age sought to emulate, but all would fail. Look upon Gharj, and die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121748" id2="17" version="1065353216">They slay not knowing that I am the seed of destruction in their hearts. I am master and creator, what the galaxy fears.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="121751" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear them enter my domain, children unknowing. They will serve.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
