<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>37</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/bronze/the_face_merchants/security_officer_stansun.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic security owes you one. Without the Black Sun's clinic, criminals are stuck with the faces they've got.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689571" id2="17" version="1065353216">The clinic's not taking any more patients. And here are those records you wanted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect. With them, we can ID those face-swapping thugs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks again. If we had more Jedi like you working the streets, Black Sun would be a thing of the past.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689575" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice work, Lieutenant. Coruscant's going to be a cleaner place thanks to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689576" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for this. Closing that clinic's a big win for Republic security, and for the people of Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you bust the Black Sun clinic, we'll round up the patients and lock them up for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689581" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a pleasure, Master Jedi. I'm Officer Stansun, Republic security. Trying to keep peace and order down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, Lieutenant. Good to see a fellow defender of the peace. I'm Officer Stansun, Republic security.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keeping Coruscant clean's a dirty job, but it's good to see I've got company. I'm Officer Stansun, Republic security.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689587" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're fighting a war against the Black Sun. Wish I could say we're winning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Word has it they're running an illegal surgery clinic, giving wanted criminals new faces. Helps them dodge arrest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic security should end their operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut them down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689591" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've tried, but the facility moves shop the second they see our uniforms.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689593" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised anyone's willing to sacrifice their identity like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689593" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's disgusting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689594" id2="17" version="1065353216">These thugs will do anything to avoid arrest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689596" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd never let someone cut this handsome mug.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Must not be as cute as me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure. These brutes only do it 'cause they have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689599" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care who I'm hiding from, no one messes with my looks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Must not be as cute as me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't blame you... but none of these thugs have a face like yours to protect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689602" id2="17" version="1065353216">This clinic concerns me how?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689603" id2="17" version="1065353216">That clinic is a menace and a threat to Coruscant's stability.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689605" id2="17" version="1065353216">More and more dangerous criminals slip through our fingers every day. Unfortunately, they move shop whenever Republic security swoops in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689607" id2="17" version="1065353216">But maybe you could pay this clinic a visit. Smash their illegal surgery droids, pull their patient files. Show them the Republic's still in charge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Black Sun's clinic won't operate another day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gladly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to hear. The sooner we shut them down, the quicker we can clean up Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I'll visit this clinic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic security appreciates any help you can offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroy the Black Sun surgery droids then download their patient files. That's all we need to pull the masks off their criminal clients.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="689616" id2="17" version="1065353216">No thanks. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry to bother you. Looks like Black Sun's getting off easy, for now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="689619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coruscant's a rough place. It's up to Republic security to protect it.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
