<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>32</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/nar_shaddaa/class/jedi_knight/vell_narroc.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperials are taking people for &quot;testing&quot; to the main lab. It's in the Red Light Sector--not sure exactly where.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655908" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's one of the busiest parts of Nar Shaddaa. We'll never find the lab.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655910" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard it's the only building with a dedicated energy reactor. Does that help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely. Contact me when you're in the Red Light Sector. I'll have a plan. Rieekan out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655914" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get these volunteers to safety. I hope you kill every last one of those Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655917" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be alright. I'm here to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655919" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chief Rieekan? The recruitment center was overrun with Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655921" id2="17" version="1065353216">No sign of Agent Galen, but I've just freed some refugees.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655922" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not refugees--heroes. These people put their lives on the line for victory over the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Name's Vell Narroc. Been recruiting volunteers for the Power Guard project since it started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655926" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those people asked to become test subjects?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655928" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire stole their homeworlds. They jumped at the chance for payback.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Over the years, hundreds of people volunteered for the Power Guard experiments. Heroes, all of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655931" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many Power Guards are there? What are they like?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about these heroes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655932" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's way above my security level--but I've heard they're amazing. Even stronger than a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655934" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did Imperials get control?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655935" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was organizing fresh recruits when Imperials stormed inside. They rounded us up, threw us in the cage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655937" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're called &quot;experiments&quot; because most end in failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655937" id2="17" version="1065353216">And probably all dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655938" id2="17" version="1065353216">People know the risk--but they're willing to try anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't know how the Empire found us, but they control the whole project now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655941" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Republic agent named Galen came here. What happened to him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655941" id2="17" version="1065353216">They got my ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655942" id2="17" version="1065353216">They captured him alive. Their leader wanted him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655944" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me where the Power Guard experiments take place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655944" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to find the main lab.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never seen the main lab, but it's someplace in the Red Light Sector. Imperials are sending people there for &quot;testing.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655947" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care how many Imperials I have to kill--they're not getting away with this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="655947" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not for long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655948" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you'd better hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="655950" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials were going to kill us. They deserved what you did.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
