<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>54</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/bronze/imperial/nowhere_to_hide/private_shorn.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235012" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll be able to hold the line now, I'm certain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235013" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're back! Did it work? Are the stealth troopers dead? Oh, um, sorry. I'm just a bit on edge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your device did its part, I took care of the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your plan was sound.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235015" id2="17" version="1065353216">It really worked? Hah! I can't believe it! You think I'll get a commendation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235017" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing to fear now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235018" id2="17" version="1065353216">They went down fighting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Republic dogs were hitting us mercilessly. I'm sure it was a real slug-out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235021" id2="17" version="1065353216">You guys really saved our skin; I wish I had a better way to show my appreciation, but I hope this does you all some good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you so much, my lord. I thought we were goners. Please take this as thanks. I wish I had something less... humble to offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235023" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know what you normally work for, so sorry if this comes short, but it's everything I've got.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235024" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe they disbanded Intelligence, that was amazing. Take this, a little appreciation for what you do for us, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235025" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think we can handle it from here. Here, take this. You'll probably put it to better use than I will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please hurry, those stealth troopers are slaughtering us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch how you walk around here! You'll end up shot in the back if you're not cautious!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235030" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ahem, sorry. It's just a few highly tempting targets like you could draw attention to this position. The enemy hasn't spotted me yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235032" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, I apologize for yelling, my lord, but I needed to warn you. We're getting hammered ahead of this position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235034" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're that bounty hunter who's been working with Darth Tormen, right? I could use a good hunter right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, Private Shon, reporting. The situation's bad up ahead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry for yelling at you, but there are some dangerous forces lurking around here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our garrison holding the Green Jedi enclave is losing ground quickly. They don't stand a chance against the Republic's stealth troopers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our forces attempting to take the Green Jedi enclave are deadlocked; they keep getting outflanked by the Republic's stealth troopers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235042" id2="17" version="1065353216">What makes these stealth troopers so effective?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stealth troopers?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235043" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't surprise me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, please. You don't understand, you'll never spot them before they've got you where they want you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why hide near the enclave?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235047" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was my squad's tech specialist. I've been observing what I can about this new threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235049" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're using some kind of cloaking technology that makes a stealth field generator look like a signal flare. But its weakness is that it's a little too good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235051" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can't even detect each other; they have to rely on their unit commanders for coordination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235052" id2="17" version="1065353216">We sever the head and watch the body thrash about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Striking their leaders is key.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly, my lord, and I think I've got a way to make clearing them out a lot easier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235055" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can't hope to best a Sith at a game of deception.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235055" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll teach them a lesson.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235056" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very true, my lord. I have a suggestion for how you could do the most damage, if you'll permit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235058" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could nab those unit commanders for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds right up my alley.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235059" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not really in a position to be taking prisoners, but I could use your help tracking them down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235061" id2="17" version="1065353216">I imagine that scrambling communications would be exceptionally effective in this case.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tried electronic warfare yet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235062" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would slow them down, but they'd still have a huge advantage over us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235064" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's something to go on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235065" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not seeing an exploit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235066" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've modified this stealth field generator to disrupt fields rather than create them. All it needs is to be tuned to the right frequencies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scan a unit commander's tactical computer, and it should expose all of the stealth troopers under their command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Synchronize this device with a unit commander's tactical computer and eliminate the unveiled stealth troopers, anything else?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me review the plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235070" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's it exactly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235072" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time for payback.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tear 'em apart, for my platoon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="235075" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay... if you see any friendlies, send them my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="235078" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah! Oh, whew, don't sneak up on me! There are stealth fighters stalking around here!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
