<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>41</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/alderaan/bronze/imperial/the_killik_problem/rylan_stallos.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318635" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Thul will lead the drive to force the Killiks underground. We will have a clean planet again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318637" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Killik hives have been poisoned. They'll swarm soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318638" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the noble houses must accept their obligation to combat them, thanks to Thul leadership.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318640" id2="17" version="1065353216">In another life, you would have made a fine royal Guardian of the Mounds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seize Organa's xenotoxins and poison the Killik hives. Thul will not ignore the infestation taking place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318643" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imagine leaving your home for a sojourn into the galaxy. When you return, you find the manor infested.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318645" id2="17" version="1065353216">The wood is rotten and wriggling; beetles carpet floors you raced across as a child, and maggots drop in tangled clumps onto your head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318647" id2="17" version="1065353216">With due respect, my lord, this is what House Thul faces--an infestation of vermin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318648" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is what House Thul must contend with--an infestation of vermin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318649" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith returned from exile to a galaxy overrun with Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318649" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire faces vermin, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you understand. Though our infestation is of a more literal kind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318652" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thousands of eyes hiding in the dark, terrifying the unwary... what's not to like?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318652" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like insects.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our exile was to stark and sterile places; perhaps I never developed your proclivities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318655" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you have a bug problem, you hire an exterminator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318655" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's an obvious solution...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318656" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Killiks--insectoid aliens here on Alderaan. They're causing problems?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318656" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard of the infestation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318657" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes--barely intelligent things. It's the nobility's obligation to contain the swarms underground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318659" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not following you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318660" id2="17" version="1065353216">So exterminate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318661" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can squash one, but not a million.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318663" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Killiks are Alderaan's native insectoid population. Man-sized, barely intelligent, it's the nobility's duty to contain the swarms underground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318665" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unchecked, they are ravaging this planet, turning palaces into hives and cocooning the survivors... generations caught in the mandibles of beasts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318666" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't have that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318667" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said they're native to this world. They were here first...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where do the bugs come from?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318668" id2="17" version="1065353216">These things frighten you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legend has it Killiks once ruled the planet. Supposedly, most flew to the stars--but how many remained in hibernation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318671" id2="17" version="1065353216">House Organa has been neglecting their responsibilities against the vermin, but even they carry defenses against Killik hunting parties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318673" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you could seize the Organa toxins and poison the Killik hives, well... the Killiks will swarm, and the other houses must defend themselves and do their part.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318674" id2="17" version="1065353216">A smart trick--I like it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe Alderaan belongs to the Killiks as much as it does to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe they belong here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318676" id2="17" version="1065353216">No Alderaanian is so naive. Bug hunting, however inglorious, is our obligation--and Organa and Ulgo have failed Alderaan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318678" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will all war against the Killiks--and Thul will save this planet from infestation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318680" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not interested. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="318681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not interested. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318682" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spoken like so many Ulgos and Organas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="318684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you seen the Killiks? They eat men alive, you know.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
