<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>58</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/imperial/stardrive_combustion/corgan_sturm.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448811" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for your help. Corellian StarDrives won't recover from this one. I'm watching the ruins, and nothing's moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448813" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was amazing--I saw the fires through my optics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Part of me still wishes we could have blown all the charges at once, but that... Corellian StarDrive's won't be funneling any more money.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448819" id2="17" version="1065353216">I enjoyed that destruction far more than I expected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448819" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was entertaining, thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing brightens the day like a batch of high explosives. Those were some big booms.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448830" id2="17" version="1065353216">This demonstration will remind the other corporations to toe the line.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448830" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the price of resistance</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Politics is for the brass and the movers and shakers, I just blow up what they tell me to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448836" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really pulled my fat out of the fire. You ever need some custom work done, I owe you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448838" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we're done, I'm leaving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got to go find my partner, but you've done more than enough already. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448848" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't tell you your job, but there's still some charges down there. We need to detonate them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grab some turf, my lord, if you want to watch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448858" id2="17" version="1065353216">General &quot;Mother&quot; Hesker sent someone to check on me, eh? Well, we're just about to start the fireworks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448862" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're just in time for the show! Grab some turf. Things are about to get fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448867" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Corellian StarDrive corporation has been funding resistance cells all over the city, so I'm turning their headquarters into a crater.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448871" id2="17" version="1065353216">As soon as I get the all clear from my buddy down there, I'll flip the switch and... boom. No more corporation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448873" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rebellion like that cannot go unpunished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448873" id2="17" version="1065353216">A suitable fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448875" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. They're the biggest corporation on Corellia, so they thought the Empire wouldn't slap them down. This should--Ah, there's my call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448879" id2="17" version="1065353216">A corporation that cares about profits should be open to negotiation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448879" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroying them seems extreme.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448881" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're funding resistance cells all over the city. General Hesker wants an example made--and here's the call I'm expecting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop wasting time and blow it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448887" id2="17" version="1065353216">My buddy's down there placing the last charges, when he's out of the way he'll call--ah, that'll be him now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blow it quick, they know we're here! Repeat, the Republic's found us, blow it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448895" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast, long range detonator's not working! The 'Pubs must have put a dampening field up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surely, you must have thought something like this might happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448898" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must have a back up plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448900" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd be pretty lousy at my job if I didn't have a backup plan. Just didn't see it getting this bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448904" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does he need help getting out of there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448904" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about your partner?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448906" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'll get himself out. Right now we've got a bigger gundark to wrestle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448910" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the problem with demolitions--too many things can go wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explosives are too reckless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448912" id2="17" version="1065353216">You like to get up close and personal, eh? Maybe there's a chance to salvage this run, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448916" id2="17" version="1065353216">A short-range detonator will still blow the charges, but you'd have to fight half the 'Pub army while doing it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448919" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't last ten seconds--respectfully, sir, you've got to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448922" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be thankful that you've given me an outlet for my rage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448922" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make up for your failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448924" id2="17" version="1065353216">The 'Pubs won't stand a chance with you taking care of things, my Lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch. The Dark Side is more powerful than your explosives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448927" id2="17" version="1065353216">An enjoyable diversion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your work's cut out for you, my Lord, Force or no Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448934" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like an explosion as much as the next person. This should be fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448934" id2="17" version="1065353216">Might as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448936" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Pub's will certainly make it fun for you, but the fireworks are worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448940" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll clean up your failure, but central command will hear about this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448940" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll clean up your mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Report me, as long as you're willing to blow this plant to the Outer Rim.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448946" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will be too easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448948" id2="17" version="1065353216">The 'Pubs have made that place a hornet's nest. Might be trickier than you think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448950" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a delay on each bomb after it's triggered. That'll give you time to get out of the blast zones.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448952" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't stick around after you set them off--the timer's not that long, and it's a big boom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="448954" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, I don't. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better me than you, right? Fine, I'll take care of it myself. See you around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="448957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ever seen a stardrive go critical? It's the prettiest white fire--like a tiny sun. When Corellia StarDrive goes, it'll look like a whole new galaxy.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
