<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>32</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/bronze/rakghoul_release/private_selro.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119575" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're sending a cleanup crew to make sure no rakghouls slipped by, just in case.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119576" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just heard from Doctor Zalaren. Between the panic room and your help, I think almost everyone got out okay.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks again. And don't worry, we're building power surge defenses in right this minute.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119580" id2="17" version="1065353216">The security systems should be a big help if you can get them online.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi! Please, wait--nobody's responding, something's gone wrong!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir! Please, sir, I can't raise anyone on the communicator--everything's gone wrong!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait! You're that freighter captain, aren't you? Everyone says you're tough--please, you've got to help me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait! Please, they've all gone silent! There's no time for me to call for help!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119591" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've lost contact with Project Quell, in the lower ground labs. It's, um, supposed to study those rakghoul creatures.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119593" id2="17" version="1065353216">They kept a whole pack of them there. The scientists wanted to study the rakghouls' behavior, try to find weaknesses we could use.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone approved this?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Zalaren was project lead. But he only took the job after checking all the security himself!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119597" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't fight an opponent you don't understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119597" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see. Knowing the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119598" id2="17" version="1065353216">But what's to understand, Master Jedi? They're rakghouls. You shoot them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me numbers, Private. How big is this rakghoul pack?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rakghouls? How many?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119601" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never saw them, sir, only those huge crates of food they brought in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like an Imperial lab.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, what? No! Project Quell was just to watch the rakghouls, not do anything to them!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119606" id2="17" version="1065353216">And something went wrong?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119607" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was incredibly stupid.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119608" id2="17" version="1065353216">I kept saying it was a bad idea! But I'm just a private, who cares what I think.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119610" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I know is, nobody's answering my check-ins. There was a power surge not long ago... maybe that opened the rakghoul pens.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119612" id2="17" version="1065353216">None of our scientists have come out. But if they reached the lab's panic room, they might still be alive. Please, you have to find them!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, I will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave this to me, Private.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here--this code will arm Project Quell's security systems. If anyone's in the panic room, the defense droids will protect them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just don't let your guard down. I don't know just what you'll find down there. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="119619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why don't you? [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me? But I won't last five minutes down--where are you going?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="119622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like we just had a power surge. Better call it in.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
