<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>9</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x2/daily/corellia/imperial/fall_of_corellia/bounty_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036019" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE STRATEGY UPDATE / FOR DELIVERY TO ALL PERSONNEL

Hypermatter reroute successful. General Konya reminds all troops that their hazardous success will not go unrewarded.

If radiation sickness persists, contact a physician immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036020" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE STRATEGY UPDATE / FOR DELIVERY TO ALL PERSONNEL

The battle for the Black Hole is about to shift in the Empire's favor.

Imperial engineers have discovered that the Black Hole's hypermatter pipelines can be rerouted. A simple redirection and Councillor Torvix's hypermatter will flow into Imperial-held territory.

Unfortunately, the rerouting switches lie within radioactive zones. Hazmat troopers guard them, shielded from radiation sickness by anti-rad serum.

General Konya has faith that you possess the bravery and strength to seize this hypermatter for the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036023" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE STRATEGY UPDATE / FOR DELIVERY TO ALL PERSONNEL

Councillor Torvix's spies have been neutralized. Resume primary assault. General Konya states &quot;The Black Hole's fall is imminent.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036024" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE STRATEGY UPDATE / FOR DELIVERY TO ALL PERSONNEL

General Konya has received reports of spies in the Black Hole.

These underworld agents hide in plain sight, feed reports to Councillor Torvix and disrupt Imperial operations. But the spies cannot hide the hypermatter radiation that clings to denizens of the Black Hole.

Personnel will be supplied with radiation meters to expose enemies. Any spies uncovered will be dealt with by proper authorities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036027" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE STRATEGY UPDATE / FOR DELIVERY TO ALL PERSONNEL

Hypermatter drops confirmed. Emergency reserves filled. Resume primary mission against Councillor Torvix.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036028" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE STRATEGY UPDATE / FOR DELIVERY TO ALL PERSONNEL

War against the Core Worlds has severely drained Imperial hypermatter stores. Fuel reserves have plummeted to critical levels. Within weeks, key segments of the Imperial fleet will be stranded.

Primary objective of Corellia strike teams remains the destruction of Councillor Torvix and the Black Hole. General Konya has now authorized a secondary objective: recovery of emergency hypermatter fuel.

Hypermatter must be siphoned immediately to maintain Imperial readiness across the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036031" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE STRATEGY UPDATE / FOR DELIVERY TO ALL PERSONNEL

Councillor Torvix's new combat droids have been eradicated--a significant blow to his forces.

Corellia will soon be left in ruins.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1036032" id2="17" version="1065353216">BLACK HOLE STRATEGY UPDATE / FOR DELIVERY TO ALL PERSONNEL

A shipment of advanced combat droids has been smuggled to Councillor Torvix's forces. Immediate response required.

The droids' weapons and defensive systems are state of the art, and their immunity to radiation offers significant advantages in the Black Hole.

General Konya has authorized all necessary resources to be devoted to their elimination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1045510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Empire by completing the following daily missions in the Black Hole district of Corellia:

[HEROIC] End of Torvix
[AREA] Asset Liquidation
[DAILY] Control the Battlefield
[DAILY] Hypermatter Directive
[DAILY] No Trace Left
[DAILY] Glow</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
