<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>125</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x2/daily/corellia/imperial/fall_of_corellia/general_konya.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005186" id2="17" version="1065353216">With Torvix dead, his people are scattered. Nicely done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005189" id2="17" version="1065353216">Static on all channels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005191" id2="17" version="1065353216">Councillor Torvix is dead, and his army is a mess. It won't be long before we make a clean sweep.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005193" id2="17" version="1065353216">When this operation is over... Corellia will be an overpopulated rock unable to power its own fleets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005194" id2="17" version="1065353216">Torvix's army is fragmented, but someone will try to pull it together. We can't allow that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005194" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let Torvix be replaced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005195" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make sure to keep the pressure on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005197" id2="17" version="1065353216">It doesn't trouble you, seeing your homeworld devastated?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005197" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're from Corellia, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005198" id2="17" version="1065353216">I brought Corellia to the Empire, and Corellia turned on me. It's not my home anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005200" id2="17" version="1065353216">After everything that happened, this planet should be wiped clean.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005200" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia deserves worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005201" id2="17" version="1065353216">But that's not an option, this time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005203" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyway, there's plenty more for us to do--and you've given us the chance to do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005205" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be the last one off the planet--but if I don't make it, at least Torvix died first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005209" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got their attention. Torvix's bodyguards are getting angry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005210" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Torvix to security--what are you doing? We have intruders!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005211" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Torvix to all forces. I'm sealing the inner vault. Deal with the problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005213" id2="17" version="1065353216">The bird is in the nest. Time to flood Torvix's command center with hypermatter--sending you the details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005214" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Torvix. What do you think you're doing? You can't unseal my vault!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005215" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen to me--we can still negotiate. The explosion will kill us all!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005216" id2="17" version="1065353216">That should do it. Hypermatter pipes flooding--and igniting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005218" id2="17" version="1065353216">Damn you! You're dead, do you hear me? Dead!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mission accomplished. Come on home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005223" id2="17" version="1065353216">Torvix has had this coming a long time. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005226" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord? There's a transmission from the Black Hole... the general wants it put through to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005227" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir? There's a transmission from the Black Hole... the general wants it put through to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005229" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you're the Sith Lord who's been hounding me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005231" id2="17" version="1065353216">So a Dark Council member is finally paying attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005233" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you're the ghost who's been haunting my people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005235" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard it was a bounty hunter who'd been troubling me. I hope you have some pull with the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005237" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Councillor Torvix. It's time to end this--you want the Black Hole facilities destroyed, and you know I can hold out forever. So we negotiate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your forces can't stand against us. And the Republic is closing in as fast as we are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005238" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're already losing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005239" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Republic realizes it can't beat me, I'll be ruler of Corellia. This is your last chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005241" id2="17" version="1065353216">State your terms, Councillor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005241" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm amenable to negotiation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005242" id2="17" version="1065353216">You pledged to serve the Empire. You betrayed your oath. There is no negotiation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005242" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your treason is your death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005243" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll reconsider. You need what I have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005245" id2="17" version="1065353216">Men beg for an audience with the Lords of the Dark Council. Do you think yourself above me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005245" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Sith. You are nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005246" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I have the upper hand, because I have the fuel your ships need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analyze the frequency and run a locator, but keep it quiet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trace this call, Private.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005250" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm listening, Councillor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005251" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to negotiate, start paying more than the Imperials. Then we can talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005251" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll consider a bribe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005252" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have my own mercenaries already, thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005254" id2="17" version="1065353216">By the end of the day, the Empire will provide me with shield generators, combat droids, anti-air cannons and access to orbital satellites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005256" id2="17" version="1065353216">In return, I will release one-tenth of my hypermatter stores to your fleet, and you will depart this system forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Desperate son of a sow just made his biggest mistake. We traced the signal and got a bead on his position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005260" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you say to killing Councillor Torvix?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005261" id2="17" version="1065353216">We haven't been able to reach him so far. You have an idea?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005261" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me your plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005262" id2="17" version="1065353216">He must know he's near defeat. We can call his bluff and force him to surrender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Diplomacy is an option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005263" id2="17" version="1065353216">With respect? I served in the cabinet with Torvix for seven years. He doesn't know when to quit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005265" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Konya--you may have lost Corellia, but there's hope for you yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005265" id2="17" version="1065353216">For once, a good idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005266" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're too kind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Torvix is using a radiation vault as his command center--impervious to portable weaponry, but not to a hypermatter detonation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take out his personal guards--let him know you're coming and he'll seal his shelter. Then flood the hypermatter pipelines and turn him into ash.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005271" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's more to it than that. What am I facing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything else I should know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005272" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it comes to killing, I'll deal the blow. This could still end another way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005272" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll decide whether he dies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005273" id2="17" version="1065353216">So long as it's over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005275" id2="17" version="1065353216">His guards are killers--the worst pirates in Republic space, armored in radiation suits or from some species immune to everything. The rest? Just his army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005277" id2="17" version="1065353216">Councillor Torvix will die. Corellia will burn. And the Republic will be left with nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005277" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's end all of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005278" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I could hope for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005280" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be in touch during the approach. Scorch his bones for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005284" id2="17" version="1065353216">Last bottle from the Coronet City Winery is over there. One drink before we jump into the abyss?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005287" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005288" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005289" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005290" id2="17" version="1065353216">General. You ordered the Empire's withdrawal from Corellia?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005291" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right. You must be the Emperor's Wrath--and since I'm not dead yet, I suppose I owe you an explanation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005293" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dark Lord. Didn't expect you to come in person; I hope you'll hear me out before the execution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005295" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right. And you're ex-Intelligence, ex-military... I can't even pull files on you, so I hope inviting you here wasn't my worst move yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005297" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're after my head, I've already put credits in your account; does that buy me time to talk?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005299" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Adele Konya, formerly of the Corellian cabinet and commander of Horizon Outpost. We may be withdrawing, but we can still be victorious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005300" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm told you're staging some sort of suicide mission. You said you needed help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005300" id2="17" version="1065353216">I received your message.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005301" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have no idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005303" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did a former cabinet member become an Imperial general?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005303" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're Corellian?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005304" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought the Empire would be good for my planet, and when General Hesker was reassigned... Darth Marr needed someone in place. Lucky me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005306" id2="17" version="1065353216">We fought and died to take this planet. Retreat is not the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005306" id2="17" version="1065353216">We shouldn't be withdrawing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005307" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could hold Corellia--but after what happened on Ilum and Denova, the Empire is fragmented. We have to regroup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005309" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're stationed on the edge of the Black Hole--an industrial site used to store and process hypermatter. Volatile, toxic and key to lightspeed travel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005311" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've sacked and burned almost everything on Corellia. Without the Black Hole, Corellian fleets will go without fuel and the planet will be isolated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005312" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seize the hypermatter and destroy the facilities. The Imperial fleet regroups, and the Republic is weighed down by a worthless planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005312" id2="17" version="1065353216">We leave the Republic nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005313" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was the plan, anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Straightforward enough. Why do you need me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005315" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what's the problem?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you regret betraying your homeworld, General?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Am I hearing bitterness?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005317" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Imperial now, and the Sith don't teach regret.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our problem is Councillor Torvix. The most corrupt man in the Corellian cabinet--recruited a criminal army for the Empire when the invasion started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005321" id2="17" version="1065353216">Torvix and his allies used Imperial equipment and weaponry to take control of the Black Hole. Now he refuses to give up what power he has.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005322" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we're going to ruin Torvix and obtain the hypermatter, I need to know everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me a tactical report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Torvix's men are mostly pirates and Exchange gangsters using our tech. We've got limited resources, and we're surrounded by the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005325" id2="17" version="1065353216">What can Torvix hope to achieve? The Republic won't take him back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005325" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does he plan to do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005326" id2="17" version="1065353216">He thinks he can still negotiate a deal--it doesn't matter that he's wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Two Corellian councillors who signed on with the Empire... one clinging to power, the other desperate for a chance to prove her worth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005328" id2="17" version="1065353216">You two have a lot in common.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005329" id2="17" version="1065353216">I ran out of chances a while ago--but unlike Torvix, I chose my side and stuck to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005331" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to take Torvix down, siphon off his hypermatter and ruin his facilities--all with limited resources and while surrounded by the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most of our troops are already gone--I've retained a few specialists, but we won't get out alive. You can help us die martyrs instead of failures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005334" id2="17" version="1065353216">You failed to hold Corellia. Whether you live or die now isn't my concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005334" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not here to save you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nor mine. We agree on that much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005337" id2="17" version="1065353216">My people are at your command. For the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1005338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone gets out alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005340" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's lost too many loyal soldiers. If there's a way to succeed and evacuate your people safely, we'll find it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005341" id2="17" version="1065353216">You hire me, and I do this job right. That includes keeping the team in one piece.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then let's get to work. My people are at your command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005344" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the Empire!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1005348" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Horizon Outpost. Edge of the Black Hole.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
