<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>21</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/smuggler/chapter_3/event_and_finale/senator_dodonna.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain! Marshall Cavarat just told me you apparently single-handedly recaptured Ivory and put half the Imperial presence in the prison to rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635461" id2="17" version="1065353216">But did Ivory tell you anything? Helping the Republic recapture prisoners they couldn't hold in the first place wasn't really the point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ivory accepted--leniency from the Republic in return for Rogun's known safe houses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635462" id2="17" version="1065353216">I made the deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635463" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain. I just got a less-than-glowing report from Marshall Cavarat. What kind of mess did you get into down there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635465" id2="17" version="1065353216">And more importantly, did you get anything from Ivory? I've outed half a dozen of Rogun's assassins on Port Nowhere--he's really gunning for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635466" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ivory gave me a list of Rogun's old bolt-holes to check out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635466" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got some targets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ivory and I worked out an arrangement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635469" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turns out Rogun's the one who put Ivory behind bars. We're working together to get his revenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ivory's with me now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635471" id2="17" version="1065353216">I told you the Republic only authorized--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, drop the act. You want Rogun as much as I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635475" id2="17" version="1065353216">With what Ivory gave me, we should be able to corner him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="635475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get Rogun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send over whatever Ivory gave you. I'll see if I recognize anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing's ringing any bells. I'll dig a little further.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635480" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the meantime, Captain, I'll work on those permits you'll need to land on Voss. I haven't slept a night since those awful beasts attacked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="635482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh-oh, Captain. Better get off the line. We've got a distress call coming...</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
