<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>175</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/camp/doctor_oggurobb.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163244" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah! We meet again! To share your company twice after so many years--I did not believe destiny could be so whimsical.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163245" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Return a friendly nod]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163246" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad we'll be working together again, Doctor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmmm... the intervening years have not treated you well.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163248" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Ignore his criticism]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163249" id2="17" version="1065353216">You spend five years in a toxic carbonite stasis and see how you feel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163250" id2="17" version="1065353216">A fair point, actually.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163252" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well you're not looking so great yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163253" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is so true! I spent the last several years in a creative slump and, sadly lacking inspiration, let myself go. But these recent events have given me a renewed vigor and inspiration!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163255" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know... I still look back fondly upon our collaboration on Makeb, toppling Toborro.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163257" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't remember working with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mmm, severe memory loss? I had not known this to be a side effect of carbonite freezing....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163259" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Stare blankly]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163260" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Return a Glare]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163261" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm standing right here, you know....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me, I did not mean to belittle your disability.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you're just not as memorable as you think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Possible... though highly unlikely....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163267" id2="17" version="1065353216">At any rate, I am Doctor Juvard Illip Oggurobb, Artist of Technology! We collaborated years ago on Makeb to topple Toborro, the Mad Mogul.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163269" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had hoped to be able to work together again, and now we have been given the opportunity. Let us not squander it with idle chatter. On to business!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, excellent! I've been looking forward to our collaboration.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163272" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Wait for Oggurobb to continue]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163273" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mmm... Interesting....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not entirely without potential... though I can't help but to have at least some reservations....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163277" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana, for her part, insists that you possess the skills necessary, and as she has given me no cause to doubt her judgment, I shall take her at her word.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163278" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Remain quiet]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you to judge me?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163280" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remind me who you are, again?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163281" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgotten already? How disappointing... and rude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163283" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am Doctor Juvard Illip Oggurobb, Artist of Technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163284" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pleased to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163285" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I you! To have escaped the clutches of the Eternal Empire--from the clutches of Arcann himself! An inspirationally bold story.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163287" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will be in sore need of such boldness if we are to be successful in our efforts here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163289" id2="17" version="1065353216">You speak Basic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163290" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah yes, how could I forget... While you will seldom hear it, in truth all Hutts can speak basic... we simply choose not to do so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163294" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given the... diverse nature of those gathered here, and the... tenuous nature of some of the friendships, I find it prudent to minimize the risk of linguistic misunderstandings. Now then: onto more pressing concerns!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163298" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is no secret that against the Eternal Empire we stand at a massive technological disadvantage. In fact, that is almost an understatement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163300" id2="17" version="1065353216">My role here is to coordinate the alliance effort to understand the Eternal Empire technology, and to develop our own to bring us to an even footing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163301" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Let him continue]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163302" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even footing? That's quite a tall order.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163303" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised you're helping us. I thought Hutts maintained neutrality.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your casual bigotry aside, I'm afraid my brethren are being profoundly shortsighted in this matter. There is no neutrality with respect to the Eternal Empire, only eventual subjugation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163306" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I, for one, have had enough of delusional moguls in my lifetime! Let them sit in their sad denial, ensconced within their opulent palaces! Let them hasten their own demise with inaction!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163308" id2="17" version="1065353216">It falls to those of us with vision to accomplish what they will not!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163309" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider me inspired.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163310" id2="17" version="1065353216">I apologize for misjudging you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163311" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were talking about standing against the Eternal Empire's technology?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163312" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not here to listen to you whine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me for losing my temper. This is a matter of some frustration for me. Let us return to the matter at hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163315" id2="17" version="1065353216">The task is daunting indeed... which is what makes it exciting! To succeed, we must gather scientists, researchers, and representatives from the galaxy's many sentient species for their fresh perspectives.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163316" id2="17" version="1065353216">[He's on a roll, why interrupt him now?]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163317" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said you already had someone in mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163318" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do! An exceptional Gand--both a Findsman and an engineer by trade--is currently located in Zakuul's Old World district.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163320" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I understand it, this individual--Yuun--is one of your former squadmates. I imagine you'll have little difficulty in convincing him to join us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Findsmen have a unique perception of reality--they can intuit what others struggle to grasp at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163324" id2="17" version="1065353216">This conversation has left me feeling inspired, and I must create.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163325" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without even saying a word, you have managed to leave me inspired... truly impressive. I must create.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, Commander! There you are. Well done! Yuun arrived a while ago, and I must confess I am already impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Immediately upon his arrival he told me he could &quot;feel that I was seeking.&quot; After a brief meditation, he located a precision torque-spanner that I had lost months ago!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163441" id2="17" version="1065353216">And then, as if it were no more challenging of a thing, he pointed out the solution to a thruster heat dissipation problem that I've been staring at for the past week!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163443" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did he put it? I believe he said something about &quot;watching the river of heat, looking to where it met the sea&quot;.... Simply marvelous.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to hear that Yuun is everything you'd hoped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Continue to recruit for us individuals of such bold talent and insight, Commander--I suspect we will see tangible results rather soon indeed!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163446" id2="17" version="1065353216">You let me know when you've found candidates, and I'll do what it takes to recruit them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163447" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not have any recruitment leads at this time, but I will send you an alert if I learn anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163449" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the meanwhile... this reflection has excited me all over again. My mind floods with inspired designs... I must create.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander! I recently had the pleasure of making introductions with Doctor Eckard Lokin. Another worthwhile find--well done as usual.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163455" id2="17" version="1065353216">A brilliant geneticist, boldly riding the bleeding edges of both biomedical and genetics research. And such a warm and pleasant personality! Truly a treat to work with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163459" id2="17" version="1065353216">But Aygo is insisting upon confining the good doctor to military duties! I need your help in swatting his grubby little paws away!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163461" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can understand Aygo's logic, given Lokin's extensive history with Imperial Intelligence, but from the moment I saw Eckard it was painfully obvious that art was his true calling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163463" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given Aygo's upbringing, I would frankly have thought him better able to understand this sort of thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163464" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right, Lokin has a place here. I'll tell Aygo to split his time between military and research duties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes! I knew you understood these things! It is why we get along so well.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163467" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, but Aygo is right. Lokin's experience and insight are invaluable for our military operations. They need him full time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bah, not you too, Commander? Fine....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163470" id2="17" version="1065353216">This day just goes from bad to worse. My new personal shielding prototype seems to have developed a bad habit of violently overloading.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163472" id2="17" version="1065353216">While the explosions are both vibrant and dramatic, our soldiers express a strong preference for creating art, rather than becoming it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163474" id2="17" version="1065353216">The life of a genius is never easy....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well then, I'll get back to work. I was just consulting with Lokin about the tolerance for genetic mutation in sentients.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163477" id2="17" version="1065353216">You see, a prototype cloaking generator we've been developing has a side effect of inducing genetic mutation. I was about to abandon it entirely...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163479" id2="17" version="1065353216">But Lokin's work has shown that most sentients have a surprisingly high tolerance for alteration before truly harmful mutations manifest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander! I wanted to share my gratitude over your recent recruitment of Talos Drellik, and commend your insight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163484" id2="17" version="1065353216">In truth, we have sorely needed an individual more specialized in ancient knowledge and the more Force-oriented technologies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sadly, my genius lies elsewhere, and as these types of technologies form the foundation of so much within the Eternal Empire, it has been a consistent stumbling block for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163488" id2="17" version="1065353216">However Doctor Drellik's insights have already started to break down these barriers to our progress, and I delight to imagine the inevitable breakthroughs that will soon follow.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163489" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Continue listening]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163490" id2="17" version="1065353216">In fact, he was just speaking to me about the thesis for his doctorate, an in-depth analysis of an ancient race known as the Dashade. Fascinating work!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently these creatures could siphon and consume Force essence! Imagine what might result if the mechanisms behind this ability could be properly researched and understood!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could we create some sort of fixed, or even portable biotechnological platform? Some sort of Force-dampening or consuming field? Or... perhaps an explosive or warhead-like delivery platform? The possibilities... so myriad it is dizzying....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163496" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... I must be alone with my thoughts. Such inspiration must be captured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander! This latest discovery of yours--the Dashade--you have outdone yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talos was outright dumbfounded--he believed that the clues he found were most likely idle legend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163503" id2="17" version="1065353216">But this Dashade... a creature that can consume Force essence? This is groundbreaking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163505" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish greatly to better understand this process, but, for his part, the Dashade is being uncooperative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163507" id2="17" version="1065353216">He will occasionally tolerate some cursory examination, but attempts at more in-depth analysis result in violent threats of surprising detail and specificity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163509" id2="17" version="1065353216">Relatedly, he has a stunningly detailed grasp of Hutt anatomy....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163511" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I will not be deterred! The potential advances of understanding are too great to give up! Think of the possibilities!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps we could bribe him with a treat of sorts. Do you suppose you could convince Sana-Rae to part with one of her trainees? One of the less promising ones, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163514" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's horrible! How could you suggest that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well I realize it is not the most tasteful of options, but the Dashade is being unreasonable!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163517" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think Sana-Rae could be convinced, no.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163518" id2="17" version="1065353216">I unfortunately agree with your assessment. A pity... sometimes truly worthwhile art requires some sacrifice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pah, I shall think of some other solution....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163521" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think she could be convinced. You should ask her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm... I had my doubts, but if you believe so, perhaps it is possible. No worthwhile art is made without some sacrifice... perhaps she actually understands this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well, I shall try to find a good time to broach the subject. Thank you again, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good idea! I'll try to convince her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent! Thank you, Commander. I shall await word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander, I've been meaning to speak to you. This latest recruit, the Talz named Broonmark...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163533" id2="17" version="1065353216">While Broonmark's penchant for rending and violent destruction is admittedly impressive--both for the primal intensity of his conviction, as well as the astounding efficiency and savagery of his expression...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163535" id2="17" version="1065353216">And while life has consistently shown me that brilliance and inspiration can come from the most unexpected places...</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163536" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Say Nothing]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163537" id2="17" version="1065353216">And while I believe that a broad diversity in knowledge, perspective, and biology, is a key strength of our effort...</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163538" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Say Nothing]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163539" id2="17" version="1065353216">I cannot help but to have some measure of concern over the likelihood of this individual deciding on a whim to try and slaughter everyone within arm's reach.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163540" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Interrupt Him] Oh spit it out already...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Broonmark is an unrepentant, xenophobic,  psychopathic murderer, Commander. I question his value as an addition to our alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Broonmark follows strength, and he's seen mine firsthand. He'll obey.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163543" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm the Alliance Commander. You don't get to question my decisions. He stays.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you want to be the one who tries to kick him out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163545" id2="17" version="1065353216">You jest, but this only underscores the problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well, I shall trust your judgment and give him a chance to demonstrate whatever brilliance you see in him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Though you will understand if I keep him well away from the rest of our research team... and possibly under guard....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163551" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose if nothing else, you never fail to add interest to my day, Commander. I should return to my art.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163565" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings, Commander! May I help you?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163566" id2="17" version="1065353216">How are things going here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163567" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are still just starting out, I'm afraid. While I am applying my talents as fully as circumstances allow, we lack both the people and resources for any work of satisfactory scale.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163569" id2="17" version="1065353216">As things stand, it is hard to imagine we will be able to come to understand our adversary, or to develop effective counter-technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163571" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're starting to see some limited progress, though I'm afraid I must stress the &quot;limited.&quot; That said, the problem with a task of this size is always finding the appropriate inroads to begin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163573" id2="17" version="1065353216">While I believe we're just now... &quot;clearing the hurdle&quot; is how you pedal humanoids put it? We still have much and more work to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163575" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am happy to report that progress seems to be picking up a bit. We're actually looking to start work on our first prototype built from the cooperative vision of the team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163577" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is an important milestone, but certainly not the last. As we look to build future advancements off of today's, it only becomes more important that we continue efforts to recruit and secure supplies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163579" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are a patron of our art, Commander. I am hopeful that you will be able to continue supporting us as we create yet more brilliant, bold, and groundbreaking artistry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander, we have actually established a respectable foundation for a continuing research and development platform.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163583" id2="17" version="1065353216">We currently have several running projects that are developing ideas into prototypes, and are finally seeing some results from our reverse engineering efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163585" id2="17" version="1065353216">This has taken no small amount of vision, boldness, genius, and perseverance... but I must also say that your continual support to this point has been quite instrumental.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163587" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we cannot be happy with the successes of today! These new initiatives demand resources and minds all the same, and we still require whatever ongoing support you can offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163596" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sorts of things can I do to help the effort here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163597" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are always in need of supplies--an artist cannot work without tools and material. If you could secure supplies for our research efforts, it would be most helpful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163599" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd also ask you to keep a keen eye out for new research associates--having a new creator who can more efficiently use what is onhand is better than merely gathering more material!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163601" id2="17" version="1065353216">I shall keep an eye out for potential recruits as well, and send you an alert whenever I find promising candidates.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163614" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll let you get back to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well, I shall return to creation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163616" id2="17" version="1065353216">I went through the trouble of finding you the help you wanted. Now I'm expecting some results.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, Yuun's... a little strange.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163618" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're never satisfied, are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pah. It is ever the burden of the brilliant to be considered strange by those who lack the vision or genius to understand the world as we do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I not impress upon you earlier the enormity of our task? Success will require as much genius as we can manage to collect.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163937" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Hutt scientist? That's new.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163938" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe they put a Hutt in charge here...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come now, Commander. Such petty closed-mindedness is unbecoming. Especially given how crucial cooperation and collaboration will be if we are to succeed in our work here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163943" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bwaha!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163945" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Alien Research] I have some things that might interest you....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163946" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent, Commander. The support is appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163962" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Back]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163966" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in More Alien Research]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1166313" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have forwarded to you our information concerning Yuun. For now, I must return to my art.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1166329" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Stare Blankly]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander! Tell that blasted protocol droid that if he ever sets foot near my food hangars again, I'll have him scrapped and use his parts for experiments!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Low calorie meals?! Pah! What... trite ignorance! Doesn't he realize food is the fuel of creativity? Meddlesome... prattling...  little.... The nerve!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170695" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where's my spanner?! I must re-center myself!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170696" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander, I'm unsure what's gotten into that protocol droid, but he recently came by and dropped off a crate of packed meals in the middle of the lab.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Firstly, I do not allow eating within this lab. Secondly, my staff otherwise has ready access to the base cantina for meals. The gesture is honestly more nuisance than help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170701" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander, someone has installed extra padding on all of the seats in the lab, plus any other surface that could be mistaken for one. It must have been that meddlesome protocol droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assuming this isn't some passive-aggressive slight against myself as a Hutt, these cushions are putting dust and feathers into the air that are interfering with our sensitive work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170705" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not to mention the fact that at least one of them has proven to be disturbingly flammable.... I've had them removed. Tell that droid to cease this nonsense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander. Do you care to tell me what that protocol droid was doing near the lab's air circulators? I.... That divine fragrance... is that Alderaanian nectar?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, aromatherapy! Of course! Inspiring the mind by inspiring the senses! I dare say that droid has actually had a brilliant idea. Ahhh, yes... I must create.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quite fascinating, really! Apparently I've been overly concerned....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1178304" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Leave while you can]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178305" id2="17" version="1065353216">In fact, he was just telling me of the Dashade, a fascinating species that--hey! Where are you going?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178312" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Findsman who is also an accomplished engineer? I salivate to contemplate the contributions such an individual would make to our cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183063" id2="17" version="1065353216">A pity that Doctor Drellik's research failed to bring us more tangible results. But such are the pitfalls of scientific exploration!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183070" id2="17" version="1065353216">We shall not let this setback deter our forward momentum! Onward, to discovery!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
