<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>170</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/camp/general_aygo.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163782" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, if it isn't the new Commander. It's a pleasure to be able to work with you again, sir. Your work at Kuat was impressive, to say the least.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163783" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been a long time, Admiral Aygo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163786" id2="17" version="1065353216">That it has! I really do wish we had more time to catch up, but the Eternal Empire's not sitting around, so neither can we.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163788" id2="17" version="1065353216">If only it was as easy to send the Eternal Empire packing as you did those Imps back on Kuat.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163790" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't remember you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, that bruises my ego a bit, but considering everything you've been tied up in--not to mention the years in stasis--can't say I really blame you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163793" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Admiral Bey'wan Aygo. We fought together at the Battle of Kuat. You really helped us out of a bad spot, and wow did you really send those Imps packing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Err.... Sorry sir, that remark was totally inappropriate, given our current alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163796" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flash a knowing smirk]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163797" id2="17" version="1065353216">That kind of carelessness jeopardizes everything we're trying to build here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163798" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're entirely correct, Commander. I won't let it happen again.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163800" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lower your voice] Those Imps really had it coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heheh... Didn't they, though?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163803" id2="17" version="1065353216">At any rate, my job is to coordinate the Alliance's military and strategic intelligence assets, and I'm looking forward to working with you to enhance our military capacity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir. Welcome to your Alliance's military headquarters. Pleasure to have you here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Likewise, Admiral. I look forward to working together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163808" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm relieved to hear it, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163810" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Agent Background] Aygo... You were a Fleet Admiral at the Battle of Kuat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163811" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph. I was. You were there too. You and that Admiral Ranken did quite a number on our forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163813" id2="17" version="1065353216">It doesn't quite sound like it's a pleasure to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163814" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me, Commander. We've been on the opposite side of a war for a lot of years... old habits.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163816" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know, I've never really liked Bothans....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163817" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe we're trusting our military command to a Republic officer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah well I've never really liked Imps either, so I guess we're kinda even there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163820" id2="17" version="1065353216">But that's all the past--it has to be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163822" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got the Eternal Empire out there now, and it's going to take all of us working together to even have a chance of stopping them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163824" id2="17" version="1065353216">My job here is to coordinate the Alliance's military and strategic intelligence assets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163826" id2="17" version="1065353216">That said, we're too small to accomplish much right now. We're going to need to start by growing, which includes both recruitment, and securing additional materiel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me know if and when you're looking to help, we've got plenty of work to go around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, Commander. How can I help you?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163830" id2="17" version="1065353216">How are things going here, Admiral?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163832" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sorts of things can I do to help the effort here?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163841" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's all, Admiral.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163847" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's pretty simple, really. We need what any war effort needs: minds and materiel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163849" id2="17" version="1065353216">While you're out in the field, keep an eye out for noteworthy recruits--candidates with experience in command, or specialists with any military or intelligence background.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Beyond that, we need war supplies, and lots of them. I'll take anything you've got on hand that you're willing to part with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163862" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be blunt, Commander: We've got an awful lot of work ahead of us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163867" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're just starting to wrap our heads around this entire alliance, and smoothing over the old rivalries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163872" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're going to need to fill out our command structure, and buy, borrow, or steal a lot more hardware before we can mount any sort of credible operations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163875" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm hoping you'll be able to lend us a hand in getting off the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163969" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Military Equipment] I've got some equipment for you, Admiral.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163970" id2="17" version="1065353216">Outstanding, Commander. I'll see it put to good use.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163975" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in More Military Equipment]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1163976" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Back]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1163985" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good day, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander, I just wanted to say excellent job in recruiting Zenith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164007" id2="17" version="1065353216">The man is a master of tactical sabotage, has a lifetime of experience leading underground resistance movements, and he's well accustomed to working under resource limitations.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1164008" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's not much for conversation, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph. It's true, his type rarely are. That kind of life tends to leave its mark. There's no arguing about his skills, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1164010" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seemed like the exact skillset we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164011" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could not agree with you more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zenith has already drawn up proposals for additional resistance operations across several worlds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164015" id2="17" version="1065353216">At any rate, I should get back to it, Commander. Again, though, great work on this one.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1164017" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's a terrorist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody ever said war was pretty, Commander... and underground resistance can be a particularly messy business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164020" id2="17" version="1065353216">The line between terrorist and resistance fighter gets real thin real fast sometimes, but Zenith is on our side on this one. He has skills and knowledge we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, Commander. I was just reading up on your newest recruit, Rusk. Excellent job in bringing him in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164026" id2="17" version="1065353216">A brilliant soldier according to his records. First to volunteer for impossible missions, and somehow always gets the job done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164028" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's certainly no stranger to being in the thick of it on the front line, or even behind it a lot of the time--his units have had high casualty rates.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1164029" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Trooper Background] Sounds like someone who could have been prime material for Havoc squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1164030" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's used to risks and does what it takes to get the job done. He's exactly what we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe we could set him up as a SpecForce officer, have him train up the more talented volunteers.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1164197" id2="17" version="1065353216">I question his ability to work alongside Imperials. He's holding on to old grudges.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164198" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand the concern, Commander, but there's nothing like necessity and a larger threat for bringing old enemies together.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1164199" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Say Nothing]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1164200" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Imperial Background] But only until that threat is gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164201" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, I guess we'll just cross that bridge when we come to it, won't we Imp?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164203" id2="17" version="1065353216">At any rate, I should get back to it, Commander. Just wanted to say good job on this one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164207" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander, I just wanted to say thank you for speaking to Oggurobb and getting him to see reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164241" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oggurobb will be giving me a stink eye for a week over this, but it's worth it. Lokin's experience, knowledge, and contacts make him utterly invaluable here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164243" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand Lokin knows a lot about biology, genetics, and whatnot... but splitting his time with research duty would have really undermined our work here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1164324" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've made the right decision, Commander. Thanks again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170717" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander. That C2 droid just did something kind of amazing. He's modified the food processors in our barracks, and now everything they're making is nutritionally optimized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some of the troops might complain a bit, but this will be great for keeping our forces in fit fighting shape. If you see that droid, thank him for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, Commander... that C2 unit has started dropping off crates of packed meals in the barracks. I'm not really sure what's gotten into it, but it's not really helpful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170722" id2="17" version="1065353216">The meals aren't going to last in the field like our standard rations, and there's not really enough here to feed an army anyhow. Could you ask it to stop?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander, we either need to talk some sense into that protocol droid or just turn it off. It's carpeted the barracks in pillows!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170725" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not to mention it's swapped the padding on just about every seat it could find to ultra-plush... stuff. It's not really appropriate for military quarters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, you care to tell me why my command room smells like some parlor in the red light sector? Ugh....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170729" id2="17" version="1065353216">This has to be that protocol droid's doing. Make it stop--please.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander. Oggurobb just sent me a holo, claiming you've authorized a dual assignment for Lokin. That he'll be spending half his time in the Research Lab. Tell me the Hutt is making this up.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171844" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's already called you about it? I've never seen a Hutt do anything that fast in my life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171846" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand he knows a lot about genetics and whatnot, but splitting his time with research work's going to really undermine us here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171847" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's not making it up. I think the Research Lab should have equal access to Lokin's expertise.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171848" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Close Discussion] Those are my orders as commander and I expect you to follow them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood, Commander, it's your call to make.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171851" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there's nothing else, I'll be getting back to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171852" id2="17" version="1065353216">C'mon, Commander, I'm serious.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171854" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Confirm Decision] I thought people in the Republic loved sharing and compromise? To think Oggurobb would be a better Rep than you...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171855" id2="17" version="1065353216">You son of a... Rgh! Shoulda known better than to try reasoning with an Imp...</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171856" id2="17" version="1065353216">What was that, Admiral?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171857" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing at all, Commander! Must be your Imp paranoia acting up again.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171858" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Ignore the remark]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171859" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you'll excuse me, I'm going to get back to being productive...</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171862" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Confirm Decision] I understand, Admiral, but Lokin's got talents useful to both you and Oggurobb. It's only fair that we give the lab equal access to Lokin's time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171863" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Reverse Decision] Okay, you've convinced me. You can keep Lokin assigned here full time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander, there you are. What happened with Lokin?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171866" id2="17" version="1065353216">We had a disagreement. He attacked me and then ran off.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1171867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lokin turned out to be more of a monster than I thought. We're better off without him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mmh. A shame we won't have access to his intel, but I trust your judgement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171870" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wonder if we'll ever run into him again down the road. There're a whole lot of stars out there, but the Galaxy seems like a smaller place every day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bah, I'm just babbling. Don't let me waste your time, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow. Enough of a monster that even an Imp says he's not worth it. Sounds like you made the right call, Commander. Oh, um... no offense intended.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, a shame. Would have loved to have access to his intel, but it sounds like he was too unstable to be worthwhile.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1171877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, we'll find others.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175963" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Innocent Look] That's not normal for Republic military housing?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175964" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Say Nothing]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe the droid figured soft pillows are perfect for you soft Pub soldiers?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175973" id2="17" version="1065353216">Least we don't spend more time killing each other than the enemy. Maybe you'd actually win a war for once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hghh.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1176488" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Say nothing]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1176704" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's a great soldier, but be careful about giving him command. I think he's reckless--the type to take unnecessary risks. His record seems to prove it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176705" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. Noted. Maybe we set him up as an officer and have him train some of our better volunteers. Apply his experience without risking his battlefield decision making.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1176707" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Smirk] It does lead to you working with all kinds of interesting people, doesn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1176708" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph. That it does.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177141" id2="17" version="1065353216">Qyzen Fess: fearless warrior, renowned hunter, expert survivalist, and respected as a leader amongst his people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177172" id2="17" version="1065353216">By itself, word that Qyzen is working with us will give us huge inroads with most any Trandoshan clan out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1177173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not to mention the Ex-Warstalkers Qyzen's bringing with him. They'll be a powerful addition to our forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1177186" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to keep a close eye on the Ex-Warstalkers that have come with him, though. They used to fight for the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177187" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree entirely. In fact, I've already had the lot scheduled for regular psych evaluations to be sure. I don't think it'll be an issue though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177189" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was mainly Kephess that the Dread Masters had control over. Most of the Warstalkers were freely following his strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177191" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmh. We've got ourselves a Trandoshan hero leading some of the strongest Trandoshan forces this galaxy's ever seen. Pretty good day in my book, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177192" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely, Commander. Still, just to be sure, I've arranged psych check-ups for all of them, considering their background with the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1177195" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think the Ex-Warstalkers he's bringing with him will be all that useful, though. They were crushed on Denova.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177198" id2="17" version="1065353216">With respect, Commander, I couldn't disagree more. The Warstalkers were among the most effective and respected merc units in the galaxy. They never lost a fight before Denova.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177206" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Warstalkers lost because the Dread Masters compromised their command and forced some pretty big mistakes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177218" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which reminds me, I should arrange regular psych check-ups for all of them. Can't be too careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177236" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess none of that's news to you though, considering the extensive history the two of you have together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177246" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's even respected by the Jedi Order. Not many Trandoshans get invited into the Jedi Temple on Tython just to catch up with old friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander. Is Rusk with you?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180470" id2="17" version="1065353216">No--we don't need a slaver in the Alliance. His unit of &quot;convicts&quot; weren't actually convicted, so much as forcibly drafted off the streets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180471" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's... horrible! I had no idea. In fact, I'm going to report it. I've still got a lot of friends on Coruscant who can get to the bottom of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Also, I'll try to screen my information more carefully in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180474" id2="17" version="1065353216">It got complicated. He pulled a blaster on me--I won.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180475" id2="17" version="1065353216">He was about to shoot an old crew mate, and I wasn't about to let it happen. Got a new recruit for Hylo out of it, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180480" id2="17" version="1065353216">He was reckless, and couldn't see reason. We're better off without him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180481" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see. I'm sorry to hear that, but it seems like you made the right call. We'll look elsewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180482" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see. Sorry to hear that. At least you got an old crewmate back--I'm sure Hylo will appreciate the help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Back so soon... I take it things didn't go so well.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not at all. He more or less cut comms as soon as he saw who I was, but not before threatening to kill me when I least expect it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bah, I was afraid it might go down this way. Oh well, nothing to be done about it. Like I said, if he can't handle working alongside Imperials, there's no point in bringing him in.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180489" id2="17" version="1065353216">He did not react very well to my bringing up Balmorra. In hindsight, that may have been a mistake.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah... I probably shouldn't have brought up Balmorra....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180491" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, it didn't. He basically saw me, said he'd kill me when I least expect it, and then cut comms.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zenith made it pretty clear that he's not going to work with Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180493" id2="17" version="1065353216">I made one small joke. Zenith blew up and threatened to kill me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1180494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on, I warned you about this! Did you even read the alert I sent you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189770" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've made a good start, Commander, but it's proving to be a lot harder than we thought to the merge Imperial and Republic forces. Differences in 'Command Philosophy'.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189772" id2="17" version="1065353216">For example, I just had to remind a certain Imperial Officer that it's unacceptable to open fire on a friendly fighter craft because it's failed a patrol maneuver.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1189773" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's terrible. We're short enough on soldiers and craft as it is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189774" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something obvious to the two of us, but not to this one. Dunno how much more of this depravity I can take.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1189775" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a waste. Should have let the craft return and then just shot the pilot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugh. Forgot who I was talking to for a second....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1189777" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing inspires quite like fear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Long story short, Commander: we're getting there, and we'll figure it out. You keep bringing in the allies and equipment, we'll be off the ground in no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1189780" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Say Nothing]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1189784" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can't figure out how to work with old enemies, how can you ask everyone else to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189785" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right, sir.... We have to learn how to make this work, and it starts with leadership.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189790" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm happy to say that things are starting to come together a bit, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189792" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our forces have all been training together for a while now. There's an incident here or there, but the old rivalries are pretty well smoothed over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189794" id2="17" version="1065353216">All the equipment you've been securing for us also has morale up, too. Nothing brightens your day like new set of cutting edge hardware.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep bringing it in, Commander. We're going to be mounting our first operations soon. We'll need everything and everyone we can get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189797" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've come a long way, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189799" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was not easy, but after all the training and cooperation, we've finally got everyone feeling more like they're part of a unified alliance force, rather than a bunch of cobbled factions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189801" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're trained, equipped, and we've got ourselves the makings of what I dare call a small fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure, we can't take the Eternal-Fleet head-on, but we are mounting our own tactical operations. Initial results have been very encouraging, and fantastic for morale.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1189805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Things are only going to scale up from here, Commander. You keep bringing us everything you can find, we'll put every scrap to good use.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1189811" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have my sympathy, Admiral. I know this isn't easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1189812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow, that's pretty rough. Hang in there, Admiral.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
