<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>165</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/camp/hylo_visz.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1166421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey there, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1166426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, if it isn't the new Commander! We didn't get much of a chance to talk earlier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167645" id2="17" version="1065353216">You lost, or just slumming it down here with the likes of us?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1167646" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Smuggler Background] You kidding? The scent of engine grease... the sound of cargo loading... this place feels more like home than anywhere else on the base.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1167647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just stopping by to have a look at things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167648" id2="17" version="1065353216">A captain after my own heart. Couldn't have said it better myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, not to change the subject, but that XS Freighter outside is yours, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even just having a quick look around the outside, you can tell there's been a lot of love put into that ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1167913" id2="17" version="1065353216">You might be the first person I've ever met who can properly appreciate my ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah! Well you don't get as good as I am if you can't understand that looks don't matter, so long as a ship's got it where it counts.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1167915" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you and I are going to get along just fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1167920" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just so long as we're clear about the part where it's my ship, not yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep 'em holstered, Commander. I know better than to step between a captain and their ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Likewise, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, here it is in all its glory: the beating heart of your alliance's supply chain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Besides, nice as your ship might be, it's not like it can really hold a candle to mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1167943" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugh. What a rabble....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167944" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph. Might want to work on that attitude &quot;Commander&quot;, or you're going to have a hard time making new friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1167960" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, explain to me who are you again?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167961" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Alliance needs a lot to keep it going--food, equipment, weapons, ships--and it needs to get everything without popping up on Arcann's scanners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167970" id2="17" version="1065353216">So naturally your friends went and found the best, yours truly, to run the supply end of this operation. I make sure you get what you need without raising any eyebrows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167972" id2="17" version="1065353216">That kind of work takes a true professional. Someone who knows where to look, how to ask, and who to ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167976" id2="17" version="1065353216">All at perfectly reasonable contract rates--plus hazard premiums and a discretion fee.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167977" id2="17" version="1065353216">How've you never heard of Hylo Visz?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1167978" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I didn't know better, I'd say you're running a massive smuggling ring out of our base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167980" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh right, the carbonite poisoning... the doctor warned us that it might have messed with your head a bit. Didn't mean to rub it in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167982" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyway, I'm Hylo Visz, one of the best freelance transport captains the galaxy has ever seen. Might be the best, but I try not to brag.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1167983" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Skepticism] Right....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1167984" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Sarcasm] And so humble, too....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167985" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, it's only arrogance if I'm not as good as I say, otherwise it's just plain honesty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember how the Mandos blockaded the Hydian Way during the war? How Coruscant was on the brink of starvation and riots, until some hero came along, broke the blockade, and saved the planet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, that hero was me. And you're welcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, that hero was me. Not that I have anything against Imps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167991" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was never officially with the Republic or anything. I just did it for the money. A whole, awful lot of money. No hard feelings?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1167992" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Imperial Background] No hard feelings. The Empire respects competence and talent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167993" id2="17" version="1065353216">In that case you're gonna love working with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1167995" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Glare Coldly]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1167996" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Mandalorian Background] No hard feelings. Mandalorians respect and honor a worthy foe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Likewise--that blockade was really something to see. Took everything I had to bust it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1167998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right... touchy subject... noted.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1167999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait--that all happened decades ago. You don't look that old.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heh, that's... a bit complicated. Suffice it to say, I wound up laying low in a stasis cell for a long time. Didn't know it'd freeze my aging too, but I'll take it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh... One last thing, while you're out and about. You ever find a Devaronian by the name of Gault Rennow, or Tyresius Lokai, you let me know...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Need to put a few new holes into that backstabber. Long story.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pleasure to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly how many credits are we talking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168009" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are a lot of zeroes. Don't worry though, it's not coming straight out of your pocket. Probably.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168010" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can they be charging us for this? The Eternal Empire is everybody's problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fuel isn't free, Commander, and neither is time. Some of these people have families to look after, and a lot of them have debts--the kind you can't ignore.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing helps keep secrets like a steady flow of credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168014" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of the great truths of the galaxy, Commander. Fact is, a lot of freighter captains are happy just to have steady work from someone who won't shoot 'em in the back when it's time to pay up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168015" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm looking out for them so they keep looking out for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168016" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Roll your eyes]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyhow, I'd give you the grand tour, but we're all pretty busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168021" id2="17" version="1065353216">All the same, I have to admit that I've stretched my network of contacts pretty thin. If this alliance is gonna get much bigger, we're gonna need a lot more help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Smugglers, bounty hunters, maybe even pirates.... anyone who has useful skills, or just knows their way around the underworld. You find anyone good, bring 'em in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168027" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've always got my ear to the ground, too. If I find any promising leads, I'll let you know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168032" id2="17" version="1065353216">You expect me to believe that a spacer with your resume doesn't know Hylo Visz?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168033" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Smuggler Background] Well, clearly not the best--that spot's already taken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168040" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're actually not wrong, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168043" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know a massive smuggling operation when I see it. Just what are you up to down here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just doing what I do best: moving cargo and getting paid.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168049" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you know you've actually avoided detection?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168050" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did I not mention that I'm the best?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seriously though, the only reason this base is still intact is that Arcann doesn't know where to look. The proof that we're doing our job is that you're still alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168054" id2="17" version="1065353216">No hard feelings? Do you have any idea what the loss of that blockade cost us?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168057" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Smuggler Background] I've done plenty of things that were more impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, keep telling yourself that, Captain....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168060" id2="17" version="1065353216">You helped ease the suffering of billions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168064" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Bounty Hunter] Wait a minute--you're Gault's old flame. The one he rescued out of stasis on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168065" id2="17" version="1065353216">That backstabbing bag of desh is the reason I was in there to begin with! What he pulled after we got our pay for breaking the Hydian Way Blockade....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teaming up with him was the biggest mistake of my life. I ever catch up to that bishwag again, I'm giving him a bolt between the eyes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry... kind of a sore spot....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168075" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, Commander. What's going on?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168076" id2="17" version="1065353216">How are things going around here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not gonna lie, things are really tight around here right now. We're straining supplies as it is, and it's only going to get worse as we try to scale up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168083" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm moving as much as I can through the contacts we've got, and the few captains we have are running themselves ragged just keeping up with that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168106" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this whole grand alliance idea wants to go anywhere, we really need to broaden our contact network, build a better supply base, and step up recruitment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168113" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, things here aren't as bad as when we first started, but if you ask me, the situation is still too close for comfort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hate to sound like a looping holovid, but we need more. More contacts, more resources, and more people. Any help you could give us would go a long way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, as a matter of fact, I just managed to nail down most of the essentials. Don't worry about thanking me, I already know I'm great.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168123" id2="17" version="1065353216">Friend of a friend of a friend got us in contact with a major mover on Bothawui, a sympathizer. Wouldn't have happened without the reputation you've managed to build up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168125" id2="17" version="1065353216">So now we've got a lot of the basics on lockdown--though that just means even more work for our freighters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168127" id2="17" version="1065353216">As usual, keep an eye out of for anyone who can lend help to our operation here, any resources, or any leads on suppliers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168132" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, don't look now, but I think we might have actually managed to turn the corner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168134" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're set up with a pretty broad supply of the basics--it's not perfect, but we've got what we need with a little room to grow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168136" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're even starting to find sources for the rarer stuff. We've actually found a contact in the Zakuul Undercity--she's got access to Eternal Empire tech.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ol' Doctor Hutt's tripping over his tail at the chance to play with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168140" id2="17" version="1065353216">I mean, don't get me wrong, we've still got a lot more to do before everything is said and done. So keep your eye out as usual for people or supplies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168142" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we're actually kinda stable for the first time. Feels nice. Maybe I'll give the crews a day off....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168143" id2="17" version="1065353216">What can I do to help around here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168144" id2="17" version="1065353216">Getting by in the underworld takes three things--the right friends, the right information, and credits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168155" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best thing you can do is keep an eye out for good people that can be convinced to join us, and for any underworld information you can get your hands on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168157" id2="17" version="1065353216">The more people we get and the bigger our contact network gets, the smoother things are gonna go here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168194" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Give Smuggled Goods] I've found some useful things for you....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168195" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooh, nice. I'll sift through this and see what we've got.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168199" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in More Smuggled Goods]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168200" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Back]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168202" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll let you get back to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168203" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fly safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168204" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah. The one good thing that came out of that whole Belsavis mess was that the stasis actually froze my aging. Guess that's something, at least.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168206" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey Commander, just wanted to say nice job bringing in Bowdaar.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168208" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's got a sharp mind, good instincts, and a lot of experience. Not to mention all of the interesting people he knows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168210" id2="17" version="1065353216">The intimidation factor is good too! People are gonna think twice about trying to cross an intergalactic pit fighting champion, even if he is retired.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168211" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Smuggler Background] Little furball's actually quite a pilot too! Taught him myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168212" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ohh, that explains the bad habits... don't worry, I'll break him outta those in no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168213" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Smirk knowingly]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168216" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess I'd better get to it. Stay safe out there, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168217" id2="17" version="1065353216">A great addition to our crew, Commander. Keep 'em coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168222" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Jawa bounty hunter... never thought I'd see the day. Even has his own crew....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168224" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's not exactly fearless, but Blizz is hands down ten times braver than any Jawa I've ever seen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168227" id2="17" version="1065353216">Little guy really knows his stuff when it comes to a firefight, too. Full custom hardware as good as anything credits could buy. Nobody who looked at him would ever guess what's coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168229" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd be happy just having him watch over our riskier jobs, but he's got all kinds of friends and contacts with other Jawas. Connections we could never make on our own.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168230" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Bounty Hunter Background] You don't have to tell me, little guy was part of my old crew for years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Takes a lot to impress me, Commander, but consider me impressed. Great find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168233" id2="17" version="1065353216">So that's where he gets it. Yeah, I guess that makes a lot of sense.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168235" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Let her continue]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168284" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow, Commander. Skadge. Got to admit I'm a little on the fence about this last one. I've worked with his type before, and it can go real wrong real fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168288" id2="17" version="1065353216">I mean, sure he's got the Black Sun wrapped around his finger--which is great, we've got access to all their muscle, territory, and contacts...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168290" id2="17" version="1065353216">...which'll let us run some jobs through them where they're strongest, covering our own tracks better...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168292" id2="17" version="1065353216">...and maybe I could have him watch over our riskier runs. Nobody in their right mind would try to mess with him. Even if they tried, he'd just rip 'em apart....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168294" id2="17" version="1065353216">Know what, I take it all back. Maybe he'll wind up being more use than he is trouble. I just need to be real careful he doesn't get too bored....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168296" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take it from a smuggler with experience--sometimes it's better to just shoot 'em before they have a chance to give you grief.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168297" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'll be a useful tool. Some jobs require a sledgehammer. A big, psychopathic sledgehammer.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168298" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Bounty Hunter Background] As long as I'm around, Skadge will behave. Give him a wide berth when he's in a bad mood--other than that, he's pretty useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168301" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess you'd know better than anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168305" id2="17" version="1065353216">Having the boss of the Black Sun on our side has got to be worth something.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168306" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll leave it to &quot;the best&quot; to figure out how to make it work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168314" id2="17" version="1065353216">So here I am, minding my own intergalactic smuggling operation, when some random XS Freighter pulls a hotshot landing, and out walks Nico Okarr.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168316" id2="17" version="1065353216">I really thought they'd just turn out to be more rumors, but hey, I'll take it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168318" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guy knows his stuff, has a lifetime of connections in the underworld, a name that opens doors... not to mention he's a crack-shot gunslinger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168321" id2="17" version="1065353216">And a fine pilot to boot. He's almost as good as me, and that's not the kind of thing I say lightly.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168322" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least he used to be--isn't he getting a little old for this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never sell a scoundrel short just because they're old, Commander. Just means they know twice as many tricks.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168324" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Smuggler Background] Fancy that, I tracked down someone you couldn't. Guess we know who the real captain is around here....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168325" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have to ask him how he managed to float those rumors to us....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1168330" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're welcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hate to pop your shields, Captain, but we found Nico because he wanted us to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1168334" id2="17" version="1065353216">At any rate, he's going to be an all-around huge help. He's good enough that he can actually help take some of the pressure off of me, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170732" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey Commander, someone's been messing with our food processors and I'm guessing it's that C2-series droid. He even went onto some of the ships.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170734" id2="17" version="1065353216">The last thing any of our freelancers want is someone telling them what they can or can't eat. Honestly, I'm surprised that droid didn't wind up shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170737" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, Commander! Want a sandwich? That C2 droid just came and dropped off a crate of packed lunches for us. They're pretty tasty--that droid can cook!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170739" id2="17" version="1065353216">And they're all neatly packed up too--our pilots can just grab a few when they go out on a run. Maybe I had that droid figured wrong. Thank him for us, would ya?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, Commander, I'm not sure what that C2 droid thinks he's doing, but he's left pillows all over the hanger and added cushions to every chair he could find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170744" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't figure out how he manages to get onto ships without getting spotted. It's kind of creepy how good he is at sneaking around....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyhow, this stuff is not helping--it's just getting in the way. Honestly, I think we should just switch that thing off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, Commander--I just had half my crew waste most of a day tracking down a leaky cargo container.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Turns out the smell was just that blasted C2 droid playing around in our air circulators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1170751" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a giant waste of time. That droid is more trouble than he's worth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1178325" id2="17" version="1065353216">Today is looking to be a pretty good day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182974" id2="17" version="1065353216">You got some nerve, Commander. I ask you to help out a friend, and you don't just do the exact opposite... you bring me some whacked-out psychopath?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Between this new... thing... and Skadge, I'm getting a lot more killers than I really need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1182977" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll give him space and keep him fed, but I'm not putting him in with any of my crews. Feel free to take him away for missions all you want.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1183033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for accommodating him. Broonmark is going to be very useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1183034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Broonmark is a... personal associate. You will keep him happy--understand?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1183035" id2="17" version="1065353216">I apologize for the loss of your Wookiee allies. It wasn't an easy decision.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1183037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do your job and skip the complaints, Hylo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah. Suddenly I'm understanding a lot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just leave me out of whatever he's useful for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183040" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt I want to know the details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got supply runs stopping through Kashyyyk already, Commander. Plus some reliable muscle that nobody wants to mess with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gonna chalk this one up as a big win. Thanks for your help!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Between this guy and Broonmark, I'm getting a lot more killers than I need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183050" id2="17" version="1065353216">Inspirational stuff--really.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1183052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time I got back to work.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
