<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>49</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/rakata_prime/shared/command_center.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127521" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's it. We're in. Theron?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay... according to the structural plans, the only way to get at the head Revanites is through that conscription center.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127525" id2="17" version="1065353216">The cyborgs are dormant for now, but they're set to go on high alert once they detect you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127527" id2="17" version="1065353216">A console overload will fry them from the inside.... Nope. Can't work the power safeties from here. You'll have to do the honors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127529" id2="17" version="1065353216">A sound plan. Theron, why can't I get this sensor to work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because Jakarro isn't a big fan of upkeep? Probably a dead relay. I'll check it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that he's gone, might I recommend not doing as Theron suggests?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127535" id2="17" version="1065353216">An overload would destroy the data as well. The Empire might want its own Infinite Army someday. You would have to fight those cyborgs, but....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127536" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're abberations. I'm setting the console to overload.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127536" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want them all dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127537" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127538" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you have a problem with my judgment, you'd be wise to keep it to yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't like my decision? Tough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, there you go. Nice work. For, you know, being Imperial and all....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Room's clear of vital signs. You're all set.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127546" id2="17" version="1065353216">There goes any concern of you getting too cozy with the Republic spy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Smart play. I'm impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make no mistake: I serve the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127548" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the Empire serves me cash, so let's try it your way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127549" id2="17" version="1065353216">As do I. We'll do this your way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, what happened? Why's the console still running?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127552" id2="17" version="1065353216">We couldn't make it work. The room will have to be traversed the hard way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127554" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so. Hey, those sensor relays were fine, by the way. Not sure what the problem is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was. The sensor appears to be working again....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent work. Theron is slicing into the facility's structural plans now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure? What did you try?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128711" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not looking great... your only option is to pass through the conscription center, dead ahead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128713" id2="17" version="1065353216">The cyborgs ahead are in some kind of &quot;standby&quot; mode. They'll activate as soon as you enter the room--be ready for a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128715" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blasted sensors... Lana, could you do a quick perimeter check? I can't tell if these contacts are real or not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128717" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128719" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, we don't have much time. We can't risk any of the tech in that conscription center falling into Imperial hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128721" id2="17" version="1065353216">Overload the console. It will fry everything inside and kill the cyborgs before they have a chance to wake up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128722" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not going to murder people in their sleep, Theron. We'll take our chances.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128722" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not how I operate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128723" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got a Sith breathing down our necks, crazy cultists all around us, and you want to take chances?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128724" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let fear guide our actions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128725" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we have something to be afraid of?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently not. I'll add the sensors to the list of things on this ship that we can't rely on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128729" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll contact you if anything else comes up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128732" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to do what's right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128733" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better to play it safe. I'm setting the console to overload now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128733" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thinking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128736" id2="17" version="1065353216">What was that? Is everything all right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128738" id2="17" version="1065353216">We found a shortcut. Anything out there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128740" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, nothing. Jakarro's sensors clearly need a bit of adjustment. We wouldn't want to be misled again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Definitely not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129021" id2="17" version="1065353216">The perimeter is clear. Is everything all right in here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129025" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go ahead and keep moving. We'll stay in contact.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
