<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>31</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/rakata_prime/shared/jakarro.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127344" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jakarro. Deefour.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1127345" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is about time! I thought maybe you got lost!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jakarro! Display at least a modicum of respect!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1127349" id2="17" version="1065353216">At last! Now that you're here, vengeance can be ours!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127458" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey. We're set to move on the Temple of the Ancients when you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127459" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the traitors' base of operations?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah. The Rakata designed the Star Forge in that temple thousands of years ago. Now it's Arkous and Darok's grunt factory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron and I will be monitoring your progress from Jakarro's ship. We'll assist you as we can, keep you apprised of matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1127464" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I will go ahead of you to make destruction and draw enemy fire!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1127466" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I still want revenge against my former captors, so I will join you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127468" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll what?! Jakarro, I agreed to no such thing! Wait, was this the talk with Agent Shan you powered me down for?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1127470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut up, droid, or you will be turned off for good!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127472" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should warn you, it's a rough road to the temple. The area's lousy with tribal Rakatans more than happy to fight. Found that out the hard way....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wonderful. We're all going to die. Wonderful!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remain focused and all will be well. I'm sure of it. We'll be in touch soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1128081" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want my revenge, and I want it now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we have a plan ready?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128610" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know if it's fair to describe it as a &quot;plan&quot;, necessarily....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1128612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quiet, droid!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128614" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've done a bit of scouting. The Revanites are camped in the Temple of the Ancients, an old ruin nearby.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1128616" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will fight side-by-side, annihilating all who try to oppose us until Colonel Darok and Darth Arkous lie dead!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1128617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since you are not quite as fearsome as the mighty Jakarro, I will act as diversion, drawing the enemy away while you approach the Temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128747" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? This isn't what we discussed! It's suicide! I demand that you detach me this instant!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1128749" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will join the rest of your body soon enough if you won't be silent!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128750" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of security do the Revanites have?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128751" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've convinced some of the local Rakatan tribes to patrol the areas around the temple for them. A truly barbaric lot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128753" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Revanites themselves are guarding the temple grounds. They're fully armed and paranoid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128755" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wonderful....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128757" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll be keeping an eye on things from the ship. As long as we all stay sharp, we'll get this conspiracy shut down permanently.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128759" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force serve you well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129027" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've gotten this far without being detected--it's time for you to go in and make some noise.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
