<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>150</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/rakata_prime/shared/lana_beniko.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127108" id2="17" version="1065353216">I feel the dark side everywhere. Remnants of the Star Forge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127113" id2="17" version="1065353216">The shuttle is ready for our departure to Rakata Prime.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127118" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to see you again, as always, but I'm afraid any further niceties will have to wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dark times are fast approaching.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127351" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know I've mentioned before a strange disturbance within the Force--a sort of writhing mass tied to Darth Arkous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127353" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought I'd use my connection to Arkous to seek out others tied to the disturbance--Revanites working against us from within. I found a few.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you learn anything?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127354" id2="17" version="1065353216">And?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127355" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we could convince them they were wrong to betray the Empire, they'd be compelled to help us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127355" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's turn them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127356" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's too late for that. From what I've been able to gather, it's clear their devotion to the Order of Revan is unshakable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127358" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave them for me to punish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127360" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want their names, and I want them now. They don't deserve to live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127361" id2="17" version="1065353216">These subversives are still in play, Wrath. Knowledge of their existence gives us leverage. Gives us power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127363" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should like to visit these Revanites. Tell me who they are so I might destroy them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tempting, but we need them alive and undisturbed if we're to maintain our strategic edge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127366" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me names. Last thing any of them'll ever see will be blaster fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127367" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate the offer, but we can't go placing bounties on embedded Revanites. Not yet, anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127369" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make me a list of these Revanites. Every last one of them will meet with a unique and tragic accident.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127370" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not yet. We still don't know how deep this conspiracy runs. But we are learning more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron Shan helped me decipher coded messages between the Revanites. Due to your interference on Manaan, they've accelerated their schedule.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that they know they're up against us, who could blame them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127373" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're afraid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127374" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough tip-toeing. We know for a fact that Arkous is a traitor. We can expose him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127374" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arkous must be reported.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127375" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't just go making accusations. Darth Arkous is a trusted and powerful member of the Dark Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127376" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I am the Emperor's Wrath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127377" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know the council would never stand for you questioning the loyalty of one of their own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127379" id2="17" version="1065353216">You forget to whom you speak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127380" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arkous may have joined the council after you, but he's known the others for ages. They trust him implicitly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127383" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's another way to stop Arkous. Theron's traced his activities to Rakata Prime. He and Colonel Darok are building their Infinite Army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127385" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shan's goals may be aligned with ours at the moment, but you need to watch how much you share with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127385" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still don't trust Shan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127386" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've not forgotten he's with the SIS, but that doesn't mean he isn't useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127388" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron Shan? You couldn't have brought this to my attention instead?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127388" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shan, and not me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127389" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would have thought it beneath your prestige. Anyway, Theron happened to contact me so I made use of him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127390" id2="17" version="1065353216">What did he want?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron's tracked Arkous and Colonel Darok to a base on Rakata Prime. They're building their Infinite Army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127393" id2="17" version="1065353216">And there's more. The implants they're using--they're made from pieces of the Star Forge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127394" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star Forge.... There was a machine on Nar Shaddaa that was built from it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127395" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd heard rumors. It required virtually nothing to create most anything. That was the Star Forge's power as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127397" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star Forge.... Tell me what you know about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127398" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star Forge was a Force-imbued, self-sustaining shipyard. Rakatan. It was destroyed centuries ago, but the Revanites have recovered some of the wreckage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127400" id2="17" version="1065353216">Its technology makes the soldiers nearly immortal. Seizes their minds as well, placing them under the Revanites' full control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127401" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's go stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127403" id2="17" version="1065353216">These fools will soon learn that only the Emperor is immortal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127405" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Arkous's gall is exceeded only by his stupidity. He has betrayed the Empire and the Dark Council for the last time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127407" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gonna put that immortality part to the test, then see how Arkous and his Republic friend do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127409" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're taking a trip to Rakata Prime. I'll drive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127410" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need, Hunter. I have a shuttle ready and waiting right here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127412" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've had enough of Arkous thinking he can play me for a fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127414" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ready a shuttle to Rakata Prime. We're going.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127415" id2="17" version="1065353216">My shuttle is already prepped, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127417" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a shuttle waiting, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127419" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire should try that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not that I want to be out of work, but why doesn't the Empire make its own army of mindless, invulnerable cyborg-things?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127422" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we can learn how to, we just might.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127424" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to learn how they accomplished this. It could prove useful to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127425" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed, it could.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127427" id2="17" version="1065353216">A generous orbital bombardment should take out Arkous, Darok, any other Revanites and their Infinite Army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127427" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll bomb them from space.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127428" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to learn the shape and extent of the Order of Revan. Blasting their leadership out of existence from afar won't help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron and Jakarro are waiting for us planetside. The sooner we depart for Rakata Prime, the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127432" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will see Darth Arkous answer for his crimes. Most importantly, we'll stop the Order of Revan before the balance tips in their favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Arkous knows you're here. I'd say he sensed your presence, but I imagine it's all the commotion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127482" id2="17" version="1065353216">He and Colonel Darok have shored up defenses outside the temple with their new conscripts. You know what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127565" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you reach the main conscription site, open a line on the control console. Theron can slice it remotely that way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arkous and Darok must know it's over for them. They've fled to the rooftop where they have a shuttle waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127570" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll shoot them down if we have to, but we really need the chance to interrogate them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get to the roof. Hurry!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127937" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127939" id2="17" version="1065353216">The way Revan was laying waste to that place, I wasn't sure you'd come out of it in one piece.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127941" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you talking about? I'm hardly in one piece....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1127943" id2="17" version="1065353216">Switch off your speech processor, droid, before one piece is all that is left!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyway, my point is: glad you got out of there. Any ally right now is a welcome ally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127946" id2="17" version="1065353216">We took care of Arkous, Darok and their Infinite Army, but where does that leave us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127946" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the next step?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127947" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a good question. Now that we know Revan's in the picture, everything changes--for the worse. In fact, it's already started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever do you mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127951" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll fill you in, Deefour. Come on, Jakarro, let's give them a chance to talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127953" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] You like me, Shan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127955" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I didn't know any better, Theron, I'd think you were somewhat infatuated with me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, it's okay. You can admit it. You're totally into me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127959" id2="17" version="1065353216">So coy. I think someone in the SIS has a crush on me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127960" id2="17" version="1065353216">What, me? Into you? That's so.... You know, don't be ridiculous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127962" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I may say, Agent Shan, you appear to be rather flush all of a sudden.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127964" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're gonna-- Jakarro and I and the droid, we're leaving now so you can have your... official Imperial debrief or whatever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127966" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't want to deal with you any more than I have to. Leave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get out. Now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127967" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a real piece of work, you know that? I helped save you--twice!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron, please.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127971" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, fine. Whatever. Come on, Jakarro.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127973" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana, when you're done, we can start picking out backwaters to go lie low in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127975" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we'd at least recovered the conscription protocols for the Infinite Army, this might feel more like a victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not that we have anyone in the Empire to trust right now. The Revanites have just proven they're everywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some good news: I was able to extract a good amount of data from the Infinite Army conscription console.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, we can't possibly hand it over to our Imperial colleagues. The Revanites have just proven they're everywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jakarro's had twelve death sentences declared on him, Theron's been disavowed by the SIS... and the Empire's placed a bounty on my head for the murder of Darth Arkous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127984" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nonsense. I'll vouch for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127986" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoever's behind this will answer to me. Everyone will know you're innocent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127987" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate that, Wrath, I do. But you can't fight this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127990" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done nothing of the sort. I'll clear up this entire matter with the Dark Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dark Lord, if I may, you would do well to disassociate yourself from me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127994" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one takes credit for my kills, whether they want to or not. I'll make this right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127995" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. Remain in the Empire's good favor. If asked to hunt me down, say that you will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127998" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll go to Darth Marr himself and make sure this asinine charge goes away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, Commander, speak to no one. Not even Darth Marr.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128001" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to put a stop to the order, and we need to do it now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128001" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is out of control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128002" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll get no argument from me. In fact, Theron and I have been discussing the best way to go about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any idea what they're paying? Maybe it'll be worth my while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128004" id2="17" version="1065353216">A bounty? Too funny.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128005" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose the upside is at least one of us is in a joking mood. At least I hope you're joking. What a mess....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128007" id2="17" version="1065353216">A fugitive from justice. Won't you be helpful now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128007" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're useless to me now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128008" id2="17" version="1065353216">That isn't fair. It's not as though I wanted this to happen. If I could fix this here and now, I would--but I can't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our names can't be cleared unless we expose the Revanites, and we can't expose the Revanites without knowing who to expose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128012" id2="17" version="1065353216">The way forward is clear: Theron, Jakarro and I are going underground. We'll find a way to uncover Revan's plan and stop him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since we can't take the direct approach anymore, the three of you working in secret is our best option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128014" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I may suggest, you should continue normally with your life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three fugitives on the run against a vast conspiracy that spans two galactic powers? Have you lost your mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Terrible idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128017" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am as lucid as ever and I say we can. You'll have your own role to play in this, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128019" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't do it alone. You'll need me alongside you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128019" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm coming with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right now, you're the closest thing the Empire has to a soul, Wrath. Without you, they'll forget themselves, fall apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128022" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dark Council is short one member, and may yet be further compromised. They need you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like it or not, Hunter, the people of the Empire have come to see you as a hero. They need you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128026" id2="17" version="1065353216">For all intents and purposes, you are Imperial Intelligence. The Empire needs you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be who you are, but be observant, and tell no one the truth about us or what you know. Above all, do not try to contact me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make this plan work, Lana.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do well out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128030" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do everything in my power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128031" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish you didn't have to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128031" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] I'll miss you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128032" id2="17" version="1065353216">It won't be easy for me, either. Just know that I'll be thinking of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128033" id2="17" version="1065353216">When will you learn that I don't take orders from you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't tell me what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do what you will. I'll be unable to stop you, the Empire will fall, and then perhaps the galaxy after that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128036" id2="17" version="1065353216">All our fates ultimately rest in your hands. Remember that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128040" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't reach you in Jakarro's ship! Take the shuttle!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron and I will-- We'll-- We'll meet you on Manaan. Now go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128111" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Arkous is intelligent, manipulative and immensely powerful. We mustn't get overconfident.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140225" id2="17" version="1065353216">Infinite Army conscripts. They're further along with production than we suspected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140226" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron's been monitoring Revanite chatter. Somewhere near you they've discovered a hidden store of Rakata weapons. See that they don't get the chance to use them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140227" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks as though their arena needs a challenger. If you're going to get past them, you'll have to give them a show they'll never forget.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140228" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd hoped to avoid much of the tribal area, but the terrain doesn't appear to be cooperating with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140230" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have to pass through the Rakatan settlement to get to the temple. It's further along the beach.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
