<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>57</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/rakata_prime/shared/rooftop_access.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127577" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait! Wait!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127579" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jakarro still wishes to confront the men who betrayed him and left us for dead. As would I, actually.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1127581" id2="17" version="1065353216">What the droid said! We are coming with you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127587" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the matter, Arkous? Shuttle not ready yet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127588" id2="17" version="1065353216">We Revanites went through a great deal of trouble to reach this point in our campaign. For you to hamper our progress, it's... regrettable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127590" id2="17" version="1065353216">You, Lana... you were never anything more than pawns to us. Important pawns, but pawns all the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me your plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127593" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you speak another word, it had better involve what you and your Revanites are planning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127594" id2="17" version="1065353216">I demand to know what absurdity you and your cult have concocted. Speak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127595" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the part where you give up and tell me everything, Arkous. Everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127596" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not even the twentieth person to underestimate me. I have the upper hand now, Sith Lord--so talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127597" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, this is where I outline our grand design and then you decide whether or not to spare my life?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127599" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wretched traitor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even among the most deceitful of the Dark Council, you stand out as a spectacular cretin, Arkous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127602" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm appalled that a worm such as you was ever deemed my equal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127603" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't even belong to the Empire and I can't wait to scrape you off my boot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pawns? Please. You wouldn't have lasted an hour as Minister of Intelligence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127605" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insults? It's no surprise that's all you're capable of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127607" id2="17" version="1065353216">We both know I'm more valuable than that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1127607" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could join you....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imagine it: the Emperor's Wrath leading the Order of Revan into a new era.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why have just one Revanite in the Dark Council when you could have two?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bet you need a lot of contracts carried out. Why not buy yourself an exclusively Revanite bounty hunter?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your Order of Revan could use someone with my skill set. With my connections.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, yes, but of course--you came all this way and ruined our efforts simply to sign up.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1127615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough! Darth Arkous will not cooperate! We kill him before he flees!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127617" id2="17" version="1065353216">This grotesque alien beast does have it partly figured out. Indeed, I won't cooperate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127619" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I'm not fleeing. We will stand our ground and put an end to your perpetual interruption. Colonel?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127621" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you could see what we were doing--what we want for the galaxy. But you can't see. You'll just have to die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128110" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait for us!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1128764" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're going to confront the men who betrayed us! We will spill their blood together!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please try to headbutt them with your own skull this time!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your plans are finished. The conspiracy ends now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128773" id2="17" version="1065353216">My, but we have a very high opinion of ourselves, don't we?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128775" id2="17" version="1065353216">This project would have accelerated our plans considerably. Losing it is regrettable, but it will not stop us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128777" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done a fair bit of damage, it's true. But the project isn't a total loss--after all, you've helpfully delivered yourselves for slaughter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128778" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've infiltrated the Republic and the Empire, raised an army of fanatics--why? What are you trying to achieve?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why are you doing all this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128779" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have a plan. You're not a part of it. That's all that matters now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128781" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surrender. Now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128783" id2="17" version="1065353216">The time for threats is over. Abandon this madness, before it destroys you both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128784" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not too late--not even for someone who's fallen as far as you. You can still be redeemed, if you will only release your hatred.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi platitudes are meaningless. All that matters is the plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel, you're not a fool--you can see your tactical situation just as well as me. Drop your weapon, and get your Sith friend to do the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128788" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tactics mean nothing. The plan has been formed over countless decades. You cannot outmaneuver it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128790" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't con a con artist. Your project is tanked. You've got nothing left. Just give it up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128796" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was planning on a little slaughter myself, actually. But I had a pair of lying traitors in mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128796" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the ones dying today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128797" id2="17" version="1065353216">Call us whatever you want. Words are meaningless. Nothing matters but the plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1128799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is it part of your plan to be torn limb from limb?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128801" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and your simple-minded beast will have the fight you came for. Colonel?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get on with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129029" id2="17" version="1065353216">This? This isn't madness. Madness would be quitting before the plan is complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129031" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will never abandon the plan.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
