<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>125</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/rakata_prime/shared/theron_shan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128076" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you see Colonel Darok, tell him &quot;hi&quot; for me... with your fist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron--they made it! I knew it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1128627" id2="17" version="1065353216">We cannot wait forever!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128629" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, all right... we'll be there right away, Jakarro. Just don't tear the limbs off of anything. Anything else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, it's good that you're here. Our &quot;friends&quot; are eager to get started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get started with what, exactly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel Darok, Darth Arkous, and their Revanite friends.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since your operation on Manaan, Lana's uncovered a few more Revanites who've infiltrated the Republic military.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128637" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been slicing the traitors' communications, and tracked the messages back to Darok and Arkous. They're in a hidden facility on the planet Rakata Prime. That's our target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128638" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you think the Revanites know you've found their hideout?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128638" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are the Revanites on alert?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128639" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do we know about Rakata Prime?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128640" id2="17" version="1065353216">No more cloak-and-dagger stuff. Let's get the biggest weapons we can and blast them into dust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128640" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to vaporize them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128641" id2="17" version="1065353216">That kind of hardware isn't easy to come by. The Revanites will notice if we start collecting turbolasers and orbital strike bombs. We need to catch them by surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128643" id2="17" version="1065353216">The messages I've decoded... that cyborg technology you ran into on Manaan was just the prototype phase. On Rakata Prime, they're in full production.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128645" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're taking pieces of the Star Forge and implanting them into their own people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128647" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star Forge?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128648" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a Rakatan weapon: a giant self-sustaining factory that ran on the dark side of the Force. Revan destroyed it three hundred years ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128650" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pieces of debris are still active, though. They self-repair and even self-replicate under the right circumstances. With that technology grafted to their bodies, the Revanites become much harder to stop.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128651" id2="17" version="1065353216">It sounds like the longer we wait, the more of these cyborgs they'll have. Let's get moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'd better hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128652" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reminds me of Rakata technology that I dealt with on Tatooine. Nasty stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128652" id2="17" version="1065353216">I saw similar tech on Tatooine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cyborgs or not, they aren't invincible. I proved that on Manaan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Harder--but not invulnerable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128654" id2="17" version="1065353216">True enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jakarro's freighter should get us onto the planet's surface undetected. We'll plan our attack from there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128659" id2="17" version="1065353216">Things are going to get worse before they get better....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sensors are showing a lot of movement in the temple. The Revanites are mustering their defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128672" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look for a control console and open a channel there--I'll be able to slice into their systems remotely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128674" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're seeing movement on the temple roof--might be Darok and Arkous trying to make an escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Incoming fire is too heavy--we can't get to you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128863" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the amount of fire Revan's ship was laying down... I wasn't optimistic. It's good to see you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1128865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget all that--my ship had better be in one piece!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh no, I'd nearly forgotten! Several of my internal components were still aboard--the ship is all right, isn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128869" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ship is fine, come see for yourself. There's something we need to talk about, actually....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128871" id2="17" version="1065353216">It truly is a relief to see you safe.  I only wish we had more time together....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128872" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's going on? Are you leaving already?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128872" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128873" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's for the best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128875" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not going anywhere, Lana. You don't have to, either.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128875" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] Then let's make time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128876" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128878" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you'd love to spy on us a bit more, but oh, look at the time!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leaving? Good riddance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128879" id2="17" version="1065353216">That isn't what I meant at all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron and I learned some... troubling things after we escaped Rakata Prime.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jakarro took it better than I thought. You told her yet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jakarro took the news better than you'd think. Have you told him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128887" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think it's best if you do the honors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128889" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll meet again soon--I'm certain of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128891" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's pretty confident for someone with a bounty on their head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are the Revanites putting out bounty contracts now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not directly, no. It's an Imperial contract, for murdering Arkous. Under any other circumstances, she would've gotten a promotion for that kind of thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128895" id2="17" version="1065353216">They also arranged twelve separate death marks for Jakarro. That's a new record for him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128896" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128897" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Disavowed rogue agent, apprehend on sight.&quot; Pretty tame compared to the others. The Director must have stood up for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128898" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you know the Director, couldn't he tell you who's behind this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ask him who framed you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128899" id2="17" version="1065353216">I checked. The evidence of my imaginary crimes came in from our internal security division, all very well forged. He'll keep looking, but we can't risk more contact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you're a dangerous man to be around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128901" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] &quot;Rogue agent&quot;, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128902" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's why I have to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128904" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Revanites haven't been able to touch you yet--your record is still clean. But it won't stay that way if you're seen working with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana, Jakarro, Deefour, and I are all going off the grid. We need to stay hidden if we're going to continue our investigation--no contact, period.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128907" id2="17" version="1065353216">No contact at all, huh? Not even a little bit?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128907" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] No contact?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128908" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Revanites will be watching you, so do what you do best--travel the galaxy, achieve impossible things, and make it hard for them to keep up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would you let the Revanites frame you? We know the charges are fake--stand up to them!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128909" id2="17" version="1065353216">We shouldn't stand for this!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128910" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you've found their base of operations, we may be able to end this threat before it goes any further.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128913" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are we talking, here? Recon, or assault?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128913" id2="17" version="1065353216">How are we proceeding?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assault--the sooner the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128916" id2="17" version="1065353216">On a scale of one to ten, how suicidal is this one going to be?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128916" id2="17" version="1065353216">More mortal danger!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128917" id2="17" version="1065353216">No worse than usual. So maybe a twelve?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128919" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's the homeworld of the ancient Rakata--hence the name. Apparently there are still a few of them there, but their society has regressed significantly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128921" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Revanites probably picked it because it was the site of a major battle involving Revan--one of his biggest victories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gladly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128925" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen Agent Fauler's reports on that one. It's good to know we're bringing along an expert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128927" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised they have so many volunteers. It must be a painful process.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1128927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds... unpleasant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128928" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're insane cultists obsessed with the past. Giving them a chance to literally put pieces of history into themselves and become nearly unstoppable? There's probably a waiting list.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128931" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't wait to see the look on Arkous and Darok's faces....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128934" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darok and Arkous are in there somewhere--just keep moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like they've got a shuttle--we can shoot it down if we have to, but I'd rather take them in for questioning if you can. Hurry!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128938" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find another ship! We'll meet at the safehouse on Manaan! Go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129037" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would take time, and we can't be sure of success. Finding Revan is much more important than clearing our reputations. Besides--we still have you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129039" id2="17" version="1065353216">What can I do while you're in hiding? There must be some way I can help with the search.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1129039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there any way I can help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129040" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is, actually.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129041" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're much too worried about all of this, Theron. We should be sticking together, not scattering apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1129041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Splitting up is foolish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trust me. This will all go much better if we work separately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129045" id2="17" version="1065353216">The busier you keep the Revanites, the easier it will be for the rest of us to slip through the cracks and find their leader.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1129046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129048" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be sure they see just how much a Jedi is capable of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129051" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do my best to provide a better example than their fellow cultists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wouldn't hurt if a few of them had second thoughts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129054" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they want to try and keep up with Havoc Squad, they're in for a workout.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129055" id2="17" version="1065353216">The tougher the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129057" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't met anyone yet who could keep up with me, but I'll do my best to make it sporting for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129058" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very gracious of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you think the masked man who attacked us was really Revan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1129060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you think it's really Revan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129061" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mean, has my ancient ancestor returned from the grave to kill us all? It doesn't seem likely, but... there was something about him. We need to learn more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Being your convenient diversion had better not get me killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1129063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, I'll play decoy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129064" id2="17" version="1065353216">After everything you've gone up against, I really doubt this will give you much trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129066" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, I'd better get moving--the faster we start running, the easier this will all be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck to you. We'll send word as soon as we have something--and then we'll see what this Revan guy is really made of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129072" id2="17" version="1065353216">No--not yet, at least. That's why we need to move quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1129076" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we had more time... but we don't. There's something I need you to do for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, that route is not working out like we planned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140022" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have to head along the beach and straight through Rakata central. Sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140024" id2="17" version="1065353216">No way around that rancor. I do not envy you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140218" id2="17" version="1065353216">Overheard some Revanites near your position. Came across a cache of Rakata-tech weapons. Might want to do something about that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1140220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look out, they put together a welcoming party for you. More of those cyborgs.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
