<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>58</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris_imp/world/rakghoul_observation/eton_vok.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take a look at this, my lord... those rakghouls have been busy. This is the ninth corpse I've found today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another one of ours--though you could hardly tell by looking. Rakghouls are notoriously messy eaters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543748" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, but where are my own manners? I'm Eton Vok. I research the rakghouls' hunting patterns and social behaviors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543749" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've always picked off the occasional grunt, true, but this is different.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543750" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admittedly, their interactions are primitive, confusing, even violent, but you can find a message in all the blood-spattered chaos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543751" id2="17" version="1065353216">This mess is the work of a mutant strain of rakghouls I've been studying. I've dubbed them berserker rakghouls, for obvious reasons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543752" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've been on the rampage for days now. Even destroyed my camp. I only escaped because they were too busy disemboweling my guards to give chase.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543753" id2="17" version="1065353216">As bad as that incident was, it's only gotten worse since.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543754" id2="17" version="1065353216">These berserkers are unfathomably aggressive. They'll attack Imperial convoys, tear entire squads to pieces--or worse, infect them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="543755" id2="17" version="1065353216">Each massacre heightens their bloodlust and swells their numbers. We need to exterminate them before they're too many to contain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573604" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rakghouls shouldn't trouble the Empire anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573605" id2="17" version="1065353216">It appears the rakghoul onslaught has finally been suppressed. Imperial operations are already reclaiming lost territory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573607" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I see you collected the data I requested. Splendid. I only hope our troops can learn to fight the rakghouls as effectively as you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573609" id2="17" version="1065353216">And not a moment too soon. I shudder to think what might have happened if those berserkers had run unchecked any longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573610" id2="17" version="1065353216">I enjoyed it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573611" id2="17" version="1065353216">They weren't so tough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573612" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm done here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573613" id2="17" version="1065353216">A pity the berserkers didn't direct their animosity toward the Republic instead. Their mindless savagery--properly guided--could have proven useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps now I can continue my studies in peace. Of course, I'll need to find new subjects....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573617" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd best hurry--the berserkers' numbers grow with each passing moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at this... those rakghouls have been busy. This is the ninth corpse I've found today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573624" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't think rakghoul attacks were that uncommon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why the fuss?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you saying rakghouls can communicate?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Social behaviors?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573628" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is that smell?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something stinks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pungent, isn't it? Rakghouls aren't cannibalistic, so smearing my clothes in their entrails makes me less... palatable to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573632" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire cannot tolerate such wanton destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573632" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will not stand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Minions have their uses, even in death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better them than you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bad things happen when you take on a job you're not cut out for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573635" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were in over their heads.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those guards were supposed to protect me. If they had to be mercilessly devoured to do so, then so be it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573638" id2="17" version="1065353216">This wouldn't have happened if you had taken the necessary precautions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573638" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were careless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573639" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll admit, I didn't anticipate a full-on assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why were you interested in these rakghouls?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573641" id2="17" version="1065353216">What were you studying?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573642" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've developed an immunity to the local toxins. Also, their mutations have made them even more savage than their brethren.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573644" id2="17" version="1065353216">So?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our troops lack the nerve to fight the rakghouls--one severed head and they all panic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573649" id2="17" version="1065353216">This requires a powerful Sith... like you, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573650" id2="17" version="1065353216">This requires a cold, ruthless professional... like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573651" id2="17" version="1065353216">This requires an experienced operative... like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573652" id2="17" version="1065353216">This requires someone with your skill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573653" id2="17" version="1065353216">This requires a small, well-trained group... like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573654" id2="17" version="1065353216">These berserkers will get a lesson in violence and mayhem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573654" id2="17" version="1065353216">So be it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count me in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. Their lair isn't far. Head down there and kill the lot of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573658" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it's no trouble, I'd also like to observe your tactics against the rakghouls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573660" id2="17" version="1065353216">This monitoring device will analyze your fights. Kill enough, and that data could teach our troops how to effectively counter the beasts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not interested. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Drat. And so, the carnage continues....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573665" id2="17" version="1065353216">These rakghouls are becoming quite a nuisance.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
