<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>47</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/world/endar_spire/childress.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622804" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Viqui tells me the data you brought is giving them warm fuzzies back at intelligence HQ.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better get to the Endar Spire fast if you want to find survivors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, there. Captain Childress. I want to thank you for taking the time to see me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622810" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did nice work on that land claim mess. Like we flew this many troops to the armpit of the galaxy so some kids could play pioneer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622812" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll take way more than it's worth to make this planet livable. Only thing interesting about Taris is that it's the worst failure the Republic's ever had.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622813" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know much about Taris's history.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622813" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622814" id2="17" version="1065353216">Way back when, the Sith were searching for a Jedi here. When they couldn't find her, they tried destroying the entire planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622816" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi escaped, but millions of people died an ugly flaming death. The Empire tried the same thing on Coruscant in the last war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622818" id2="17" version="1065353216">The destruction of Taris was a terrible loss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622818" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire won that day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622819" id2="17" version="1065353216">And we almost let it happen again on Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you need me here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622822" id2="17" version="1065353216">You spend time in Republic space, you ought to care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622824" id2="17" version="1065353216">An Imperial bombardment destroyed civilization on this planet. A planet! And they tried the same on Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three hundred years after Taris, we still don't know squat about how to defend against a bombardment once ships are in low orbit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until we learn to defend ourselves, we're at the Empire's mercy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622827" id2="17" version="1065353216">That can't happen again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622828" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's why I'm here. Learn what we can so we don't repeat the mistakes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good men die when we don't learn from our mistakes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622830" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to change that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622831" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's why I'm here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look to the past to reclaim the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622833" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must learn better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622834" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you mean studying dusty records might save my men's lives, you got that right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makes you feel like the Empire could squash you like a bug.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gives me the chills.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most people don't realize how vulnerable we are. And if my mission here succeeds, they'll never have to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622839" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could take a battle cruiser or two, but I don't know if I can stop a whole bombardment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622839" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm good, but not that good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622840" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could handle a few battle cruisers, but not a whole bombardment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622840" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're good, but not that good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha! We're not there yet. Right now, we're just trying to learn what we did wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622843" id2="17" version="1065353216">So what's the job?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sent commandos to defend a research team at the crash site of the Endar Spire--the last Republic warship shot down over this planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622846" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we're lucky, that ship recorded the whole bombardment. But my team's lost contact... which means there are desk jockeys in the wild with the most valuable data on Taris.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622847" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they've still got coms, tell them help is on the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622847" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll go find the team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622848" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's this ship? Why's it so valuable?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the Endar Spire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622849" id2="17" version="1065353216">There were Jedi aboard, back in the day. Now, we hope it's got data on the attackers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622851" id2="17" version="1065353216">The crash site's a ways out. Fast as you can make it--I don't know if we've got survivors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Research team's your number two priority. Data's the most important thing. Take anything the Endar Spire recorded to Commander Viqui at the outpost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Took the Republic three hundred years to get to this. It can wait a while longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="622855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Count me out. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622856" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate freelancers. Give me a good chain of command any day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="622858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Miserable garbage heap of a planet.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
