<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>26</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/event/bounty_hunting/imperial/breadcrumb_bh_event.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113374" id2="17" version="1065353216">I demand to know what the lot of you are up to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113375" id2="17" version="1065353216">What transpires here that would have Sith assisting bounty hunters?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113376" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey. What's with the procession? And the Sith?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113377" id2="17" version="1065353216">You. Stop. Tell me what's going on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113378" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grabbing a contract from the bounty broker. Sith's turning one in, believe it or not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113384" id2="17" version="1065353216">No assistance. Her bounty, fair and square. You could be doing the same, if it suited you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113385" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't hear? Love to know how you avoided the onslaught of holo-adverts. Lucky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113386" id2="17" version="1065353216">Headed to the broker. You know, the bounty broker? Guess you haven't heard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113391" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Bounty Brokers Association is taking all comers now. Limited-time-offer sort of thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some non-Cartel Hutts run the BBA, but the whole promotion's endorsed by the Empire. To them, the BBA helps take out the trash.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113394" id2="17" version="1065353216">These Sith and whatnot think it's easy, what we do. You ought to pitch in--help us proper hunters prove them wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like it could make for a fun distraction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1113572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider me intrigued.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113573" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't exactly my line of work. Why should I bother?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1113573" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm no bounty hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do the bounties have to be delivered alive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1113574" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer killing to capturing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113575" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why've I never heard of any Bounty Brokers Association before?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1113575" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's this &quot;Association&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113577" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe the Great Hunt winner's already got a full plate? Yeah--I know who you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Beats me. Heard of them now, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Profitable, too. Some of these bounties are impressive scum--way beyond run-of-the-mill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Notoriety? Travel? Credits? Get your hands on some defiant scum? All sound like good reasons to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Carbonite or casket--long as you can prove the deed, either's acceptable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hutts own and operate the Association. No longer Cartel affiliated, if that's important to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1113589" id2="17" version="1065353216">The BBA's set up shop in the fleet. Chat up one of their brokers--they'll get you approved and ready to hunt.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
