<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>331</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tython/class/jedi_knight_new/master_orgus_din.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604690" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations, Knight. I'll meet you on Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Orgus... everyone... I've discovered a situation requiring further assistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604693" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our suspicions about Coruscant were correct. The dark presence we have long sensed is strongest here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604694" id2="17" version="1065353216">I keep hearing about this dark presence, but I haven't sensed it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604694" id2="17" version="1065353216">I feel nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604695" id2="17" version="1065353216">Had you spent as much time in meditation as the Council, you might.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604697" id2="17" version="1065353216">What could be worse than a fallen Jedi attacking us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604697" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then it wasn't Bengel Morr.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604698" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what we need to find out. The security of the entire Republic is at stake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604700" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've already defeated one dark presence today. Might as well go for two.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604700" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll deal with it, no problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604701" id2="17" version="1065353216">This darkness blinded us to threats much closer to home. I advise great caution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something malignant works in the shadows of the capital. We must find it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604705" id2="17" version="1065353216">This situation calls for our very best. Master Orgus, you and your former pupil should join Master Kiwiiks on Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come to the Senate tower as soon as you can. Master Kiwiiks out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604709" id2="17" version="1065353216">No rest for us, my friend. Complete any unfinished business you have and take a shuttle to Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604710" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll leave immediately, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604710" id2="17" version="1065353216">My work here is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604711" id2="17" version="1065353216">No offense, but I've had enough of Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604711" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't wait to leave here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604712" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looking forward to getting away, myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604714" id2="17" version="1065353216">All I get is a pat on the back and a new mission? I just saved this temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604714" id2="17" version="1065353216">What, no parade?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604715" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll build a bronzium statue of you--promise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604717" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to wrap up some things before I go. Meet you on Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Farewell. The Force will be with you--always.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604725" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Flesh Raiders are still a threat, but without Bengel's leadership, they'll be scattered and ill-equipped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604727" id2="17" version="1065353216">This temple could've been devastated. The entire order is in your debt, Padawan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604728" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy found weaknesses in our security. We have to guard against another Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's tighten our defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed--and now we have concerns beyond the Flesh Raiders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604731" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't give the Flesh Raiders time to regroup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604731" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should go to war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604732" id2="17" version="1065353216">Going to war only guarantees more violence. It's better to tighten our defenses. Besides, we have threats closer to home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604734" id2="17" version="1065353216">I crafted my own lightsaber. I'm a Jedi Knight, now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604734" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't call me Padawan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604735" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rank of Knight is only conferred by the Council--and we have a more pressing topic to discuss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604737" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recent developments in the Twi'lek settlement demand a response.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604739" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their Matriarch, Ranna, betrayed me, and now we hear the Flesh Raiders killed her. The settlement is in chaos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their Matriarch betrayed me to Bengel, but she surrendered herself to us for judgment. Your doing, I understand. Good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604743" id2="17" version="1065353216">The young Matriarch, Ranna, betrayed me to Bengel. She has since disappeared, and the settlement is in chaos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their Matriarch, Ranna, betrayed me to Bengel. Reports indicate she still leads the settlement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604747" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know the Twi'leks, Padawan. How do you recommend we proceed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604748" id2="17" version="1065353216">We created instability by refusing to help them. That has to change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604748" id2="17" version="1065353216">They need our support.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604749" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happened to Master Orgus is almost unforgivable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604751" id2="17" version="1065353216">But if we do forgive--and work with them--it can only improve both our communities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604752" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Twi'leks need guidance. We should take charge of their settlement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604752" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should take control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi don't govern others. That kind of power is too easily abused.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604755" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't need to govern the Twi'leks--just keep a close eye on them. Be ready to intervene.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604756" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're a danger we can't afford--and they don't belong here. I say we round them up and ship them anyplace else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Force them off Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604757" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forced resettlement of the Twi'leks runs against everything we stand for. Containment is a better option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604759" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least we know they can't be trusted. We won't put them in a position to betray us again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604761" id2="17" version="1065353216">This young Jedi saved us all from a terrible threat by defeating an experienced Force user.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Although Bengel Morr's body hasn't been found, the fact remains this young Jedi saved us from his army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604765" id2="17" version="1065353216">This young Jedi captured a fallen member of our order and saved this temple from destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604767" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see no reason for her to remain a Padawan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604769" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see no reason why he should remain a Padawan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604771" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your final trial has been marred by dark events, but I can't argue with your accomplishments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your bravery, heroism and sacrifice show great depth of character. You represent our best hopes for the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604775" id2="17" version="1065353216">You arrived on Tython a Padawan, but you leave a Knight of the Republic. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604776" id2="17" version="1065353216">I promise to uphold every standard of the Jedi and Galactic Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604776" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a great honor, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604777" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm eager to do some good in the galaxy. Send me somewhere I can help out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604777" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's my next mission?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Plenty of trouble spots in the galaxy. We'll find one for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604780" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's about time. No more &quot;Padawan do this&quot; and &quot;Padawan go there.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604780" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604781" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's right. Now the real work begins.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="604783" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = requests permanent assignment to assist Jedi // T7 + Jedi = unstoppable</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604784" id2="17" version="1065353216">This little droid and I have been through a lot. We're a great team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604784" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a fine idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I see no reason why you shouldn't stay together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604787" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Unstoppable&quot; is a strong word, but you have your uses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's not go that far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604788" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teeseven has served faithfully for many years. He'll serve you equally well. Request granted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604790" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need some machine underfoot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604790" id2="17" version="1065353216">No thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="604791" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = requests upgraded servomotors // T7 = agile</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604793" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good for young Jedi Knights to have a trustworthy assistant. Your request is granted, Teeseven.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604795" id2="17" version="1065353216">After a few small upgrades, I think Teeseven will serve you well. Request granted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604797" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're getting a priority signal from Coruscant. It's Master Kiwiiks....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Padawan... I must have you to thank for being alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604802" id2="17" version="1065353216">I defeated Bengel Morr, Master. He's dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Poor man. He was so lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604805" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fought Bengel Morr, and he fell into the ravine. He's dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Force willing, we'll recover the poor man's body and give him a proper funeral.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604808" id2="17" version="1065353216">I captured Bengel Morr, Master. He's resting quietly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604809" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done a great thing. He deserves a second chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604811" id2="17" version="1065353216">The horrors he witnessed on Coruscant broke him--destroyed the gentle Padawan I trained.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604813" id2="17" version="1065353216">You, however, faced a challenge beyond any trial I could assign. There's nothing more I can teach you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="604815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi = big victory // T7 = congratulates Jedi</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604817" id2="17" version="1065353216">All that's left is for you to enter the Forge and construct your own lightsaber.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604819" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no substitute for the weapon you create yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604821" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is this place, Master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forge?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604822" id2="17" version="1065353216">The first Jedi came here to construct their lightsabers millennia ago. It's strong in the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Haven't I done enough work for one day?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Terrific--more chores.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Creating a lightsaber is more than work; you're building a connection to the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Normally, we make Padawans gather materials themselves--but you've proven enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604829" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are all the physical components--the rest will come from your mastery of the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="604831" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = stay with Jedi + keep guard</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604833" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll carry Bengel's body to the Jedi Temple. Meet me there when you're ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604836" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll return to the Jedi Temple and organize a search party for Bengel's body. Meet me there when you're ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604839" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll carry Bengel back to the Jedi Temple and get him help. Meet me there when you're ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604845" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Flesh Raider camp's out of commission, Master--but they were all Force users. They killed a Jedi named Laotah.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604847" id2="17" version="1065353216">His body is in these ruins. What should I do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604848" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll reclaim our fallen later. Just got a distress call from the Twi'lek settlement. They spotted Bengel Morr!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604850" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our forces are spread out dealing with the secret camps. We're the only ones who can handle this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604852" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on my way to the settlement. Meet me there!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604856" id2="17" version="1065353216">One camp is in the ruins of Upper Kaleth. That patrol you fought earlier was based there. Now's your chance to finish them off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604857" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why spread our forces thin to hit all the camps at once?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604857" id2="17" version="1065353216">We shouldn't split up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604858" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we only go after a few, the Flesh Raiders could warn the rest and regroup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604860" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if I run into your old Padawan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bengel Morr could be there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604861" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you see Bengel, retreat and contact me immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604863" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're asking a lot. When I become a Knight, I want a special lightsaber or something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604863" id2="17" version="1065353216">I deserve extra credit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604864" id2="17" version="1065353216">When this is over, we'll talk about your unhealthy need for recognition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful in those ruins. We haven't explored them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contact me when your mission's complete. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604870" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally put the Flesh Raider base out of commission. How are things on your end?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Spoke to your old Padawan over the holo. He's doing all this so he can destroy the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bengel Morr contacted me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then he's not Sith himself--good. If I can get to him, reason with him....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604874" id2="17" version="1065353216">I let Ranna perform a family-bonding ritual with me. Her mother died, and I wanted to console her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604874" id2="17" version="1065353216">I disobeyed the Jedi Code.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604875" id2="17" version="1065353216">A mistake born out of compassion is common for young Jedi. At least you had the good sense to admit the error.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi don't form attachments because those bonds are hard to break. Now that's exactly what you must do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604878" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't let my relationship with Ranna become a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604878" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604879" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to hear it. Let's get back to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi are supposed to honor their promises, aren't they?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604881" id2="17" version="1065353216">This feels wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604882" id2="17" version="1065353216">And that's why a good Jedi never promises anything she can't deliver. Regardless, we don't have time to debate this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604884" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry. This won't be a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604884" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] I understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good, because we don't have time for distractions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604887" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know Jedi aren't allowed to form attachments, but... something happened with Ranna.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604887" id2="17" version="1065353216">I disobeyed the Jedi Code.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604888" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm proud of you for admitting the mistake. A lesser Padawan would've kept it a secret.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever feelings you have for that girl, bury them now. If you don't, they'll only bring you suffering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604891" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry I let you down, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please accept my apology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604892" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not the first Jedi to seek comfort in a time of crisis. Just put it behind you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not every relationship ends badly. Why should I be afraid to care about someone?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604894" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604895" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you heard anything I've said? Just as well I'm getting you out of that settlement....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604897" id2="17" version="1065353216">As far as I'm concerned, it was a one-time thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604897" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] I won't see her again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just make sure there aren't more &quot;one-time things.&quot; Ranna won't be the last attractive woman you meet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thing I returned to the settlement. Flesh Raiders tried to poison the crops, but I stopped them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604900" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Flesh Raiders struck back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Poison? They're getting desperate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please tell me I'm getting out of this blasted Twi'lek settlement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604903" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm bored out of my mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604904" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful what you wish for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604906" id2="17" version="1065353216">At the Flesh Raider command base, I found coordinates to a number of secret camps--too many to send only Jedi Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604908" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't enter that Flesh Raider base until you knock out their energy shield. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604909" id2="17" version="1065353216">The man who attacked you when you first arrived? His lightsaber had a familiar aspect. This droid's holorecording confirmed my suspicions.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="604911" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = sorry for bringing bad news</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604913" id2="17" version="1065353216">The hooded figure in that recording is named Bengel Morr. He was my Padawan--but he never completed his training.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bengel was in the Jedi Temple on Coruscant when the Sith destroyed it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604916" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force was with him if he got out of there alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604916" id2="17" version="1065353216">Somehow, he survived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604917" id2="17" version="1065353216">The temple was annihilated. Hundreds of Jedi died that day. We never recovered all the bodies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604919" id2="17" version="1065353216">He waited a long time to reveal himself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604919" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was years ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604920" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still don't understand why he just disappeared. Doesn't make sense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604922" id2="17" version="1065353216">His face isn't visible in the holo. Maybe your mind's playing tricks on you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604922" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could be imagining things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604923" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know my Padawan's voice when I hear it. What I don't know is how--why--he changed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bengel was strong in the Force, and the most gentle being I've ever known.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604927" id2="17" version="1065353216">For him to turn against the Jedi... he has to be stopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apologies for keeping you waiting. Our people's Matriarch--my mother--is dying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604930" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's terrible news. Will you be alright?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604930" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm so sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604931" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't think the burden of leadership would feel so heavy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604933" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wasn't expecting to lead our people for many years.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604935" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should be at her side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go to her.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604936" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're kind, but my mother wants me here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604938" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mother said my work with you must come first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604940" id2="17" version="1065353216">We all have to go sometime.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604941" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose Jedi don't let themselves feel sadness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604943" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have our sympathies, Ranna--but the enemy won't give us time for mourning. Please tell us what you've learned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604945" id2="17" version="1065353216">My scouts have identified a Flesh Raider command base in the mountains. It's protected by an energy shield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604947" id2="17" version="1065353216">The shield's power generator is hidden on a different mountain, in a well-guarded cave network.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604949" id2="17" version="1065353216">That command base is probably coordinating all the attacks in the region. I need to get inside there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604951" id2="17" version="1065353216">You up for knocking out the power generator?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604952" id2="17" version="1065353216">When have I ever let you down?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604952" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604953" id2="17" version="1065353216">First time for everything--not that I'm worried.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604955" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll need backup. Can't we send someone else to handle the power generator?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me go with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604956" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've shown you can handle Flesh Raiders. We need you there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604958" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to complete my training. Is this mission part of my final trials?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this one of my Jedi tests?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please keep your mind in the present, Padawan.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="604961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Important secondary mission = perform high-level scan of enemy forces // Mountain paths = too dangerous for T7</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604963" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. See if you can give the droid an opening to gather more intelligence.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="604965" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = give Jedi head start // Follow when path is clear</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604967" id2="17" version="1065353216">That energy shield is your top priority. Knock it out fast as you can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Kiwiiks told me what you found in Kaleth--a Flesh Raider who used the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604971" id2="17" version="1065353216">She thought he was learning things from an old holocron. I wish that were true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604974" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm here, Master. What is it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604975" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm on my way back to the Twi'lek settlement. Meet me there soon as you can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604976" id2="17" version="1065353216">You left without explaining anything. What has you so worried?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me what you found.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604977" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll explain when I see you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604979" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm already on my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604980" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been surviving the ruins of Kaleth. Thanks for asking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604980" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm fine, by the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604981" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I didn't think you could handle it, I wouldn't have sent you there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find me at the Matriarch's compound. Orgus out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604985" id2="17" version="1065353216">Travel safely out there. The Flesh Raiders are on the move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast those Council meetings. I'd die of old age before my colleagues ran out of things to say.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604989" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather do something about problems than discuss them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604989" id2="17" version="1065353216">I prefer action to speeches.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still, there are times when talking is exactly what's needed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604992" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you always felt this way about your fellow Masters?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604992" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't like the Council?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604993" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't misunderstand--they're good people. I just prefer to get things done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604995" id2="17" version="1065353216">It seems talking is what they're best at.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="604995" id2="17" version="1065353216">They are long-winded.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604996" id2="17" version="1065353216">Council members earn their seats after many victories and sacrifices. Respect that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="604998" id2="17" version="1065353216">This situation has come at you fast. You're braving dangers many Jedi never face.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605000" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't blame you for having questions. This may be the only time to ask them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605001" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make sense of things later. Let's find our enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605001" id2="17" version="1065353216">My questions can wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605002" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know people who can help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605004" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the impression you haven't had a Padawan for years. Why did you ask to train me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why did you choose me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605005" id2="17" version="1065353216">As Jedi, you learn to trust your instincts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605007" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I met you in that cave, my instincts told me that I was meant to train you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605009" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know why, or for what purpose, but the Living Force brought us together for a reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605010" id2="17" version="1065353216">I look forward to learning from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605010" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad it did, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605011" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expect you have things to teach me, as well. Let's get to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605013" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think the Force is alive? That it wants something from us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605013" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Living Force?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605014" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Want&quot; is too strong a word. Let's just say we'll accomplish more together than by ourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605016" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't much care for mystical philosophy, but whatever floats your speeder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605016" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph. Anyway--to find our hidden enemy, we'll need allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605019" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the feeling you know more about this threat than you're telling me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605019" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you're hiding things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605020" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have... a bad feeling about this. But that's all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605022" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I know more, I will tell you. Trust me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605023" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you wouldn't keep anything from me without a good reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605023" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605024" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not keeping secrets--just avoiding careless rumor. We need real answers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605026" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're leaving me unprepared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605026" id2="17" version="1065353216">By then it could be too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605027" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force will guide us both through this--with a little help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605029" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can I trust you when you don't trust me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605029" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a two-way street.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605030" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do trust you. I'd just rather get real answers than stand around making wild guesses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605032" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a group of Twi'lek Pilgrims on Tython. They've been fighting the Flesh Raiders for months.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605034" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic asked us to deny those Twi'leks aid--they settled here illegally--but frankly, we need them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605035" id2="17" version="1065353216">How are they violating the law?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605035" id2="17" version="1065353216">An illegal settlement?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605036" id2="17" version="1065353216">When Tython was first rediscovered, the Twi'leks petitioned the Senate to settle here. Their claim was denied--too dangerous--but they came anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please tell me this isn't a diplomatic mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605038" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm hoping for some action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605039" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Twi'leks are in the thick of it. I suspect you'll have to fight your way to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605041" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic shouldn't be telling the Jedi what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605041" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgot how impressionable Padawans can be. Remember, Jedi exist to serve the Republic--even when we disagree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605044" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Twi'leks have a settlement in the mountains. That's your next stop.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Establish a base camp and speak to the Matriarch. Find out everything the Twi'leks know about Flesh Raiders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605047" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready to get back out there--do some good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605047" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll go right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything you can tell me about the Twi'lek leader?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Matriarch?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Word is she's not our biggest fan. You may have to convince her otherwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605051" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Twi'leks won't share what they know, how far can I push them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605051" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if they don't cooperate?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't push--bend. Show those people we're here to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605054" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll join you soon. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605060" id2="17" version="1065353216">I searched the temple archives. This Force user leading the Flesh Raiders never received Jedi training.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then the Sith have found us. Shouldn't we get ready for them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm yourself, Padawan. We can't be certain of anything, yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605066" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we've all sensed a growing darkness--perhaps it's finally revealed itself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605067" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy I faced wanted to destroy the Jedi Order. Can't get much darker than that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605067" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is darkness here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, that brightened up the room....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone want to bring me up to speed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605070" id2="17" version="1065353216">What have I missed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605071" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're just having a nice end-of-the-world chat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your &quot;growing darkness&quot; just tried to kill me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605073" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm proof of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605074" id2="17" version="1065353216">See? It's not just me who's worried.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone, this is the Padawan who saved our people in the training grounds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605078" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Master Kiwiiks and her extremely vocal Padawan, Kira. The other Masters are transmitting from distant worlds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605080" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's unfortunate our numbers are scattered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed. The temple's safety is unexpectedly threatened. The Flesh Raiders were disorganized primitives before today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605083" id2="17" version="1065353216">They carry blasters and work like an army. We need to find out why.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605084" id2="17" version="1065353216">They didn't change overnight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605085" id2="17" version="1065353216">We clearly underestimated the natives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without the man organizing them, they're just mindless savages.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605087" id2="17" version="1065353216">But their leader is dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605088" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt it's that simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605090" id2="17" version="1065353216">The man leading the Flesh Raiders probably wasn't acting alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605092" id2="17" version="1065353216">Much of Tython remains unexplored, and we have few resources to spare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605094" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle it--with the help of my new Padawan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605096" id2="17" version="1065353216">Orgus, you haven't taken a Padawan since Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605098" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force is strong in her. Stronger than I've seen in decades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605100" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force is strong in him. Stronger than I've seen in decades.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605102" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can think of no finer Master to complete this Padawan's training.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605103" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll complete my final trials once we've dealt with the Flesh Raiders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605103" id2="17" version="1065353216">Training can wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605104" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is what you should aspire to, Kira.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605106" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me neither.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get too excited. You're in for some hard work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605109" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I'm so special, shouldn't the leader of the Jedi train me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605109" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can--you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605110" id2="17" version="1065353216">My duties to the order come first--and don't underestimate Master Orgus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605112" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find supplies in my chambers downstairs. Go equip yourself. I'll meet you there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tython is full of dangers, even for Jedi. If you must go out, don't travel alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605119" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take my lightsaber back, if you don't mind. Feel naked without it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605123" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go on. This won't take long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="605124" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Flesh Raider had your weapon. I used it to defend myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="605124" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have yours, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="757227" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Master.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
