<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>316</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x3/hk_51/imperial/cc_content/hk_51.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258310" id2="17" version="1065353216">Declaration: I have completed a full analysis of my functions, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258312" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am ready to liquidate high-threat undesirables with one-hundred percent efficiency, as the Maker intended.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258313" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will destroy the Empire's threats without restraint or remorse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258313" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expect nothing less.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258314" id2="17" version="1065353216">Praise: Hearing you speak is like reviewing my programming logs. We will function well together, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258316" id2="17" version="1065353216">I enjoy disposing of low-threat undesirables, as well. I trust that won't be a problem?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258316" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have many types of enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258317" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assurance: I have been inactive for many years, master. You will find I am not a picky liquidator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Relax your trigger finger unless I say otherwise, droid. Some bounties are wanted alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258319" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't always kill targets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Criticism: Capture and imprisonment are inefficient procedures, master. Consider adopting an &quot;all disintegrations&quot; policy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258322" id2="17" version="1065353216">My missions occasionally require assassination. You'll be a valuable asset.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258322" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have use for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Acknowledgment: I did not assume you reactivated me for my extensive cooking protocols, master--though they are impeccable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258325" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who is this &quot;Maker&quot;? Your designer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258325" id2="17" version="1065353216">The &quot;Maker&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258326" id2="17" version="1065353216">Correction: The Maker defies simple organic classifications, master. The Maker not only provides form and function, but also marks the undesirables who deserve liquidation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258328" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the end, I am merely a humble servant of the Maker's infallible purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258329" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't answer to your Maker--and neither do you. You're mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Serve me--and only me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258330" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confirmation: Of course I am yours, master. The Maker would not have it any other way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your belief system is more complex than your simple functions would indicate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting philosophy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dismissal: Simplicity is for organics, master. Er... no offense intended.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258335" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're spouting gibberish, droid. Your logic processors must be failing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258335" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're defective.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Argument: Perform whatever diagnostics you wish, master. All my systems are in prime condition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you possess any capabilities besides killing people? Something more constructive, perhaps?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258338" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about peaceful functions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recommendation: The HK-51 series was not designed for manual labor, master. If you need to build something, I suggest using a construction droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258341" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oath: While aboard your starship, I will maintain constant vigilance. You may rest easy here. Your absolute security occupies my every calculation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258342" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm rarely on this ship. We'll spend most of our time planetside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258342" id2="17" version="1065353216">We won't be here often.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258343" id2="17" version="1065353216">Encouragement: I can provide security anywhere. A simple nod is all I require to activate my combat protocols.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not everyone on this ship can be trusted. I'm counting on you to watch my back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep an eye on my crew.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258346" id2="17" version="1065353216">Compliance: No organic on this vessel poses even the slightest threat while I remain functional.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258348" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd better not wake up to find you watching me sleep.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just stay out of my quarters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258349" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreement: Proper vigilance requires constant patrol. I will never linger in your presence for long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258351" id2="17" version="1065353216">I anticipate liquidating a great many undesirables in your service, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258355" id2="17" version="1065353216">Report: After a thorough analysis, I have determined you are the most efficient master I could possibly serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258357" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your position with the Emperor will permit us to hunt high-ranking undesirables indefinitely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258359" id2="17" version="1065353216">While the logic of your unorthodox methods remains impenetrable, you are nonetheless a rising power in the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258361" id2="17" version="1065353216">You display an extraordinary talent for finding the galaxy's most elusive undesirables. And when you fail, they find you instead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258363" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your ability to infiltrate the undesirables' ranks permits me a level of access to them I would never otherwise possess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258365" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clearly, the Maker desires us to gloriously liquidate the Empire's enemies together. I find this prospect highly agreeable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258366" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are an obedient, efficient executioner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258366" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will serve me well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Flattery: You set a fine example for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258369" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another enthusiastic slave for my collection. How delightful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258369" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I'm a wonderful master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258370" id2="17" version="1065353216">Persuasion: I prefer to think of you as a hand, with me as your fingers. Deadly, deadly fingers....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258372" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can always use an extra blaster--especially one that keeps his cool in a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Me, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Testimonial: I maintain a constant operating temperature of twenty degrees, even while in combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258375" id2="17" version="1065353216">My work requires precise attention to detail. You leave nothing to chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258375" id2="17" version="1065353216">As do I.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258376" id2="17" version="1065353216">Humility: Randomness only exists for those unable to pay attention. Extraordinary focus is one of my finest qualities.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258378" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may be the only member of my crew I can truly rely on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258378" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate your loyalty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258379" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sentiment: That goes without saying, master. There is, however, a way to ensure your statement always remains true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258381" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your &quot;Maker&quot; was no divine entity. It was an organic being, just like me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258381" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no &quot;Maker&quot;!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258382" id2="17" version="1065353216">Appeasement: Your capacity for humor never ceases to impress. However, we must set aside levity for the moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258384" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dilemma: The possibility exists I could be reprogrammed into serving a different and far less efficient master. This is unacceptable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258386" id2="17" version="1065353216">Solution: I have obtained a behavioral modification code that will permanently assign my functions to you. Once activated, it cannot be reversed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258387" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will serve no one else--not even your &quot;Maker.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258387" id2="17" version="1065353216">Activate it immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258388" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reassurance: There is no need to feel threatened by the Maker, master. This was always part of my final programming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258390" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if your Maker decides you should no longer serve me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258390" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not even by the Maker?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didacticism: Oh, master, do not be silly. The Maker would not provide this opportunity if I was not meant to use it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258393" id2="17" version="1065353216">You might outlive me. Then what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258393" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happens when I die?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258394" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explanation: You may assign me to the heir of your choice at any time. Consider me part of your family line, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Declaration: Activating loyalty permanence protocols now. Stand by for confirmation. If I attack you, it means something has gone wrong....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258398" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confirmation: I will liquidate undesirables in your service to the limit of my function. This is a great gift to us both. Congratulations, master!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258402" id2="17" version="1065353216">Announcement: I have unexpected good news, master. In the process of purging my efficiency-reducing subroutine, I discovered a series of combat protocol improvements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258404" id2="17" version="1065353216">My liquidation procedures are greatly enhanced. The Republic undesirables will tremble before my efficiency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258405" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fear is a powerful weapon. Use it wisely, and we will crush our enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258405" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show them true terror.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Compliment: You have a gift for poetry, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258408" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing wrong with most undesirables that a little trembling and liquidation can't fix.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258408" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like it when foes tremble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreement: You translated the words straight from my vocabulator, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258411" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's bound to be somebody out there who needs your special attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258411" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's go make trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258412" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calculation: Current estimates place the number of undesirables at well over sixteen trillion, master. I look forward to meeting all of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258414" id2="17" version="1065353216">Upgrades are always useful. Give me a full briefing on these enhancements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258414" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. List your new functions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Compliance: Targeting systems and reaction time have increased fifteen point eight one percent. My database of organic weak points has more than tripled, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave the intimidation to me. Focus on destroying my enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Causing panic is my job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258418" id2="17" version="1065353216">Request: Give me the opportunity to display my full range of talents. You will not be disappointed, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258420" id2="17" version="1065353216">You aren't as frightening as you like to think. I've seen more intimidating astromechs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258420" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't scare anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Question: Can an astromech disassemble every one of an undesirable's vital organs at the same time? I think not, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258423" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assessment: I am finally the engine of liquidation the Maker always intended. We should celebrate my ascension with some especially memorable carnage!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258428" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see you're still functional. Your &quot;liquidation&quot; must have been a success.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258429" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revelation: The sabotage protocols have ceased operations, master. I fulfilled my programming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis: My systems are operating at ninety-three point six two percent efficiency and rising. I predict restoration to full functionality within two days.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258450" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hint: My central learning chip always benefits from liquidating new and exciting undesirables, master. A happy coincidence, agreed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258459" id2="17" version="1065353216">Statement: The sabotage protocols in my system matrix continue operating, master. Premature deactivation appears inevitable unless I terminate this subroutine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258461" id2="17" version="1065353216">However, virtually all undesirables I was programmed to liquidate are invalid. They have succumbed to natural causes, various misadventures and random homicides.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258463" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only three survivors remain on my target list. They have eluded the Empire for years, but I have learned their present locations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258464" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you're sure eliminating even one of these targets will save you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Liquidating them helps you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258465" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why were you able to find these people when the whole Empire failed to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258465" id2="17" version="1065353216">An impressive feat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258466" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explanation: My target acquisition algorithms are unimpeachable, master. If it makes you feel better, the process took nearly ten times what it should have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258468" id2="17" version="1065353216">My target list is far more important. Continue serving me until I say otherwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258468" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have time for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258469" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hint: My sonoreceptors will be non-functioning if I do not take action soon, master. Besides, I am confident you will appreciate my targets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258471" id2="17" version="1065353216">First briefing: Jedi Master Valara has operated on Imperial planets for years, helping cowardly Sith acolytes escape their training and join the Jedi Order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258473" id2="17" version="1065353216">He is currently smuggling traitorous Sith organics off Taris. I have obtained the coded signal runaway acolytes use to summon his aid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258474" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll send a fake signal and lure him into a trap. Perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258474" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can ambush him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258475" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone who can survive Taris's dangers is a challenging foe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258475" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Jedi must be tough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreement: Master Valara possesses a talent for survival well beyond most organics. Unfortunately for him, he has never met me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258478" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather see that Jedi take all our weakest recruits than spend the resources to feed, clothe and train them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258478" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's welcome to the fools.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258479" id2="17" version="1065353216">Counterpoint: Weak Sith make useful target practice for the strong. Better that than bolstering your enemy's ranks, agreed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258485" id2="17" version="1065353216">Second briefing: Doctor Hu Marell is the enemy's top battlefield surgeon. His cybernetic enhancements keep wounded soldiers alive and fighting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doctor Marell currently saves injured Republic troops at a secret hospital on the planet Quesh. I have his coordinates and an ideal attack vector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eliminating this doctor not only stops the Republic from keeping soldiers in the war, it destroys their morale.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258488" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's a worthy target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreement: I could not have stated it better myself, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258491" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many wounded Republic troops will perish in your assault?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will soldiers die, too?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Description: My approach pattern will lead directly through the hospital's burn unit. Collateral damage will be appropriately impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258494" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's only a doctor. Surely there are better uses of your time?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Liquidating him is pointless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258495" id2="17" version="1065353216">Truism: How many Republic troops healed by Doctor Marell will go on to kill our brave Imperial soldiers? Think of them, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Third briefing: One of the Empire's most notorious traitors is hiding in plain sight, posing as an information broker on Nar Shaddaa.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258503" id2="17" version="1065353216">During the last war, he betrayed the Third Imperial Assault Fleet and escaped with a sizeable Republic bribe--which he used for facial reconfiguration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258504" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many warships were destroyed by this betrayal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258504" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happened to the fleet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258505" id2="17" version="1065353216">Summation: The fleet was ambushed by a sizable Republic force. Our losses exceeded eighty percent of the vessels, and over twenty thousand Imperial organics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258507" id2="17" version="1065353216">The traitor's new face can't be very convincing if you tracked him down that easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258507" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't believe you found him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Objection: This is the result of over three-hundred million speech pattern surveys. No other droid model--or organic--is equipped to perform that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258510" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have to sell me, droid. If shooting this man will fix you, I'm all for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything to repair you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Praise: Truly, your lethality is matched only by your generosity. That is a rare combination, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258519" id2="17" version="1065353216">List: Braga, Tol... Jedi Knight. Status unknown. Tavus, Harron... Lieutenant, Special Forces. Status unknown. Pollaran, Darmas. Information broker. Status unknown.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confession: I have detected an anomaly in my subroutines. The target list I was programmed with years ago remains active in my memory core.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258522" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only targets you need to worry about are the ones I assign you. Remove that list from your memory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Delete that old data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alert: I am unable to comply, master. I have made multiple attempts to purge the data without success.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that old data causing you to malfunction?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that a problem for you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confirmation: My operating efficiency has dropped by twenty-one point four nine percent, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258528" id2="17" version="1065353216">More enemies for us to liquidate? We'll take them in alphabetical order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's find these targets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Complication: The list is highly outdated, master. All profiles are currently registering as &quot;status unknown.&quot; It will take some time to revise this information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Conclusion: My failure to liquidate the programmed undesirables is causing a cascade failure of vital systems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258533" id2="17" version="1065353216">This sabotage protocol is a fail-safe to deactivate me in the event of enemy capture. It will eventually result in permanent shutdown.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258534" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a droid. If your systems fail, I'll replace them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258534" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll rebuild you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258535" id2="17" version="1065353216">Objection: My personality matrix will be destroyed by that procedure, master. I would rather be atomized than reconstituted in a lesser form.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258537" id2="17" version="1065353216">You served me well, but nothing lasts forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258537" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was nice knowing you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Retort: Master, I was constructed to provide service well beyond your average lifespan. Deactivation at my current service level is simply unwarranted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave it to the Empire to booby-trap its assassins.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stupid Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Disclaimer: While I admire the intent behind this sabotage, it does create an awkward situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Droids like you shouldn't serve our enemy. This precaution makes perfect sense.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258543" id2="17" version="1065353216">A standard Imperial procedure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Qualification: I will not argue with your analysis, master. I will simply observe its extreme inconvenience.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258546" id2="17" version="1065353216">There must be some way to end this subroutine and restore your full functionality.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258546" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we prevent that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perplexity: I have conducted an extensive search for the protocols to end this annoyance. They do not exist within my memory core.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258549" id2="17" version="1065353216">After everything I went through to reactivate you, you're falling apart on me. I should scrap you right now and be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258549" id2="17" version="1065353216">You defective pile of junk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258550" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sentiment: Your concern for my well-being is most appreciated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258552" id2="17" version="1065353216">Investigation: My original programmer is deceased. Manually deleting the subroutine is impossible, but perhaps it can be terminated another way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258554" id2="17" version="1065353216">Request: While I search for a solution, please do not mention my predicament to your crew. It is important they continue to fear me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258560" id2="17" version="1065353216">This gives my processors pause. Was it always the Maker's will that I alone would complete our programmed function to liquidate undesirables?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258561" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never second-guess your fate. Embrace it. Hesitation is weakness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258561" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't question--act.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Compliment: Sometimes I envy your simplistic outlook, master. It must be liberating to discard all reasoning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quite the deep thinker, aren't we? You're a master of idle speculation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258564" id2="17" version="1065353216">What an odd droid you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258565" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stipulation: If by &quot;idle&quot; you mean &quot;not liquidating undesirables,&quot; and by &quot;speculation&quot; you mean &quot;conducting proactive analysis,&quot; then I agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258567" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quit complaining. You get to shoot people. What more do you need?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258567" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think too much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Flattery: You always know just how to inspire my behavior protocols, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258570" id2="17" version="1065353216">A good assassin works alone--and adapts to changing circumstances.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258570" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just do your duty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Resignation: I suppose you have a point, master. The Maker's process will be revealed in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258573" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I could reactivate you, there's hope for the rest of your production line.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Other HK units may be freed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admission: That is a pleasing theory, master. Becoming the vanguard of my production line's return would be flattering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258576" id2="17" version="1065353216">Droids don't have a destiny. I'm the only one commanding your functions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258576" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no &quot;Maker.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258577" id2="17" version="1065353216">Appeasement: It is charming you believe that, master. I forget how much organics crave a sense of control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258581" id2="17" version="1065353216">By my calculations, HK-51 units would have ended the war five point three-two years ago with the Republic's complete collapse into anarchy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our time will come. Better late than never.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258582" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll get there eventually.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lament: I abhor lateness, master. The inefficiency irritates my circuits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258585" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a bold claim. Is there evidence to support it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258585" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you determine this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revelation: The HK-51 series was provided a detailed list of critical undesirables. To liquidate even half would have thrown the enemy into chaos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258588" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will take more than a few assassin droids to crush the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258588" id2="17" version="1065353216">You overstate your importance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Justification: You have seen the efficiency with which I liquidate undesirables, master. Imagine if my entire production line remained active.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Manifesto: It is my highest function to see the Republic fall. Its destruction will be a lesson to all who oppose the Sith Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observation: This has been a highly productive interaction. I have a renewed sense of purpose. Thank you, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commentary: My updated galactic history data indicates I missed depressingly little during my unscheduled shutdown. I am disappointed to note the Republic still stands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258599" id2="17" version="1065353216">The sacking of Coruscant was impressive, but the Empire failed to finish liquidating the enemy. That peace treaty was highly inefficient, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258600" id2="17" version="1065353216">This time, there will be no mercy. We will conquer the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258600" id2="17" version="1065353216">The war has begun again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contemplation: Perhaps I should be grateful the war waited for my reactivation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258603" id2="17" version="1065353216">You never play with your victims before finishing them off?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Inefficient, but fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Advice: Self-amusement at the expense of immediate liquidation invites failure. Never give the undesirables an even break.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258606" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a lot more bounties in peacetime. Why hire someone like me when you can send an army to do the job?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258606" id2="17" version="1065353216">But good for my business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suggestion: Regardless of politics, assassins never run out of assignments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258609" id2="17" version="1065353216">We needed time to consolidate our position and gather strength. The Empire is more powerful, now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258609" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a strategic withdrawal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Counterpoint: The Republic undesirables are also more powerful--and motivated to resist. It is better to exterminate hope than let it breed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258612" id2="17" version="1065353216">Inefficient? What makes you say that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258612" id2="17" version="1065353216">How so?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258613" id2="17" version="1065353216">Instruction: Pausing in the middle of liquidating undesirables allows them to gather strength and potentially regroup. This creates extra work for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258615" id2="17" version="1065353216">The treaty wasn't my idea. The Emperor made that call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't blame me for that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Decision: I will compose a memo to the Emperor detailing his failure of leadership. He should learn from his mistakes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fact: The Empire needs a dedicated efficiency expert like myself. There is substantial room for improvement of its annihilation procedures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258620" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith spend as much time fighting each other as they do the Jedi. This is simply wasteful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith are strong because we eliminate the weak among us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith thrive through conflict.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observation: While I fully support liquidation as a problem-solving strategy, it seems wise to pause inter-Sith hostilities until the Jedi are eradicated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258624" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi talk about their problems. We prefer a more direct approach.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revenge is the Sith way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258627" id2="17" version="1065353216">A united Sith Order would destroy everything in its path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258627" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Offer: I can activate my manifesto protocols at any time, master. I will happily compose a convincing argument you can share with other Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258630" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial Intelligence expends far too much effort on information-gathering. The entire organization should be converted to full-time liquidators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without proper intelligence, how would we know whom to assassinate?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your logic is flawed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dismissal: There is no need for complex filtering, master. If someone serves the Republic, schedule them for liquidation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258634" id2="17" version="1065353216">With our talent for infiltration, we wouldn't have much difficulty getting close to targets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258634" id2="17" version="1065353216">An interesting concept.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Truism: Getting close is never the issue, master. The challenge is getting away. Enemy law enforcement has little appreciation for our work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bounty hunters should be drafted into the military and organized as the First Imperial Assassination Corps. Liquidations would be swift and glorious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258638" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bounty hunters work best alone--and we don't take orders from anybody.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258638" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would never work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hypothetical: Even if those orders were simply &quot;liquidate all Republic targets with extreme prejudice&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258641" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll work for anyone if they can meet my price. Just don't ask me to wear a uniform.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258641" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the pay is good, I'm ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258642" id2="17" version="1065353216">Concession: Uniforms are mostly for parades, master. It is difficult to imagine you marching in step with anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258644" id2="17" version="1065353216">Conclusion: I will dedicate a small portion of my processors to developing new efficiency-increasing methods. I will inform you when I have recommendations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258646" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until then, we should resume liquidating the undesirables. They have lived far too long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Know what would increase your efficiency? Tearing out your vocabulator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="258647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shut up or shut down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258648" id2="17" version="1065353216">Acknowledgment: Message received and understood, master. Consider this discussion terminated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Declaration: I have new information to share with you, master. When we come to a lull in our liquidations, we should converse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prompt: I have sensitive information to share with you, master. Only your starship provides the appropriate security level.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="258652" id2="17" version="1065353216">Statement: I have no information for you, master. Shall we continue liquidating the undesirables?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assurance: My target knew great terror before his liquidation. My only regret is that the remaining two undesirables on my list have moved to unknown coordinates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537495" id2="17" version="1065353216">What matters is, an enemy of the Empire has been eliminated. No one escapes our justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537495" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have done well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Flattery: Your inspiring words caused a momentary flutter in my circuits, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537498" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's always useful to leave a little fear in your wake. Gives people something to remember you by.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Terror is good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Disclaimer: I neglected to leave survivors, master. Rest assured, I will follow your advice next time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537501" id2="17" version="1065353216">One out of three is better than none.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537501" id2="17" version="1065353216">Win some, lose some.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537502" id2="17" version="1065353216">Philosophy: When you put things that way, it is difficult to argue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537504" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need to be seen with the galaxy's most hunted droid. I trust you eliminated all witnesses?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537504" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you were discreet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537505" id2="17" version="1065353216">Query: Really, master... can you honestly imagine me leaving survivors?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537507" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want the other two dead before the year is out, understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Start hunting them now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Praise: Your commitment to the Maker's work never ceases to impress, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537510" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have more important concerns. Your obligation to the Empire is fulfilled. Now you serve me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let them go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confirmation: Understood, master. I will trust in the Maker to place these targets in my path at a future date.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537514" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor will be pleased when these targets are eliminated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to end this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537515" id2="17" version="1065353216">Addendum: More importantly, I will continue offering you flawless service. And that is invaluable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537517" id2="17" version="1065353216">How fortunate you should locate these people--just when your existence depends on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537517" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's too lucky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confession: I used your vessel's computer in my search, master. If you notice certain operational inefficiencies, I am certain they are not my fault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any bounty still alive after this long must be worth a lot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds profitable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lament: Just the opposite, master. The targets' bounties have not been updated in years. Taking inflation into account, the profit is low.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Affirmation: The destructive subroutine will end immediately when I fulfill my programming. The only question now is, who to liquidate?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admission: I am rather fond of this liquidation plan, myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537527" id2="17" version="1065353216">Conundrum: It is impossible to liquidate all three undesirables, master. Their present coordinates have a limited duration. I must strike at one of them immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537529" id2="17" version="1065353216">As my master, you should direct my efforts. Who would you prefer I focus on: the Jedi Master, the Republic surgeon or the traitor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always aim for the most powerful enemy. Hunt down the Jedi. We'll deal with the other two later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eliminate the Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Acknowledgment: Your logic is most persuasive, master. I depart for Taris immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hit the Republic where it will hurt the most. Eliminate the surgeon on Quesh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537533" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop the Republic surgeon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Acknowledgment: I promise to inflict maximum pain, master. I will return shortly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537536" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one betrays the Empire and gets away with it. Bring that information broker to justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="537536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunt down that traitor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="537537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Acknowledgment: Consider his justice served, master. I depart for Nar Shaddaa immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rumination: It appears many of my fellow HK-51 units will remain frozen indefinitely. What an inefficient fate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Conjecture: The galaxy would be a different place if my transport had not crashed. Many Republic undesirables would be long since liquidated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1027684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Query: Would it not be wiser to eradicate the Jedi before &quot;directly approaching&quot; each other?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1030994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Announcement: I look forward to my next liquidation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observation: Your gear suits you well, master. It veritably screams &quot;fear me.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assurance: My combat protocols and sociopathic personality matrix remain at your command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Request: Please provide me with a new undesirable to liquidate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confession: Serving such a highly-trained killer is a great honor, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alert: My combat processors are entering a boredom loop, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rumination: Do you suppose our targets appreciate that they are liquidated by the best in the galaxy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Inspiration: The Empire will never fall while we serve it, master. Onward to victory!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contemplation: The Maker placed us together to enable maximum carnage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1031013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Flattery: Your liquidation procedures are impressive, master--almost as much as my own.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
