<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>113</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/tython_and_korriban/republic/colonel_darok.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your service has been greatly appreciated, but your work here is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118335" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no time to waste. Move out!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's the data from the Dark Council chambers, Colonel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Congratulations. You just succeeded in a mission many people never dared to dream was possible. We've proven that victory--true victory--is within reach.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just imagine: all of the Emperor's followers, truly defeated at last. We're close now, I'm sure of it. This is a great day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118341" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that we've attacked Korriban, how long will it be until the Republic can move against Dromund Kaas?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118341" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's the next step?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Purely a matter of logistics. If we can open up the lines from--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118343" id2="17" version="1065353216">The success of this operation depends on you. Remember that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118346" id2="17" version="1065353216">...Blue Squadron approaches Korriban at maximum speed. Bombing commences on signal &quot;aurek&quot;. Wave one shuttle follows and secures the LZ...</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118348" id2="17" version="1065353216">...and then wave two comes in. Perfect timing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118349" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're actually planning an attack on Korriban?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118350" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. And your part in the plan is critical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118352" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Colonel Darok--he's in charge of the op. I'm Theron Shan, SIS. We spoke on the holo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118353" id2="17" version="1065353216">So we're invading Korriban--take me through your plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118353" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about your plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any relation to the Jedi Grandmaster, Satele Shan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shan? That's a familiar name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118355" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is why I keep asking for a codename.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118357" id2="17" version="1065353216">We aren't here to discuss genealogy. Time is critical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our objective is to raid the Sith Academy. Specifically, the databanks held inside the Dark Council chambers on the Academy's upper level.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118361" id2="17" version="1065353216">The information in those databanks could win the war. Once the first attack wave clears a landing zone, it will be your job to go in and get them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118362" id2="17" version="1065353216">And once we have the data? What then?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118363" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will exfiltrate immediately and rendezvous back here. My associate, Commander Jensyn, will remain behind to collect secondary objectives as time allows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hit the academy, grab the data, and escape. When do we begin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118365" id2="17" version="1065353216">Immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have the Empire's forces really become so weak that we can charge straight in like this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118367" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about enemy defenses?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118368" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not exactly. We'll be exploiting a brief gap in their patrols, which is why we have to move immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118370" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we're going into the Sith Academy, we shouldn't just grab a few trinkets. We should level the place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118370" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's do as much damage as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118371" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bigger job, bigger payout--is that your line of thinking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118373" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't need us to tell you how tough this will be. The Sith Academy is one of the most secure locations in the entire galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118374" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why didn't you just tell me the target up front?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118374" id2="17" version="1065353216">You never mentioned Korriban.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118894" id2="17" version="1065353216">The sooner we can stop the Sith, the sooner the galaxy can finally know peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118895" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you underestimate the tenacity of the Sith. This was one battle--we still have many more ahead of us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118895" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be too proud of yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118896" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't ask much in return. A moderately-sized parade, one or two landmarks named after me....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's talk rewards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118899" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's Tython! We need everything we've got!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118901" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you talking about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial forces just hit Tython. Iso-5 bombings, strike teams in the Jedi Temple... they need our support, now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123751" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our forces are sweeping the rest of the muck off of Tython as we speak, and reconstruction crews are already being prepped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123753" id2="17" version="1065353216">This could have been much worse. Thanks to you, the enemy has only bloodied our nose--and hardened our resolve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123755" id2="17" version="1065353216">The timing of this attack--just as we made our own assault on Korriban? It's too much to be a coincidence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123757" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's possible the enemy's intelligence isn't the shambles we were led to believe. I'm sure the SIS will determine how this slip-up happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. We will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123761" id2="17" version="1065353216">All the same, you've succeeded in two critical missions for the Republic, back to back. You're heroes, and you deserve to be recognized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even so, you've just won two critical battles for the Republic, back to back. You're a hero, and heroes deserve to be recognized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123765" id2="17" version="1065353216">The medal of valor. No commendation this prestigious has ever been awarded so quickly; the Chancellor was truly impressed. As am I. Congratulations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123766" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate the recognition, Colonel. But there's still more to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123767" id2="17" version="1065353216">The timing of the attacks, Colonel--and the message from that Sith lord. We have to figure out what really happened here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123767" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still have questions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep the trinkets, Colonel. We need to find the person responsible for this and deal with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget the blasted medals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123769" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have the information you gathered. I'm sure we'll identify the culprit very soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123771" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, then: I've been tasked with organizing the Tython cleanup, and I want to be sure the Jedi Council knows they have our full support. If you'll excuse me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123773" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know about you, but I need a drink.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123775" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we're fortunate, the Empire will realize they're beaten sooner rather than later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe the Sith will surrender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123776" id2="17" version="1065353216">An end to this war? I could stand to see that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123776" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I signed up for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123777" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know about you, Colonel, but I prefer to spend my great days in the cantina.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123777" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should be celebrating!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123779" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, I normally charge by cargo mass. I don't know Korriban's mass offhand, but I'm sure if we check the HoloNet....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's talk rewards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123780" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did this happen?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123781" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're willing to help, we might be able to find out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123783" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blue Squadron: complete refueling operations and launch immediately. Any wave one troops not injured on Korriban: re-equip and board shuttles.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shan, you gather whatever sensor data we have and forward it to all forces. I want everyone en route in five. Move!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stopping the Empire may call for more than just our strike force. Can we count on reinforcements?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we get more backup?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123787" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll arrange for every available resource while you're in transit. We don't have time to wait, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123789" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is too much to be a coincidence. I don't think it's wise to rush in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123789" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to stop and think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123790" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is your home base being attacked, Master Jedi. You can meditate on the ramifications later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123792" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're soldiers. It's not our job to decide what's wise, it's our job to fight the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123794" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it's as unwise as you think, we'll up your pay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123796" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire must not be allowed to capture Tython. We cannot afford to hesitate. Period.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to make the Empire wish they'd never even heard of Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. Don't hold anything back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speed is what I'm known for. We'll have Tython back before you know it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1123801" id2="17" version="1065353216">You got it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123802" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1123804" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll pull up every bit of data we've got and talk you through the whole way. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126102" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know it's hard to leave an operation sometimes. I've been there. But your part is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126104" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will. But you've done more than enough for one day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126106" id2="17" version="1065353216">That may be wishful thinking--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126108" id2="17" version="1065353216">The homeworld of the Sith... this is much more serious than you led me to believe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1126108" id2="17" version="1065353216">You never mentioned Korriban.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126109" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assumed you'd just grab the facts right out of my head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126111" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126113" id2="17" version="1065353216">Open comms aren't the safest place for honesty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126115" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you had told me the plan up front, I would've had you start paying me right then and there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1126115" id2="17" version="1065353216">You never mentioned Korriban.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like I made the right move, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126118" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never expected such a ruthless plan from a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126120" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and I think very much alike.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126122" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regardless, it's not an option. There isn't time to land the necessary hardware for a full-scale demolition. We'll take what we can get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126125" id2="17" version="1065353216">But if we succeed... we could learn more about the Empire's moves than every SIS operation from the past decade combined.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126127" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our forces are ready. Victory for the Republic depends on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126128" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I'll go immediately. May the Force be with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126129" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126130" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can always rely on the Jedi to aid in such important tasks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126131" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126132" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad won't let you down, Colonel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126133" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Dependable&quot; is my middle name!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126134" id2="17" version="1065353216">Move out.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
