<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>12</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/tython_and_korriban/republic/theron_transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron to strike team. Sensors show Imperial forces entrenched all the way to the Jedi Temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sensors show some kind of shielding around the Jedi Temple Library--the Imps must be up to something in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imps have sliced the defensive shield grid--they're cutting off our approach vectors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron to wave two. Welcome to Korriban. You'll need to traverse the Wilds up ahead to reach the Sith Academy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperial defenders have a barricade up ahead. There's no time to go around--you'll have to break through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127912" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dark Council chambers are on the upper levels. You'll need to access the main elevator to reach them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wave one managed to soften the Imps up a bit, but you've still got your work cut out for you. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127929" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith Academy isn't far now. Keep it up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1127936" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have much intel on the upper-level defenses--be ready for some heavy opposition.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128101" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enemy artillery is going to make any large-scale deployments very messy. See what you can do to fix that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128104" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you reach the command platform, try to clear out the enemy forces and open things up for the next wave of reinforcements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1128106" id2="17" version="1065353216">Track the shield power back to its source and shut it down, then see what's going on.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
