<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>49</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/tython_and_korriban/republic/theron_shan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124015" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was Grand Master Satele, wasn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Currently acting as emissary to the Drayvos League. Nowhere near Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124018" id2="17" version="1065353216">We aren't close, of course. Your order is pretty particular on that point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124019" id2="17" version="1065353216">She gave you up when you were a child, then?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not that I'm complaining. You Jedi have your rules, and it turns out I don't have your talent anyway. Everything's worked out for the best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124021" id2="17" version="1065353216">The rules of our order are important, but that doesn't mean they're easy to live by. It's good that you hold no resentment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1124021" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's good to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124022" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are more important things in life than wallowing in past troubles. More than enough to deal with in the present.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124024" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you ask me, you turned out pretty well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1124024" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] I'd say so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124025" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope that means you're willing to hear me out a bit, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124027" id2="17" version="1065353216">In my experience, most &quot;Jedi rules&quot; only stand in the way of getting things done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1124027" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never liked rules.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you're not like any of the other Jedi I've met.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124030" id2="17" version="1065353216">We aren't exactly close; the Jedi don't much care for family dynamics. Doesn't mean I can't check up on her, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124031" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're her son, why weren't you raised as a Jedi?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124032" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was, actually. But I don't have their particular talent, so I found... other employment. Honestly, I'd say things have worked out just fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most people don't have &quot;interplanetary super-spy&quot; as their backup career. Do you enjoy it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1124033" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you think of the SIS?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sometimes. But you end up dealing with a lot of lies in this business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124035" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you ask me, you turned out pretty well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1124035" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] I'd say so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I'm guessing you won't mind staying and hearing me out a bit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124038" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi have too many rules. That's no way to live life.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1124038" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're definitely better off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124039" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess a soldier would know a bit about rules. But that isn't what I asked you here to talk about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124041" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure you've spent enough time around any rules to have a fair impression of them, Captain. But that isn't what I asked you here to talk about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124043" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even without the Force, I know when things don't add up. These ops, Colonel Darok... something's being buried here. I'm sure of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124045" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the real question is, are you going to take your shiny medal and go home like Darok's hoping, or are you ready to start digging?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124046" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you were to do some digging, where exactly would you start?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1124046" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you have in mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124047" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were just as involved in all of this as the colonel. Maybe you're working for him. Pretending to be an ally to see how much I know already.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1124047" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure I can trust you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124048" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not saying this wasn't all a bit strange, but looking at our own people? You're jumping at shadows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1124048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be paranoid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1124049" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I do for a living.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126150" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd start by recruiting someone I could count on. Someone who'd be willing to face down the Emperor himself if it came to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126152" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd start by recruiting someone I trusted. Someone insightful, who could always find the truth of things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126154" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd start by recruiting someone with experience in black ops. Someone who's spent time sniffing out traitors would be a plus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126156" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd start by recruiting someone outside the system. Someone who's used to working outside the lines, around the edges.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then, I'd find out everything I could about Darok and that Sith Lord you talked to. See if there are any connections.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126160" id2="17" version="1065353216">And then, once I found something, I'd contact my new friend and we'd get to the bottom of all this. But this is all just speaking hypothetically, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126161" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126162" id2="17" version="1065353216">Been great chatting with you. We'll have to do it again sometime. See you around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow. And I was worried you wouldn't be suspicious enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126166" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't have to do anything if you don't want to. But I'm going to learn everything I can about Darok and that Sith Lord you talked to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126168" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I find something, I'll contact you. Then you can decide whether you want in on the fun. Fair enough?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fair enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1126172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I'll be seeing you.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
