<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>80</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally. Let's relax and kick off our boots.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Noise, heat, sweat. I can hear their beating hearts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Off-duty soldiers, scared locals... they try to hide it, but they're shell-shocked. Just waiting for something to blow up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Braden, Jory and I would always end up in places like this after a successful bounty. Jory said, &quot;Spend your credits while you still can, little girl.&quot; Good advice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to the war zone. Get ready for a bumpy ride.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305594" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remember the craters and trenches of Yn and Chabosh. The terror of the dying. It was glorious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305595" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought this place was supposed to be pacified--we're in the middle of a war zone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305596" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope they don't have to use those guns while we're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makes me grateful to be with you. I would not want to work here on the best of days.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this what the Empire calls war? Hiding in a warehouse?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess this is Troida. Probably a lot nicer before the occupation, but you take what you can get....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305602" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like the fighting hasn't slowed production here much. They must put out a ton of armament per day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305605" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm guessing this place has seen better days. Then again, maybe not.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where is the glory in capturing a heap of junk?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305607" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a lot of slag. So glad I'm not in the salvage business anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kinda reminds you of Hutta, huh? Not as soggy, but just as much junk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great view--let's see... we got rocks, and some more rocks....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305612" id2="17" version="1065353216">The claws of Balmorra scream for blood.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305613" id2="17" version="1065353216">You smell that? Scorched metal, chems, dead things. Don't lean over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those trenches look huge enough to drive a walker through! Can you imagine what this must've been like during a full-scale invasion?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even safe areas on this planet feel like the place could go up in flames at any moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not delay, little master. Take, conquer, kill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Brave little Imps in the middle of a war. Want to play with them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never seen an ion cannon this close before... you don't think that's going to fry my implants if we get too close, do you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm, a lot more goes into making a droid than I ever thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305624" id2="17" version="1065353216">That reminds me of my cage on Korriban. Let's move on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305625" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you say we pop that thing, make the whole place burn?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305626" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't exactly look stable, and with all the droids going berserk, I don't want to be anywhere near it if it melts down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305629" id2="17" version="1065353216">A camp with no campfire? What's this world coming to?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305630" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cower, little Imperials. Cower.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's take a break, all right? I want to check my weapons while the shooting's stopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305632" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't envy these guys. Nothing but a couple tents between them and some berserk droids or a resistance ambush. Not the ideal place to be camping.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305635" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gee, you think they got enough guns to protect this place?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305636" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think we have found the secret to raining death from the sky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice rig. Wanna kill everyone, try to pick up pirate HoloNet channels?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305638" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugh, this place is giving my link all sorts of interference. Records say this is the control tower for Balmorra's planetary defense satellites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305641" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place smells even worse than it looks. And that is saying a lot.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305642" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place is poisoned.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305643" id2="17" version="1065353216">That stuff is foul. Takes brass to live here, though--spitting up green goo every morning and going out to fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305644" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, isn't that a healthy shade of green... looks like the waste is leaking from that factory over there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305647" id2="17" version="1065353216">I ever tell you I have a fear of being stomped to death by bugs?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305648" id2="17" version="1065353216">Creatures bred for war. At last, some worthy opponents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305649" id2="17" version="1065353216">We used to eat bugs back home, sometimes. Knife the shell, crack it open, suck down the guts. I hated it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305650" id2="17" version="1065353216">This doesn't add up, I found a couple of small entries on the Colicoids. They sound like a sentient species... not like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305653" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have one thing to say--yuck. Scratch that, two things--yuck and ugh.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305654" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a nest. The queen must be near.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305655" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many of these things are there? This planet's gonna get eaten alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh boy, I think the noxious coat of slime on everything is the least of our worries... coming in here was such a bad idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305659" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's nice to find a little oasis in the middle of all this crazy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305660" id2="17" version="1065353216">You walk as a giant among worms, little Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305661" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here's what I figure--the guys with rank stay under the shield dome. The grunts get assigned out here. What does that make us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Balmorra's not so bad sans the shooting. I bet it was downright pleasant before all this fighting started.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305665" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I was on the lam, this is where I'd hide. Don't tell anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Murder in the dark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305667" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ash in the soil and a gun in my hands. Let's go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wonder what was going on out here. Think this used to be a Balmorran resistance camp?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305671" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy sure has nice digs. Bet the Imperials are jealous.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305672" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's drive the Balmorran rebels away in terror.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now this is a base. Won't be when we're done with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think they've got enough flags? If they had as many soldiers, we might actually have a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305677" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd think a war happened here or something. Just a wild guess.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305678" id2="17" version="1065353216">The smoke of the battlefield, the smell of death. It's almost as if my master were alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305679" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at this: It's my new favorite playground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305680" id2="17" version="1065353216">This... this is awful. We aren't going through that, are we? I don't want to end up another forgotten body in this no-man's-land.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305683" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're looking for a little trench warfare--and really, who isn't?--this is the place for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305684" id2="17" version="1065353216">You cannot hide, little Balmorrans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I look like a trench rat? There's fun, there's stupid and there's suicidal. This is just stupid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305686" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear trench warfare is as bad as it gets. Cowering in a dirty hole hoping a bombardment doesn't hit too close, or penned in with dozens of others desperately fighting with nowhere to go....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305689" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place is immense. Something tells me we're going to be here for a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305690" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the great fortress of the Balmorran rebels?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some kind of control center. Don't really care about the details so long as the sparks fly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305692" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place isn't a factory, it's a fortress. I don't think the Balmorran freedom fighters could maintain a stronghold like this without outside help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305695" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pretty desolate, huh? Empire sure did a number on this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305696" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire still has the power to destroy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305697" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nasty place. Hear those things scuttling around... might want to check your gun battery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh, looks like this place has been resettled. I suppose it's too much to hope these Colicoids are the reasonable kind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305701" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, if I were a freaky mutated bug, this is where I'd want to be. No question.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="305702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure it's wise to swim in this substance?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305703" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know what's in there, and I don't really want to. Balmorrans locked it down for a reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="305704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ick, try not to breathe that. That's a hazard vault. It's where factories store the dangerous waste that can't be processed.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
