<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>32</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/qtr/1x3/daily/belsavis/republic/section_x/major_endran.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006240" id2="17" version="1065353216">Section X used to run like clockwork. Now this....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006243" id2="17" version="1065353216">The doctors gave me a clean bill of health, Major. The healthiest mind they'd ever seen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006245" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give our new allies the rundown. Secure Section X. That is all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wonderful, you're here! It's chaos out there, Master Jedi. Pure chaos!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006249" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major Endran, sir. I've been told you outrank me here. To avoid confusion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006251" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect timing, Captain. We've got a real mess on our hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006253" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally! Major Endran, at your service. Just been prepped for your arrival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006255" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Conlath's nervous breakdown came at the worst time. One second, we're battling the Empire; the next, we're staring down the Dread Masters' lieutenants.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006257" id2="17" version="1065353216">No idea what these Dread Guards are hunting for. But they've released an army of the Dread Masters' monstrous servants to help!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006258" id2="17" version="1065353216">This prison still holds many horrible secrets. If the Dread Masters claim even one of them, losing Belsavis may be the least of our concerns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their hunt cannot succeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006259" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't even want to think about it, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006261" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Empire supported the Dread Masters, they'd have landed an army of soldiers to aid their hunt. We may be facing a rogue Sith operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006261" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith must act alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006262" id2="17" version="1065353216">Explains why the Dread Guards kill everyone they see. Imp, Republic, doesn't matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Neutralize the Dread Guards, dishearten their legion, and we'll break the back of their offensive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Armies I can handle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006265" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't wait to see Havoc Squad back in action, Major.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006267" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless the Dread Masters lost the keys to their dreadnaught, I'd say they're looking to make a giant score.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006267" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're after something big.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever they're after, let's hope we never see it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006270" id2="17" version="1065353216">What Dread Guards?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006270" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dread Guards?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006271" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters' foul captains. I've seen one kill ten Jedi without breaking a sweat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006273" id2="17" version="1065353216">Control yourself, Major. Or you'll be sent for psych evaluation with your general.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006273" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Relax, already. Everyone gets so freaked out around these Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1006274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take it easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006275" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right. Need to keep my head. It's that or die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006277" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lucky for us, the Imps aren't on good terms with the Dread Masters' thralls. We're looking at a three-army showdown in Section X.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your head down, and check our battle notices. It's the only way we're stopping the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1006281" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you see a Dread Guard, run.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
