<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>59</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris_imp/world/spilling_chemicals/lya_charrel.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616969" id2="17" version="1065353216">The newest reports indicate that the toxins are seeping into the water table. Ha! Nothing will purify that ruin now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616970" id2="17" version="1065353216">My sensors picked it up the moment you opened the containers. Well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because of you, Taris ChemWorks remains as the Empire intended--a deadly, chemical-burned ruin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speaking of, I should treat you for contamination. I'd hate for you to get ill from the exposure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chaos, sabotage and destruction. It'll do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616975" id2="17" version="1065353216">All in a day's work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616976" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to enjoy your work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616978" id2="17" version="1065353216">I only regret not being able to see their faces when the Republic learns of the contamination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616979" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do I do if your decontamination doesn't work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616979" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if I get sick...?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616980" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, in the slim chance that your lungs begin to liquefy--I can take care of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616982" id2="17" version="1065353216">After all, it's important to protect the Empire's talented assets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616983" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a waste of my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616984" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry you don't approve, but you've been valuable help. The Republic won't recover from the blow you've dealt them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616986" id2="17" version="1065353216">The longer you take, the more time those Republic fools have to find and destroy those chemicals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616989" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, please excuse the mess. I don't get many visitors in the lab.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616991" id2="17" version="1065353216">You gave me a fright. I thought you were here for the environmental reports.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616993" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry, we don't get many visitors to the lab. Most people avoid us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still, I'm glad you stopped by. The Republic's efforts to clean and recolonize Taris are accelerating, but I've found a way to stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616997" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just need someone to release the dangerous toxins inside a crumbling, mephitic ruin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most of Taris is a ruin. Be more specific.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="616998" id2="17" version="1065353216">What crumbling ruin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="616999" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Taris ChemWorks--a shuddering remnant of its past, filled with leaking stockpiles of poisonous waste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your accent--you don't sound Imperial.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="617001" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not from the Empire....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617002" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire welcomed me when the Republic accused me of war crimes--but my past isn't important. Taris's past is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before the Empire bombarded Taris, the ChemWorks was a prosperous factory full of deadly chemicals. Those chemicals are still there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617006" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic can't possibly make this place livable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="617006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recolonize Taris? Absurd.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617007" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd be surprised; they've already established water purification plants. However--the Taris ChemWorks will be their undoing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before Taris's destruction, the ChemWorks produced all manner of deadly chemicals, which still remain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617011" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic burned off most of the pollutants, but they missed the barrels of 3-5-7 trichloroheptane, a beautifully lethal poison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we know why the Republic missed them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="617012" id2="17" version="1065353216">How'd that happen?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617013" id2="17" version="1065353216">The factory used to be a maze of secure storage depots. Without a proper inventory, it's understandable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617015" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not familiar with that particular chemical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="617015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trichloro-what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trichloroheptane. Among other things, it's a virulent poison that forms an acidic mist when exposed to air. It would quickly contaminate the entire area.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="617018" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm waiting for my part.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly. If the factory were unguarded, I could take care of it myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617021" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, the Republic knows the ChemWorks is central to Taris's reclamation. They stationed a squad of commandos there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617023" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can force your way in and break open the chemical containers, the resulting corrosive fog will poison the soil for a century.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617024" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic has none who can oppose me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="617024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Simple enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617025" id2="17" version="1065353216">The weak minds of the Republic are no obstacle to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="617025" id2="17" version="1065353216">Simple enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617026" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're lucky I came along when I did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="617026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Simple enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Infiltration and sabotage are my stock and trade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="617027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Simple enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617028" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you succeed, you'll cripple the Republic's cleanup efforts. I wish you luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617030" id2="17" version="1065353216">Foiling the Republic is one thing. You want to ruin a planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="617030" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is all that really necessary?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617031" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not permanent damage, strictly speaking. Besides, the faster the Republic gives up, the fewer of us need to die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617033" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ruins of the ChemWorks are located near the Republic's outposts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Move quickly. If the Republic figures out what chemicals we're looking for, they'll destroy them first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="617037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find another. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617038" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll regret not helping me, just as the Republic shall regret opposing me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="617040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic fools. Soon they'll regret ever having opposed me.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
