<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>14</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/open_worlds/class/jedi_consular/remnants_of_natukar/rakata_engineer.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1065749" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not just a hologram?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077031" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the plague must have struck your people first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where did you hide them? In space? A nebula, perhaps?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Obviously, you've never tried to hold a galactic empire together.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1077047" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is a world. A place where the Shrouded One I crafted still slumbers. See, here are its stars, its hidden place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077182" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not helping, Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077184" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't even imagine being blinded to the Force, let alone losing your whole civilization because of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apparently, there was no word in Rakata for &quot;redundancy measures.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077188" id2="17" version="1065353216">Actually, Torwin's been uncharacteristically quiet; I can make some inquiries, in case he's planning something unsavory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1078741" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, the Rakata mastered holocron technology; it has knowledge, personality. See his vestments? This was created in the last days of the Infinite Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1079970" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hooray, I can help!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1079972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shouldn't you be cheering Torwin on? Your Empire's been trying to destroy our Republic for generations, and this boy might actually do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1079972" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must be in favor of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1079973" id2="17" version="1065353216">We want victory, not a firestorm! If Torwin wakes the Shrouded Ones, they won't discriminate. We'll all go the way of the Rakata.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
