<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>37</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/open_worlds/class/jedi_consular/remnants_of_natukar/ship_holoterminal.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076444" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know Torwin--where would he go? Back to his family, perhaps?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1076444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where could he be?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never to his family. He needs information, as we do. I've posted guards on my libraries, in case my Rakata artifacts prove tempting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076720" id2="17" version="1065353216">It makes sense to know what we're getting into, but do nothing until I join you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1076720" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scout, but don't act.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076747" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, so considerate. Very well. You'll have the coordinates as soon as they're deciphered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076752" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, you conquered me in battle. But after conquest, one must rule wisely. My expertise shouldn't be brushed aside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then maybe you should go to Natukar ahead of us. Just in case.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1076753" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076754" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're Sith. If I trusted you completely, I'd be a fool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1076754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Caution is also wise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076755" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll use your expertise how and when I wish. For now, I've told you my orders. Send the maps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1076755" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll do as I tell you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076757" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine. You'll have what you want. I'll be waiting aboard my ship; you've given me food for thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076776" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be waiting aboard my ship. Let me stop Torwin. That's all I ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Naturally. But right now, betraying you would cost me everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1076789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Done. You won't regret this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077271" id2="17" version="1065353216">After Makeb, a Shrouded One might be just what the Hutt Cartel needs to free itself from Republic control. We'll need to tread lightly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1077271" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts might want it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps, but we still have to pinpoint the exact location of the Shrouded One on Sleheyron, from the hologram's data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1077279" id2="17" version="1065353216">Slow down. You still need me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077280" id2="17" version="1065353216">Certainty without proof is dangerous. Torwin could have a completely different strategy in mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1077280" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could be wrong about this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077281" id2="17" version="1065353216">And unfortunately, since I hold the charts and data on the Shrouded One's exact location, it seems our alliance must stand. For now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1077281" id2="17" version="1065353216">So I can't be rid of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077286" id2="17" version="1065353216">Indeed. Our citizens know loyalty; if a Jedi comes for Torwin, they'll die to keep him hidden. Unless I convince them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077287" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well then. I suppose our truce can stand a little longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps, but Torwin has no power base. He needs resources, and expertise. Besides, he's always been more comfortable around non-Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure if that's funny or sad. Both?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077332" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, I hear the constant threat of death will do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1077834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Torwin will seek out those scientists for help. They'd rather die than turn him over to a Jedi, but they shall assist a Darth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1078812" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope so, because those charts just became our only lead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1078815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sleheyron would certaintly fit Torwin's projected course.... Our Empire has scientists there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1078817" id2="17" version="1065353216">And good luck sifting through it without me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1080017" id2="17" version="1065353216">What were they?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1080023" id2="17" version="1065353216">At least tell us what the Shrouded Ones are.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1080025" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am empty of that. The Rakata feared what knowledge of the Shrouded Ones might grow in us, and punished questioning.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
