<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>5</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/voss/heroic_weekly/mission_board_imperial.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187875" id2="17" version="1065353216">Outsiders and potential allies: The Voss seek knowledge of the past. Scholars opened a tomb, ancient and untouched. None survived.

Monsters and machines, horrors beyond memory, awaited them. Voss warriors were sent to fight. Now they are lost, also. Outsider help is required.

Enter the tomb under the Old Paths. Destroy its guardians. The Voss will have knowledge. Outsiders will have their reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Outsiders and potential allies: Voss commandos defied the law and entered the Nightmare Lands. Unthinking bravery. Corruption has overtaken them.

It has destroyed their minds, but enhanced their bodies. They wield strange powers and command wild beasts. Darkness seeps beyond the Nightmare Lands' borders.

Bring the warriors a merciful death. End their suffering. The Voss will be grateful. Material reward offered.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention outsiders and potential allies: The Gormak have led the Rock-eater into the tombs near the Shrine of Healing.

An escort of Gormak guides and controls the powerful cyber-beast, seeking a passage into the Shrine of Healing itself.

Entire Voss commando units sent to stop the beast have been devoured.

Defeat the Gormak guardians and destroy the Rock-eater, and material rewards will be granted.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1187878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attention outsiders and potential allies: A challenge.

The Trial of the First Commando opens below the shrine. Only the greatest Voss commandos participate. They duel and grow strong.

First Commando Nakar-Sel hears of your Empire's strength. He speaks: Prove it against him, and the commandos who make Gormak weep.

The healers watch. There will be injury, but none shall die. If you do not fear pain, win pride.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1197901" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Voss could use assistance with a number of dangerous, high-priority missions. Completing these missions will increase your reputation among the Voss.

Complete [HEROIC] Ancient Guardians
Complete [HEROIC] Cleanse the Corrupted
Complete [HEROIC] Rock Eaters
Complete [HEROIC] The First Commando's Call</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
