<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>35</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/voss/bronze/republic/all_animals_deserve_a_chance/dagus_parral.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85501" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few years with those vorantiki running free, and the ecosystem will start to balance out again.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85502" id2="17" version="1065353216">My field sensors are reporting vorantiki returning to their territories. You did it!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85504" id2="17" version="1065353216">They can't thank you for this, so I will. I found this during my botanical cataloging; I hope you can use it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85506" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't let innocent animals be turned into those cyber-monstrosities--please, you have to set those vorantiki free.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85507" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just look at this world. So much variety. There's creatures here that couldn't evolve in any other biosphere.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85509" id2="17" version="1065353216">And what do the Gormak do? They take these beautiful animals, like the vorantikus, and turn them into cybernetic monsters! It's horrific!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85510" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds incredibly inhumane, not to mention painful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does it hurt the animals?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85511" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know, but I doubt they enjoy it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forcing animals to be their war machines... this will be a dark chapter in Gormak history.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85513" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Gormak demean themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who cares about the Gormak? It's the vorantiki that matter, and the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those Gormak are a little too creative when it comes to weaponry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Living war machines.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85517" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the poor vorantiki aren't the only ones being harmed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85519" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's like the Gormak decided they just weren't scary enough as they are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85519" id2="17" version="1065353216">And terrifying.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85520" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have you know that, aside from the occasional blood frenzy, vorantiki are lovely creatures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85522" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's a &quot;vorantikus&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85522" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Vorantikus&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85523" id2="17" version="1065353216">A fascinating apex predator with distinctive dorsal--er, those large, bluish, carnivorous animals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even without the Gormak implanting them, they could still bite you in half.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85525" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're all monsters anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85526" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, no! Well, maybe, but the vorantiki's natural aggression is being heightened by these tech implants.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Making them into... cyber-beasts is destroying predator-prey dynamics and breeding cycles; Voss's ecology is suffering.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85530" id2="17" version="1065353216">But, if we could free the animals before they're implanted, the Gormak will waste months trying to capture more. The vorantiki go free, the Gormak are distracted--everyone wins!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="85531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I can help you get these creatures back to the wild.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85531" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like this plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wonderful! I'd appreciate anything you can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85534" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't these beasts attack me?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85535" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, it's fine, the Gormak keep them docile for implantation. The vorantiki should ignore you--just don't smell too tasty.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85537" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll show you where to find the vorantikus pens, but be careful, there'll be plenty of Gormak nearby. You can't help the animals if you get hurt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="85539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget it. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85540" id2="17" version="1065353216">But it's for the good of... forget I asked.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="85542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those cyber-beasts are a blight on Voss.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
