<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>34</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/class/trooper/general_garza.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708451" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come in, Major. This is General Garza. The situation on Belsavis is complicated, so let's begin immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708453" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis houses a top secret prison colony for the worst offenders in the Republic--Sith Lords, war criminals and mass murderers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708455" id2="17" version="1065353216">That prison is under heavy assault--the Imperials are attempting to free their captured comrades. While you're in the field, do whatever you can to impede them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708456" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the impression the prison break isn't why I'm here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me my primary objective.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708457" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did the Imperials hear about our top secret prison?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who tipped the Imps off?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708458" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unknown. The Empire has its spies, just as we have ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why fight to hold people we don't want? Why not bomb the whole prison?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a waste of time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708461" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not everyone in the Republic shares your outlook on prisoner management.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708463" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your primary objective is to extract the pilots of Dagger Wing, an elite navy starfighter unit, from within the prison zone and return them to service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Were these pilots shot down? Will they need medical attention?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708464" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me their situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708465" id2="17" version="1065353216">They weren't sent to Belsavis on a mission. They're inmates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708467" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can swap war stories.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708468" id2="17" version="1065353216">Socialize on your own time, Major. This is an important operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708470" id2="17" version="1065353216">If these guys aren't army, why are we involved?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why can't the navy do this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708471" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ground-based extractions are generally handled by the army, regardless of who is being extracted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708473" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pilots of Dagger Wing are serving life sentences on Belsavis for participating in an unauthorized bombing mission that killed thousands of Imperial civilians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708475" id2="17" version="1065353216">The attack was so brutal that High Command had no choice but to disavow the incident and sweep away the pilots responsible--permanently.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why did they target civilians?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did Dagger Wing go rogue?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708477" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dagger Wing thought they were acting in the Republic's best interests at the time. But results far outweigh intentions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708479" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we locked these guys up for life, what are the odds they'll fly for us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708479" id2="17" version="1065353216">They might hold a grudge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Freedom is an excellent bargaining tool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there ever a mistake you people don't try to hide?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="708482" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just one more cover-up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Decisions from High Command are not open to debate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708485" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic needs Dagger Wing back in the fight, regardless of their past crimes. Starfighter pilots of their caliber are in very short supply.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="708487" id2="17" version="1065353216">A prison guard captain named Zess will direct you to Dagger Wing's CO, Conrad Gall. Contact him, extract the pilots and then report back to me. Garza out.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
