<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>221</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/nar_shaddaa/rusk_and_skadge/rusk.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175502" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose I should expect you to do the impossible by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175504" id2="17" version="1065353216">You Jedi never cease to amaze.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175506" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm guessing you've had some experience as a negotiator during your command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems you're used to talking your way out of dangerous situations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175510" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sometimes forget that you Sith can get what you want without violence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175512" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not surprised that a bounty hunter has ties to criminal organizations, but I am surprised how you leveraged them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175514" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have to wonder if that was your plan all along. You certainly read that Houk like a book.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175516" id2="17" version="1065353216">My predictions for that engagement ending in a peaceful resolution were negligible. I can't help but feel like it's delaying the inevitable.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175517" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is, but Black Sun is a problem that we can afford to put aside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hard to stay focused on the objective when you have to worry about watching your own six.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175520" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's possible we could be a good influence on some of them. It's an opportunity to do something with their lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175521" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the purpose of the legion. Except it's controlled--structured. Leaving that scum to their own devices puts a lot of people at risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175523" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just convinced a band of street thugs to take on the premier superpower in the galaxy. I doubt I'm delaying anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175524" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fair, but when the vermin scatter they'll be harder to root out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175526" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's moot now anyway. You made your call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eighty percent of my squads have successfully captured their objectives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175532" id2="17" version="1065353216">With their ringleader in our custody, any remnants will be too busy fighting among themselves to effectively regroup.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175534" id2="17" version="1065353216">The death of their kingpin will be a crushing blow to their morale. Any holdouts are as likely to be fighting each other as my troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175536" id2="17" version="1065353216">Black Sun's operation on Nar Shaddaa has been effectively neutralized.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175537" id2="17" version="1065353216">So your mission here is complete?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175538" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to speak with command, but I can safely say that the campaign is concluding.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for allowing me to be part of this operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175541" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi, it's always an honor to have you at my side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175543" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd earned it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175545" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't puff yourself up too much for having overcome a glorified street gang.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175546" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't claim that the legion is the match of a proper army yet, but the Black Sun Syndicate is nothing to scoff at.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175548" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Supreme Chancellor is going to be pleased with the results.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175550" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still have a lot to shore up before I withdraw the legion from Nar Shaddaa, but you'll hear from me soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175551" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be in touch after things are shored up here. The legion will need a new objective and I'm willing to hear what you're after.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175552" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Rusk.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175553" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll involve the Eternal Empire, that much you can count on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175554" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't be a dull briefing then.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just make sure this scum is ready for a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175557" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're always ready for a fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad to have you back, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175560" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rally up soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175564" id2="17" version="1065353216">All preparations are made. Just waiting on you. Ready to pull the Black Sun's interests on Nar Shaddaa apart?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175566" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Refuse Quest] Not yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175570" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hup to, Dead Men! It's time to earn that free air you're breathing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to you, I have units across Nar Shaddaa waiting to move on Black Sun's holdings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175574" id2="17" version="1065353216">The icing on the cake? We've learned where their kingpin runs the entire operation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175575" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see what the commotion is all about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175576" id2="17" version="1065353216">Final preparation is underway.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175578" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you plan to do with that information?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175579" id2="17" version="1065353216">End this campaign in one fell swoop.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally. Put an end to this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175582" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175584" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm pulling together my strongest squads for a raid on the Black Sun headquarters. There's a spot for you, if you're interested--you've more than earned it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Rusk--I'd like to see this though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175586" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you might feel that way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175588" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could be. Tell me what we're up against.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175589" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would rather have earned your cooperation in my fight against a more serious enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175590" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can talk about that once these gangsters are put in line. Working together here shows that we can work together elsewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175592" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even among criminals, Black Sun has a reputation for extreme brutality.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175594" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't know their numbers, but we can count on them being well-fortified and bloodthirsty.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, I've had the pleasure of crossing paths with them before. Killers, kidnappers, and terrorists at best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not much different from the White Maw. We've handled worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even their smuggling operations on Coruscant were unnecessarily sadistic. They stitched the contraband inside their couriers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175599" id2="17" version="1065353216">We found worse here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175601" id2="17" version="1065353216">I caught them dealing in nerve gas back on Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175602" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have my units ready their chemical weapons kits. I appreciate the heads-up.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175604" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was once on the hit list of a guy called Rogun the Butcher. I can handle this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175605" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not going to ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175607" id2="17" version="1065353216">The worst terrors they can imagine are pedestrian to a Sith such as me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175608" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure I'll find their horseplay quite charming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't remind me of the things you Imperials enjoy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175611" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've crossed paths with at least one of their kind before. &quot;Brutal and sadistic&quot; puts it lightly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175612" id2="17" version="1065353216">And that's why we've got to put them down.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175614" id2="17" version="1065353216">My experience with the underworld is that their methods are often crude and sometimes effective.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175615" id2="17" version="1065353216">This bunch seems to make up for it with enthusiasm.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175617" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you and your troops are up to the task.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175618" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've trained this lot into a respectable fighting force, and I'm sure a few have old scores to settle.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175620" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're street thugs. This won't even be a challenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never underestimate a cornered enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175623" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should be prepared to deploy any minute now. You ready?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's finish this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rally up, Dead Men! Operation Sunset is underway.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175627" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Refuse Quest] I'll need to make preparations of my own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175628" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got some time. But that intel we gathered will get stale before long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175632" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're close. I can feel it. We just need to find the weak link that'll bring it all down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175633" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have the names of several underbosses. Taking them into custody should speed things along.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175634" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've identified some locations where the Black Sun does their business. We'll be raiding them soon. Maybe something will turn up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175635" id2="17" version="1065353216">The initial legwork is light on valuable targets, but we're learning what sectors Black Sun likes to terrorize.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep up the good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay the course.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175638" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was hoping this would be finished sooner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wars aren't won in a day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175640" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have forces dispatched throughout Nar Shaddaa, but aside from rumors we've discovered little actionable intelligence.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175641" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Requires Influence Level 10] Have you found your target yet?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175644" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Deliver Intelligence] I found this on Black Sun members I encountered in the city.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175645" id2="17" version="1065353216">These crooks don't seem to be big on record keeping, but their comm logs are proving useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175646" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are helpful. They're all pieces to the bigger picture.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175647" id2="17" version="1065353216">That should keep us on the right path at least. I'll look over it for clues.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175649" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Give Contraband] I've brought something you should be able to bribe the locals with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175650" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can work with this. There's an information broker who'll always talk with the right incentives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175651" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've weeded out the liars from the reliable snitches. They're providing decent intel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175652" id2="17" version="1065353216">Much as I dislike it, these incentives have earned us some cooperation. You find any more, bring it my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175653" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll parcel it out carefully. Your contribution is appreciated. Don't let the troopers know you're collecting this stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175655" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Requires Underworld Influence Level 5] My contacts have turned up some useful information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your contacts are good. This will be a huge help.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175658" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll see what I can dig up myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175659" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful out there. The members of Black Sun are as bad as they come.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get your act together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175661" id2="17" version="1065353216">These scum know how to work the streets, I've just got to make sure they stay out of trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175671" id2="17" version="1065353216">Private Merghal, repeat subsection eight of article four-four-six of the Emergency Powers Act.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175673" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pssh, like I read any of that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175675" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll have plenty of time to in solitary confinement. You'll stay there until you can recite every regulation by heart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175677" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh yeah?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175679" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your next violation earns you a firing squad. Understand?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, okay! I get you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175683" id2="17" version="1065353216">Report to Provost Decker for processing. Get out of here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stars, it's good to see your face. Sorry about the undignified welcome. They don't make leashes tight enough for this lot.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175686" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to see you too. It seems like you've climbed the ranks since I've been gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175687" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are very few people who would choose this command, but I'm honored to shoulder the burden for the good of the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175689" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think I fully understand your situation here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175690" id2="17" version="1065353216">They look like rough customers. You must have your hands full.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175691" id2="17" version="1065353216">Disciplinary actions account for thirty-two percent of my duties. But that number is dropping... these scum are wising up to how good they have it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175693" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm disappointed, Rusk. I expected bigger things from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone has to do the dirty work. If I can give these sorry louts the opportunity to do one good thing for society, then it's worth it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175696" id2="17" version="1065353216">You just threatened that man's life. That's extreme, even for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175697" id2="17" version="1065353216">Apologies, Master Jedi. I know your order's stance on the convict legion. Ugly truth of the matter is, most of them shouldn't be outside a brig.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175698" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not here on behalf of the Jedi. Aygo wished for me to speak with the commander here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175699" id2="17" version="1065353216">Convict legion? All of these soldiers are prisoners?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Handle your soldiers as you please.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175701" id2="17" version="1065353216">Justify it however you like. Threatening a subordinate with violence is appalling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not everyone can live up to the example of the Jedi. This lot can't even live up to &quot;passable&quot;.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wasn't expecting a visit or I would have spared you the messy welcome. I'd advise you not to mix with the troops here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175705" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aygo suggested I speak with the commanding officer here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why the warning?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175707" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a military police insignia. Since when do we forego a court-martial?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175708" id2="17" version="1065353216">These men and women have already been sentenced. They're enjoying a stay because of their service to the war effort.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175710" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not on official business, but if Fideltin Rusk is around I need to speak with him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175711" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't approve of how you discipline your soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175712" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't a unit of the Republic's finest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175714" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every trooper here has been condemned by the state for crimes that would make you retch. It's my duty to keep that in check.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175716" id2="17" version="1065353216">But enough about me. Just what happened to you?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175717" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a conversation for another time. Right now, I need your help again. I'm gathering allies to strike against the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175718" id2="17" version="1065353216">Straight to the heart of the problem. At least that hasn't changed.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175720" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was held captive by Zakuul. I've been trapped in carbonite until recently.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175721" id2="17" version="1065353216">In carbonite... or like before?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175723" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been in Wild Space, fighting against the Eternal Empire. Getting back was... difficult.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175724" id2="17" version="1065353216">I feel like you're not telling me the whole story.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175726" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi, I haven't forgotten the last time we failed to strike at the Emperor. You're sure that didn't happen again?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Truthfully, the Sith Emperor has been in my head. Arcann imprisoned us both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175728" id2="17" version="1065353216">That boy imprisoned you and the Emperor? Not so surprising that he managed to conquer the galaxy now.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175730" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm certain, Rusk. The rest is just details.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175731" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's good enough for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175733" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think I let the Emperor dominate me again?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175734" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like to think that's possible, but you just vanished. Years without a word. It casts some doubt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175736" id2="17" version="1065353216">What can I do to help you again?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175737" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got soldiers. I could really use more troops in my Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come with me, Rusk. I need your skills.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175739" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would be my honor, Master Jedi, but I've been given this responsibility by the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175741" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're sniffing around for a place to hock contraband, I've got a strict zero-tolerance policy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aygo said I should get in touch with a Fideltin Rusk. He around?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Easy, now... apparently I don't want to get on your bad side. I'm looking for the person in charge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175744" id2="17" version="1065353216">You found him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Care to explain why you were threatening that guy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175747" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're some sort of protestor, take it up with your Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zero tolerance meaning &quot;I shoot anyone I disagree with.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175750" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have an outfit of hardened criminals that would like nothing more than to shoot me in the back. Zero tolerance means execution. For them, at least.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175752" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey buddy, I'm a Republic citizen--this &quot;martial law&quot; bunk isn't going to fly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175753" id2="17" version="1065353216">This area is off-limits to civilians. Period. I can promise that you don't want to be locked up with the people I have here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175754" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mind yourself, merc, or you might wind up in this outfit. Why are you trespassing in my headquarters?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175755" id2="17" version="1065353216">I represent an alliance against the Eternal Empire. You the senior officer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another confederacy of misfits. Wonderful.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175758" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looking for Fideltin Rusk. Where do I find him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175759" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Republic sovereign territory per the Makeb treaty. Diplomatic envoys require proper authorization. Vacate immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175760" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not here on behalf of the Sith Empire. I command an alliance against Zakuul. Who's the senior officer?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175761" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would be me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Provost Marshal Fideltin Rusk, Dead Man's Legion. What's this about?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175764" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aygo told me you might be receptive to lending your army to our cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you at least tell me how I can contact Fideltin Rusk?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175766" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's Provost Marshal Fideltin Rusk, and you're speaking to him.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aygo said I should find you. He's part of my alliance against the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175768" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Dead Man's Legion sounded interesting to me. Like something I could use in the fight against Zakuul.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175769" id2="17" version="1065353216">A joint operation? Interesting proposal, but it's not within my power.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175771" id2="17" version="1065353216">A treaty will not save you from a Sith's anger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175772" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen action on every planet in your Empire. It's going to take more than threats to move me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175773" id2="17" version="1065353216">I respond poorly to threats.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175774" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not going to repeat myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175775" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm only here because Aygo said you might be sympathetic to our cause: ending the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175776" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard he'd retired. You're telling me he's out with you and fighting Zakuul? That's a better use for a leader of his caliber, but it doesn't change the facts.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175778" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need you to calm down. I am not your enemy. I'm searching for allies willing to fight Zakuul, not each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175779" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admire your bravery, citizen, but you aren't talking to some mercenary outfit. The convict legion is a military unit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175781" id2="17" version="1065353216">It may not look it, but this is a military unit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175783" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith Empire hasn't been cooperative since Arcann invaded. About time that's changed, but I'm committed to this front.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chancellor Madon has deployed the Dead Man's Legion to suppress a gang war for our Hutt allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175787" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't entertain any appeals to take my army elsewhere until we've mopped up here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175788" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps I could speed that along?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175789" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would boost operational efficiency considerably. The less time this lot spends on Nar Shaddaa, the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175791" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like politics to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175792" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts are claiming it's our responsibility, since the problem originated from Republic space.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175794" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why is the Supreme Chancellor wasting troops on peacekeeping in Hutt Space?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175795" id2="17" version="1065353216">This operation ensures the Hutt Cartel remains cooperative. The Republic doesn't need any more enemies right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175797" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our objective is to root out fugitives of the Black Sun Syndicate that fled Coruscant and established themselves here. I need intelligence about their workings.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any leads?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aside from wandering the worst parts of town and shaking things up, we've got very little to go on.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175801" id2="17" version="1065353216">To what end?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175802" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find their ringleader and crush the whole problem at its core.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175804" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts should have provided that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175805" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've been obstinate, and a power play this brazen has them shaken. Most seem to be busy securing their own investments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Getting our hands on information from Black Sun members themselves would be the most useful, but working underworld connections could be a force multiplier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175809" id2="17" version="1065353216">If all else fails, we may have to rely on securing illicit goods to grease some palms.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175810" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's all we have to go on, we'll have to make do.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175811" id2="17" version="1065353216">No promises, but if I discover something I'll speak to you again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175812" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will continue to act as my base of operations until our campaign is complete. Bring anything you find here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1175813" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Refuse Quest] Good luck with that. I don't plan to plumb the depths of this cesspit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175814" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be overseeing the search from here, Master Jedi. I hope to have better news next time we speak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then kindly move along.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1175821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let your guard down. These soldiers are all hardened criminals.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1183075" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Smuggler Background] Definitely my area of expertise.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188831" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Hand Over 1 Looted Intelligence]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1188831" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Hand over 1]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188832" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Hand Over 5 Looted Intelligence]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1188832" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Hand over 5]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188840" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Hand Over 1 crate of Illicit Goods]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1188840" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Hand over 1]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188841" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Hand Over 5 crate of Illicit Goods]</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="1188841" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Hand over 5]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1211699" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Back]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
