<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>13</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/bronze/knight_fall/master_kirbi_hologram.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119932" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are being picked off one-by-one. We have doused our fire, but still they find us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119934" id2="17" version="1065353216">They seem to smell the Force in us; the light draws out their own darkness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119936" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were wrong. This is far worse than a plague. They cannot be saved. I hope we still can....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Masters Tre Trimbal and Luquena are dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119939" id2="17" version="1065353216">They ventured too close to the lair and were attacked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119941" id2="17" version="1065353216">There was... something else... leading the rakghouls. It seemed impervious to the power of the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119943" id2="17" version="1065353216">I fear we've now drawn its attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119944" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have set our camp near a rakghoul lair but have had little luck making contact with the creatures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119946" id2="17" version="1065353216">We take heart that our theories are sound, for there is a palpable dark side presence coming from the lair.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119948" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is that influence we must combat to turn back the plague.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119949" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are here on a mission of mercy. I am recording this holojournal to preserve our efforts for posterity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119951" id2="17" version="1065353216">All evidence indicates that rakghouls are not beasts but formerly sentient victims of a plague that mutates the body and mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="119953" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was Sith science that created the plague. And where the Force has corrupted, perhaps the Force can also heal....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
