<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>59</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/imperial/wookiee_revolt/captain_helricks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455719" id2="17" version="1065353216">You certainly showed those shaggy brutes who's boss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455721" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can occupy the factory now, Captain. The Wookiees won't bother anyone any more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455722" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's good news, I'll send troops in immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455724" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will provide a bit of comfort to my men. Good to see those hairy savages shown their place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455725" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Wookiees were a weed that needed pulling before it took root.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455725" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rebellion must be crushed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455726" id2="17" version="1065353216">When word gets out, we'll see a lot less of things like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your appreciation is welcome.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455729" id2="17" version="1065353216">How could I not be? Thanks to you, Corellia will soon become a proud, important member of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455731" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's truly been a honor to meet you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455732" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't always be available to clean up your failures, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455732" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be thankful I was here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455733" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll work harder to defend the glory of the Empire in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455735" id2="17" version="1065353216">Re-stocking, I hope? Word's spreading about those Wookiees; the longer they hold the factory, the worse it'll get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heal yourself up, Wexell. Don't worry, those savages will be punished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455738" id2="17" version="1065353216">My Lord, you honor a poor soldier with your presence, but you're a welcome sight about now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455740" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you--General Hesker told me what you did against the Selonians. You couldn't have come at a better time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive my sentiment, sir, but it's a relief to have someone of your caliber and dedication here at last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455744" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've a right lethal look about you; that sort of attitude is handy right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455746" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's the Wookiees--shaggy brutes tore into my men with a vengeance. Less than a third of us escaped, and most look worse than Wexell here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455747" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're a long way from Kashyyyk. What are Wookiees doing on Corellia?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455747" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't expect Wookiees here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455748" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellians like them as factory workers--they're supposedly industrious, clever with tools, and have strong backs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455750" id2="17" version="1065353216">It sounds like the Wookiees put your men through the grinder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455750" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry for your losses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455751" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're soldiers who performed honorably. Can't say the same for our foes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455753" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're only Wookiees, Captain--no match for Imperial troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455753" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you lose to animals?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455754" id2="17" version="1065353216">In a proper fight we might have held, but the savages weren't much interested in one of those. We weren't expecting such resistance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455756" id2="17" version="1065353216">My men have been converting Corellian factories for the Empire's. No problems until we got to the magnogravitics plant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455758" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Wookiees in the plant refused to hand it over--they ambushed us, and now they're holding the factory. It's a bitter pill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455759" id2="17" version="1065353216">An example needs to be made of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455759" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take care of your Wookiees.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455760" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll be dangerous. The Wookiees aren't interested in negotiation or reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455762" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Wookiees won't attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455763" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right, but it's ultimately not the Wookiees that concern me. I'm more worried about what happens when word gets out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your failure has created an explosive situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your incompetence is dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455766" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think I'm not aware of what has happened, either with the Wookiees or my men?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every hour they hold that factory, it inspires others into thinking they can defy the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455770" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate to say it, but we need a show of force to discourage this from happening again. Your capabilities are beyond ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455771" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Wookiees will learn their strength is no match for my fury.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455771" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will crush those savages.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455772" id2="17" version="1065353216">They will learn the meaning of fear before the power of the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455772" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll show them no mercy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Am I being paid by the pelt, or for the job as a whole?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455773" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle your problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455774" id2="17" version="1065353216">Central command manages the details of your reimbursement. The Wookiees will make you earn every credit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once word spreads, Corellia will learn the price of defiance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455776" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll handle the Wookiees.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455777" id2="17" version="1065353216">A Wookiee's a tough fight, even on equal footing--and they've all the advantages here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455779" id2="17" version="1065353216">They know every nook of that factory, and now they've had time to make ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455781" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I get the chance, I'll go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455782" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd hoped to see more enthusiasm from you, but I'll take what I can get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455784" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Wookiees won't go easier on you just because you're heart's not in it, so keep careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455786" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're going into Corellia's own savage jungle. Hopefully we can raise a glass when it's all done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="455788" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Refuse Quest] Not a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455789" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose not everyone lives up to their reputation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="455791" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the face of heroism in that tank--if he hadn't distracted them long enough for us to escape, we'd be dead.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
