<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>28</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/rishi/hub_1/heart_of_the_aggressor/shared/central_control_console.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron? Are you getting this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Loud and clear. I'm in. Full access.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133055" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the sort of momentum we could never create on our own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133057" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to maintain that momentum. Surely, if the Revanites are done with the Nova Blades as Revan indicated, they're on to the next stage of their plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133058" id2="17" version="1065353216">There'd better be something in the Nova Blades' files that sheds some light on what Revan's doing with those hyperspace routes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1133058" id2="17" version="1065353216">A plan we know little about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133059" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, tell me about it. I'm starting to feel like flying blind is the new normal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133061" id2="17" version="1065353216">With Margok dead, there'll be a power vacuum on Raider's Cove.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1133061" id2="17" version="1065353216">What of the Nova Blades?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Either the Nova Blades recover or another faction takes hold. I feel it's not our concern, really.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana's got a heart of stone sometimes, but yeah--let Raider's Cove worry about Raider's Cove.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1133066" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not worried.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133068" id2="17" version="1065353216">Say all you like about Revan, he was never as powerful a Sith as I am now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan's hardly the first Force user I've had to take down. It won't be a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133071" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not just Revan here; it's all his coconspirators. We don't know how many in the Republic and Empire are pulling strings for him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1133073" id2="17" version="1065353216">While Theron's pulling down data, I suggest you start to make your way back to Raider's Cove. Hopefully, he'll have found something of use by then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134510" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm in. There are dozens of comm logs in here... hundreds. Sent to people all over the galaxy. Coruscant, Dromund Kaas, Corellia....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134512" id2="17" version="1065353216">The names are all encoded, but breaking through that is only a matter of time. I'm going to get started right away. Great work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134514" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should hurry back. Despite what we overheard earlier, the Revanites could show up at any moment to try and help their allies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134516" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be back in no time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134519" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know that Jedi and Sith celebrate victory in quite the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, now you'll have a chance to find out firsthand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Copy that--heading home now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134523" id2="17" version="1065353216">See you soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134525" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you said planning a party would be getting ahead of ourselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do forgive my basic sense of caution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1134570" id2="17" version="1065353216">Besides... I think we've earned a bit of a celebration.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
