<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>61</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/yavin_4/fates_unsealed/shared/unlock_3.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142269" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time. You've finally arrived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142271" id2="17" version="1065353216">Help has arrived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142272" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan. But... you're alive. Leading the Revanites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142273" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now I've seen everything. Aren't you supposed to be... alive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142274" id2="17" version="1065353216">The brooding monster inside those temple walls, he is not Revan. He is an abomination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142276" id2="17" version="1065353216">His obsession, his arrogance, this angry crusade--it's all blinded him to the truth. The many lives he'll sacrifice to revive the Emperor will be nothing compared to what will follow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142278" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's within your power to stop the abomination. But you won't be able to do it alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142280" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142282" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi and I, we both felt it--a ripple in the Force. You had a visitor. A manifestation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142283" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was Revan. But not the Revan we've been after this whole time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1142283" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like Revan is dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142284" id2="17" version="1065353216">We both suspected that may be the case. It doesn't matter who's inside that temple. What's important is that we end his plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142285" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan wants me to succeed, but claims I can't do it on my own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142286" id2="17" version="1065353216">It appeared to be Revan. He claims to be on our side, and that the one we've been chasing isn't him after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1142286" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's perplexing....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142287" id2="17" version="1065353216">He said he was Revan, and the one we've been after isn't. I'm not entirely sure I buy it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1142287" id2="17" version="1065353216">Possibly a phony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142288" id2="17" version="1065353216">That all remains to be seen. And for now, it's irrelevant. All that matters is that we stop the Revanites.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142289" id2="17" version="1065353216">He didn't seem to think I could do it on my own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142290" id2="17" version="1065353216">It had to be a trick of the Force. Some strange attempt by Revan to confuse me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1142290" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt my senses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142291" id2="17" version="1065353216">It said it was Revan, and that it's on our side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1142291" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the Force expert....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever you witnessed, you must put it behind you and look ahead to the enemy within.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142294" id2="17" version="1065353216">All told, the Revanites may be the fiercest adversaries we've ever faced, and this temporary alliance with the Republic is unstable at best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1142296" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must gather our forces. We must endure. The fate of not only the Empire but the galaxy itself depends on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143217" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. You have opened the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143218" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan? How is this possible?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143219" id2="17" version="1065353216">Through the Force, anything is possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143221" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Emperor's followers struck me down... I learned to release my attachments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143222" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then who's wearing your mask and leading your followers?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143223" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... do not know. But I recognize much of myself in him. The darkness I left behind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143225" id2="17" version="1065353216">He must be stopped. His fury will only strengthen the Emperor, not destroy him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143226" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your descendants are close by--Satele and Theron Shan. Why speak to me instead of them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1143226" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why appear to me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143227" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must remain apart from them. My attachments have always driven me too far, and I have always refused to see it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143229" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry I wasn't there to fight with you. We might have been able to avoid all of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1143229" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish I had fought with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143230" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good that you didn't. I told myself that I was not altered by my centuries in the Emperor's grasp....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143232" id2="17" version="1065353216">But my actions were those of a madman, consumed by rage. I am glad to have left such evil behind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143234" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must do what I could not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143235" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you know how to stop this madness, tell me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1143235" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143236" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are on the right path. Continue. Survive. Persevere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143238" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done it! The way is opening!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143239" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just spoke to Revan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143240" id2="17" version="1065353216">You... what? He was there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143241" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was his spirit. He couldn't tell me who's wearing his mask, but he did confirm that trying to kill the Emperor wouldn't work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143242" id2="17" version="1065353216">The man who tortured me was an imposter? How could he know so much?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143243" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can sort that out when we face him. For now, we need to focus on the weapon he has primed inside the temple.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143244" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right. We're only going to get one shot at this... once our forces enter the temple, it's only a matter of time until our friend pulls the trigger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143246" id2="17" version="1065353216">A joint strike--committing all of our forces and the Empire's--has a good chance of pushing through the temple and disabling the weapon before it can fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143248" id2="17" version="1065353216">An operation like that needs perfect coordination--and trust. It might take some doing to get our troops working together at that level.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143249" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps a smaller team would be a better option?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143250" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about a small-unit operation?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143251" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could get a smaller group in faster and more quietly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143252" id2="17" version="1065353216">A small team might be able to infiltrate the temple and reach the device before it can be activated. But they'll be facing some steep odds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1143253" id2="17" version="1065353216">The joint strike is safer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143254" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have led the mission this far. Our victory is within reach--we'll let you decide how best to achieve it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1143255" id2="17" version="1065353216">A small team will work best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1143275" id2="17" version="1065353216">Revan's spirit....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
