<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>920</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/ambient/cc_poi_barks.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060654" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never even heard of Makeb. But... new planet, new people to work over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060655" id2="17" version="1065353216">We knew a woman who vacationed on Makeb. It's a tourist planet; why is the Empire here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060656" id2="17" version="1065353216">This station is running on minimal power to conceal its energy signature. Almost like the Empire doesn't want anyone to know it's here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060657" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suppose we linger on the station a while before descent? Have some breakfast before we're shot at.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Local transmissions are heavily encrypted. This station is hidden.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060726" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you think it would take to topple that thing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060727" id2="17" version="1065353216">Planetary-scale architecture. In another life, we'd spend hours on the grass, looking up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060728" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd suggest moving quickly... and hoping they don't have snipers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060729" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will attempt to interfere with the outgoing transmissions. We may proceed with the devastation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060730" id2="17" version="1065353216">Weapons out. I promise to linger over the view later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060731" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, real nice planet we're on. It's like I'm six years old on Rattatak again....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060732" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful! We'd be... embarrassed to see our careers end under rubble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060733" id2="17" version="1065353216">How bracing. It appears the planet has some fight in it after all!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060734" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm alright. Bit shook up. Let's hope they built the gravity hook to last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060735" id2="17" version="1065353216">I estimate the groundquake epicenter at three hundred kilometers distant. We appear to have escaped the worst.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060736" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, I'm a city girl, but--that's not a bad view. Spit over the side?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060737" id2="17" version="1065353216">The air is thinner here, but it is clean. Taste it. Smell yesterday's rain. Our time is short.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060738" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stroll a bit, take in the view. A bit of light exercise can take your mind off the end of civilization.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060739" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our soldiers are dying across the galaxy. I'd love to show them this view. Just for a moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060740" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not like it here. The electromagnetic inference in the atmosphere is... displeasing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060741" id2="17" version="1065353216">Race you to the bridge. Let's slam this whole freaking ship down a Hutt's throat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060742" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're ready for the next assault. Let's hope the captain doesn't try to shake us off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060743" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I prefer boarding actions on a starship. Less chance of being thrown off the side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060744" id2="17" version="1065353216">Marvelous design, really--what I wouldn't have given for a spy ship like this in the old days. Almost a pity to destroy it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060745" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enemies detected. They know that we have arrived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1060807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Smoke, oil and burning metal... if you don't love that smell, you're not living!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061218" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope no one does the same to our escape vehicle, shall we?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not the most elegant form of sabotage, is it? Still, sometimes expediency wins out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061223" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've always wanted to fly one of those things. That... particular ship won't be an option, I suppose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061224" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ship is now nonfunctional, but I find the patterns created by burning metal soothing. I suggest you avoid breathing the carcinogenic vapors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061227" id2="17" version="1065353216">I used to love spots like this. Smash in some faces, raid the wine cellar and invite a few friends... I miss the simple life, you know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061228" id2="17" version="1065353216">Solida Hesk certainly enjoys her creature comforts. We find the extravagance... not unpleasant, but perhaps inappropriate.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1061577" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb is place of great ceremony, Herald, but do not let gold and glory dazzle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061578" id2="17" version="1065353216">They say Makeb is a playground for the wealthy elite. Heiresses, bored investors... at last, a civilized world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061579" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice enough station. Wonder why the guards look so worried.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061580" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear the people of Makeb could buy and sell the Outer Rim a dozen times over. Guess we'll find out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keylander Station, the &quot;Gateway to Makeb.&quot; I hear the souvenirs are pricey.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1061582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why so grand a place to live? Is not mesas beauty enough?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061583" id2="17" version="1065353216">And right here, Jedi, is proof of why credits and influence aren't always a bad thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Huh. Security's built right into the architecture. Can you see it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061585" id2="17" version="1065353216">It takes guts to build a house that nice, right next to a drop that high.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh my goodness. Shalim's so lucky. Imagine waking up to that view every day.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1061587" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now here is beauty. Smell of soil and living things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061588" id2="17" version="1065353216">A world rich with civilization, and naturally, our travels take us into wilderness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay sharp. Those rock formations? Sniper's paradise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061590" id2="17" version="1065353216">Defending this kind of terrain must be a nightmare. Only place to retreat is down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061591" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can see why tourists used to come here. Now there's just mercenaries. The war touches everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1061592" id2="17" version="1065353216">Herald, they strike from behind!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi, I'm picking up--blast, they're here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ambush! Get down!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enemies on our six!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look out! Behind us!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1061597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph. Would have more beauty as wilderness. But still, is full of prey and dangers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061598" id2="17" version="1065353216">What marvelous statuary. Inspired by the Great Manifest Period. Not that these thugs care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Money. Power. Meant nothing once the Hutts made their move. Better fix it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now this is living. Just need to kick the Regulators around a little, and we're good to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061601" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could never build cities like this at home. The Hutts don't deserve it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1061602" id2="17" version="1065353216">We build and build. But we forget: The ground has jaws that gape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you have any idea how bad a groundquake would have to be to cause this? &quot;Extremely bad&quot; barely covers it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quake ripped the city in half. Glad we weren't here for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061605" id2="17" version="1065353216">Okay, now I get why Doctor Avesta is so worried. How long can Makeb survive quakes like this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061606" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was caused by one groundquake? Just one? We'd better hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1061607" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ground crumbles under buildings, and Hutts build to escape. Is foolishness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, naturally, the ark is gigantic; it was designed to ferry Hutts around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061609" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're hijacking that? Hope you brought a ladder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoa. Imagine dropping your hydrospanner from the top of that thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1061611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, where's the ark? I thought it... oh. Oh, wow.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062073" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regulators have had teeth and claws drawn, Herald. Is good work done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent, now perhaps our friends at the ark can finish their work in peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062075" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see how tough the Regulators are when they can't shove a blaster in someone's face.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062076" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice. Maybe the Regulators can throw rocks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good, that should keep the ark engineers safe. And annoy the Regulators.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062230" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems shame to chain mesas with light bridge. But, has its uses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062231" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, that's a lovely light-bridge design. We're going to horrendously misuse it, aren't we?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could have used those light bridges on Balmorra. Imps wouldn't have been able to resist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062233" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb's got some genius engineers, that's for sure. Let's see what that light bridge can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062234" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oof. How could anyone walk on that light bridge every day? I'm feeling dizzy just looking at it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062235" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regulators lie, dishonor, destroy. No mercy, Herald--we break their spine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062236" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've had just about enough of these Regulators. Holiday, darling, want to help us teach them a lesson?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062237" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive barge. Let's bring it down in flames.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Storm Carrier's perimeter is breached. They'll throw everything at us. Be ready!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062239" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Regulators should be brought to justice for what they've done. Ready when you are, Master!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha. Finally, the Hutts make prey worthy of us!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062329" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is what isotope-5 is capable of. Worth investigating--if we can survive the next five minutes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062330" id2="17" version="1065353216">That droid looked a lot smaller on the holo....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toborro set this thing on civilians? He dies. Painfully.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062332" id2="17" version="1065353216">That stink... and the size of it. What have the Hutts done?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have shielded landing pad, Herald. Should be no ambush from reinforcements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062334" id2="17" version="1065353216">There we go. The landing pad force fields are up and holding.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Landing pad force fields are up. For now. Hope the Hutts don't have a plan B.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Landing pad secured. Any Hutt reinforcements will have to sit and wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062337" id2="17" version="1065353216">That should keep the Hutts and their reinforcements out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062338" id2="17" version="1065353216">All these weapons and they still can't stop us. I'm sure there's a proverb in there somewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062339" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is what happens when you give scientists an unlimited budget and say: &quot;Build whatever makes you feel safest.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here is where they craft their mechanical beasts and foolishness. Is no sanctuary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062341" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, Jedi! Oh, the credits that must have been lavished on research here.... Sorry, I have something in my eye.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lots of tech, lots of toys. Watch your step.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062343" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are too soft for points, Herald, but this prey can still confuse enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062344" id2="17" version="1065353216">That should keep these uncouth fellows occupied for a bit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062345" id2="17" version="1065353216">That should distract the enemy. Real work's still ahead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062346" id2="17" version="1065353216">That should give the bad guys something else to shoot at.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062347" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a shame to release them just to be shot at. But if they can help us save the whole planet....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062348" id2="17" version="1065353216">To cut into heart of a world. Strange to think of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062349" id2="17" version="1065353216">Phew! Somebody's been overclocking those laser mechanics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062350" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we need to make anyone disappear, Jedi--Makeb's core, right there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062351" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yikes, I think the hair on the back of my neck is cooking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062352" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're so far up! Too bad, I really wanted to see what the heart of a planet looks like.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have Toborro at bay, Herald. Only remaining is to burn out his lair.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062355" id2="17" version="1065353216">The planet's being turned inside out, yet the despot's palace survives. Still believe there's justice in the galaxy, Jedi?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062356" id2="17" version="1065353216">No chance of getting in by the front door. Better be discreet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062357" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope Doctor Droidmaker really did build a secret entrance, or this is going to be a long siege.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062358" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toborro's in there holding Makeb by the throat. And for what? He really must be insane.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062359" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trinkets and foolishness. Cannot shield from death that comes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062360" id2="17" version="1065353216">So small things, these fuel rods, to be saving a world's people. Should bring to safety.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062361" id2="17" version="1065353216">Herald, is more enemies coming! From barge overhead!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062362" id2="17" version="1065353216">More old things. True history should live in heart and mind, not in gathering dust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062363" id2="17" version="1065353216">It would appear Toborro's sense of decor went the way of his sanity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062364" id2="17" version="1065353216">And there's our fuel rods. Mind how you go; if we drop them, the ark's not going anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062365" id2="17" version="1065353216">Er, Jedi--that transport appears to be bringing some friends!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062366" id2="17" version="1065353216">The barbarians are moving in, I see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062367" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whole place smells of crazy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062368" id2="17" version="1065353216">Last piece of the puzzle. Now we can get the ark out of here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062369" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heavy carrier coming in! Bringing reinforcements!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062370" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rather be saving lives than artifacts. But, the past's worth keeping.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062371" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember, this guy's nuts. No telling what he could try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062372" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect. Now we just need to make it out alive, and we've got one fully fueled ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062373" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heads up! Whatever that is, it's dropping more reinforcements!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062374" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess when thugs are destroying a planet, raiding a library suddenly doesn't seem as bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062375" id2="17" version="1065353216">He surrounds himself with beauty, but all I can feel here is madness and rage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062376" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. I thought the fuel rods would be bigger. I hope there's enough to fuel the whole ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062377" id2="17" version="1065353216">Overhead! More mercenaries are coming in!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062378" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a good lesson, I suppose. What civilization comes to, if anarchy goes unstopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062474" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = dislikes orbital stations // Reason = too many stairs</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062475" id2="17" version="1065353216">I remember the Empire's orbital stations. They're about as sterile as ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062476" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugh, forgot the extra kolto. They'll have the shops open, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062477" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb is a vacation spot. Never thought the war would bring us here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your orbital stations remind me of the Empire. Calm, orderly.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062480" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shalim's plantation = beautiful // Hutts = don't deserve Makeb</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062481" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remember that vacation you've been promising? Can it start now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062482" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should see what the Hutts have been up to at the pool. Or the casinos....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062483" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmm. Needs more turrets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062484" id2="17" version="1065353216">Beauty and wealth. A prime target for the Hutts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rough terrain ahead // T7 = switching to all-wheel drive</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062487" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice view. Kinda makes you homesick for Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugh, nature. Give me Nar Shaddaa any day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062489" id2="17" version="1065353216">Plenty of cover. Poor visibility, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062490" id2="17" version="1065353216">A petting zoo, compared to the jungles of Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062492" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regulators = incoming // T7 = charging combat implants</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062493" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess they're on to us now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey! We're trying to make a call here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062495" id2="17" version="1065353216">Halt, Regulator scum!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dispatch them quickly, Jedi. The scientist is waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talaos City = infested // Jedi + T7 = drive Regulators out</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice fountain. Except for all the scum standing around it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062500" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's our welcome party. I can smell 'em from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062501" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could flank them... or take them head-on... your call, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062502" id2="17" version="1065353216">There will be civilians among this rabble. We should be cautious.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062504" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Jedi = falls in trench // T7 = will attempt to extract!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062505" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ouch. Hope nobody was home when that happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062506" id2="17" version="1065353216">I really should have brought more kolto.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062507" id2="17" version="1065353216">A grave for the Regulators. Only joking, Master Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062508" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing can match the power of nature--though a true Sith comes close.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ark = must require many astromech units</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062511" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you think powers that thing? Live Jedi?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062512" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know our sad, boring little freighter? I'm thinkin' it's time to upgrade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still not big enough for the Hutts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062514" id2="17" version="1065353216">A class-zero launch engine. It has been centuries since I saw such methods.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Weapons = destroyed // Regulators = halted // Ark = not safe yet</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062517" id2="17" version="1065353216">That ought to slow them down... until they find bigger guns.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Boom! Let's see 'em take that ark now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062519" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regulator weapons destroyed. Objective achieved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062520" id2="17" version="1065353216">A pity we could not have stockpiled these. I suspect our fight will not end here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Light bridge = very high // T7 = pities Hutt droids</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062523" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we got enough lightsabers, I bet we could make one of those.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062524" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's the light bridge. Have I mentioned I'm afraid of heights?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062525" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attractive design, cheap construction. No wonder the Hutts like them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only the Hutts would construct such an easily eliminated passage.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062528" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = recalibrating motion sensors for increased altitude // Recalibration = complete</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062529" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, we're on. Now let's find the reactors and blow the place up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062530" id2="17" version="1065353216">This thing doesn't seem so big once you're on it. Just as high, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maintain awareness. This is no pleasure barge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062532" id2="17" version="1065353216">A defensible transport. Mercenaries do make useful things from time to time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062577" id2="17" version="1065353216">Droid = fueled by isotope-5 // Jedi + T7 = avoid hitting power cells</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062578" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's one of the isotope-5 droids. Kinda cute for a super-fueled death machine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062579" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is an isotope-5 droid. Let's get a look at it... okay, enough looking!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062580" id2="17" version="1065353216">An isotope-5 droid. Approach with caution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062581" id2="17" version="1065353216">I recognize this creature from the hologram. Toborro's droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hutt reinforcements = blocked // Jedi + T7 = victorious!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062584" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see 'em get through that. Would it be wrong to laugh when they try?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suddenly I feel a little claustrophobic. Let's get moving, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062586" id2="17" version="1065353216">A clever utilization of force field technology. Noted for future reference.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062587" id2="17" version="1065353216">The barrier has bought us some time. We should use it wisely.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Native Makeb creatures = should be rescued too // Jedi = ask if ark has room?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062590" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like zoos. Not so much mad science labs. Maybe someday we'll visit one that's under control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure you want to be in here? There are a few too many things for us to be killed by.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062592" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not much of a sanctuary anymore. If it ever was.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062593" id2="17" version="1065353216">The heart of the Hutts' terrible science. It will burn.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Creatures = lucky to be free // Hutt forces = not so lucky</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at 'em run. I almost feel bad. Wait--no, I don't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062597" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice to watch someone else fight the beasties, for a change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062598" id2="17" version="1065353216">An unorthodox solution. Ought to keep the Hutts busy, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062599" id2="17" version="1065353216">Primal instinct at work. A joy to behold.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi + T7 = must move quickly // Makeb = rapidly destabilizing</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062602" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at the size of this thing. No wonder Makeb is falling apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062603" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've worked with laser scalpels before. Never this big.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Diabolical. We can't let the Hutts get away with this, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062605" id2="17" version="1065353216">If such power could be used from orbit... a thought for another time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062607" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = glad palace damaged // Toborro = deserves worse!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062608" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even militarized Hutts can't resist a good palace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a bad-looking place. Little crooked, maybe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Form over function. The hallmark of a Hutt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let this facade fool you. Toborro's strongest forces await us inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062613" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = glad Jedi has taste // Toborro = has none</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062614" id2="17" version="1065353216">All this, while Makeb gets destroyed. Makes you mad enough to... meditate, I guess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062615" id2="17" version="1065353216">See, Toborro's just your average Hutt. Wallowing in luxury, ignoring the peons outside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062616" id2="17" version="1065353216">More decor than defenses. The odds are in our favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062617" id2="17" version="1065353216">A gaudy, useless display. Even the Dark Council does not indulge in such excess.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ark + fuel rods = people of Makeb saved!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatcha got there, Kira? Oh, nothing, just fuel for the ark that will save Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful with those fuel rods. Wouldn't want you to explode or anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062622" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've exceeded mission parameters. Enough fuel here to power ten arks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062623" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should deliver these fuel rods quickly. Makeb does not have long.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062625" id2="17" version="1065353216">T7 = scanning transport // Transport = carrying many Regulators</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you seeing this thing? The transport that's blocking out the sun?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that's a transport. These mercs don't do anything subtle, do they?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062628" id2="17" version="1065353216">A troop transport. We should expect major resistance ahead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some kind of transport. Carrying more Regulators, no doubt.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Archives = many tetrabytes of data // Jedi + T7 = must recover</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Really? The groundquakes weren't enough?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never much of a historian, myself. Not that I condone this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062634" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people of Makeb should've secured their secrets elsewhere. Not in a museum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062635" id2="17" version="1065353216">How quickly history can be destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062837" id2="17" version="1065353216">I visited this station years ago. It has moved far from the planet it serves. Interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Space stations--so ugly. Give me fresh air and sky!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062839" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've heard Makeb hired some top-flight mercenaries to protect the planet. Don't see any here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062840" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're going to Makeb? This is gonna be great! It was voted the number one vacation destination in last year's HoloNet survey!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062841" id2="17" version="1065353216">I laid low on Makeb after a job a few years back. Beautiful planet. The ride down from here is a thrill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Checklist: Servomotors oiled, weapons primed, deletion techniques updated. Bring on the troublemakers!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062844" id2="17" version="1065353216">No wonder the Hutts conquered Makeb. The mesas are too open for effective defense.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062845" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trees! Places to climb! Fresh air! Just what Bowdaar needed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow, look at that view! You suppose those pillars are natural formations?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062847" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, when this mission is over, we really need to spend some time here. Months, maybe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062848" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's about time we visited a nice planet. It's always more fun to shoot people in pleasant scenery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Advice: Sheer drops offer a highly effective method of deleting troublemakers, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pathetic fortifications. Shalim's fighters are amateurs.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062852" id2="17" version="1065353216">These tress are too short for good climbing. Also, I would be shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062853" id2="17" version="1065353216">This landing zone's hot, Captain. Better keep our heads down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at those floaty things! I bet we could ride one like a balloon!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Snipers could have a field day here. Good thing I am one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062856" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anticipation: Sensors detect over three dozen potential troublemakers within a kilometer of our coordinates!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regulators incoming!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enemy reinforcements!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain, watch out!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062861" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ambush! Ambush!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062862" id2="17" version="1065353216">Here they come!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Warning: Ambush!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062867" id2="17" version="1065353216">An urban combat zone--my favorite kind.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not break beautiful cities. It's bad luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062869" id2="17" version="1065353216">You suppose any of these people realize how much trouble they're in?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062870" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would you look at this place? It's a looter's paradise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062871" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice town. Too bad we have to put holes in it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anticipation: The city's population appears to be primarily troublemakers, Master. How wonderful!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062875" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no greater destructive force than nature itself.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not linger. The next quake could close these walls on us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Groundquakes did a number on this place. I'm surprised more folks didn't get hurt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ouch--what a crack. On the bright side, the city's really opened up to new development.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062879" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd hate to be in charge of redrawing the street maps here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regret: I have never had the pleasure of deleting an entire city neighborhood, Master. Someday... someday....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only Hutts would build something this large that only serves one purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is the ark supposed to look like that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062884" id2="17" version="1065353216">That must be the ark, Captain. Bet you could cram Talaos City into it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062885" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is the ark? It must have engines on its engines.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever the Hutts are getting out of Makeb, must be worth spending a fortune on this ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062887" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis: This is either the ark, or an enormous practical joke. Potentially both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062889" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the last of the Regulator stockpiles. They can't retake the ark from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now the Regulators have no teeth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062891" id2="17" version="1065353216">We did it! Without all their fancy hardware, the Regulators are just another bunch of bucketheads.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062892" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the last of it. If the Regulators didn't hate us before, they sure do now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062893" id2="17" version="1065353216">All done. Imagine how rich we'd be if we'd sold that hardware instead of destroying it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confirmation: Mission objectives have been met, Master. The Regulators are now forty percent less combat effective.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062896" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's where the enemy will make its crossing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bridges made of light aren't safe. Why do people here use them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062898" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get nervous every time we cross a light bridge. After this, it'll be even worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062899" id2="17" version="1065353216">I really hope nobody tries this dirty trick with the light bridge on us. I hate poetic justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062900" id2="17" version="1065353216">When we drop that army off the light bridge, nobody will ever want to use those things again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observation: This platform provides an excellent vantage point for witnessing the impending carnage at the light bridge, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062903" id2="17" version="1065353216">An impressive battle platform. It will look beautiful going down in flames.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062904" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Storm Carrier will not save the Regulators--not while you and Bowdaar live!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062905" id2="17" version="1065353216">The bigger they are, the louder they explode. Let's do this, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062906" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do they call it the Storm Carrier? Are there high winds in the cargo hold?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have to hand it to the Regulators--they spared no expense on this thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Announcement: I am disabling collateral damage restraint protocols while aboard the Storm Carrier, Master!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062910" id2="17" version="1065353216">We won't last long against this droid--strike hard and fast!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bowdaar's fur is standing up straight. What powers this droid?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hello, ugly droid! We're here to smash you--don't take it personally!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062913" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at that blasted droid! This is going to hurt, isn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062914" id2="17" version="1065353216">This droid looks like it could fight us all day! Let's not do that!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Request: Please investigate installing an isotope-5 power upgrade in me when this is over, Master!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062917" id2="17" version="1065353216">The platform is secured.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062918" id2="17" version="1065353216">No more Hutt reinforcements will be landing here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062919" id2="17" version="1065353216">That'll keep Toborro's people out for a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062920" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toborro won't be landing anyone here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any Hutt forces that try to land here are in for a nasty surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062922" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alert: This platform is now secured against unauthorized landings by Hutt troublemakers. Most disappointing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062924" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see no sanctuary here--for us, or the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pathways to battle in all directions. I like this Sanctuary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062926" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Sanctuary place looks like all kinds of trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do all the deadliest places have such happy names? &quot;Sanctuary&quot;--right!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062928" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm betting this place was named Sanctuary for the irony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Information: My long-range sensors indicate we will not run out of troublemakers to delete in the Sanctuary. Hooray, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unpredictable diversions are the best kind.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062932" id2="17" version="1065353216">The beasts are free to devour their tormentors. Bowdaar approves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062933" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're free. Let's hope these critters don't come back to bite us on the rear--literally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062934" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go, beasties! Shoo! Go eat the Hutt minions!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062935" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do love a good distraction. Hope those things keep Toborro's forces busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confession: Few things are more pleasing to my sensors than natural predators running amok.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062938" id2="17" version="1065353216">This drill is carving straight through the planet. We need to turn it off.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062939" id2="17" version="1065353216">This drill will destroy Makeb unless we stop it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful, Captain--who knows how much power this thing puts out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062941" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whew! I'd hate to be on the receiving end of this thing's laser. Where's the &quot;off&quot; switch?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quite an operation Toborro has here. Let's shut it down, shall we?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062943" id2="17" version="1065353216">Opinion: What an entertaining method for deleting troublesome rocks and soil. Gives me ideas, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get inside that palace and find Toborro before this mesa collapses.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062946" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toborro is somewhere inside that palace. He will pay for what he's done!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062947" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's Toborro's palace, huh? Good thing I packed extra ammo.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062948" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's where Toborro lives? I bet parties there are incredible!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062949" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't want to be inside that palace when the next quake levels this mesa. C'mon....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis: This mesa has already suffered significant damage, Master. We should find Toborro quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at this room... Toborro must be trying to distract us with bad taste.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062956" id2="17" version="1065353216">I smell a Hutt close by. Be ready, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at this place. You just know Toborro overspent on all this junk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope we have time to loot this place. My ship quarters need sprucing up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Judging by the tasteless decor, we're in Toborro's main room.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trivia: I estimate this room alone cost over thirteen million credits to construct and decorate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062962" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have the isotope-5 fuel rods. The ark will fly.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062963" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should take these isotope-5 fuel rods to Shalim. The ark needs them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062964" id2="17" version="1065353216">With these fuel rods, that ark can finally get off the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062965" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who's going to carry the fuel rods back to the ark? Just wondering if I need to take my anti-radiation pills.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062966" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have the ark's fuel rods. Let's get out of here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Assertion: These are the isotope-5 fuel rods that will power the ark. Mission accomplished, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062969" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a Regulator heavy transport overhead.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062970" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Regulators travel in a flying fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062971" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm betting that transport is crawling with Regulators. I'm starting to hate those guys.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Boy, the Regulators know how to get around in style. Look at that thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062973" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thing for us that Regulator transport isn't outfitted for surface bombardment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Identification: The vessel flying overhead is a heavy troop transport used by the Regulators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rescuing a museum. Now I have done everything.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1062977" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Makeb must die, its legacy will survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get what we came for. Don't want to be trapped in a museum when another quake hits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062979" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every time I enter a museum, it reminds me of Jedi training.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062980" id2="17" version="1065353216">You rescue Makeb's culture. I'll liberate the valuables.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Observation: Organics should outfit themselves with data encoders and store their historical records internally. It's simply more efficient.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analysis: The Empire maintains a minimal presence here, master. I suspect our mission will be a secret one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speculation: Given Makeb's unstable atmosphere, many construction workers likely perished building that gravity hook.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1062999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alert: At the risk of stating the obvious, master, this mesa is tectonically unstable. Be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hypothetical: Combined with a weapon of adequate range, my line of sight from this vantage point would afford unlimited targets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hint: The vessel's defenders are preparing to engage us. Calculating targets for maximum liquidation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Praise: An impressive liquidation, master. I am proud of you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reassurance: I have calculated the precise demolition points to bring down this structure, master. I'll require three tonnes of detonite.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alert: Liquidation protocols set to &quot;armor-piercing&quot;!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Declaration: Invader vehicles have been disabled with maximum efficiency.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Promise: I will endeavor not to liquidate everyone, master. I'll leave some for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reminder: Heat shields would be a welcome addition to my chassis, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rumination: One must admire the ingenuity on display here. Sadly, it will not save the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Information: This droid has a unique power signature. Cataloging it as isotope-5, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Report: Mining operations have been re-engaged, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remark: A most impressive hole in the ground, master. Truly, Makeb is a planet of wonders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Extrapolation: Clearly, Makeb's organics do not fear heights.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Query: A groundquake has divided our path--do we take the high road, or the low?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cheer: Flying undesirable liquidated!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Approval: The Archon's defenses have been weakened by groundquakes, master. Let us proceed with his liquidation!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reassurance: The Archon's home furnishings are intended to intimidate organics, master. I remain undeterred!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blizz think this space-place not very busy. Maybe all Empire-people like planet so much they not want to leave!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, Makeb. I retired here once. Spent a year in the resorts before the crown prince of Alderaan noticed he'd mysteriously spent a hundred million credits on vacation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063764" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow, it's so quiet here. I'm picking up next to nothing on my link, what I do get is so heavily encrypted I think I gained ten kilos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph, seen one of these, seen ten. When we gonna see a place worth trashin'?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Checked, Makeb. Not my kind of vacation spot, but the wildlife's something to see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, I've collated a list of five-star resorts on Makeb should you wish to establish an itinerary. The first three thousand seem especially nice.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063769" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooh... Boss going to climb sky-thing? Blizz want to ride!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063770" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please tell me we aren't riding in that thing; the music's terrible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063771" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh wow, it just keeps going and going. Have you ever seen anything like that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ain't seen nothin' that tall since Coruscant. Bet it'd snap like a twig if we gave it a little shake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't look fortified. Great field of fire, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063775" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ahh! Boss! Help! Blizz feel ground move! Blizz make it angry?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugh. For a &quot;groundquake,&quot; there seems to be an awful lot of sky falling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063777" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoa...! I'm okay. I'm okay. Freaked out, but okay....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah, now that's what I call shakin' the place up! This dump ain't so bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063779" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reminds me of home. Geonosis used to rock me to sleep.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063781" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aww... Blizz think Blizz see-scope get busted in rock fall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063782" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd watch where you admire the view, with the way things have been shaking around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063784" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish someone could take our picture. I'll just paste us in later.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063785" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shoulda drug some of those runty mercs up here and seen who could toss one farther.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Phew, shoulda brought my rifle.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063788" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wee! How come we never ride boss's ship from outside?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Try not to get too cavalier out here. You're the only one with flight rockets, remember?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063790" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're going to let me tap into this thing before we crash it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063791" id2="17" version="1065353216">How you figurin' we get in? Punch a hole, or jump on the roof 'til some chump pops his head out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063792" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good fight and a cool breeze. Can't ask much more.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063794" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why boss go and blow up good parts?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Landing pads are for droids and amateurs. Ever park a shuttle on the roof of a Hutt barge? They hate that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063796" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made sure nobody was in that, right? Kidding!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063797" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ever made a swoop punk watch his ride burn? Never gets old.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Didn't put up much fight, did they?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, pretty! Remind Blizz of Anchorhead with more paint! Less sand, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063801" id2="17" version="1065353216">The owner should have a word with the groundskeepers. The view was a little more... even last time I lived here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063802" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I finally quit the bounty business, I want to live in a place like this. Well, without the ecological devastation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063803" id2="17" version="1065353216">White's my favorite color. Nothin' shows a good smash up like white.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063804" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fancy. Think it's all show?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Um, boss see big noisy box speeder?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063807" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd like to take this moment to remind you that you are not, in fact, a hovertank--no matter how much you dress like one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I'm alone in this, but I have no idea how you fight a hovertank....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that's what I'm talkin' about! Time to take this can for a joy ride!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice hardware. No Basilisk, but nice.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Big box speeders not so tough. Blizz prefer sandcrawler.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063813" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is going right to the top of my &quot;stupid ideas that actually worked&quot; list.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063814" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey! Take my picture on top of one of these!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph, still say we shoulda stole one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Decent memento. Think I'll frame it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Um, boss. Blizz think cantina closed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063819" id2="17" version="1065353216">A cantina. What say we drink to Makeb?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063820" id2="17" version="1065353216">That scanner you picked up seems to think this is the place. Have a look?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wouldn't be caught dead in this froufrou-lookin' dump.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Movement. If it's our mark, he's not alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooo! Boss, rock-river! See!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Funny, a Hutt once told me to visit a place like this when I died.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow, it's hot in here. What I'd give for one of those heat resistors Blizz was playing with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Workin' a sweat yet, runt? Cute little sauna we got here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Proof life can adapt to anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Boss let Blizz see how shiny floor work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063831" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd make some crack about a light bridge being shaky ground, but given the rest of Makeb....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063832" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was reading up on this light bridge tech, it's really fascinating. Sturdier than conventional materials too, unless you have a power outage.... Let's hurry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063833" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come on, I don't trust nothin' flimsy enough to see through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063834" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's our base. Give a knock?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooh! Krayt-droid! Boss! Boss! Can Blizz keep?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063837" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see the Hutt taste in droids matches their taste in food: overdone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063838" id2="17" version="1065353216">It looks like something out of one of my bad holovids. You know, where a droid tramples a city?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063839" id2="17" version="1065353216">That it? Gonna whip this overgrown dumpster with one arm behind my back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never been a fan of droids. No mandokar.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blizz think boss got it working now!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063843" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're really going down there, aren't we? Whatever they're paying us, it ain't enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063844" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now we just hop down to the middle of a highly unstable planet on the brink of tearing itself to pieces. Piece of cake, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063845" id2="17" version="1065353216">You done muckin' with that thing yet? Itchin' to gut a couple more of these critters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally found a nice vacation spot.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Big machine dig this hole? Blizz want to try!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, no one ever accused mining conglomerates of finesse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063850" id2="17" version="1065353216">This plan was scary enough without all the frenzied subterranean monsters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hope you ain't afraid of heights, runt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corridan's never going to believe this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063854" id2="17" version="1065353216">Um, boss... what &quot;atomization hazard&quot; mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063855" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Imperials ever do manage to get their hands on this isotope-5 stuff, we had better see a cut.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063856" id2="17" version="1065353216">These mining platforms are scary stuff; they're basically giant disruptors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063857" id2="17" version="1065353216">How 'bout we set off some real fireworks? Flip the switch on this bad boy, and let's crack this sorry rock in two.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Beats a shovel, that's for sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063860" id2="17" version="1065353216">This give Blizz idea for stretchy road, even be soft on feet!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063861" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's one way to change a traffic pattern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063862" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch your step around here; I don't want to find a sinkhole the hard way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063863" id2="17" version="1065353216">This ain't nothin'. Ever seen a city block drop out of the sky? More fun when you're on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mind rockslides.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kaboom! Good shot, boss!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063867" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could've dodged that easy. What? I could.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice shot! You make it look easy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch that flyer pop.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063870" id2="17" version="1065353216">One down.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, boss. Blizz not have trusty field-frequency tuner....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063873" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't suppose we have time to sneak in as delivery people?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063874" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get the feeling the Archon isn't keen on visitors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063875" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pff. It'll take more than this to keep me from killin' another Hutt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gardens in a fort. Sad.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1063878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blizz kind of scared of machines here, boss. We go soon?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063879" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you ever wondered why I spend so much time planning my exits, it's to avoid winding up in a place like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063880" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't get how anyone could use these on another living thing. Just disgusting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could get some use outta this place, better believe it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1063882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another reason to die fighting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065063" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear the shuttle ride can get a bit bumpy. Wish we were taking the Thunderclap.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Antivirals... check. Tropical antibacterials... check. Antivenoms... check....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065065" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soon, this station's halls will resound with the cheers of a Republic victory!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065066" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate these stations. Never a decent bar.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fear and concern permeate every seal and bolt around us. We must bring harmony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065071" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. The view was worth the ride down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065072" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someday, I hope we can come to places like this without blasters in hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065073" id2="17" version="1065353216">This beautiful planet will not suffer the depredations of the Hutts for long! Havoc Squad is here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't blame the Hutts for moving in. Got half a mind to stay myself.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065075" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is beauty here, but only in the eyes. This is a place of turmoil, not splendor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065078" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect terrain for snipers. Keep an eye out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065079" id2="17" version="1065353216">Poisonous plants and animals are common in wilderness like this. Stay on your guard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065080" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uneven terrain detected--weapon stabilizers at maximum!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065081" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blowing up rocks and trees is never as satisfying as taking down a big, fancy building.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whether in trees and rocks, or cities and structures, a path can always be found.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065085" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hostiles! Look out!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir! Enemy contacts!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enemy scum detected!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065088" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regulators! It's an ambush!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065089" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are under attack!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065092" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gotta watch those corners--enemy could be hiding anywhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065093" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope we can get relief workers in to help these civilians soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065094" id2="17" version="1065353216">Engaging urban combat protocols!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065095" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hmph. Place is a wreck. Might be some valuables scattered around, at least....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065096" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun perceives great hostility hidden within these stones. We should be cautious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065099" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like Lemda was right about these groundquakes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065100" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate to think of the civilian casualties from a quake powerful enough to do this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065101" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no doubt that the Republic's expert engineers can repair even damage this extensive!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pff. I've put bigger holes in stuff than that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065103" id2="17" version="1065353216">This world tears at itself in fury at the unrest marring its surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065106" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was expecting big, but that's... big.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065107" id2="17" version="1065353216">So this is the ark. The Hutts really have been busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065108" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts build large, but do they build as well as the Republic's noble shipwrights? I think not!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065109" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow. How much do you think we could sell that for on the Nar Shaddaa ship markets?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065110" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ark. Its scale is impressive, but many design flaws are immediately evident.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065113" id2="17" version="1065353216">Regulators ought to have a hard time without any heavy weapon support.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065114" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the last of the Regulators' assets. The ark engineers should be safer now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065115" id2="17" version="1065353216">The weapons of our enemies lie crushed beneath the heel of freedom!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065116" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see if the Regulators still want to play now that we've smashed all their toys.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065117" id2="17" version="1065353216">If only the enemy's aggressive intentions were as easily destroyed as their weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065120" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right--let's hope those droids can't fly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065121" id2="17" version="1065353216">These light bridges hardly seem ideal for daily use.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065122" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemies of the Republic march to their own destruction!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065123" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will be the first bridge I've ever taken out without using any explosives.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065124" id2="17" version="1065353216">In one stroke, we turn our enemy's march of aggression into a swift defeat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065127" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got you covered, sir. Let's move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065128" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy could have anything aboard this ship. We should stay alert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065129" id2="17" version="1065353216">We strike now into the very heart of our enemies! For the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065130" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think we could get one of these for our missions?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065131" id2="17" version="1065353216">This warship's design is elegant, if vicious. The embodiment of violence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065134" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of the isotope-5 droids--time to see how tough they really are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065135" id2="17" version="1065353216">An isotope-5 droid... ready to engage on your command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065136" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let the Hutts' shoddy design face the ultimate in Republic combat engineering!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065137" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks a bit bigger in person, boss. This could get hairy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065138" id2="17" version="1065353216">This droid appears no different from its makers--powerful and indiscriminately violent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065141" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, we're secure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065142" id2="17" version="1065353216">This force field should hold the enemy back for the time being.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065143" id2="17" version="1065353216">Landing pad secured--ready to proceed!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065144" id2="17" version="1065353216">That ought to keep Toborro's goons off us for a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065145" id2="17" version="1065353216">The force field's integrity is pristine--we may proceed without further interruption.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065148" id2="17" version="1065353216">What in blazes are they doing in this place?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065149" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate to imagine what sort of &quot;research&quot; has been going on here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065150" id2="17" version="1065353216">No &quot;sanctuary&quot; could hide the enemies of freedom from us!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065151" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wonder if any of the critters here are endangered? Probably be worth something.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065152" id2="17" version="1065353216">Technologies and biologies have been twisted to unnatural purposes here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065155" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's not a good diversion, I don't know what is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065156" id2="17" version="1065353216">That should keep the enemy busy enough for us to proceed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065157" id2="17" version="1065353216">Embrace freedom, noble creatures! Strike back at those who held you in chains!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wish I could see the looks on those idiots' faces when their little pets come after them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065159" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every creature must find its own path to contentment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065162" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're cutting straight into Makeb's core... no wonder this place is breaking apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065163" id2="17" version="1065353216">What were the Hutts thinking? They had to know the damage something like this would do....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065164" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must disable this crude device before Makeb is utterly destroyed!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think we could strap one of these babies to our ship?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065166" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such tremendous power... Yuun has seen nothing like it since the Gauntlet....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065169" id2="17" version="1065353216">This must be it. Let's get in and get what we need before it's too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065170" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutt lives like this while the planet collapses around him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065171" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've found the despot's lair! Eradication protocols engaged!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Place this nice is just begging for a few tactical warheads.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065173" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are no signs or markings to call this place home. It is a lair of evil, nothing more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow. Who pays real credits for this junk?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065177" id2="17" version="1065353216">With all of these baubles, Toborro can't be far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065178" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should melt these extravagances down to forge a statue commemorating our imminent victory!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065179" id2="17" version="1065353216">What? I'm still right here. Not looting anything. Not one thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065180" id2="17" version="1065353216">These objects point the way to their cruel master. Toborro is near.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065183" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got what we came for--let's move!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065184" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should get these fuel rods back to the ark immediately, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victory is ours! Let us return to the ark for its triumphant first flight!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065186" id2="17" version="1065353216">You grab the fuel rods, I'll just make one final sweep for... enemies....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065187" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our time is short. These fuel rods must be returned to the ark at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065190" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enemy reinforcements incoming!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065191" id2="17" version="1065353216">That transport! More enemy forces!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065192" id2="17" version="1065353216">More enemy forces overhead! Activating additional targeting routines!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065193" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like these guys have friends with air support, boss.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065194" id2="17" version="1065353216">The vessel above brings renewed hostilities!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065197" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess collateral damage isn't a problem for the Hutts' people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065198" id2="17" version="1065353216">How would anyone target an archive? It's despicable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065199" id2="17" version="1065353216">Analyzing blast marks to estimate enemy armament, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065200" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is just downright sloppy work.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065201" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun cannot comprehend our enemies' motives. To collect assets, yes. To destroy history, no.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065208" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hijacked a few ships over Makeb in my time--mining barges, luxury cruises. Even had a couple run-ins with local security. Hope no one here recognizes me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065209" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never thought our travels would take us to a planet like Makeb. Not that I'm complaining.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb--a planet of corporate excess and overpriced tourism. What's the Empire's interest here?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065211" id2="17" version="1065353216">The soldiers here are tense. I would know the reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065212" id2="17" version="1065353216">I always wanted to visit Makeb--purely for pleasure, mind you. The planet's civilization is far too young to have any archaeological merit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065213" id2="17" version="1065353216">These space stations are dead places. Nothing but metal and darkness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065325" id2="17" version="1065353216">That must be the gravity hook. Not exactly subtle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065326" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I thought the mesas were tall. Amazing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065327" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive. Note how the architecture complements the planet's natural landscape. Makeb's builders are nothing if not precise.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065328" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is nothing. I tore down buildings twice as high on Yn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at the size of that!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065330" id2="17" version="1065353216">There could be many eyes up there, watching us. We should move quickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065334" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think this is bad? Try piloting a busted gully jumper through a hurricane on Poderis. Rattle the teeth right outta your head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065335" id2="17" version="1065353216">That can't be good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065336" id2="17" version="1065353216">For all its beauty, Makeb isn't exactly hospitable.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065337" id2="17" version="1065353216">This planet thrashes like a wounded animal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065338" id2="17" version="1065353216">Steady, there!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065339" id2="17" version="1065353216">The world trembles at your passing, lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow, a view like this, really makes a guy contemplate his place in the galaxy and--yeah, okay, I'm messing with ya. Let's go kill something, huh.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065341" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's so beautiful up here. Peaceful. You can almost forget everything happening below.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065342" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think I'm beginning to understand the planet's appeal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065343" id2="17" version="1065353216">A long fall to the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065344" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh my. We are... quite high, aren't we?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mind the edge, lord. Ambition may yet surpass reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065348" id2="17" version="1065353216">This ship's not gonna crash itself. Let's get to work, yeah?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065349" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful. One wrong step and it's all over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065350" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever happens, let's try to be elsewhere when this ship goes down.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065351" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let us send this ship screaming to the ground below.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065352" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugh. The sooner we're back on solid ground, the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065353" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our enemies know we are here. Let us end this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065354" id2="17" version="1065353216">Waste of a good ship, you ask me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065355" id2="17" version="1065353216">That takes care of the landing pad. Let's go find Solida Hesk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065356" id2="17" version="1065353216">No place for Solida Hesk to run to now. We may take her at our leisure.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065357" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now there is no escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065358" id2="17" version="1065353216">I confess I'm starting to see the appeal in vandalism.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065359" id2="17" version="1065353216">No way off, no hope of rescue. The trap is set.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065364" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice digs. Always saw myself retiring in a place like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065365" id2="17" version="1065353216">Solida Hesk seems to be doing well for herself. No doubt she earned every credit legally.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065366" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people of Makeb build their homes pretty enough, but their estates lack the grandeur and majesty one finds on Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065367" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have seen palaces smaller than this. Does this Solida Hesk think herself a queen?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065368" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do hope Solida Hesk is home. Would be a shame to come all this way for nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065369" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is no stronghold. A child could break these walls.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065370" id2="17" version="1065353216">This would be so much easier strapped behind a good starfighter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065371" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got to take out those hovertanks!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065372" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're not planning to fight those things head-on?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065373" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts bring toys to war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065374" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I thought those hoversleds the Hutts always used were big.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065375" id2="17" version="1065353216">On Kalee, I hunted beasts as tall as ten men. These tanks do not frighten me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065376" id2="17" version="1065353216">The hovertanks are scrap. Riot!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065377" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've given the rebels a fighting chance. The rest is up to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065378" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the last of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065379" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have crushed the Hutts' toys.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065380" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done, my lord!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065381" id2="17" version="1065353216">A glorious battle, lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065383" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like it's a cantina, closed for business. Hope they kept some of the good stuff inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065384" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like this is the place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065385" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our quarry must be in there.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065386" id2="17" version="1065353216">A crumbling hole to hide in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065387" id2="17" version="1065353216">Readings indicate our man is inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065388" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our hunt ends here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065389" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I thought Tatooine was hot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065390" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Ryen once taught me an exercise to ward off the heat. I still can't do it without thinking of him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065391" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suggest we not linger. Collapsing worlds and lava do not mix well.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065392" id2="17" version="1065353216">The planet bleeds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065393" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cripes, but it's hot! I'll wager no Hutt's dared venture down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065394" id2="17" version="1065353216">The heat is good. Ignites an inferno in the spirit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065395" id2="17" version="1065353216">The light show is nice and all, but honestly, some basic durasteel would be a lot simpler.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065396" id2="17" version="1065353216">Beautiful technology. I wonder why we don't see many bridges like this off Makeb?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fortunate that the bridge is still up. Let's not push our luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065398" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy's stronghold lies at the other side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065399" id2="17" version="1065353216">These light bridges--they've never been known to short out... have they?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065400" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am ready for whatever lies across.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065401" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me that thing has a weak spot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065402" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful, we don't know what this droid is capable of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065403" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts know how to build a death machine, I'll give them that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065404" id2="17" version="1065353216">A machine is no match for the conqueror of Yn and Chabosh!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065405" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, there go any doubts I had about isotope-5's potency....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065406" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now we see which is stronger--Hutt science or Sith instinct.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065407" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now comes the fun part.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065408" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think that did it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065409" id2="17" version="1065353216">The power appears to be back online.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Into the abyss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065411" id2="17" version="1065353216">And down we go! This is just like that excavation on Krayiss--without the insane Force apparitions, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065412" id2="17" version="1065353216">The way is open.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065414" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I know the Hutts, there's more than a few bodies lying at the bottom of that hole.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065415" id2="17" version="1065353216">The miners were toying with forces beyond their control, digging like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065416" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't think the Hutts could one-up their work on Varl. Clearly, I was wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065417" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mouth of oblivion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065418" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've operated my fair share of drills, at excavation sites and so forth. But this--this dwarfs anything I've seen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065419" id2="17" version="1065353216">The miners pierced the planet's heart. They were surprised the blow was fatal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heh, wish Talos was here. Guy's terrified of heights. Probably dangle him from the edge, watch him squirm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065421" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given everything that's happened, the Hutts can't still be drilling, can they?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065422" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd like to see some of this isotope-5 for myself. Finally see what all the fuss is about.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065423" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts know nothing of conquest. Only annihilation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065424" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just a fraction of the operating costs here would have financed my excavations for a decade!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065425" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts have killed a planet. Impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ouch. Glad I wasn't here when this happened.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065427" id2="17" version="1065353216">This devastation... it's just awful. I hope everyone made it out safely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065428" id2="17" version="1065353216">This planet is crumbling before our very eyes. It can't be long now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065429" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another wound in a dying planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065430" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts have a long history of ruining planets, but they've never been as... thorough as they've been here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065431" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such destruction. Such power. If only you could harness it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065432" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a natural. Now, try it with your eyes closed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Got him!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065434" id2="17" version="1065353216">How gratifying.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Burn, little fighter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065436" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hah, very good, my lord!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065437" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps the next one will provide better sport.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065438" id2="17" version="1065353216">Place looks like a fortress. Won't be easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's end this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065440" id2="17" version="1065353216">It appears the Hutt isn't taking visitors. No matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065441" id2="17" version="1065353216">Walls of light will not hold me back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065442" id2="17" version="1065353216">The place looks well guarded. But if history has proven one thing, it's that no stronghold is impenetrable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065443" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Archon must be hiding in there. Pity the Hutts can't run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065444" id2="17" version="1065353216">This room brings back some bad memories. Take it from me, the Hutts have some pretty twisted pastimes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065445" id2="17" version="1065353216">Terrible things have happened in this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065446" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh look, we found the Archon's recreation room. Charming.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065447" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place reeks of death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065448" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutts are masters at dispensing pain and torment. I shudder to think what went on here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065449" id2="17" version="1065353216">Either you kill your enemy, or he kills you. There is no honor in prolonging death.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065925" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't know Makeb, but we follow Sith clan to the ends of the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065926" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb, vacation hot spot for Alderaan's petty nobles. Maybe I'll get lucky and run into an old acquaintance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065927" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, everyone on this station is flooded with apprehension. It's as if they're holding their breath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Quiet chatter, light station traffic, encrypted comms. Sure sign of a covert op.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065929" id2="17" version="1065353216">I pulled Makeb's tourism profile, my lord. The resort prices are staggering, far above a captain's salary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ugh, Imperial stations are so stuffy. Can't wait to hit Makeb's resorts and take in some sights.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065931" id2="17" version="1065353216">We feel the Hutt clan's eyes. Sith must keep moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065932" id2="17" version="1065353216">The planet roars with the Sith clan.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065933" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our claws belong on the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065934" id2="17" version="1065353216">The hull is weak. Sith clan must carve its way inside!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065935" id2="17" version="1065353216">The flames of battle cleanse us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065936" id2="17" version="1065353216">We paint the Hesk palace with a new shade of crimson.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065937" id2="17" version="1065353216">The shell is strong, but the meat inside is soft.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065938" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hovertanks shatter under the Sith clan's fist!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065939" id2="17" version="1065353216">The scent leads inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065940" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are not meant for such heat.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065941" id2="17" version="1065353216">We charge to the stronghold!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065942" id2="17" version="1065353216">We rend the Hutt droid to scraps!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our hunt leads deeper into Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065950" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy cracks open the planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065951" id2="17" version="1065353216">We smell burning ozone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065952" id2="17" version="1065353216">The planet tears itself apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065953" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith clan revels in a fiery kill!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065954" id2="17" version="1065353216">Force fields don't block our hunt!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1065955" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hutt questions when he should kill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065956" id2="17" version="1065353216">So that's the gravity hook. I've seen bigger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065957" id2="17" version="1065353216">How exciting! Even the planet seeks to destroy us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that's a long fall. Shame we didn't keep any mercenaries around to march over the precipice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally, no more hiding. Let's fill this ship with the screams of our enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pity someone wasn't inside. But a girl can dream, can't she?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065961" id2="17" version="1065353216">No red carpet? Someone needs to teach Solida Hesk some manners.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pathetic machines. I'll litter the battlefield with their wreckage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065963" id2="17" version="1065353216">No more hovertanks? Pity. My lightsaber was just warming up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065964" id2="17" version="1065353216">End of the line. This spy better be grateful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065965" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fires burn fiercely, master. But they run cold compared to my rage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065966" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few meters below us lies an agonizing, fiery death. How invigorating!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is this monstrous scrap heap supposed to frighten me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065968" id2="17" version="1065353216">That woke the mining equipment. Now, let us burrow deeper into this dying planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065969" id2="17" version="1065353216">How lovely. The Archon spared us the hassle of digging his grave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065970" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're placing considerable hope in this drill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065971" id2="17" version="1065353216">The very ground cracks open before us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065972" id2="17" version="1065353216">My favorite kind of fireworks!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065973" id2="17" version="1065353216">How cute. The cowardly slug actually thinks his shield will stop us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065974" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see the Archon has a taste for inflicting torment. Perhaps we can trade some pointers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Incredible. If the view's this impressive from the ground, imagine gazing out from the top.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065976" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm fine, master. Makeb's more volatile than I thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065977" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few moments with this view, and I could almost forget about the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065978" id2="17" version="1065353216">They know we're here, master. No turning back now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065979" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mesa's cut off. I hope nobody's foolish enough to try and land here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065980" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reminds me of the noble houses on Alderaan. Extravagance this grand often hides the corruption within.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, those hovertanks will destroy the civilians! Time to level the playing field.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065982" id2="17" version="1065353216">At last, the civilians are free to revolt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065983" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful, master. There may be civilians within.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065984" id2="17" version="1065353216">The molten blood of Makeb runs thick. We must be getting close.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065985" id2="17" version="1065353216">The stronghold lies before us. The isotope-5 is almost ours!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065986" id2="17" version="1065353216">No machine, not even one powered by isotope-5, can stand against the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb's core beckons us, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065988" id2="17" version="1065353216">The miners cut Makeb to the bone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful, master. One strong gust and we could be swept into oblivion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065990" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makeb's convulsions grow more violent. Hopefully, these wounds will heal in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065992" id2="17" version="1065353216">A quick end to a deadly enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Self-defense appears to be an obsession among the Hutts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Residual pain floods this room, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065996" id2="17" version="1065353216">There she is. Must be a few dozen kilometers tall. Too bad we're not here to demolish it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065997" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aftershocks. Natural tremors. Best to keep moving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prime sniper spot. Sun to your back and kilometers of unsuspecting targets. View's not bad either.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1065999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ship this size will light up the sky when we take it down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not bad for improvised explosives. Next time, unleash military-grade ordnance, crater the whole landing pad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Target's likely holed up inside. Estate this size is going to have some heavy defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066002" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once trained in a hovertank. Too slow for my taste, but they pulverize enemy lines like nothing else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seen hovertanks bombarded, never ripped apart up close. Didn't know what I was missing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066004" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lurker's in the cantina. Once we deal with him, drinks are on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't see this on Makeb's tourist vids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heard stories about light bridges shutting down. One second they're on, the next... forget I said anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066007" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's see how powerful isotope-5 really is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066008" id2="17" version="1065353216">Power online. Turbolift active. To the core!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066009" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fifty megatonnes of high-yield explosives couldn't carve a shaft that deep.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066010" id2="17" version="1065353216">Drill laser this size cuts through kilometers of rock. Shame we can't fire it at the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aftermath of a major groundquake. Watch out for aftershocks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bull's-eye! You're a natural, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066013" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Archon's entrenched. Nothing we can't handle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066014" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rooms like this are a soldier's nightmare. Better to die on the battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive. Perfectly suited to our base of operations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful, my lord. Perhaps we should move to safer ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066017" id2="17" version="1065353216">From this vantage point, we can monitor Makeb for kilometers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our intrusion's been detected, my lord. Blocking comm traffic until we neutralize the spy vessel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Crude but effective, my lord. It will take weeks to clear the wreckage and complete repairs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066020" id2="17" version="1065353216">Solida Hesk enjoys a life of excess. If she wishes to retain these pleasures, she had best cooperate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066021" id2="17" version="1065353216">Class-seven hovertanks, my lord. Few vulnerabilities outside of a close-quarters assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066022" id2="17" version="1065353216">A sound victory, my lord. With the hovertanks routed, rebellion is imminent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be wary, my lord. We mustn't rule out an ambush.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066024" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, temperatures are spiking. To avoid combustion, I'd advise against straying close to the molten streams.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066025" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fascinating technology, light bridges. Most other structures would melt from the extreme heat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066026" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive construction, but all prototypes have a weakness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Power is restored, my lord. The turbolift awaits.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066028" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mine shaft. They must have worked for years to breach the planetary core.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066029" id2="17" version="1065353216">The power capacity of such a drill must be staggering.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066030" id2="17" version="1065353216">A groundquake swallowed the road whole. We'd best watch our step.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impeccable shot, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066032" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Archon's defenses are many, but they will fall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hutts know only terrible methods of extracting information.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066034" id2="17" version="1065353216">So that's a gravity lift. Not bad. Don't tell me we have to climb that thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066035" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoa, there. That was a close one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wow. Looks just like the tourist vids. From the mesa peaks to the... oh, dizzy. Don't look down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. They spotted us. Let's sink this ship and scram--you know, before all the explosions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066038" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sheesh! Hope the sabotage was worth it. Think I singed a lekku.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Snazzy. Bet Solida Hesk's got some priceless trinkets locked inside. Think she'll mind if I grab a few mementos?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hovertanks? Seriously? These mercs aren't messing around.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those hovertanks weren't so tough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ritzy cantina. Smart hideout, but I bet the drinks cost a fortune.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066043" id2="17" version="1065353216">Phew, nice sauna. Wonder how much weight a Hutt would lose locked down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay calm, Vette. One foot in front of the other. It's not like there's a giant lake of fire right below you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066045" id2="17" version="1065353216">Call it a hunch, but that droid doesn't look friendly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hope that didn't wake any more of those beasties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at that. Almost as bottomless as a Hutt stomach.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aw, the mine looks so tiny from up here!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066049" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something tells me this mesa is on its last legs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066050" id2="17" version="1065353216">Boom! Take that, evil mercenary guy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066051" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ooh, a force field. Somebody's scared of us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066052" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. A Hutt interrogation chamber. Now I'm going to have nightmares.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066154" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a good thing we aren't required to climb that thing. We won't have to climb it, will we? Master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066155" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, it may please you to note I was unaffected by the groundquake. I hope it pleases you. How may I please you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066157" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people down there seem so very small. This must be how you feel all the time, master!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, do you plan to replace your starship with this vessel? I assure you my duties will be unaffected.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066159" id2="17" version="1065353216">Odds of salvage: extremely low. Your capacity for destruction is unrivaled!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066160" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps one day I'll have the pleasure of waiting upon you in such a place. If only I were capable of dreaming, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066161" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that a good example of &quot;bristling with armaments,&quot; master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066162" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, your capacity for destruction chills me into providing even better service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps I should restock the ship's galley from this cantina, master. I shall remain vigilant for your potable preferences!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, perhaps I should take the lead? If I begin to melt, you shall know to turn back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066166" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never realized &quot;heart of the volcano&quot; was more than an expression, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master! Please note that this droid and I don't share the same manufacturer!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066169" id2="17" version="1065353216">The generator is operating with eighty-seven-point-nine-nine-one percent efficiency, master!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066170" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take caution, master! I'm detecting yet another opportunity for a fatal fall!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066171" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, I'm programmed to recognize that this is an amazing view.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take care, master. The ground is somewhat perforated.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take that! I mean, excellent shot, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those shields are only slightly less intimidating than you, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, no. If I have done something to displease you, punishment is unnecessary.... My apologies, master. I misunderstood the situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066177" id2="17" version="1065353216">I always appreciate the opportunity to restock the ship's stores. We are headed past the market, aren't we, Master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066178" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps we should not stray so close to the edge, Master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066179" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me, Master. The pollen here is affecting my vocabulator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066180" id2="17" version="1065353216">How very rude!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066182" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose locals consider this to be art, master. Discerning tastes such as ours know otherwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066195" id2="17" version="1065353216">The latest city maps don't include this massive trench, Master. I shall notify the cartographers at the next available opportunity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066199" id2="17" version="1065353216">One day, I shall serve on such a magnificent vessel. Not to imply any current dissatisfaction, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066201" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, the ark is safe from an assault from here. I admit to unexpected levels of satisfaction in preventing its destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066203" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have absolutely no qualms about destroying a droid army, Master. I'll deactivate the light bridge myself, if you wish!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066204" id2="17" version="1065353216">The complete lack of safety railings speaks to the Regulators' character, wouldn't you agree, Master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066207" id2="17" version="1065353216">That droid is broadcasting &quot;destroy all enemies&quot; on a loop, Master. I suspect he means you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066208" id2="17" version="1065353216">It feels good to be surrounded by walls again, Master, no matter how temporary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066214" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wonderful news, Master! None of the local wildlife can fully digest me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066216" id2="17" version="1065353216">The beasts should pay you no attention, Master. I've treated your armor with a dissuading agent that is reportedly quite pungent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066217" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, I'm not sure whether to marvel at the efficiency or shudder at all this waste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066218" id2="17" version="1065353216">How does Toborro live out of so many towers, Master? Hundreds of turbolift repair technicians, perhaps?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066220" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's true what the say about Hutts, Master. Extravagance is the bare minimum.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066225" id2="17" version="1065353216">By the Maker! With these rods, the ark shall fly! What a sight it shall be, Master!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066230" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, above us! That vessel is impressively monstrous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066231" id2="17" version="1065353216">This building comprises the entire cultural history of Makeb. Funny. You'd think it would be bigger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Elegant design, but this structure is highly defensible. Those walls are reinforced, and I spot three hidden weapon systems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066819" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ready to move in, on your mark. I'm almost nervous to break anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066820" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are shielded energy sources inside the walls. I expect they power droids and heavy defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Crude shells of technology, to be cracked and devoured like eggs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066822" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mercenary forces had every advantage. They miscalculated. Unfortunate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Detecting multiple life-forms inside. Minimal armaments. We may proceed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Adjusting internal cooling systems. Perhaps you should do the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066825" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Stronghold vaults are shielded. I cannot detect the isotope-5 from here... but I am curious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Its artificial intelligence is primitive. I have designed more advanced microorganisms. But its energy is beautiful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Power engaged. We should be able to proceed to the core.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066828" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have taken measures to preserve my core program. If we are buried here, I will survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066829" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Hutts came, a family took refuge here. I can hear a child's recorded distress signal. They were all taken by the mercenaries.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066830" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have never personally witnessed extensive groundquake damage before. I enjoy deriving the equations; they are crude, but intricate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066831" id2="17" version="1065353216">The pilot is dead. Downloading flight log. You may proceed to destroy another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066832" id2="17" version="1065353216">The atmospheric charges have isolated me from galactic communications. Kill the Archon quickly, or I will take additional measures.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066833" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are unusual chemical compounds in the air. The Archon formulates his interrogation serums precisely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those hovertanks are up to military specifications. Makeb really did fund its mercenaries well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Target destroyed. Would it be wrong to take a souvenir? Not everyone gets to destroy a hovertank on foot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lurker should be inside. Looks like a cantina--must have been abandoned after the Hutts took over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066837" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't often get nostalgic for Hoth, but there are moments. Shall we proceed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stronghold One ahead. Weapons charged. We'll find the isotope-5, sir--one way or another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tactical assessment--well, no one's ever fought a thing like this before, so your guess is as good as mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066840" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got power. Let's hope the lifts are working right--it's a long way to fall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066841" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at it... is every planet like this on the inside?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a very defensible position for a base. Let's hope the Hutts don't find it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066843" id2="17" version="1065353216">These people on Makeb... look at what they've been through. No one deserves this, or the Hutts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066844" id2="17" version="1065353216">Target destroyed. I trained on surface-to-air missiles with the Chiss... never perfected it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066845" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got a lot of ground to cover and enemies everywhere. Let's find our people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066846" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Archon interrogated our people... that was our team. They were our responsibility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066847" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hovertanks: brutally slow and unmaneuverable, best used to intimidate. Just remember to duck when they start shooting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not the most delicate mission we've ever accomplished--but I think congratulations are in order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066849" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this is the Lurker's safe house, he must have been desperate indeed. Keep one hand on your weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066850" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew a good man who died in the magma caverns of Saleucami. Dehydration. Sweating to death is not a pleasant end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stronghold One lives up to its name. And I was worried we'd been in for a disappointment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066852" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not a cyberneticist, but even I know that droid's not running on standard power cells. Isotope-5 is no myth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066853" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're lucky this equipment even works. You can almost smell the rust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066854" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's something exhilarating about pushing the boundaries of science. A whole planet, ready to destroy itself... we'll go down in history, one way or another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a bad place for a picnic lunch--at least until the groundquakes send this whole structure tumbling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066856" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've seen planets bombarded by meteors that suffered less damage than this. It makes you wonder if we could destabilize cores on purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066857" id2="17" version="1065353216">Marvelous shooting--although the Regulators might disagree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066858" id2="17" version="1065353216">I heard rumors about a Hutt spymaster a long time ago. I never thought I'd be standing at his front door--but there are questions I'd like answered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at the lighting, look at the tools--the Archon isn't brutal. He extracts information with an interrogator's precision.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice ride. Get one for me, and I promise to show you a real good time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066861" id2="17" version="1065353216">A swarm of insects can kill the largest bantha--but most banthas don't carry heavy weapons. We should be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066862" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now who's scary? Who's got the biggest gun now? Yeah, you heard me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066863" id2="17" version="1065353216">That should be enough. Let's hope the people of the settlements are grateful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066864" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our quarry should be inside. Let's hope we're the first to find him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066865" id2="17" version="1065353216">First cantina we find, and it's a mess. Freaking tragedy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now we know why security is minimal from this direction. Watch your step, for both our sakes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066867" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate it hot. Let's finish up in here and get out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's bust down the door and rob the place. You get the isotope, I'll get the cash.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066869" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is why we came to Makeb. If our intelligence is correct, the isotope-5 is somewhere inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066870" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mean looking. Give me a locked room and a steel pipe, and I'll bet you twenty credits I can take it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066871" id2="17" version="1065353216">That must be the Hutts' prototype. We're ready when you are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better than jumping, I guess. Looks like we've got power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066873" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those creatures... how many will be lost if Makeb is destroyed? Strange to think.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066874" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could put anything down there and no one would ever find it. No one would ever find us, either.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066875" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the beating heart of a dying world. Listen to it. We must do right by Makeb.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066876" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you think? If the Hutts rush us, we can always jump for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066877" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people of Makeb could have destroyed the beauty of their world. Instead, they built things like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bad enough quake will rip apart anything. It's no fun when you can't do much about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066879" id2="17" version="1065353216">Careful. If there's another groundquake, we'll be swallowed whole.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha! Look at that thing go down--didn't know what hit him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enemy fighter down. A pity it's come to this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chaos, but there are dangers here. The Archon is prepared for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066883" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know, I'm looking forward to this. It's been way too long since I shot a Hutt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066884" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice setup. I don't think your team made it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1066885" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are instruments of pain and interrogation. What has the Archon done?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
