<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>87</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/jedi_consular/bunker_generator.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048087" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... I don't believe it. We're registering a drop in the generator's power levels. You actually beat that monstrosity.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1048089" id2="17" version="1065353216">Herald, is thought I have. These beasts, all connected to your Force by this dark thing, this Torwin Vehl.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1048091" id2="17" version="1065353216">But is no pattern to them. These prey are made, unleashed, but are no true army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048092" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this was another creation of that Sith fellow Zah'lis mentioned, he's been busy. Not doing anything useful, mind you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048094" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't throw the term &quot;mad science&quot; around lightly, but why would Torwin Vehl bother making an army of Force-sensitive animals?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048095" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another animal made Force sensitive. More of this Sith Torwin Vehl's work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048097" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems pointless. Why not make Force-sensitive people?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048099" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dray Zah'lis was another of these &quot;rough sketches.&quot; Perhaps there have been others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1048099" id2="17" version="1065353216">He did, remember?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048100" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another Force sensitive nightmare. Probably made by that Sith you saw in your vision, Torwin Vehl.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048102" id2="17" version="1065353216">This doesn't make sense. These creatures aren't organized. Who builds an army like this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048103" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was like the other creatures Torwin Vehl made; like the Force was twisted up inside it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048105" id2="17" version="1065353216">These poor animals. This isn't an army. It's just sadistic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048106" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master, you must be careful. If this Torwin Vehl makes an army of these horrid things, what else could he do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interjection: Master, may I observe that the creation of these Force sensitive organics is tactically brain-dead?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048109" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this Sith, Torwin Vehl, seeks to create an army in this fashion, he lacks any understanding of the term.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048110" id2="17" version="1065353216">These creatures aren't meant to be an army. They're... tests. He's experimenting with his gift.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1048110" id2="17" version="1065353216">These beasts are experiments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048112" id2="17" version="1065353216">My vision showed Torwin Vehl at the center of a galactic firestorm. These beasts don't match what I saw. There's some connection I'm missing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1048112" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't foresee these beasts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3137" id1="1048113" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cannot say, Herald. Seeing was not for my eyes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Frankly, Jedi, if it's a choice between these freakish things and utter annihilation, that's barely a moment's thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048115" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe we changed things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048116" id2="17" version="1065353216">What else can we do but try and stop him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048117" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'll find it. He can't stay hidden forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048118" id2="17" version="1065353216">I... don't really know what to say, master. Would some tarine tea help you think?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048119" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dismissive: I wouldn't presume to know the status of your mind, master, short of conducting exploratory surgery.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048120" id2="17" version="1065353216">All that matters is stopping Torwin Vehl before Bothawui is overrun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1048120" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's just put a stop to this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hate to interrupt, Master Jedi. But there's something you should know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048122" id2="17" version="1065353216">How could anyone... nevermind. I've got news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052183" id2="17" version="1065353216">We found this canister buried near the bunker entrance. Full of some kind of paste. It stinks. When those beasts went crazy, their breath smelled the same way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052184" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps this paste makes these animals more aggressive when they eat it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052184" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe it drove them berserk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you tell what's in this paste? That might provide a clue.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052185" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's it made of?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052186" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it drives those creatures insane, Lieutenant, it's probably not safe to breathe too close to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052186" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful with it, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052188" id2="17" version="1065353216">Makes sense, but why is it here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052191" id2="17" version="1065353216">Um. Good point. Bassel, secure this thing, would you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052193" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd been wondering how the Imperials got those beasts to attack this bunker.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052195" id2="17" version="1065353216">My sergeant said he saw the canister being buried yesterday. He thought it was a refugee hiding their stuff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052196" id2="17" version="1065353216">This person your sergeant saw, did he give you a description?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052196" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we identify the refugee?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052197" id2="17" version="1065353216">That canister was probably intended to draw the beasts here, then enrage them into attacking everything in sight. Clever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052197" id2="17" version="1065353216">The paste was a lure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052198" id2="17" version="1065353216">As the Empire gets more desperate, it gets more creative. We need to stay alert.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052198" id2="17" version="1065353216">A cunning new tactic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052199" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hang on. Getting a transmission. Imperials incoming--a whole company. No way we can hold the bunker with the forces we have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052202" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not touching it. But it smells medicinal. Definitely not natural.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052206" id2="17" version="1065353216">Human, he said. And young, not much more than a teenager.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052210" id2="17" version="1065353216">Although... we could use the generator. Make sure that if the Imperials take the bunker, they never leave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052211" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought the point of saving the bunker was to ensure the generator isn't misused.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052211" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isn't the generator deadly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052214" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just what are you proposing here, Lieutenant?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052214" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's ominous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052215" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there's a way to turn this disaster to our advantage, I'm interested.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052215" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like the sound of this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052216" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we close the generator intakes and restart it on minimum power, the generator will emit its toxins as an odorless gas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052218" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let the Imps take the bunker. A few hours of breathing that gas, and they'll be finished. We destroy Imperial reinforcements... and get a little payback.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052231" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given what the Imperials intended to do to Bothawui, it seems only fitting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052231" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree. We'll poison them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good. Just hit the intake override panel there, and then restart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052234" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the right thing to do: for us, for the resistance, for everyone on Bothawui. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052236" id2="17" version="1065353216">For now, Commander Niccos is asking you to meet him at the command post. He said he has news on some Sith you're looking for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052237" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could use a minimal dose of the gas, leaving the Imperials weak, but alive. Then your men could capture them easily.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052237" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd rather take them prisoner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gassing people to death is not acceptable, Lieutenant, whatever insignia they're wearing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052238" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't commit murder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052239" id2="17" version="1065353216">Capture them? They'd still try to fight back--I could lose more men!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052241" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any losses on our side would be minimal. In return, we save lives and gain valuable prisoners and intelligence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052241" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better than killing hundreds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052242" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're crazy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052244" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see. Perhaps yours is the better solution, after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052244" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then let's gas them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052245" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Kaley, I'm giving you a direct order. Capture those Imperials alive and bring them back to base. Is that understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1052245" id2="17" version="1065353216">I order you to capture them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052246" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kaley, unless you want a court-martial, remind yourself what a direct order means.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think carefully, Lieutenant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine! Order acknowledged. So long as you acknowledge you're throwing away Republic lives to save Imperial ones.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052286" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll... put a plan together. Meantime, Commander Niccos is asking to see you. Something about a Sith you were looking for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052287" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're the enemy! They've burned this planet to the ground!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052289" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's not wrong, Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052290" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if we want to make it right, Kaley, we must be better than them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps, but he's still your superior.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052294" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps, but she's still your superior.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052296" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought you were on our side. But I guess I don't have the authority to disagree... sir.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
