<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>37</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/jedi_consular/lieutenant_kaley.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022192" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch your back. Things are getting weird around here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022193" id2="17" version="1065353216">So we lose a prime opportunity to kill Imperials, and my men suffer for it. I hope you're happy. Sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022194" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice work at the Nar'less Bunker. The only good Imperial is one that's breathing toxic gas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022195" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once we grab our gear, we're heading for the exit; you see to the generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022196" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop right there! Identify yourself! How did you get past those things?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022197" id2="17" version="1065353216">I saw your distress call to Commander Niccos, Lieutenant. I'm here to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1022197" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you Lieutenant Kaley?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022198" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. If you've got a plan, Master Jedi, Kaley and the rest of us can head for the exit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022200" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's end can't come soon enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045434" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you've been through a terrible ordeal, but I'm not your enemy. Breathe easy, and let's talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1045434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Try to calm down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045435" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm the person with the lightsaber. That should answer all your questions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1045435" id2="17" version="1065353216">I killed them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045488" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kaley, he's a Jedi. He's probably here to stop the generator overload.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045499" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, we heard about Dray Zah'lis. That treacherous son of a stone-ray got off easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045516" id2="17" version="1065353216">How long do we have to stop it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1045516" id2="17" version="1065353216">How imminent, exactly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045517" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm trying to learn more about these creatures, and their purpose. I believe they were created by a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1045517" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm investigating the beasts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045519" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you say so. Welcome to the darkest corner of the Nar'less Bunker. The Imperials and their monsters tore open our defensive line.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nearly a hundred dead, for nothing. One of the biggest creatures got into the power room and cracked the generator casing. A toxic overload is imminent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045522" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's fine, Kaley. She's a Jedi; she probably came to stop the generator overload.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045525" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've encountered traitors in the Bothan resistance. Perhaps this situation is due to more than bad luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1045525" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't trust these Bothans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045526" id2="17" version="1065353216">With you here, we can push back to the entrance. That just leaves the generator; hitting the emergency shutoff should fix this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith critters? Figures. They just came out of nowhere; it's like they're in a frenzy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045544" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best case, probably less than an hour.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1045573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant, I've faced ancient horrors and torn Sith Lords from their pedestals. I'll handle this for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1045573" id2="17" version="1065353216">You haven't seen me fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1047698" id2="17" version="1065353216">But you'd have to kill that beast inside to reach it. It'd be a suicide mission. That thing is a terror.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1047701" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forewarned is forearmed. If you can tell me anything about this creature, now's the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1047701" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about this beast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1047777" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no intention of falling to this beast. Your men have done enough, Lieutenant; leave it to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1047777" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody's dying today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048057" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our blaster shots only seemed to annoy it. And somehow it could knock us over like feathers, even if it was barely touching us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1048077" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good luck. I only wish we'd had some luck defending this place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1052064" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mean Dray Zah'lis? Hmph. That traitor's lucky the resistance didn't catch him first.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
