<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>43</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/bothawui/class/jedi_consular/security_console.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="65" id1="1022202" id2="17" version="1065353216">[You have initiated containment measures.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022207" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi. I heard from our last surviving scout--he said he'd given you a lead on Torwin Vehl, and... where are you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022208" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a cold storage facility. It looks like Torwin has been using it to conduct his experiments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1022208" id2="17" version="1065353216">In some sort of laboratory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1022209" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough. You will be dealt with, Jedi. And then... I need a moment's clear thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="65" id1="1022211" id2="17" version="1065353216">[This console is displaying a number of functions for the lab, including defense and containment protocols.]</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056542" id2="17" version="1065353216">The information led me to a facility full of those beasts--I think he's been using it as a laboratory. But there's no sign of Torwin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056542" id2="17" version="1065353216">My search isn't over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056543" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't been able to corner Torwin yet. I found a facility full of his beasts, but he's still on the run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not killing Torwin, sadly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056544" id2="17" version="1065353216">More of those monsters? I... we can't take many more attacks. What do you recommend?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056545" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send a team to secure this facility and these beasts. We can study them offworld and learn more about Torwin's ability.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056545" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to learn from the lab.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander, I'm authorizing the destruction of this lab and all its specimens. Nothing should remain to threaten the Bothan people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Burn this place to the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Confirmed. If any more are loose, we need all the intel we can gather.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056549" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood. Believe me, I'll have no shortage of volunteers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait. Master Jedi, your signal is breaking up. Can you hear me? What about Torwin Vehl--can we track him down?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056553" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. Not since I finally convinced that fool boy to leave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056556" id2="17" version="1065353216">All it took was opening a few cages, to show the mindless savagery of what he's made. To show him that without discipline, there can only be chaos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056557" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wondered when you'd turn up again. Clearly one beating wasn't enough for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056557" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a sore loser.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056558" id2="17" version="1065353216">You unleashed these beasts and endangered your own men, just to prove a point to Torwin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056558" id2="17" version="1065353216">This destruction was a lesson?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen to me. For the galaxy's sake, I have to find him. Tell me where he is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056559" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where is Torwin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056560" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gone. I watched his shuttle take off myself. He won't defy me again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056562" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you didn't kill me. Victory is relative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Describing a flame doesn't have the impact of sticking your pupil's hand in a fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056566" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am both Darth and general, a servant to Darth Marr, entrusted with the... the honor, of protecting Torwin Vehl.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056568" id2="17" version="1065353216">These aberrations he has made scream through the Force. But I know my duty. Questioning it would make me no better than a Jedi, with your endless hand-wringing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056569" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't truly believe that. You are questioning your path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056569" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can sense your uncertainty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056570" id2="17" version="1065353216">I cannot allow an enemy of the Republic to stand!</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056570" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know my duty, too. [Attack]</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056571" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll go one further, Sith. If you obey without question, you're no better than a droid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1056571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your mind is enslaved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056572" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know my path leads to order. Torwin will be made to understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056573" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then strike!</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1056576" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've thrived on duty, as Jedi fall prey to their own uncertainties. To....</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1062636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bothawui is your responsibility, Commander; this is your decision. I have a Sith to find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1104" id1="1062636" id2="17" version="1065353216">My only concern is Torwin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1089" id1="1062641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Understood. I'll sleep a lot better if that facility's destroyed; I'll get a team together.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
