<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>136</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/star_fortress/story/local_contacts/alderaan_contact.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180558" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force is with us, Commander. We must not fail.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180561" id2="17" version="1065353216">The attack is underway. Our allies have engaged the enemy. The rest is up to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180564" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will maneuver our allies into position and meet you inside the shield generator's bunker.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180567" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are finally ready, Commander. I have signaled our allies we have the supplies they need to bolster our assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our allies will be ready to fight once we can supply them. I've found a few caches. How goes your search, Commander?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180577" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good news, Commander. I have successfully negotiated an alliance of minor noble houses to help us assault the shield generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180580" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seek out the enemy's fortified shield generator. If you discover external defenses, destroy them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180583" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are the Commander I've heard so much about. Welcome. I am Choza Raabat of the Jedi Order. I serve your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Safe journeys on Alderaan. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184667" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is finally done, Commander. The sky over Alderaan is free of the Star Fortress's shadow.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184669" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see my decision to join your Alliance was the correct one. I am only one Jedi, but I will serve you with the same loyalty I gave the Order.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184671" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whenever you need me, I stand ready to fight by your side. May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184675" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy station over Alderaan is vulnerable, but it will take great effort to destroy the Star Fortress from within.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184677" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm coordinating strikes by our warships to keep the enemy off-balance. They're buying you time to enter the Star Fortress and bring it crashing down.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184679" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the enemy stronghold falls, I'll be free to join you on other missions. Hurry, Commander. Alderaan needs your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184683" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star Fortress has lost its defensive shield. Now, the final assault can begin.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184685" id2="17" version="1065353216">I made a disturbing discovery about the motive behind Zakuul's actions on Alderaan. The enemy is more depraved than I thought possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184687" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zakuul has orchestrated chaos here to record the resulting violence and broadcast it as entertainment for its people.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184688" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're doing all this to entertain Zakuul's people? That's horrible!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do the people of Zakuul actually enjoy seeing this?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184690" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know how many partake of the holofeeds, or why. Perhaps Zakuul's people don't realize what they're seeing is actually happening.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184692" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they want a show, I'll give it to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184693" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must not stoop to the enemy's level. The Alliance must be better, or all of this is for nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184695" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've done all we can to help Alderaan from here. We must now go to Odessen and plan the assault on the Star Fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184697" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will meet you there, Commander. And when we've achieved total victory, I look forward to serving at your side.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184700" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have identified a perfect location to set the detonation charges. We'll go together, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184703" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go to the shield generator and breach its outer walls. I will find you inside, and together we will destroy the facility.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184705" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in supply crates.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent. This will help our cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184708" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Report the Alderaan Resistance Campaign is complete to receive a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184709" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have undermined Zakuul's efforts to destabilize Alderaan--and saved countless lives. Well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184711" id2="17" version="1065353216">But our work is not yet finished. The supplies we have are still not enough to destroy that shield generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184712" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find more supplies.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184713" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184715" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start the Alderaan Resistance Campaign. Completion will grant a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184716" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zakuul's schemes to pit the noble houses against each other must be ended. Seek those in a position to settle these pointless conflicts and help them achieve victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184718" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start a Heroic Mission to secure supply crates.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184719" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are many in need of our help. Anything we do to aid them will be rewarded with the supplies we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184721" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start an Eternal Empire Champion Duel.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zakuul has dispatched agents to Alderaan. They may be hunting us. Our best hope of remaining undetected is to eliminate these threats.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184724" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you have more supplies, meet me back here. Until then, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184727" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were deeply impressed by your victory over the shield bunker's guardian. You proved Zakuul is not invulnerable.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184728" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to finish the job and destroy that shield generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184729" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which noble houses have offered to join us?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184730" id2="17" version="1065353216">None you would recognize. They are houses that have lost everything to this war except the will to free their home world.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184732" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroying the enemy would've been easier with you helping me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184733" id2="17" version="1065353216">We do not walk an easy path, unfortunately.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184735" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will take a strong coordinated effort to bring down the shield generator. People, weapons, supplies.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184737" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our allies have been beaten down by years of war. They can commit forces to the cause, but they lack adequate materiel.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184739" id2="17" version="1065353216">The larger noble houses--and our enemy--have the supplies we need. We should split up and do what we must to secure them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184741" id2="17" version="1065353216">The more conflicts orchestrated by Zakuul that we can end now, the better-off Alderaan will be when the Star Fortress falls.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184743" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seek those in need of help, gather what supplies you can, and meet me here. Be safe, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184745" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm relieved to meet a fellow Jedi. It seems like there aren't many of us left.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184746" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are not. Those who didn't fall to the Eternal Empire have scattered to the fringes. I've tried contacting them, without success.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184748" id2="17" version="1065353216">That failure extends to reuniting your former crew. Kira Carsen has proved especially difficult to locate.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184749" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kira and I were close, but I haven't felt her presence, either. I don't know what that means.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184750" id2="17" version="1065353216">As Jedi, we must remain above such worries. If you and Kira are meant to be reunited, it will happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184752" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm more concerned about the Sith, Lord Scourge. If he isn't dead, then his silence after my return is troubling.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184753" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admit, the records of your connection to the Emperor's Wrath surprised me. Such ties rarely last long.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184755" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you found anything about &quot;Doc?&quot; He isn't a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184756" id2="17" version="1065353216">A man matching his description is rumored to be wandering the Outer Rim, but I can't say if that information is true or not.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184758" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had hoped to locate your old crew, Barsen'thor, but their whereabouts remain unknown. I offer myself in their place.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184759" id2="17" version="1065353216">My padawan, Nadia Grell, was young and inexperienced. I worry what's become of her.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184760" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's not the first padawan to lose her master. In the end, we can only hope she follows the path.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184762" id2="17" version="1065353216">If anyone could cover his own tracks so well even a Jedi couldn't follow them, it's Tharan Cedrax.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184763" id2="17" version="1065353216">The datafiles describing him and &quot;Holiday&quot; were... colorful, to say the least.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Iresso is Republic military. He shouldn't be that hard to locate.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184766" id2="17" version="1065353216">He is officially listed as MIA. My access to unofficial records is limited, unfortunately.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184768" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thank you for trying to find them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184769" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know how it feels to lose allies without warning.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184771" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attachments are not the Jedi way. The past is behind us, and the future is uncertain. We must focus on the present.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184772" id2="17" version="1065353216">I, too, was once forced by fate to release my old attachments.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184774" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've worked with Jedi before, but I'm not used to ordering them around. How do you feel about this arrangement?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184775" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do whatever you require of me. I volunteered for this assignment.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184777" id2="17" version="1065353216">You serve a Sith. That must be difficult for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184778" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not difficult at all, because I don't serve you. I follow a path laid before me by Grand Master Satele Shan.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184780" id2="17" version="1065353216">I received a message from her, telling me you would come here. She wants your Alliance to succeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184782" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's my job to ensure your victory over the Eternal Empire. No more, and no less.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184783" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish to speak with Satele Shan. Make it happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184784" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would do so if it were within my power. Our communications are controlled by her. If that changes, I'll inform you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Obey my commands and spare me your simpleminded Jedi rhetoric.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184787" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. One cannot fill a closed vessel.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184789" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will not pretend we're anything alike, but I can sympathize with your situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184791" id2="17" version="1065353216">We might become friends. Give it a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184792" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi are taught to welcome new possibilities. I will try.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184794" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never had a Jedi under my command. Are you prepared to accept orders from someone like me?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184795" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't be here if I weren't ready to serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184797" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, you serve me. I command the Alliance, and everyone in it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184798" id2="17" version="1065353216">If my loyalties concern you, understand I have no attachments to anything or anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184800" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does the Jedi Order serve the Alliance, or just you?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184801" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't presume to speak for the entire Order. My path to this moment was long and difficult.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184803" id2="17" version="1065353216">You and I have something unique in common. We both became exiles against our wills, and returned to a galaxy that had changed in our absence.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Twelve years ago, I was on a scouting mission in Wild Space. My ship crashed on a barren world. I had no way to summon rescue.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184807" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was alone for ten years, until a survey vessel from Zakuul set down on my planet. First contact with its crew went... poorly.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184809" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assumed command of their vessel and discovered everything had changed while I was stranded. War had resumed, but the only victor was Zakuul.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184810" id2="17" version="1065353216">Twelve years... you missed a lot more than I did.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184811" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galaxy was at peace when I left it. I knew it couldn't last, but I never imagined all this.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184813" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happened to the crew from Zakuul? Did you kill them all?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184814" id2="17" version="1065353216">I harmed no one. I subdued them, questioned them, and released them to safety.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184815" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was kind of you to let them go free.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184816" id2="17" version="1065353216">There was no kindness to what I did. It was simply the Jedi way.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you learn anything useful?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184819" id2="17" version="1065353216">I learned that I needed to redefine my place in the galaxy. I believe you understand what that is like.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184821" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a fool. Zakuul's people don't deserve mercy. If they could've killed you, they would have.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184822" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not defined by my enemy's actions--only my own.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184824" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you wind up with the Alliance?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184825" id2="17" version="1065353216">I visited Asylum on my way back to Republic space. I saw the suffering there, even before Emperor Arcann's attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184827" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I heard what happened to Asylum--and the rise of your Alliance in response--I knew I would join.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184829" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I have strayed far from our present concerns. The mission here is vital.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184831" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alderaan has suffered greater than any of the Core Worlds. Matters have only worsened since Zakuul placed its Star Fortress in orbit.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184833" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have tracked the enemy's activities, and one thing is clear: Zakuul is actively encouraging Alderaan's civil war. The noble houses are more hostile than ever.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Alderaan's leaders are responsible for this conflict--not Zakuul. The civil war existed years before the Eternal Empire got here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184835" id2="17" version="1065353216">While you were away, the houses made a concerted effort to settle things peacefully. Zakuul has undermined that process at every turn.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184837" id2="17" version="1065353216">How is Zakuul turning the noble houses against each other?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184838" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy has carried out a series of assassinations and sabotage operations. Each time, they've misdirected blame to an innocent noble house.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe all these worthless nobles will finally kill each other. Problem solved.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184841" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not the nobles who bear the brunt of this violence. It's their subjects. The poor and innocent die by the thousands.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184843" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star Fortress is the heart of Zakuul's treachery on Alderaan. With it removed, this world might have a chance to rebuild.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184845" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the battle station is protected by a powerful shield generator here on the surface. We must eliminate it, first.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184847" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have an important meeting with potential allies. Your best course of action is to scout the shield generator's location and test its vulnerabilities.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184849" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1190446" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zakuul's schemes to pit the noble houses against each other must be ended. Seek those in a position to settle these pointless conflicts and help them achieve victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192608" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Alien Research crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192609" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Military Equipment crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192610" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Ancient Artifact crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192611" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Smuggled Goods crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192629" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Go Back.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192741" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Do Nothing.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1193991" id2="17" version="1065353216">The lone Bafforr tree is silent and unfulfilled, but the forest is all-wise and capable. Sow our seeds, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1193992" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have been away from the galaxy for some time. Much has changed--especially the company.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1193993" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force will see us to victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1193994" id2="17" version="1065353216">We remain vigilant, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194389" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find peace among your allies. Together, we preserve.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194390" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm happy to share stories with you, Commander. My wisdom is yours.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194391" id2="17" version="1065353216">The path to the future requires that we trim away the thorns of the past. Let the Force be your guide.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194392" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Alliance will see harmony and balance returned to the galaxy.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
