<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>112</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/star_fortress/story/local_contacts/belsavis_contact.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once this place is flaming rubble, that Star Fortress will be wide-open to attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180596" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy doesn't know what hit them. My recruits are as good as I thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180599" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get my recruits into position and meet you inside the shield generator bunker.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180602" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did it, Commander! That's everything we need to start this shield-busting party.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180609" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not fully supplied yet. What can I do for you, Commander?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180612" id2="17" version="1065353216">I swear, I think I felt the ruckus you kicked up at that shield generator all the way over here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scout out that shield generator and let me know what you find.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander! Good to meet you! K'krohl's the name, talent scouting's my game. Your Alliance pays me to track and evaluate escaped prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't mind me. I got a legal permit to be on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scratch one Star Fortress! I wish I could've been there to see it. I'm not missing out on anything else.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184854" id2="17" version="1065353216">You just missed a party, Commander! A bunch of my Belsavis recruits stopped by to celebrate you taking down that Star Fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184856" id2="17" version="1065353216">They made you a card and everything. It's around here somewhere. The point is, everything's turned out great for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184858" id2="17" version="1065353216">From now on, Bitsy and me are only a holocall away. Looking forward to our next mission, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184862" id2="17" version="1065353216">That Star Fortress over Belsavis is unshielded. If we're taking it out of the sky, now's the time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184864" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've already negotiated a salary fighting for you full-time--but not until this business is over. Let's get it done, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knocking down that Star Fortress won't be easy, but if anyone can do it, it's you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184870" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're as good as they say--maybe better! Everyone on that Star Fortress knows they lost their shield. That's gotta be scary for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184872" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you're not a fan of my job here, but you have to admit--my recruits helped.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our losses were surprisingly light. I've got quite a few ex-cons thinking they're getting off this rock to help the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184876" id2="17" version="1065353216">But my new job is coordinating the Star Fortress attacks from your camp on Odessen. What should I do with my recruits before I ship out?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave the prisoners here. They can't be trusted.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184878" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll send them to an isolated rendezvous. By the time they figure out I'm not coming, it'll be too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bring them along. The Alliance is a second chance for anyone willing to serve.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184881" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I've been telling them. I'm glad to hear it coming from you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184883" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll take them with us. They'll get the most suicidal missions I can find.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184884" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll just tell them we're honoring our deal. They'll figure out the rest on their own.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do what you think is best. You know them better than me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184887" id2="17" version="1065353216">They followed orders and behaved themselves. I think they're worth keeping around.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184889" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if they ever do step out of line, I still have Bitsy. Thanks for trusting my judgment.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe when that Star Fortress is a big pile of space garbage, I'll get out of the recruiting business. I'd like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knocking out that shield generator was the most fun I've had in years. I wouldn't mind signing-on with you full time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184895" id2="17" version="1065353216">But that Star Fortress has gotta go, first. I'll see you on Odessen, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184898" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know where to plant the detonite so it'll bring this whole place down. Looking forward to seeing you in action, Commander. Let's go!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184901" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got troops, gear, and a clear shot at the generator bunker. I'll meet you inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't start without me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184903" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't dream of it, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184905" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't think you'd join the fighting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184906" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been on the sidelines for too long--and Bitsy needs to go for a walk.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your recruits are expendable. Understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184909" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll cut their leashes. What happens after that is their problem, am I right?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your fingers crossed I still have an eye for talent. Let's move out.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184913" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in supply crates.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184914" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a find! This gear looks new--and no bloodstains!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184916" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Report the Belsavis Resistance Campaign is complete to receive a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184917" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey, that's great news! A lot of those bad things you stomped were hassling my recruits. Good riddance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184919" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is getting us closer, but we're not there yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184920" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep looking for more supplies.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184921" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep my recruits from deserting while you're gone. It's a full time job.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184923" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start the Belsavis Resistance Campaign. Completion will grant a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184928" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start a Heroic Mission to secure supply crates.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184929" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of my recruits gave me a lead on where you could get some supplies. It's worth a try.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184931" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start an Eternal Empire Champion Duel.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184932" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm hearing rumors that say Zakuul is sending its heavy-hitters to stir things up. That's trouble we don't need.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184934" id2="17" version="1065353216">On the other hand, I bet you anything their people are well-supplied. Two birds with one stone, am I right?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once we've got everything we need, we'll take down that shield generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Should've figured that bunker would have external defenses. Glad you took them out, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184941" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now for the real tricky part--getting enough detonite inside that place to burn it down for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184943" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can provide warm bodies for the assault, but they'll need outfitting. I hate to put it on you, but supplying troops ain't exactly my specialty.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184944" id2="17" version="1065353216">There must be some way to get what we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184945" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not a delivery service--and your &quot;warm bodies&quot; are disposable scum.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184946" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not so loud! You never know who's listening.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184948" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the record, I agree with you--but we'll lose our recruits if we don't at least pretend to care they'll survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184950" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's all kinds of emergencies on Belsavis. People in need tend to be grateful when you help them out. And hey, there's always looters to steal from, am I right?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184952" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll let you know once we've got enough supplies to mount the assault. Good luck, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184955" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I think someone's worth recruiting to fight the Eternal Empire, I make them an offer. If they refuse, I introduce them to &quot;Bitsy.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fun work. Never a dull moment. But that Star Fortress is making all kinds of trouble. We need it gone.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184958" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one told me the Alliance is recruiting escaped prisoners.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko hired me to identify anyone I think can be &quot;rehabilitated&quot; and send them to the fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some of these folks ain't all bad. I mean, sure, they've killed a few people--but who here hasn't, am I right?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184962" id2="17" version="1065353216">These prisoners can't be rehabilitated. That's why they're on Belsavis. I'm shutting down your recruitment drive.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184963" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I just bought a house! Oh, well... I didn't pay much. It's a buyer's market.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184965" id2="17" version="1065353216">The thing is, we still have to do something about that Star Fortress before we go.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184967" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you evaluate prisoners for rehabilitation?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184968" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they attack on sight, that's a meaningful predictor of future behavior.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184970" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not too many get past that stage of the screening process. But I'm an optimist. I keep trying.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184972" id2="17" version="1065353216">My job would be a lot easier if that Star Fortress wasn't stirring up the crazy down here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184974" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see the potential in gathering some disposable cannon fodder. How many recruits have you found?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184975" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eh, not enough. Most of my negotiations end with Bitsy. I blame that blasted Star Fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184977" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is a Star Fortress doing above Belsavis? Why is it here?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184978" id2="17" version="1065353216">It ain't to keep law and order, that's for sure.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184980" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mentioned someone named &quot;Bitsy.&quot; Who is that?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bitsy's my top-of-the-line Czerka military assault cannon! When negotiations turn sour, Bitsy takes over. Real conversation-stopper.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184983" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been needing Bitsy a lot lately, and I think it's on account of that Star Fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184985" id2="17" version="1065353216">At first, I couldn't figure why Zakuul would set up a fancy battle station over Belsavis. Seems like overkill, y'know?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184987" id2="17" version="1065353216">But then I started seeing Zakuul shuttles flying down to the lowest vaults, where the worst prisoners are locked-up.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184989" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're releasing them to run riot up here. I'm starting to think Zakuul had the same bright idea as the Alliance. Maybe they're on their own recruitment drive?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184990" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a disaster in the making. The worst threats the galaxy has ever faced are imprisoned down there. They can't be controlled--not even by Zakuul.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184991" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sooner or later, one of these lunatics is gonna find a way off Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184993" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Zakuul is recruiting, that's good news. It means they're getting scared of us--and desperate.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184994" id2="17" version="1065353216">The trouble is, I can't recruit the crazy ones--and they're killing my prospects.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184996" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we take down that battle station, the enemy won't have a base of operations to keep up this nonsense.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1184998" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're taking down that Star Fortress. Where do we start?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1184999" id2="17" version="1065353216">The first thing to do is hit the shield generator protecting the Star Fortress. I've got coordinates, but no strategy. That's where you come in, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take a look at that shield generator and see what we're up against. In the meantime, I'll gather some recruits and rendezvous back here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1190412" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start the Belsavis Resistance Campaign. Completion will grant a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1190413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you believe the Republic and the Sith Empire are still going at it over this place? Just crazy, am I right?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1190415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Between you and me, some of my better prospects are deserters from those armies. If you settled the score here, they'd be free to sign up.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1190437" id2="17" version="1065353216">From now on, Bitsy and me are only a holocall away. Looking forward to our next mission, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192580" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Alien Research crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192581" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Ancient Artifact crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192582" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Military Equipment crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192583" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Smuggled Goods crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192947" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Go Back.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192948" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Do Nothing.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194408" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm working on some new recruits from the Outer Rim. They're rusty, but they'll polish up in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194409" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bitsy's getting anxious with all this waiting. What do you say we take her out for a spin, Commander?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fun group you've got here. Plenty of scars to keep the stories interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194411" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're snatching the best recruits from the galaxy's underbelly and leaving Zakuul with the damages.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194412" id2="17" version="1065353216">Need someone &quot;enlisted?&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Recruitment is on the rise. People put their history aside to stand with you, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194414" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's go rattle some heads. To the right cause, that is.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone need some extra motivation? Bitsy's happy to play the &quot;negotiator.&quot;</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
