<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>94</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/star_fortress/story/local_contacts/hoth_contact.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180510" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander, we are so honored to meet you. We volunteered for this assignment because we were told you would oversee it personally.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180513" id2="17" version="1065353216">See the shield generator with your own eyes. We must record our notes of this first meeting while the memories are fresh.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180515" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are so cold on this world. The only upside is we can see the heat images of others perfectly.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180518" id2="17" version="1065353216">You return alive and victorious. We are greatly pleased to see you again. We were told of your mighty battle at the shield generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Abundant success, Commander! You have proven yourself as the greatest war leader on Hoth.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180533" id2="17" version="1065353216">The time to strike has come. We will join you inside the shield generator bunker.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eat our bolts, Zakuul scum! Also, tell us your names for posterity!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180544" id2="17" version="1065353216">We did not expect to arrive before you, Commander! But it is good, because now we will witness your every achievement in this battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1183351" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was exhilarating, Commander. We now feel less self-conscious about revealing that was our first combat mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185361" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star Fortress of Hoth is destroyed! This is good... and bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185362" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Alliance insurgency on Hoth stands ready to aid your assault on the Star Fortress, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185386" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are always pleased to see you, Commander. What do you bring?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185387" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Alien Research crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185388" id2="17" version="1065353216">An excellent find.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185391" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Report the Hoth Resistance Campaign is complete to receive a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185392" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your success bolsters the insurgents! Many who questioned joining you now see the benefit.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185395" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are still not prepared for a successful assault. More supplies, please.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185396" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find the rest of what we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185397" id2="17" version="1065353216">Safe travels, Commander. We will be here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185399" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start the Hoth Resistance Campaign. Completion will grant a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185400" id2="17" version="1065353216">We believe if you can definitively settle certain longstanding conflicts on Hoth, those involved may come to see you as their leader.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185402" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start a Heroic Mission to secure supply crates.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185403" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have discovered an opportunity for a battle worthy of history that could also achieve our materiel needs.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185405" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start an Eternal Empire Champion Duel.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185406" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the first time, the Star Fortress has dispatched forces to Hoth's surface. We must conceal your insurgency.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185408" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will soon have enough supplies to mount a successful insurgency. Remain steadfast, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185548" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good, because the enemy's threat to the Alliance and those who would join is ended. Bad, because Hoth has a new debris field to fight over.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185550" id2="17" version="1065353216">But there is also spectacular news! Theron Shan has approved our transfer request. We and our blasters will be ready whenever you need us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185553" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have requested a transfer to serve as your combat adjutant once the mission is complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185555" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will monitor your battles from here and record your exploits with breathless anticipation. For history!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185557" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't tell. You really are a natural with those blasters.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185558" id2="17" version="1065353216">You flatter us. We still think we are more skilled at composing historical chronicles.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185560" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're lucky to be alive. What were you thinking, following me here?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185561" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were thinking we would die. But it would be worth it. Our chronicle would live on and inform future generations of your grandeur.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now we hit that Star Fortress with everything we have.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron Shan has requested our assistance planning the final assault on the enemy battle station. We will fly to Odessen and see you at your camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185566" id2="17" version="1065353216">It has been our greatest honor to fight by your side. We hope to do it again after the Star Fortress is destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Holorecorder activated, blasters charged, bladder empty. Let us do this!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185572" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will deliver these final supplies and signal the attack on the Star Fortress shield generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185574" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will find you inside the facility. It will be our tremendous honor to fight at your side.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185576" id2="17" version="1065353216">Also, your efforts will expand the scope of our chronicles on your behalf. Truly, a victory for all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find the enemy and ensure it does not report back. Also, take its things. They may prove useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185581" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were observed by potential allies. They were favorably impressed, and are now prepared to forswear their old loyalties and join you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about these potential allies. Who are they? What factions are they from?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185583" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic, Sith Empire, White Maw, Chiss Ascendancy, Ortolan settlers. All see the Star Fortress threat. All have reason to join you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185585" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you send me out on some kind of test?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185586" id2="17" version="1065353216">We would never presume to test you, Commander! However, a demonstration of your prowess turned more heads than our words of praise ever could.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185588" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't want traitors in my Alliance. What's to stop them from &quot;forswearing&quot; me?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185589" id2="17" version="1065353216">We believe you command equal parts of their respect and fear. We cannot imagine anyone else who could supplant you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185591" id2="17" version="1065353216">History teaches that all successful insurgencies require two elements: dedicated loyalists, and abundant implements of warfare. We can provide the former if you provide the latter.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185593" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hoth is home to many camps. Some friendly, many not. But all are sources of the supplies your fledgling insurgency will need.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find supplies and bring them to us. When we have enough, our forces can lend their aid to destroy the shield generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185597" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate your enthusiasm, but this is a dangerous world. You're risking your life coming here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185598" id2="17" version="1065353216">All life is risk. We observe this truth throughout history.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are you? One of Hoth's stranded pirates?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185601" id2="17" version="1065353216">By the stars, no! We are a respected military historian.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, good--just what I needed. Another fan.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185604" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are much more than your fan. We are your biographer.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185606" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are the individual named Hemdil Tre. Before the war, we were the official chronicler of military antiquity for the Grand Nest of Cona.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185608" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are well-studied in all matters of warfare. We are also what the combat instructor called &quot;a freak of nature&quot; when firing blasters.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185610" id2="17" version="1065353216">We leaped at the chance to lend our fields of expertise to you and your Alliance. We hope to compose the definitive chronicle of your struggle against the Eternal Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185611" id2="17" version="1065353216">I look forward to seeing you in action. Bring me up to speed on the situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185612" id2="17" version="1065353216">A two-gun historian. That's... unusual.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185613" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are versatile, but we are no Commander, like you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185615" id2="17" version="1065353216">My version of the truth is the only thing you should write down. Understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185616" id2="17" version="1065353216">History conforms to the victorious. Every chronicler knows this truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185618" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have taken a full accounting of the situation on Hoth. Things are much the same as they were before the Star Fortress arrived.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Republic and Sith Empire still fight the White Maw and other pirate bands for control of Hoth's starship graveyard. But now, Zakuul watches from above.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185622" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enemy does not interfere. Instead, it adds fuel to the fire by sending new starship wrecks to Hoth's surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185624" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star Fortress broadcasts a false Alliance signal, drawing those who would join our cause. When the vessels arrive, the enemy shoots them down.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185625" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to send out a counter-signal and warn people about this trap!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185626" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron Shan is working on this, but the enemy's control over hyperwave communications is near-total.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185628" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many potential allies has the Star Fortress shot down?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185629" id2="17" version="1065353216">We estimate at least three dozen warships of various classifications. The smallest was a scout vessel. The largest was a light cruiser.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185631" id2="17" version="1065353216">A clever snare. I'll have to use it myself, someday.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185632" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have studied numerous examples of adopting enemy tactics with great success. The key appears to be replicating the intent, not the exact process.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185634" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have located the enemy's shield generator facility, but were unable to approach. It is heavily guarded. We recommend you see for yourself, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185636" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will continue our negotiations with those here who might aid the Alliance. We hope to have good news upon your return.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1190443" id2="17" version="1065353216">But there is also spectacular news! Theron Shan has approved our transfer request. We and our blasters will be ready whenever you need us.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1190448" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start the Hoth Resistance Campaign. Completion will grant a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192653" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Ancient Artifact crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192654" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Military Equipment crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192655" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Smuggled Goods crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192849" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in supply crates.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192869" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Do Nothing.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192877" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Go Back.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194420" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander. Your heat pattern shines beyond all others.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194421" id2="17" version="1065353216">We stand by your side to educate and assist.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194422" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your accounts continue to swell, Commander. We are honored to chronicle your heroism.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194423" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are happy to share reports on military stratagems at your leisure.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194424" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Victory&quot; shall be the epilogue of this Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194425" id2="17" version="1065353216">As our numbers grow, we find difficulty in discerning individuals. This is good.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194426" id2="17" version="1065353216">All roads have two paths: One to victory, one to defeat. You are our feet, Commander. Guide us well.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194427" id2="17" version="1065353216">A single holobook will not suffice in telling your tale.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
