<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>119</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/star_fortress/story/local_contacts/nar_shaddaa_contact.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180631" id2="17" version="1065353216">You lead, I follow, we kill. Let's go.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180634" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've taken the enemy by surprise. Zakuul didn't believe you could organize a resistance on Nar Shaddaa. Frankly, I had my doubts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's finish this. Meet me inside that shield generator's bunker.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180640" id2="17" version="1065353216">We could always use more support, but it's too risky to wait any longer. It's time to move on the shield generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180647" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear you've been busy, Commander. How can I help?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180650" id2="17" version="1065353216">You struck the enemy and drew blood. Even the Hutt Cartel approves of you, although they can't admit it publicly.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scout the shield bunker. When you get back, we'll talk.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander. Lana Beniko sends her regards. She tasked me with coordinating your efforts against the Star Fortress threatening Nar Shaddaa.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180659" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have no business.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185363" id2="17" version="1065353216">I watched the Star Fortress explode. It's one of the most beautiful things I've ever seen.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185364" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a small fleet loyal to the Alliance sitting on standby at Nar Shaddaa. When you're ready to strike the Star Fortress, they'll provide a distraction.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185365" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in supply crates.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185367" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start the Nar Shaddaa Resistance Campaign. Completion will grant a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185368" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start a Heroic Mission to secure supply crates.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185369" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start an Eternal Empire Champion Duel.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185370" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are exactly what we need. I'll make sure the right people get them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185371" id2="17" version="1065353216">That resolution has been a long time coming. Without its distraction, we're much closer to our own victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185374" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we need more supplies before we can mount a successful assault on the shield generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185375" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find the rest of the supplies we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185376" id2="17" version="1065353216">The more you find, the more people step forward to help us. We'll win this, yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185378" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time to settle old scores between the Republic, Sith Empire, and Hutt Cartel. Many resources we need are being used up by their conflicts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185379" id2="17" version="1065353216">I found an opportunity to secure the kinds of things we need. It's worth looking into.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185380" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zakuul has taken note of our efforts. They've stepped up their patrols.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185382" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you have more supplies, I'll be waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185638" id2="17" version="1065353216">You held your end of the bargain, and now I'll hold mine. I pledge myself to you until the Eternal Empire is no more.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185639" id2="17" version="1065353216">That may take a long time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'll have to pick up the pace. I'll be ready when you need me, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185641" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no reason we can't enjoy working together.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185642" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't mix love and war. It never ends well. But I'll protect you when needed. Until then....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185643" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt I'll be calling on you often. You don't seem trustworthy.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185644" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've only stabbed one person in the back, and they deserved it. You don't. But suit yourself, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185647" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you survive the attack, come find me. I promised I'd stay and help you end this war, but only if you save my home first. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185651" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing better than humbling someone who thinks they have all the power. Now Zakuul's hounds know what it feels like to be afraid.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185652" id2="17" version="1065353216">You enjoy striking terror into people a little too much.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185653" id2="17" version="1065353216">Zakuul's enforcers barely qualify as people. They surrendered any claim to that word when they threatened our freedoms.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not yet, they don't--but they will. I'll see to it personally.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185656" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've earned what's coming.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185658" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't give them time to regroup. We need to hit the Star Fortress right away.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185659" id2="17" version="1065353216">As much as I love Nar Shaddaa, I promised Lana I would join the Alliance on Odessen and coordinate strikes on the Star Fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185661" id2="17" version="1065353216">I also pledged to serve as your bodyguard should you succeed in destroying it. Seemed the least I could do.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185663" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm headed for my transport. See you on Odessen, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185666" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the plan's in motion and there's no holding back. We need to reach the nerve center of this bunker and burn it down.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185668" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lana Beniko ordered me to watch your back in here. Lead the way, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185671" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll deliver these last supplies and signal Alliance forces to move in. Find me inside the shield generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185673" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care who wins. I just want peace and quiet--and gear for our people.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185675" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know where to find one of their elite agents. They tend to be well-equipped. We can turn the enemy's weapons against them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185678" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have several factions willing to join the Alliance and destroy the Star Fortress, but there are... complications.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185680" id2="17" version="1065353216">The black market has dried up thanks to Zakuul's enforcers. Our allies are willing, but weak. We need to make them strong.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185681" id2="17" version="1065353216">A campaign like ours requires military-grade gear.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185682" id2="17" version="1065353216">Weapons and explosives, definitely. But we also need medpacs, combat stims, droid parts... you name it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185684" id2="17" version="1065353216">What difference will that make? They're all cannon fodder, anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185685" id2="17" version="1065353216">They aren't an unlimited resource. The better-equipped your &quot;cannon fodder&quot; is, the more likely they'll survive to be useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185687" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about these allies. I need to know who's with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185688" id2="17" version="1065353216">All of the gangs are contributing foot soldiers. But we have genuine freedom-fighters, too. Evocii. Asylum-seekers. Anti-slavers.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185690" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic, Sith Empire, and Hutt Cartel continue their old grudge matches all over Nar Shaddaa.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185692" id2="17" version="1065353216">Settling these pointless fights will focus everyone on the real threat, and gain the resources needed to supply your forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seek out opportunities to gather supplies, and I'll do the same. When you have something, meet me here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185696" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sense the dark side of the Force within you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185697" id2="17" version="1065353216">I made no effort to conceal my nature. I was told you are open-minded, for a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185699" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see no reason to conceal my true nature from you. But we are not alike.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185701" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I had to guess, I'd say you're some kind of Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then Lana was correct. You're more than a pretty face. &quot;Some kind of Sith&quot; gets close to the truth, but not quite.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185704" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you know Lana? Do you work for her?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185705" id2="17" version="1065353216">At the moment, I serve the Alliance. That may continue, depending on how I feel later.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185707" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was training on Korriban when the Eternal Empire's forces attacked. I learned afterward that Arcann and his brother led the invasion.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185709" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had only begun learning the ways of the Force. When my overseer died, I was forced to flee Korriban. This is where I wound up.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185710" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not too late to seek a different path. I could teach you the Jedi way.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185711" id2="17" version="1065353216">That won't be necessary. I follow my own ways--no one else's.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Join me, and I will complete your training in the dark side.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185714" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have all the training I desire. Seek a new apprentice elsewhere.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185716" id2="17" version="1065353216">So, you aren't a real Sith. Ever consider my line of work? I could show you the ropes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185717" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not seeking employment, and you would find me difficult to train.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are there other refugees from Korriban hiding on Nar Shaddaa?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185720" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have a club, if that's what you're asking. But yes, there are others like me here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't lie to me. Before you entered the Sith Academy, you were a slave. By running away, you became a fugitive of the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185723" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, I became a fugitive when I decapitated my overseer. I only ran away after that.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185725" id2="17" version="1065353216">You aren't telling me the whole story. I don't like people who keep secrets from me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185726" id2="17" version="1065353216">My overseer's death was not entirely at the enemy's hands. She was a cruel-hearted woman. No one misses her.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185728" id2="17" version="1065353216">I offer no apologies for what I did to get here. You've seen Korriban. It's where people like me go to die.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185730" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be distracted by details. We need each other. It's that simple.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185732" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's why you're helping the Alliance? To get revenge for what happened?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185733" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was happy to escape Korriban. I never looked back. The past doesn't concern me, only the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185735" id2="17" version="1065353216">I offered to aid the Alliance because I care about my new home--and I know what happened to Bothawui.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185737" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's get right to business. Tell me everything you know about the Star Fortress and what it will take to defeat it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185738" id2="17" version="1065353216">On the surface, it may seem unchanged--but Nar Shaddaa has not been the same since the Star Fortress appeared.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185740" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is no longer a free world for people who want to get lost. Everything that happens here is monitored, recorded, and transmitted back to Zakuul.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185742" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone who ventures into the open risks being ID-scanned by Zakuul's agents and taken away without formal charges or a trial.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185743" id2="17" version="1065353216">They must be looking for something--or someone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185744" id2="17" version="1065353216">And when they find what they're looking for, Nar Shaddaa will no longer have any value. It will become the next Bothawui.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who are the people being targeted?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185747" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no clear pattern. They've arrested gangsters, political dissidents, homeless refugees, and even corporate executives with clear records.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185749" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know what Zakuul is after, and I don't care--I just want to see this world made safe for everyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185750" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's an odd statement coming from a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185751" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are odd times. I've adapted to them. Can you?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185753" id2="17" version="1065353216">True Sith do not seek safety--or to protect others.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185754" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't serve dogmatic beliefs. I alone decide what matters.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185756" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed--this has to end. Where do we start?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185757" id2="17" version="1065353216">Part of me wants to give Zakuul a little more time to remove the undesirable elements.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185758" id2="17" version="1065353216">And who decides which people are &quot;undesirable?&quot; I escaped being a slave to the Sith Empire. I won't bow to its replacement.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185760" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care what's happening here, or why. I just want to destroy the Star Fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185761" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star Fortress reactor is protected by a shield generator here on Nar Shaddaa. I have the coordinates.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185763" id2="17" version="1065353216">The generator is inside a bunker. Zakuul keeps changing up the security patrols defending its perimeter.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185765" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a coalition of forces willing to help bring down the Star Fortress, but they need a show of force from the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scout the shield generator's bunker, make a show of eliminating its external defenses, and you'll have the start of an army here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1190354" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care who wins. I just want peace and quiet--and gear for our people.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192566" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Alien Research crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192567" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Ancient Artifact crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192568" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Military Equipment crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192569" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Smuggled Goods crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1193023" id2="17" version="1065353216">Taking a break from the mayhem?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1193024" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are many here who have known hardship. We understand each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194428" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Eternal Empire isn't slowing down, and neither should we.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194429" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith here recognize my scars. They know the marks of Korriban.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194430" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Jedi here had as many warriors as they do opinions, this war would be over.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194431" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galaxy needs this Alliance to succeed. Don't let them down.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194432" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't leave one empire to get trampled by another. Let's finish this war.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194433" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm used to the noise of Nar Shaddaa. It's hard to concentrate here when it's so... quiet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1195333" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Do Nothing.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1195851" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Go Back.]</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
