<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>105</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/star_fortress/story/local_contacts/tatooine_contact.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180700" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's like blasting wraids in a box canyon!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180703" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was starting to think you got lost! I guess you're buying the drinks when this is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180706" id2="17" version="1065353216">Last one to the shield generator buys all the drinks!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180709" id2="17" version="1065353216">This will do nicely! I think we're finally ready. Let's hit that shield generator right between the eyes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180716" id2="17" version="1065353216">Staying cool out there?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Heard you took out heavy resistance at the shield generator. That got Zakuul's forces stirred-up--and not only them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180722" id2="17" version="1065353216">Scout that shield generator's bunker and see what we're up against. I'll have news when you get back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180725" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome back to Tatooine, Commander. The locals still talk about your last visit. You left quite an impression. The name's Leyta, but everyone calls me &quot;Deadeye.&quot; I'm your contact here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180728" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not looking for trouble. That doesn't mean it won't find me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1183343" id2="17" version="1065353216">You smell that? Burning detonite. There's nothing else like it. Reminds me of home.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185221" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron made me a holorecording of the Star Fortress going up in flames over Tatooine.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185223" id2="17" version="1065353216">I almost feel bad for the locals. It blew up on the nighttime side of the planet. Folks must have thought morning came early.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185225" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing I hate more than a bully. We did a good thing, Commander. And it looks like I'll be sticking around.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185227" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need a good blaster at your side, you know who to call. See you around.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185231" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any gang on Tatooine with a starship is ready to punch you an opening inside that Star Fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185233" id2="17" version="1065353216">The sooner we take that thing down, the better. I heard what happened to Bothawui.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185235" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tatooine isn't much to look at, but there are good people living on it right next to the bad ones.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185237" id2="17" version="1065353216">And if you need any other motivation, I might just be persuaded to stick around as your hired gun once this is all over.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185240" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star Fortress shield is down. Time to finish the job and knock that hunk of junk out of the sky forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185242" id2="17" version="1065353216">Theron Shan wants me to help coordinate the strike from Odessen. Looks like you're stuck with me a little while longer, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185243" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll always have a place on my team if you want one.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185244" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks! I haven't had a real job in... well, I've never had a real job. Could be interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185246" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you know about organizing raids on battle stations?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185247" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's still a shootout. The fundamentals don't change. It's all about positioning and aim. The blasters are bigger, that's all.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185249" id2="17" version="1065353216">And our allies on Tatooine? What about them?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185250" id2="17" version="1065353216">They think you're aces, and they plan to keep fighting. Don't worry, I'll keep them together for the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185252" id2="17" version="1065353216">My transport is waiting. See you on Odessen.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185255" id2="17" version="1065353216">This bunker's got a weak spot. We plant explosives there, and this place will go down like a drunken bantha.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185257" id2="17" version="1065353216">You lead the way. I'll cover your back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185260" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get this last batch of gear to our friends and meet you inside the shield generator. See you there!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185262" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Smuggled Goods crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice haul, Commander. I don't know what half this stuff is, but it'll come in handy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185265" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Report the Tatooine Resistance Campaign is complete to receive a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice work!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185268" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're off to a great start. With a few more supplies, we should be all set.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185269" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185270" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be here.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185272" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start the Tatooine Resistance Campaign. Completion will grant a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185273" id2="17" version="1065353216">You may want to check in with your old friends and see what sort of help they need. They can express their gratitude with some shiny new gear.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185275" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start a Heroic Mission to secure supply crates.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185276" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing that greases palms faster than desperation. I know something you could do that'll net us lots of gear.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185278" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start an Eternal Empire Champion Duel.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185279" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think Zakuul knows you're down here. They sent some big guns to hunt you down.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185281" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've always subscribed to the idea of shooting first. There's no telling what kind of gear you could loot off Zakuul's finest.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185283" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm getting the supplies to our allies. When you have more to distribute, come find me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185286" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your message was heard all over this dustball. Every gang in hiding discovered it still had a backbone.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185288" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think we've got enough foot soldiers to mount a full-scale insurgency. The trick now is getting them military-grade gear.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185289" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me guess... you need me to provide that gear?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185290" id2="17" version="1065353216">They said you were a genius. I never doubted it.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185292" id2="17" version="1065353216">The criminal syndicates should have more than enough firepower of their own.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185293" id2="17" version="1065353216">They have blasters, sure. But desert warfare is a whole other thing. These thugs are used to living in cantinas.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185295" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic and the Sith Empire never completely gave up this world. You can still find their outposts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185297" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm thinking the Alliance can build some goodwill and secure the supplies we need to hit that shield generator where it hurts.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185299" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do some digging and see what turns up, but it'll go faster if you help. You know where to find me.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185301" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's an interesting nickname. How did you get it?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185302" id2="17" version="1065353216">The hard way. I killed a whole lot of people who disagreed with me. Started on my home world, Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185304" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of the bigger tribes kept coming after mine. Stealing our food, treating us like slaves. I went to have a chat with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185306" id2="17" version="1065353216">We started out just trading words, but in the end it was all blasters. When the smoke cleared, I was the last one standing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185307" id2="17" version="1065353216">That explains why they call you &quot;Deadeye.&quot; You must be amazing with that blaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185308" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not some trick-shot artist, if that's what you're thinking. I aim where it counts, that's all.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185310" id2="17" version="1065353216">You killed the entire tribe? No one survived?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185311" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some ran when the blasting started. I guess they're alive. The rest got what was coming to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185313" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impressive. I assume that slaughter was only the beginning of your reputation.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185314" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know why people keep picking fights with me. I must have the kind of face they want to punch in.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185316" id2="17" version="1065353216">My family decided it was best if I left Corellia for a while. I've been kicking around the Outer Rim ever since.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185318" id2="17" version="1065353216">But those Eternal Empire scum keep bothering me. I finally had enough and signed on with your Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough about me. Let's talk about that Star Fortress and why it's orbiting Tatooine.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185322" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't say Tatooine impressed me. I don't even remember being here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Consider yourself lucky. Most people spend their whole lives trying to forget this planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185325" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never thought I'd have to revisit this backwater planet.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185326" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the thing about Tatooine. Every time you think you've seen it for the last time, there it is again.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185328" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were all surprised when that Star Fortress showed up in orbit. We couldn't figure what Zakuul wanted with Tatooine.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185330" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why does the Eternal Empire care about Tatooine enough to put a Star Fortress over it?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185331" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the first thing the rest of us wondered when it popped into orbit. You'd think Zakuul had bigger wraids to roast.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185333" id2="17" version="1065353216">Near as we can tell, Zakuul thinks this world is some kind of criminal haven. They send forces down here to &quot;clean things up.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185335" id2="17" version="1065353216">Two of the bigger syndicates vanished overnight. Zakuul killed everybody. The other gangs went into hiding. It's hard to know how many are left.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185336" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't approve of Zakuul's methods, but I suspect life has improved for the honest citizens.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185337" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you kidding? The ranchers and moisture farmers are scared to death. They figure they're all next on the list.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185339" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunting random thugs seems like a waste of time for Zakuul's forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185340" id2="17" version="1065353216">I got a theory that Tatooine is a testing ground. They may plan to do this on other planets they consider &quot;high crime.&quot; Corellia, for instance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nobody kills these scum except me. I was here first.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1185343" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't expect me to shed any tears for criminals.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185344" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fair enough, but I'm looking at the bigger picture--and I don't like what I see.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185346" id2="17" version="1065353216">People should be free to misbehave. Zakuul's idea of law and order is killing everybody it doesn't like. And yes, I'm aware of the irony, so move on....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185348" id2="17" version="1065353216">My orders are to help you turn that Star Fortress into Tatooine's third sun. But we won't get far until we take out its shield.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185350" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a bunker nearby housing the shield generator. We've got to find a way inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185352" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should go take a look, but fair warning--there's probably something nasty patrolling the perimeter.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1185354" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been calling in some favors. I should have some good news when you get back.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1191031" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Report the Tatooine Resistance Campaign is complete to receive a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1191038" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start the Tatooine Resistance Campaign. Completion will grant a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1191084" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Do Nothing.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1191279" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need a good blaster at your side, you know who to call. See you around.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192656" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Alien Research crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192657" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Ancient Artifact crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192658" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Military Equipment crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192742" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in supply crates.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1192759" id2="17" version="1065353216">I actually miss the smell of Bantha. Is that odd?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1192760" id2="17" version="1065353216">It turns out that shipping in womp rats for target practice isn't considered a &quot;priority.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1192761" id2="17" version="1065353216">My toes get cold here. I haven't experienced that since Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1192762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some of the crew needs to work on their blaster grip. It looks like I'll have to share some tricks with the five-fingers.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1192763" id2="17" version="1065353216">So many faces, but you collaborate as well as the tribes back home. Zakuul is clearly underestimating their competition.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192776" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Go Back.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194434" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's go find some excitement, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194435" id2="17" version="1065353216">The next idiot who waves his hand in my face looking for my &quot;Deadeye&quot; gets to eat my blaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194436" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your eyes on the action, Commander, and you'll never miss.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
