<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>80</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/flashpoint/star_fortress/story/local_contacts/voss_contact.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180665" id2="17" version="1065353216">When this shield generator is destroyed, the Star Fortress will be open to attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180668" id2="17" version="1065353216">My men already engage the enemy. I request the honor of joining you in battle, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180671" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll meet inside the Star Fortress shield generator bunker. Victory will be ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180674" id2="17" version="1065353216">My warriors stand ready. The time has come. We will enter the shield generator bunker. Destroy it from within.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180680" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Smuggled Goods crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180684" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done well. Now we must breach the shield generator. Burn out its heart.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180687" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seek the shield generator. Learn what you can.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180690" id2="17" version="1065353216">You honor me, Commander. We met years ago. But you wouldn't remember.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180693" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have no quarrel. Be at peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1180851" id2="17" version="1065353216">My brothers attacked you. I was too young for war. They said to hide. I obeyed, and survived their mistake.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1180852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, but I don't remember killing your brothers.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1181568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why did your brothers attack me?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1181570" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know what I can do. Don't cross me, and we'll get along fine.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181571" id2="17" version="1065353216">You killed many in the old war. My brothers were only five of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181572" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are the Death Who Walks. You will bring your ruin to our enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181573" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was during the old war. Your people allied with our enemy. The Voss.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181575" id2="17" version="1065353216">I reveal our shared past out of respect, Commander. There is no quarrel between us. My brothers fought well. You fought better.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1181578" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're saying no Gormak infants are healthy since the Star Fortress appeared over Voss?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1181580" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I'm here to do. Where do we start?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1181581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't be superstitious. It's a space station, not a curse.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our king believes it poisons us from above. The young, the old, and the weak suffer.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181583" id2="17" version="1065353216">I tell you what I know. My people are dying.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181585" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star Fortress has powerful defenses. Its shield generator must fall--and even that is guarded.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181588" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are the Commander. You will find its weakness. I mark the shield generator's location. Go there. See what must be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181591" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will gather soldiers. You must gather supplies. When all is ready, we strike as one.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1181595" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where can I find supplies?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1181596" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have time for this. Tell your soldiers to find their own supplies.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only power defeats power. Emperor Arcann took ours. You can restore it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181600" id2="17" version="1065353216">This world has many in need of your strength. Lend it to them. Take what we need in return. Bring supplies here.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181602" id2="17" version="1065353216">When we have enough, the war can begin.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1181603" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start the Voss Resistance Campaign. Completion will grant a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1181604" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start a Heroic Mission to secure supply crates.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1181605" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start an Eternal Empire Champion Duel.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1181606" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Report the Voss Resistance Campaign is complete to receive a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181609" id2="17" version="1065353216">We do not strike until prepared. My soldiers need supplies.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good! These will serve us well.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181611" id2="17" version="1065353216">A great victory for our cause! You bring us to the brink of victory, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181612" id2="17" version="1065353216">The old war still rages. It distracts this world from facing the true enemy. To destroy the Star Fortress, you should end this conflict.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181613" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is a great need for your strength, Commander. Answer the call. You will be rewarded.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Emperor Arcann's hunter pursues us. Strike it first, and we'll remain strong.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181946" id2="17" version="1065353216">I watched my brothers die by your hand. I learned from you. And now, I am ready to serve you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181956" id2="17" version="1065353216">No child of my people has been born healthy since the Star Fortress appeared in our sky. It brought a plague to my world. We must destroy it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181975" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a privilege to be your ally. Together, we'll fight the Eternal Empire. Break its curse on my world.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Return with more supplies, so we may destroy the Star Fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181997" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we're not yet ready to invade the Star Fortress shield generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1181998" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll find more supplies.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1181999" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good hunting, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's move. I'll see you inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182004" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be joining me?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182005" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just stay out of my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1182006" id2="17" version="1065353216">I live to serve your Alliance. If my death brings victory, so be it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1182007" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've prepared for this my whole life. I will not fail you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1182010" id2="17" version="1065353216">When today ends, the enemy's shield will lie in flames.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1182040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Follow me. We'll destroy this place together.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1182047" id2="17" version="1065353216">When this shield generator falls, the Star Fortress will finally be vulnerable to attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1182146" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did it, Commander! The cursed Star Fortress above my world is finally dust. The poison from the sky no longer afflicts my people.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1182154" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fate is strange. If my brothers had killed you, my world would still be cursed. It is... right... that things turned out this way.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1182157" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must press the attack before the enemy rebuilds the shield generator.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1182162" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Star Fortress must fall. Only you have the strength to do that, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1182182" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now I am free to fight at your side. Your foes are mine, now and forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1183458" id2="17" version="1065353216">A great victory! Without its shield, the Star Fortress is yours for the taking!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1183460" id2="17" version="1065353216">My orders are to coordinate the assault from Odessen. We'll meet again there, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1183465" id2="17" version="1065353216">And when that cursed fortress dies, I will serve at your side. For my people. For the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1183467" id2="17" version="1065353216">Free my world, and I will serve at your side for the rest of my days. Good hunting!</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1190387" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Start the Voss Resistance Campaign. Completion will grant a massive Influence gain.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1190401" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Do Nothing.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1190431" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now I am free to fight at your side. Your foes are mine, now and forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1190439" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Alien Research crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1190440" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Ancient Artifact crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192659" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in Military Equipment crate.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192981" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Turn in supply crates.]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192985" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Go Back.]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194439" id2="17" version="1065353216">Honor to you, Commander.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194440" id2="17" version="1065353216">My new brothers share stories and knowledge of places unknown. I wish to see these wonders one day with my own eyes.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194441" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Eternal Empire is a poison to all. We must be the cure.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194442" id2="17" version="1065353216">We face our foes as one. United, we shall succeed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194443" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Death Who Walks returns. Our enemies have time to rest, for now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194444" id2="17" version="1065353216">So many new technologies. Their marvels are endless.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194445" id2="17" version="1065353216">The galaxy is full of colors that I did not know existed. My people deserve to see the beauty beyond the stars.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1194446" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will silence the Eternal Empire and bring light to those in shadow.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
