<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>52</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/world/imperial/catalyzing_the_conversion/master_sergeant_korum.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549792" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll try to exercise a bit more caution from now on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549793" id2="17" version="1065353216">The droids appear to have lost interest in us. No doubt they're hunting down their new prey.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now the Republic can enjoy being slaughtered by these antiquated tools of destruction. I'm in your debt.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful about what you set loose in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let this happen again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549797" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wise words. I don't think I have the manpower to suffer another incident like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549799" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549800" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got to go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that those droids aren't shooting us anymore, we may be able to deactivate a few and study them more closely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549805" id2="17" version="1065353216">In time, we may even be able to replicate their technology. Belsavis is more intriguing than I feared....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549807" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let yourself get overwhelmed by those war droids. They're extremely deadly en masse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549810" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a relief to see you here, my lord. Don't mind the troops' sulking. Being reduced to cannon fodder isn't sitting well with them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549812" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope you're for hire, bounty hunter. I've had it with these troops--a few bloodbaths and they become impossible to motivate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549814" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome, sir. Ignore the troops around here... fear has made them a bit prickly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah, welcome. Don't let the troops' gloominess alarm you. Their expendability is starting to get to them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549818" id2="17" version="1065353216">This prison is far more dangerous than we originally thought... and far older.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549820" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many of these vaults were constructed thousands of years before the Republic came. Imagine the secrets inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549821" id2="17" version="1065353216">I doubt whoever built those vaults just filled them with loot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549821" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mean &quot;imprisoned&quot; inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, the contents of these vaults tend to be more dangerous than valuable, as we've discovered....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549824" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Republic didn't build the vaults, who did?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where'd they come from?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549825" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some long-forgotten alien race. They used the vaults to imprison all the vile monstrosities they didn't want running amok.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549827" id2="17" version="1065353216">So?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549828" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been blasting open the older vaults in hopes that whatever horrors were locked away might turn on the Republic guards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549830" id2="17" version="1065353216">In one vault, we discovered ancient war droids--ungrateful wretches that vaporized my men on the spot. Now they're on the warpath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549831" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you want me to destroy them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549831" id2="17" version="1065353216">So it's my problem now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Actually, no.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549834" id2="17" version="1065353216">What were a bunch of old battle droids doing locked up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why were they imprisoned?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps for exhibiting the same genocidal tendencies they've been demonstrating all week. Still, they may have their uses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549837" id2="17" version="1065353216">You brought this on yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549837" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is your fault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549838" id2="17" version="1065353216">We figured they'd attack the Republic, but most of the guards have already fled the area. They would do well to keep running.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those droids, properly controlled, would be invaluable. However, our reprogramming spikes need to be inserted manually.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549842" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lost thirty men trying to dominate the ancient droids. Validating, in a way, but these massacres are crippling us. I need your help uploading those spikes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549843" id2="17" version="1065353216">There may yet be a way to recover from your blunder.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549843" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll fix your mistake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549844" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we don't harness their power, the Republic will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549844" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't pass this up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549845" id2="17" version="1065353216">No sense killing something when you can get it to kill for you instead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549845" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a good plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549846" id2="17" version="1065353216">This situation calls for skill and subtlety, not sheer numbers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549846" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549847" id2="17" version="1065353216">It won't be easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once installed, the spikes are designed to make the droids target only people wearing Republic guard uniforms.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549850" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until then, though, those droids will be extremely hostile. If they get you in their sights, they won't let up. And they don't miss.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="549852" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd get killed. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549853" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what everyone says. I guess &quot;death and glory for the Empire&quot; just doesn't motivate people like it used to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="549855" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's more to this prison than meets the eye.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
