<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>54</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra_rep/bronze/assault_on_traken_4/sergeant_jojames.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297282" id2="17" version="1065353216">To J Company!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297283" id2="17" version="1065353216">Haha! That was fantastic!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297285" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you see that fat one run away? I think he was a lieutenant. Started crying for his mama.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297287" id2="17" version="1065353216">You guys really put the fight in our boys. Won't be any holding them back now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297288" id2="17" version="1065353216">After seeing what they can do with a Jedi covering them, there won't be any holding our boys back.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297289" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've got to stop being so blasted great. Half my boys want to quit now and go freelance.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297290" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm pretty sure every kid in this unit wants to grow up to be you today.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297291" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it pushes back the Empire, it was time well spent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="297291" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was glad to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297292" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hear hear!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="297294" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm awesome!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297295" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ha! None of my friends are going to believe I know you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297297" id2="17" version="1065353216">Come back any time you want to share a keg with J Company!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="297298" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop cheering and pay me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297299" id2="17" version="1065353216">Money? I'm a grunt. They barely pay me to eat. But I'll send a note to Command, see if they can swing anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297301" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you're always welcome to a Corellian ale on J Company!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297303" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready to see some Imperial fireworks!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297304" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's about time the Republic brought some real talent to bear!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297306" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Empire sees you all in one place, they're gonna hightail it right off Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297308" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never gotten to work side-by-side with a real Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297310" id2="17" version="1065353216">When word gets out we've got Special Forces on the ground, we're going to get a wave of new recruits!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297312" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear you can give our best and brightest a run for their money.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297314" id2="17" version="1065353216">You got any time to spare? We're about to take down the Empire's communications center, and it'd strike some real fear in their hearts if you led the charge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297315" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let the Empire see that the Jedi and Republic stand united to free Balmorra!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="297315" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hoo-wah! You need a microphone or something? Get the whole squad fired up?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297318" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Leading the charge,&quot; is hardly my specialty, but if we can frighten the Empire off, perhaps fewer lives will be lost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="297318" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will do what I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297319" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh, right, Master Jedi. Long as it's our lives we're saving, not theirs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297321" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can I turn down an offer like that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="297321" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297322" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hoo-wah! Hey, if I survive this, can I get you to sign my helmet? It'd be a kick for the guys back home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297324" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want me to lead your army?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="297324" id2="17" version="1065353216">You thought this through?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297325" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure. Never had a celebrity in the unit. It'll be good for morale.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="297327" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you want me to do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297328" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they put you on it, they obviously don't need anyone of my caliber.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="297328" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not worth my time.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Need, shmeed. I just thought you'd want to join the fun!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Traken-4's an Imperial base, heart of the Empire's Balmorra communications. We're gonna hit it hard and fast, take it out before they warn anyone the Republic's landed.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297333" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're in, you can go ahead and take out their artillery before we move in with full strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="297334" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get your men ready. They won't have much of a window.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="297334" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll go right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297335" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're chomping the bit, don't you worry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="297337" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll try to fit it in.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297338" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll be watching. Minute you take out the first ring of defenses, I'll give the signal.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297340" id2="17" version="1065353216">Use this. It should jam the frequency for their AA guns, sensors, comm relays. The whole shebang.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we move in and boom! Imperial jelly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="297344" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too risky. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297345" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then it's all up to J Company!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="297347" id2="17" version="1065353216">This planet's gonna be ours by sunset!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="492563" id2="17" version="1065353216">You got any time to spare? We're about to run the Empire off Balmorra for good, and it'd strike some real fear in their hearts if you led the charge.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="492564" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whoever holds the Balmorran Arms Factory holds Balmorra. Empire thinks they can retake the factory by finishing an abandoned access corridor.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="492566" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got the ordnance to destroy the monster drill they're using. You take out the Imps' defenses along the way, and we'll hit the drill together.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
