<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>234</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/daily_area/oricon/imperial/lord_hargrev.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115483" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm attempting to warn the Imperial fleet, but they may not intercept in time. You are the only chance to stop those ships.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115486" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where is your ship hiding? Perhaps we shall destroy that, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115489" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have much time. I recovered the computer core, but the Dread Masters are launching an attack on the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115490" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast it all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115492" id2="17" version="1065353216">That explains the signals we're picking up. Hyperdrives coming online not far from the fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115495" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get the gate codes off the computer. We're going into the fortress next.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115496" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, of course. But please--do not let the Dread Masters' ships reach our worlds. What they would do... is unthinkable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115498" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hurry as you wish. But you will watch your planets burn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115502" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of your acolytes has gone mad. Your protection may be... wanting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115504" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am concentrating, I am trying to focus--what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115507" id2="17" version="1065353216">The watchtower. That's where we'll find the gate codes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115510" id2="17" version="1065353216">The troops are almost ready. We can secure a route to the fortress and protect your flank if you act as vanguard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115512" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we still need a way through the fortress gates. According to our recon data, they're built with highly dense materials: conventionally unbreakable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we circumvent them? How are they controlled?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115514" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's an outer watchtower with command of the gates. Its computers are built with ancient Sith and Rakata technologies--we scanned it from orbit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115516" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the Dread Masters' designs--if you can seize the machine core, I can extract the codes needed to attack the fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115518" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll have our troops start moving on the fortress itself. Bring us the machine core and and they'll strike at your command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115521" id2="17" version="1065353216">The threats have been dealt with, and the Dread Masters' technology neutralized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115522" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115524" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know, all my life, I aspired to heights of cruelty and passion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115526" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the Dread Masters... they went too far. We went too far. Passion without humanity is meaningless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shall I have Maiya salvage what you didn't destroy? I'm sure someone clever could make use of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Send a squad to gather what's left. Let's not let the Dread Masters' skills go to waste.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115529" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed. Salvage the tech.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115530" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters build weapons for their sick satisfaction--not to win wars. There's nothing we can learn from them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115530" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. It's pointlessly cruel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115531" id2="17" version="1065353216">So be it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115537" id2="17" version="1065353216">Breathe of the spores. Feel your mind crackle in perfect magnetic radiance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115539" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our devices transform worlds so that the very ground produces fear. Primitive, biological instinct.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115542" id2="17" version="1065353216">You only delay what must be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115545" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is the legacy of Dread Master Styrak. We feel the void he has left.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115546" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every world will be lush with terror.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115547" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every moment you stay, you come closer to understanding our vision.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115550" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is base--whatever you've done, it's made the soldiers less susceptible to hallucinations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115555" id2="17" version="1065353216">We just picked up a power signature near your location. Be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115558" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where do they come from? Can you find it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115561" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are they not beautiful? My deadly creations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115562" id2="17" version="1065353216">A true weapon not only kills. It terrifies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Accept them. Let them embrace you. Let them pierce you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115566" id2="17" version="1065353216">You believe my creations are vulnerable? Then go. Tear them apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115569" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until next time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Something dangerous is out there. We must destroy it before it destroys us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115575" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive the interruption, but we should discuss our plans for the Masters' fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115577" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not yet. I sense... pain, fear, and death nearby. Two sources of power outside the fortress walls, coming for us. I see no more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay and shield us from the Dread Masters' power. If you lay out a strategy for the fortress, I'll intercept whatever's out there now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115578" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll investigate. Get ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115579" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are grateful. And we will be ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115580" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never thought I'd meet a Sith Lord who'd turned his back on atrocity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115580" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're an enlightened Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115581" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you mocking me? My hands are not clean. The things I've done... even you might cringe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115583" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's the best you can do, no wonder you lost the task force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115583" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's awfully vague.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115584" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it weren't for me, we'd all be bleeding from the ears! I'm all that stands between us and insanity!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115586" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you should concentrate on shielding our minds, my lord.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115588" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can you find out what's out there before we're all slaughtered? We'll have the soldiers ready to attack soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115589" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get it done. I'll make sure whatever's out there doesn't come any closer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115594" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once, I thought myself a monster. I played in rivers of blood and laughed as innocents quaked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yet when I touched the Dread Masters, I saw that my darkness was but a shadow of true depravity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115598" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you want us to trust you because, what... you've been redeemed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps you'd rather return to the field to have your skull split?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115602" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better than working for Sith dogs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't fear the Dread Masters. Fear me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Obey. You have no choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115605" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hold your life in my hand. You will march because I demand it. You will fire on our enemies because the alternative is unthinkable. Am I understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. I understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115608" id2="17" version="1065353216">I admire your charm.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever our differences, we all came to this world to stop the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115609" id2="17" version="1065353216">We both have the same goal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115611" id2="17" version="1065353216">We failed to do it alone--but if we work together, we have a chance. Should we survive... we go our separate ways.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115612" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're serious? All right. Let me talk to my men.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115614" id2="17" version="1065353216">How diplomatic. Perhaps it's for the best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115615" id2="17" version="1065353216">What you were saying to them....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115616" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was true enough. In the Dread Masters, I saw a cancer. Now I recognize my own disease.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115622" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think these allies will make you stronger? They will make you weak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115623" id2="17" version="1065353216">Abandon your cause. There is only despair here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115624" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have come far since last we met. You have potential.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Submit and know purpose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115626" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will taste your fear--or we will taste your rage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115627" id2="17" version="1065353216">These soldiers are doomed. Our nightmares suffuse them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115628" id2="17" version="1065353216">The things we will show you. The humiliations you will endure....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115631" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have our new recruits. Suggest you return to camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without more soldiers, we can't move on the enemy fortress. Find them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you Lord Hargrev? Darth Marr asked me to find you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115637" id2="17" version="1065353216">What?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115639" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're the remains of the task force, yes. You'll have to forgive us--Lord Hargrev is shielding our minds from the Masters, but it takes a toll.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are there any ships still functioning? What's your current objective?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me a status report.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115641" id2="17" version="1065353216">For now? Surviving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115643" id2="17" version="1065353216">What have the Dread Masters done to you, exactly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115643" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seem... troubled, Hargrev.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115644" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's exhausted, that's all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115646" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't need to worry about my mental competence. Maiya will fill you in--I need to concentrate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115648" id2="17" version="1065353216">This operation is now under my control. I am the Emperor's Wrath, my word is law and you will obey unto death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115648" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm taking command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115649" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know who I am. Whoever you answered to before, now you serve me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115649" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm in command now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115650" id2="17" version="1065353216">My oath is to Lord Hargrev.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115652" id2="17" version="1065353216">And your feebleminded loyalty is appreciated, but we can make an exception in this case. Fill our new leader in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115654" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have experience with the Dread Masters and expertise that you need. If you want to survive, you'll take my advice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115654" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm in command now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115655" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place is a mess. I'm not Sith and I'm not a soldier, but if you want to survive you follow my directions--understood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Follow me if you want to live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Hargrev is in command here. But... as a representative of Darth Marr, you have our attention.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115658" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just get on with it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115660" id2="17" version="1065353216">Between their mental dominance and their orbital weaponry, the Dread Masters managed to annihilate our ships. The survivors regrouped here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our hope was to make one final push to the Masters' fortress, but the Dread Guard has us trapped. We don't need firepower--we need manpower to break out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are there other survivors who can reinforce you? Give you the manpower you need?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115664" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic. They came to Oricon, too--I can feel their soldiers out there. Trapped and afraid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115665" id2="17" version="1065353216">In that condition, they won't be hard to bring to our side. Especially not when we share an enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115665" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll press them into service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Marr called you a sadist. But you sound like you're sympathizing with Republic troops.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115666" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does their fear bother you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115667" id2="17" version="1065353216">My tastes are not at issue here! Those soldiers are.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115669" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is your plan? Round up our bleeding enemies and hope they sign on?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115669" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's your best idea?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115670" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're desperate, they have no hope of rescue and we share a common enemy. You can mold them like clay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115672" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's murder out there. The Dread Guard have machine support--enough to cut our reconnaissance into pieces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115674" id2="17" version="1065353216">How long before we're overrun?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hours, at best. Point taken.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115678" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will shield you against the madness as well as I can. Bring us the soldiers we need to survive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115682" id2="17" version="1065353216">Three more gone, my lord. Two commandos took knives to one another--hallucination-induced psychosis, apparently--and Major Strix fled camp.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115684" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stupid, stupid... knives? They can't even resist carving one another like roasts?!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115686" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sorry. I know the things they saw... I can feel the Dread Masters, I can push them, but I can't stop it all. I'm so sorry, Maiya....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115689" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have come far too late.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115691" id2="17" version="1065353216">By Oricon's next sunrise, your worlds will burn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115694" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not listen to the voices. Do not let them speak to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115840" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay and help as long as you wish. I'll have my men prepare a meal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115843" id2="17" version="1065353216">The madness is gone. I can feel it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115845" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can feel it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115846" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters are dead--all of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115847" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Guard are falling back. We should target any surviving clusters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115849" id2="17" version="1065353216">Learn to celebrate, Maiya.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115851" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were inside. What was it like? Were you... tempted at all? To live as a union of fear, without mortal inhibitions....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115852" id2="17" version="1065353216">What I saw stays with me. Understand?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115852" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's not your concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115855" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said it before. When you look into the face of darkness, there's nothing tempting about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115855" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a palace of horrors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115856" id2="17" version="1065353216">No, I suppose not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115858" id2="17" version="1065353216">They wanted to crush my spirit. To unmake me. But I would have been powerful, unchained by responsibility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tempted? Yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Find a planet somewhere and forget this war. You might come close enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115861" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're also getting strategic updates from Darth Marr. Border sectors where he needs reinforcements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115863" id2="17" version="1065353216">And so the bloodshed must continue. At least the cancer in the Sith is gone; the Empire is a healthy body once again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115865" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your final instructions for Oricon?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115866" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fortress and the palace are yours. Take the Dread Guard, if they surrender, and build whatever stronghold you like.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seize any secrets you find.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115867" id2="17" version="1065353216">How... unexpectedly generous. I assure you, my memory is quite keen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Destroy what the Dread Masters created. Don't let the cancer come back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Purge the evil from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115870" id2="17" version="1065353216">My &quot;perspective&quot; is what haunts me. But I take your meaning.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115872" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give Darth Marr my best next time you see him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115876" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now then, Maiya. We have much work to do... and our friends have much more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115877" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force serve you well, Lord Wrath. We live and die in your master's name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115879" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give Darth Marr my best, Dark Lord. I wish you well in your dealings with the council.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115881" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give Darth Marr my best, my friend. You walk a fine line, but I wish you well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115883" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give Darth Marr my best, hunter. I doubt you'll want for work any time soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now come, Maiya. We have much work to do... and our friend has much more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115889" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hear them buzzing in my mind. They're waiting in the palace for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115912" id2="17" version="1065353216">The fortress is open. Tear the Dread Masters apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get to the fortress. Kill them for all of us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115919" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Wrath. It is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dark Lord. It is done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115923" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are ready, my mysterious friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115925" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is done, hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115927" id2="17" version="1065353216">The gates to the fortress are open. Squads of Republic and Imperial troops are holding a path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115929" id2="17" version="1065353216">And now that you've neutralized the Dread Masters' attack, I expect you'll go for the throat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop them. Show the Empire that their depravity leads to weakness, not strength. Make sure no Sith is ever tempted to follow their path.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115932" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I'm finished, no one will remember the Dread Masters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115932" id2="17" version="1065353216">I intend to do so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115933" id2="17" version="1065353216">I gather you're not coming to the fortress with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115933" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're staying to meditate?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115934" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not here to debate the Sith Code or to set an example. Battles are won through superior weapons and tactics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115934" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is war, not philosophy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115935" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ultimate weapon is the sharpened spirit of a Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115937" id2="17" version="1065353216">My acolytes and I will confront the enemy through the Force as you break their flesh. Perhaps we may even be useful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115939" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115941" id2="17" version="1065353216">You dared to stop our launch. For every Dread Guard killed, we will destroy one of your soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115943" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless you wish to bargain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell us a secret. Tell us what you fear and we will spare your servants.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115946" id2="17" version="1065353216">My soldiers have already cleared a path and your fortress stands open. Do what you want; it's too late to stop me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115946" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let them die. I need no one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115947" id2="17" version="1065353216">Die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115949" id2="17" version="1065353216">I saved as many as I could. I tried.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115951" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soon. You will join us soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115953" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop it. You want to know something I'm afraid of? I'll tell you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115953" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine--I'll tell you something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115954" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speak. Name your fear!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Darth Baras sought to use me as his weapon. I overcame him. But there are others, and I wonder if I can defy them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115955" id2="17" version="1065353216">Becoming someone's tool.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115956" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have been a slave, an apprentice, a collector of dark spirits. I have claimed power from nothing. But death itself still pursues me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every day I lie and manipulate. Every day I risk losing sight of my purpose and forgetting why I even do this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgetting my identity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115958" id2="17" version="1065353216">One day, if I live long enough, I won't be fast or strong or sharp. I'll be a Grand Champion whose time is past.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115958" id2="17" version="1065353216">My skills fading away.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115959" id2="17" version="1065353216">There aren't a lot of people in this galaxy who are close to me. The thought of losing them... yes, it scares me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Losing people I care for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let that thought suffuse you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115961" id2="17" version="1065353216">I make sacrifices, I endure misery, but I accomplish what I set out to do. Someday it may not be enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115961" id2="17" version="1065353216">Failing to achieve my goals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115962" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will suffice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough humiliations. You will join us soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blood and failure will stain you. Then you will be ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115967" id2="17" version="1065353216">Birth. Pain. Fear. Death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115968" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imagine the Citadel burning. Riots in Kaas City. The heads of Sith and slaves will roll as madness overwhelms all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our chemicals will mix with the pollutants of Nar Shaddaa. So many people, so afraid, so close together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115971" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters have aborted the launch, and we've sent a warning about any ships that might have escaped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115973" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're ready to move on the fortress at your command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116453" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire cannot endure without the Emperor's guidance. When he returns, then we will be strong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116453" id2="17" version="1065353216">First we need our Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116454" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. All glory to the Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116456" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters may be gone, but the future of the Sith is uncertain. There are many visions, and only one Order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116456" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Sith are still fragmented.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116457" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we trust the Dark Council to bring unity, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116459" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire has an opportunity--but reforms must be made, or we'll be undone by the same mistakes as always.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116459" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire still must change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, well... we shall see if the Dark Council agrees.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116462" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dread Masters were never the worst of your problems. You want to survive the Republic, get your acts together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116462" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your Empire is still troubled.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116463" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not a Darth or a council member. Your voice reaches more powerful ears than mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116465" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about you? You had your moment, when you saw the darkness inside you... what will you do with that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116465" id2="17" version="1065353216">And are you still &quot;redeemed&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116466" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't intend to start a clinic for war orphans, if that's your concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116468" id2="17" version="1065353216">As for the rest... I don't know. I have much to think about without a cloud of madness around me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Think of these civil wars as a deck-clearing exercise. Those of us who survive are better off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1116470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Conflict makes us stronger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116471" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree, but that doesn't mean disease is to be cultured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116473" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of these days, the Empire will need the Dread Masters' power--no matter what Darth Marr and the others believe. Just remember who assisted you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1116475" id2="17" version="1065353216">And as for you, Lord Hargrev... don't forget the lessons you've learned. The Empire needs Sith with perspective.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118211" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will see it done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118214" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're mine, now. If I say &quot;march&quot;, you'll march. If I say &quot;fight&quot;, you'll fight. If you do anything else, you'll die. Got it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118227" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time is against us. The Dread Masters' forces must be stopped.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
