<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>7</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/daily_area/oricon/imperial/mission_terminal.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1117216" id2="17" version="1065353216">OFFICIAL IMPERIAL DIRECTIVE
FROM: Maiya Vix, Aide to Lord Hargrev

Some Republic forces have survived the destruction of their fleet but remain trapped within the wreckage nearby. They're desperate, and they share a common enemy with us in the Dread Masters. 

Free the Republic soldiers. One way or another, we'll convince them it's in their best interests to assist us.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1117217" id2="17" version="1065353216">OFFICIAL IMPERIAL DIRECTIVE
FROM: Maiya Vix, Aide to Lord Hargrev

Lord Hargrev has sensed two sources of dark power that threaten to hamper our progress into the Dread Masters' fortress. One source emanates from a seemingly unaffected area of the moon.

Please investigate the area and eliminate the energy source, as well as any other threats that emerge.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1117218" id2="17" version="1065353216">OFFICIAL IMPERIAL DIRECTIVE
FROM: Maiya Vix, Aide to Lord Hargrev

One of two sources of dark power sensed by Lord Hargrev originates from an area transformed by dark side corruption. Lord Hargrev is certain the power source is helping to intensify the waves of madness affecting our team here on Oricon.

Please investigate the area and put an end to the cause of this corruption.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1117219" id2="17" version="1065353216">OFFICIAL IMPERIAL DIRECTIVE
FROM: Maiya Vix, Aide to Lord Hargrev

A computer located within the fortress watchtower holds the key to breaching the outer gates. Lord Hargrev's thorough understanding of ancient technologies will allow him to interface with it, but he cannot abandon our support staff to do so.

Retrieve the watchtower computer core so that Lord Hargrev may extract the gate codes needed to breach the Dread Masters' fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1117220" id2="17" version="1065353216">OFFICIAL IMPERIAL DIRECTIVE
FROM: Maiya Vix, Aide to Lord Hargrev

The Dread Masters' forces intend to launch an attack on the Empire. For obvious reasons, this cannot be permitted.

Defeat the Dread Guard and disable their ships to prevent them from striking at Dromund Kaas.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1117221" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aid the Empire by completing the following daily missions on Oricon:

[DAILY] Fallen Forces
[DAILY] False Paradise
[DAILY] Dread Engines
[DAILY] The Tower's Core
[HEROIC 2+] Preemptive Strike
[AREA] Oricon Decimation</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1125558" id2="17" version="1065353216">OFFICIAL IMPERIAL DIRECTIVE

Please see courier droid D5-F2 on Vaiken Spacedock for important details regarding an urgent mission.

For the Empire.

[PRIORITY] This mission begins the story on Oricon. Advancing the story will unlock repeatable daily missions.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
