<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>76</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/daily_area/oricon/imperial/station_comm_officer.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115188" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is station comm control. Routing a message from Darth Marr.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115189" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Wrath, this is station comm control. We have a message on your frequency from Darth Marr.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115190" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dark Lord, this is station comm control. Priority message for you from Darth Marr.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115191" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is station comm control. We have an incoming transmission from Darth Marr--your identity isn't on file, but the computer thinks you're authorized to decrypt....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115192" id2="17" version="1065353216">Put it through and erase any record from your comm log.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115193" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunter. This is station comm control--we have a priority message from Darth Marr.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115194" id2="17" version="1065353216">Put it through.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115195" id2="17" version="1065353216">No niceties today, Wrath. My time is short.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115197" id2="17" version="1065353216">No politics today. My time is short.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115199" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have little time, so I ask you to listen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115201" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too many betrayers have attempted to seize power of late. Darth Malgus's men are finished, but the Dread Masters endure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115203" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since you freed them on Belsavis, their madness has driven them to conquest. A dozen systems have fallen; you've seen their power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115204" id2="17" version="1065353216">I killed one on Darvannis. I know what they're capable of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115205" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since you freed them on Belsavis, their madness has driven them to conquest. We slew one on the planet Darvannis, yet five remain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115206" id2="17" version="1065353216">I take it something has changed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115207" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were the Emperor's favored servants, yet idolized fear above the Empire. Now we have found their fortress on Oricon, a remote moon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115208" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Emperor went silent, the Dread Masters should have bowed to me. Now they will have no choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115208" id2="17" version="1065353216">They will soon obey my power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115209" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no loyalty in their hearts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115211" id2="17" version="1065353216">Power such as theirs cannot be contained. It rises until obliterated, as you well know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115211" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their betrayal was inevitable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115212" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their insanity goes too far. It breeds destruction, not glory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115214" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you expose them? And what brought them to that moon?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115214" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why Oricon? Why now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115215" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interrogation of a Dread Guard revealed the truth, but we know little of the moon itself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115217" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've met a lot of crazy Sith--the Dread Masters are something else altogether. This moon is their base?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115217" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're a bunch of lunatics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115218" id2="17" version="1065353216">We are certain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115220" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Masters are still Sith. Seeing they've lost, they might rejoin the Empire--or at least submit to a superior force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115220" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any chance they may surrender?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115221" id2="17" version="1065353216">The time for diplomacy is past, and the superiority of our force remains to be seen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115223" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we know where they are, it's time to turn that moon into dust. Or have things soured already?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115223" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then don't wait to attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115224" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic moved before we did, sending a full fleet to Oricon. Its armada was undone by the Masters' powers of fear and madness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115226" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our task force followed--a rapid strike deployment led by one Lord Hargrev, upon the insistence of Darth Rictus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115228" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hargrev is a braggart and a sadist, but he has studied our foe. He believed that he and his acolytes could shield our task force from the Masters' power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115229" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why do I suspect Hargrev overestimated himself?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115229" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me guess: He was wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115230" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never heard of Hargrev. Where's he come from? What's he really capable of?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115230" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's Hargrev's background?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115231" id2="17" version="1065353216">He studied under Lord Silthar; had he spent less time in his &quot;agony dungeon,&quot; he might have become a Darth long ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115233" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given my experience with the enemy, why wasn't I consulted about your task force?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115233" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should have been informed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115234" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were needed elsewhere, and military decisions are mine to make. But... I may have been in error.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115236" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have heard nothing since Hargrev's ships arrived in-system twelve hours ago. Either his forces were defeated... or Hargrev has betrayed us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Either way, the Dread Masters will sense weakness and counterattack. I have no forces to spare--you represent our last chance to stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115239" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have an army at the ready, Lord Marr. What exactly do you want?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115239" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you asking of me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115240" id2="17" version="1065353216">You presume I desire to mend your mistakes. But that is not my role.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115240" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am not your weapon to wield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115241" id2="17" version="1065353216">Challenge me before the council if you wish. But turn away, and Korriban itself may burn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115243" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am your equal on the Dark Council, Lord Marr. I may have other affairs to attend to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115243" id2="17" version="1065353216">You assume too much of me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115244" id2="17" version="1065353216">These matters threaten our very survival. Besides--I expect you will seize the chance to uncover the Masters' secrets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115246" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you need my resources to protect the Empire, you'll have them. But don't treat me as a mindless assassin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115246" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not your thug, Marr.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115247" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you have operatives capable of infiltrating enemy territory, send them. My interest is not in our egos, but our survival.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115249" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's your money--but if I spent as much time hunting Jedi as I did your kind, you might be winning this war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115249" id2="17" version="1065353216">I seem to kill a lot of Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115250" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115252" id2="17" version="1065353216">I freed the Dread Masters. They never did show gratitude. Why shouldn't I be the one to stop them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115252" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a score to settle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115253" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even you cannot slay the Masters singlehandedly. If you can reach Oricon, however, you may find some remnant of Hargrev's task force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115255" id2="17" version="1065353216">If all else fails... send any warning you can of the Dread Masters' strengths. Perhaps then we can limit our losses to mere sectors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115256" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well. Forward whatever data you have and await my word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118147" id2="17" version="1065353216">Best of luck to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118148" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are no incoming messages at this time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since their... release from Belsavis, their madness has driven them to conquest. A dozen systems have fallen; you've seen their power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118150" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since their... release from Belsavis, their madness has driven them to conquest. We slew one on the planet Darvannis, yet five remain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118217" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. Forward whatever data you've got and wait for my signal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118465" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will make sure the Dread Masters' treason ends now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1118465" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1126232" id2="17" version="1065353216">Dread Masters = defeated // D5-F2 = in awe of you</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1126233" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oricon operations = ongoing</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1126234" id2="17" version="1065353216">D5-F2 = unable to find incoming messages // You = try again later</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1126238" id2="17" version="1065353216">Important message = incoming // You = please stand by....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
