<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>43</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/daily_area/oricon/imperial/watchtower_computer.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Long ago, you sought to free us from Belsavis prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since then you have grown. In mind and body; in skill and in spirit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115065" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meanwhile, we have tasted death. On Darvannis, you ripped Lord Styrak from our union.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Meanwhile, we have tasted death. On Darvannis, the Empire slew Lord Styrak and ripped him from our union.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115069" id2="17" version="1065353216">From our wound bleeds our memories; our names; our ambitions. We tasted oblivion, and it drowns us. Like you, we are changing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talk to me, Dread Masters. Why are we here? Why are you telling me this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115070" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is it that you want?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115071" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand. You're in pain. If we work together, it doesn't have to last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115071" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I can help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115072" id2="17" version="1065353216">Poor Masters. Do you miss your brother? Come face me, and I'll reunite you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115072" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not impressing me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115073" id2="17" version="1065353216">You do not comprehend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115075" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once, we desired an empire. Now, with the death of Lord Styrak, we are going mad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115077" id2="17" version="1065353216">The wound must be healed. Our union requires a sixth--or there will be only chaos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115079" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have ruined worlds together. Alone, your deeds are legendary, and legions tremble at your names.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115081" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of you may possess strength enough to join us. Your mortal dreams will be our feast, and our union will grow strong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115082" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were the Emperor's Wrath; you drove a Jedi to the brink of madness and strike terror into the hearts of millions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115084" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soon you will join us as our Scion of Terror. We will feast on your dreams, and our union shall be strong again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115085" id2="17" version="1065353216">You turned on the Emperor and the Empire. You are not worthy of my allegiance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115085" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't join traitors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115086" id2="17" version="1065353216">You of all Sith know power and darkness and secret terror. Once a wretched slave, you became a being worthy of worship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115088" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now you will join us and we will feast upon your dreams as we grow strong together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115089" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can promise power--but I will never be a slave again. And you cannot defy me forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115089" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to control me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115090" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will not deny the truth when you have been humbled, stripped of all but fear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115092" id2="17" version="1065353216">You walk in darkness, spreading fear by whispers. You learned the power of Lord Jadus, who sees much that we see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115094" id2="17" version="1065353216">You stalk your prey, using terror as well as weapons. How many of your victims ran at the sound of your name?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115096" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are not Sith, but you may join us, serve us as Kephess did. We will feast upon your mortal dreams, and our union will be strong again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115097" id2="17" version="1065353216">You brainwash your servants. I know how that works--and you don't want to try it on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115097" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one controls me again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115098" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your resistance cannot last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115100" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make it simple: You want a bounty hunter, you offer to pay. But I doubt you have enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115100" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a pretty weak deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115101" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is my offer to you: Open your fortress and accept that you've lost. Your lives will be spared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115101" id2="17" version="1065353216">One chance: Surrender.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115102" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pointless words.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115104" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I were to say yes--if I were to accept a part in your &quot;union&quot;--how would we begin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1115104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's suppose I did join you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115105" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must first be degraded. You must be humbled and humiliated, stripped of all but fear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115107" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even now, our ships prepare to launch and deliver our devices to other worlds--Dromund Kaas, Nar Shaddaa, and Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115109" id2="17" version="1065353216">Populations will be infected and planets overgrown. Mothers will kill daughters as soldiers weep in terror.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1115111" id2="17" version="1065353216">All you love and prize will fall. You will try to stop our ships and fail. Then you will be ready to join us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1118208" id2="17" version="1065353216">Long ago, we learned of your abilities in the Belsavis prison.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
