<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>104</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/rishi/class/consular/master_oa.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time I saw myself out. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Barsen'thor. The equipment is ready--try to relax during the brain scan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136826" id2="17" version="1065353216">The crystal matrix is developing, but it has to anchor itself on your experiences and knowledge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136828" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll ask you questions as the Force guides me. The holocron will record your answers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ask your questions, Master O'a.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136829" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's begin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136830" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force grants you visions, and you ask me about them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136830" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sort of questions?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136831" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just about. I've been doing this a long time; don't worry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Swear not to repeat what you hear. The galaxy may not be ready for my teachings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136832" id2="17" version="1065353216">My responses must be secret.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136833" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's the role of the holocron to share your words and thoughts with those you'd choose. I won't share them with anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136834" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then begin.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136835" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic may not fall tomorrow--but in a thousand futures, it falls eventually, one way or another.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136837" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see a half-trained Jedi in the forests of Sarkhai, where your apprentice bore your holocron after your death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136839" id2="17" version="1065353216">The half-trained Jedi wants weapons to fight those who destroyed the Republic. She wants vengeance. What answer do you give?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136840" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've fought every day since I became a Jedi. But nothing good comes of vengeance. I can help her control her emotions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136840" id2="17" version="1065353216">She must fight without anger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136841" id2="17" version="1065353216">So she learns, and she fights, and she wins victories and dies. I can't see if the Republic is restored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136843" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've no desire to show people how to kill. Let me teach her to heal the galaxy, not cause more bloodshed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136843" id2="17" version="1065353216">I teach diplomacy and healing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136844" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a difficult path for her, but she walks it well in the end. She teaches others. She learns her enemies aren't her enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136846" id2="17" version="1065353216">Teach her of the Rakata and the Esh-kha. Show her the galaxy's great weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136846" id2="17" version="1065353216">The old war machines are hers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136847" id2="17" version="1065353216">So she makes war, and stars die. Her name is etched in history, at least for a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136849" id2="17" version="1065353216">In another time, I see a Sith find your holocron. He loathes you. Your soldier died to defeat his great-grandsire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136851" id2="17" version="1065353216">He seeks to learn what made you strong; walk your path on the now-ruined world of Tython. Will you guide him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136852" id2="17" version="1065353216">If he walks my path, sees what I've seen and learns what I've learned, then the galaxy will have nothing to fear from him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes. There is wisdom in truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136853" id2="17" version="1065353216">He does see what you saw, but he resists it--he kills--before the lesson takes. In the end, though, he redeems his home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136855" id2="17" version="1065353216">No. He doesn't even understand what he's looking for. My teachings aren't for him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136855" id2="17" version="1065353216">He is not ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136856" id2="17" version="1065353216">His fury is something to behold--but he never grows strong. He dies in battle, unmourned, unremarkable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136858" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll show him my path in all its peril. If he survives, he'll emerge stronger. We gain enlightenment through fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136858" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'll find death or growth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136859" id2="17" version="1065353216">He does walk your path, and he does survive. He's not Sith, by the end. He spreads your ways to the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136861" id2="17" version="1065353216">You already have many titles: Jedi Master, Barsen'thor, Herald. You could bear others: Seneschal, Hierophant of the Jal Shey, Betrayer of Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136863" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which will you choose as your legacy? When your holocron is activated, how will it name itself?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136864" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was named Barsen'thor, Warden of the Order, by the Jedi Council. I aspire to be worthy of the name. It's how I'd like to be remembered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136864" id2="17" version="1065353216">My duty is as Barsen'thor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136865" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not my titles. I'm a person, nothing more or less, and my real name will do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136865" id2="17" version="1065353216">No titles. Just my true name.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136866" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've sought knowledge and understanding in the galaxy's darkest places. I am more than a Jedi. Let them remember every facet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every title is important.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we're done. You've got yourself a holocron; now all you need to do is spend your life filling it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136869" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know where your next fight is, my friend. I don't know if any of us will make it through the year.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136871" id2="17" version="1065353216">But if I outlast you, I promise to protect what we built today, if I can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136872" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've done me a great kindness. It's good to know that whatever happens, I'll leave behind something of value.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136872" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Master O'a.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136873" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's my privilege to serve a Council member.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136875" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a Jedi Master. I could use you at my side--there's a battle coming to Rishi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136875" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay and fight with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136876" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm clumsy with a lightsaber and frankly a bit of a coward. On Tython, at least I can do some good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136878" id2="17" version="1065353216">It won't matter in the end. Holocrons are memories, and memories fade. Only the living count.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136878" id2="17" version="1065353216">Legacies never last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136879" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps. But soon, memories may be all that remain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136881" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136882" id2="17" version="1065353216">And you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prepare your mind. I'll make sure I'm ready here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ah! Barsen'thor! You know how long I've been meaning to find you? Kept hoping we'd do this on Tython.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136888" id2="17" version="1065353216">But when the Force gets pushy--says &quot;Be on Rishi in three days! You'll know why!&quot;--well, I make an extra effort. And here you are!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136889" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're Master O'a?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136890" id2="17" version="1065353216">That I am, here to help build your holocron. Can't disappoint Lara Cordan when she's trying to form the New Rift Alliance!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136892" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, or the first of the Esh-kha neo-Savants, a century or so from now. He'll need good advice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those aren't guesses. You've had such visions through the Force?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136893" id2="17" version="1065353216">You saw that in the future?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136894" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of my talents, but it's not always a blessing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136896" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the future demands my holocron, then far be it from me to get in the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then let's not disappoint.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136897" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like you, Barsen'thor. Shall we get to work, then?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136898" id2="17" version="1065353216">If those are visions, what you've seen can change; the future is ours to reshape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Prophecies are meaningless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136899" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, I understand how volatile the future can be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136901" id2="17" version="1065353216">These days I see mostly darkness, dead planets... lots of ways the future could go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still, if anyone survives this war, they'll need your holocron to rebuild! Ready to start?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136904" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do we do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136905" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are some nuances. It's not just a recorded message--it's an interactive program, a reflection of your mind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136907" id2="17" version="1065353216">A holocron can speak, answer questions... it can't think, but it will have the knowledge and memories you provide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136908" id2="17" version="1065353216">On Tython, I worked with our ancestors' teaching holograms. On Coruscant, I recovered the Noetikons, which contained recordings of multiple Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136908" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've used holocrons before.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136909" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Noetikons! Fabulous devices. You understand, then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your expertise in holocrons--where does it come from?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136911" id2="17" version="1065353216">How'd you learn to build them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Habit of tinkering in my youth and a very stern Master who made me fix what I broke. But it is my calling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136914" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the holocron only contains what I record, what if I record a lie?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Suppose I record falsehood?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136915" id2="17" version="1065353216">It might still work, or it might destabilize the personality matrix, crash the whole system. Try not to lie.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136917" id2="17" version="1065353216">First thing is to scan your brain, establish a baseline. For that, we need you at a very particular level of consciousness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136919" id2="17" version="1065353216">On Tython, you'd use a meditation chamber to achieve a &quot;Susheer State&quot; of serenity. But every culture has similar rituals--we'll make do with what Rishi provides.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136920" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Rishii people must have traditions for reaching higher states of consciousness. What do we know of them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136920" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do the natives meditate?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136921" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't know much about the Rishii people. What's meditative for them could end up killing me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could that be dangerous?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136922" id2="17" version="1065353216">Granted, but the odds of it going that wrong seem slim. I did some reading--found a Rishii shamanic blessing that should work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136924" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just once, I'd like to visit another planet without indulging in superstitious gibberish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1136924" id2="17" version="1065353216">More primitive solutions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136925" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you're volunteering to return to Tython, I'm more than willing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136926" id2="17" version="1065353216">Speak, O'a. Tell me about the Rishii techniques.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136927" id2="17" version="1065353216">I did some reading. There's a Rishii shamanic blessing similar to one used by the Jawas of Tatooine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136929" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll walk you through it--it starts with the gathering of kishu reeds. Wear gloves if you don't want scars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anything else?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136931" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Susheer State attunes your mind to the Force. That could mean dreams, visions, of the past and future. Embrace them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136933" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take you through each step on the comm, but best you make this journey alone. When you're finished, we'll begin construction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not now, please!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
