<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>16</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/02/rishi/class/consular/transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136744" id2="17" version="1065353216">The reeds are the structure of life. Now they burn, and the smoke flows inside you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136746" id2="17" version="1065353216">Structure and form is bequeathed to the intangible air, the unseen mind. Your thoughts gain perfect shape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136748" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were the best I ever knew. Goodbye, Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136750" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no life. There is the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136752" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136754" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have achieved a Susheer State. Come, and we will build your holocron.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136757" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let the waters rid you of everything but self. &quot;There is no emotion, there is peace.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136759" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Hand closes. The rejuvenation begins.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136761" id2="17" version="1065353216">Targeting Republic battle cruisers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now, there is a place sacred to the Rishii. Build a fire from the reeds there, and we will proceed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136766" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you've got an armful, on to the next step: Purity of body, purity of spirit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136768" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bathe yourself in the waters of Rishi. Cleanse yourself of all concerns, and let nothing trouble you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136771" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you gather the reeds, feel yourself open to your surroundings. If you hear voices through the Force, past or present, do not fear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Yuon is taking a new apprentice?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136776" id2="17" version="1065353216">The reeds represent life and the structure of life. Feel the toughness of their forms--and within, sense the flow of the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1136778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Breathe with the wind as you gather them. Smell their sap. Let the simple task calm your mind.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
