<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>426</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/companion_characters/trooper/m14x/m14x.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="63958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Affirmative!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571518" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir? How can I be of service?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="571519" id2="17" version="1065353216">You needn't worry, sir, my armored chassis is impenetrable to your touch, no matter how repetitive!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir! It is a tremendous pleasure to be here aboard your ship. And what a ship it is!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692829" id2="17" version="1065353216">A BT-7, if I'm not mistaken. One of the Pollad designs--a very fine vessel, appropriate for the Republic's best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692831" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will ride this durasteel eagle into the heart of the Empire and bring our fight for freedom to the door of the Emperor himself!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692832" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll make a great addition to Havoc.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692832" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to the team.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692833" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm proud to know that you feel that way!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692835" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll get to that as soon as our other missions are complete.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692835" id2="17" version="1065353216">Um... okay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692836" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fantastic, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692838" id2="17" version="1065353216">I really don't need a patriotic speech every five seconds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692838" id2="17" version="1065353216">Calm down, please.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692839" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course not, sir--I'm sure your patriotism is as unflinching as my own!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692841" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have loaded all pertinent data--let us proceed with our noble duty!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692845" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, I cannot describe how proud I am of Havoc Squad's accomplishments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692847" id2="17" version="1065353216">By all measurable statistics, we've had a real and significant effect on the Republic's success in the war against the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692849" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are an unparalleled leader--a warrior without equal. As long as I continue to function, I will proudly serve at your side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692850" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the finest combat droid I've ever known. I'm honored to fight with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692850" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll be glad to have you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you very much, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692853" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll always be glad to take down Imps with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Years of carnage to come.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692854" id2="17" version="1065353216">As will I, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692856" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am planning on retiring someday, Forex.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692856" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't be fighting forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692857" id2="17" version="1065353216">And when you do, I'm certain that I will receive special dispensation to carry on as your loyal bodyguard and comrade-in-arms!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692859" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someday soon, the Republic will march to victory atop the burnt husk of the Empire, with Havoc Squad leading the charge!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692865" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a trap, sir! Colonel Rebus was even more devious than I had expected!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692866" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mean it was all a setup?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692866" id2="17" version="1065353216">What happened?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692867" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're here, so I'm guessing the trap didn't work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692867" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't have been too bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692868" id2="17" version="1065353216">Affirmative--in spite of the odds arrayed against me, I still managed to prevail!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692870" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you underestimated your target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692870" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should've been careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692871" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was not alone in the deception--the SIS also believed this was a genuine opportunity to strike.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692873" id2="17" version="1065353216">All of the hints and clues that led me to Rebus were fabricated. It was all a scheme to capture my power core!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692875" id2="17" version="1065353216">As soon as I defeated the last of the Imperial security teams and confronted Rebus, he activated a special-built device that overloaded my primary energy controls. I was frozen!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692876" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you manage to turn the tables on him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692876" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you escape?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692877" id2="17" version="1065353216">How could Rebus neutralize your power core when he'd never even seen it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692877" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't seem possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692878" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't be sure, sir. Perhaps some documentation was made during my time as an unwilling accomplice to the Havoc traitors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692880" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised you got out in one piece.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692880" id2="17" version="1065353216">What a mess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692881" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a very tense situation, no doubt about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692883" id2="17" version="1065353216">As Rebus and his final few guards approached, I discovered that I still had control over a handful of secondary subsystems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692885" id2="17" version="1065353216">By manipulating those systems, I was able to trigger a full emergency shutdown and a rear servo lock, violently propelling me forward just as Rebus came to face me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692886" id2="17" version="1065353216">You actually escaped by collapsing on the guy?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692886" id2="17" version="1065353216">You fell on him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692887" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess that's one way to take someone down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692887" id2="17" version="1065353216">Creative, I'll give you that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692888" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a desperate ploy--but it was successful!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692890" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're telling me that shutting yourself off saved the day?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692890" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is insane.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Precisely, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692893" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I'd hoped, shutting down my power core caused Rebus's device to shut down as well. All systems were restored within ninety-six seconds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692895" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rebus's surviving guards were still attempting to lift me off of him at the time, so I dealt with them and carried the colonel back to base. Mission accomplished!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692896" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's definitely one for the records, Forex.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692896" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd say so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was Rebus injured when you fell on him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692897" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was he hurt?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692898" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, but luckily, Republic medical technology is the best in the galaxy--I was assured that he has a nonzero chance of speaking and walking again!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692900" id2="17" version="1065353216">These missions have to stop, Forex. They're too dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692900" id2="17" version="1065353216">This has gone too far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing is too dangerous for Havoc Squad, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692903" id2="17" version="1065353216">With Rebus in custody, the entire galaxy is a safer place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692905" id2="17" version="1065353216">It will be some time before I can locate an even more impressive target. As soon as I do, you'll be the first to know!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our opportunity has arrived, sir! We've received intelligence reports that Colonel Rebus is about to test his latest project!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692913" id2="17" version="1065353216">A secret proving ground has been established on Hoth. Security will be extensive, but nothing compared to Rebus's usual protection.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you've got your opening.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692914" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692915" id2="17" version="1065353216">How long do we have to move on this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692915" id2="17" version="1065353216">When does testing begin?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692916" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have no intelligence on the length of the testing process. I believe it would be best to act as quickly as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692918" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hate that frozen rock.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692918" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not Hoth again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692919" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's fitting that vermin would take shelter in such an inhospitable location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Neutralizing Colonel Rebus will devastate the Empire's weapons programs. Even I cannot calculate the number of lives that this mission could save.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692923" id2="17" version="1065353216">By robbing our enemies of their most despicable weapons, we will rob them of victory--ensuring freedom for generations to come!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692925" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will set out at your command, sir! By robbing our enemies of their most despicable weapons, we will rob them of victory!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir! I've found information on weapon projects that Colonel Rebus was involved in! Would you like to hear about them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692930" id2="17" version="1065353216">What has Colonel Rebus been up to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692930" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's hear it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692931" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go ahead, Forex. I've got a few minutes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692931" id2="17" version="1065353216">I guess so.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692932" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most recently, Colonel Rebus was involved in the Gauntlet superweapon that we so skillfully destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692934" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's had a hand in many other projects over the past eighteen years. The Blight Matrix, the Galactophage, Subjugation Droids--even the Plasm Resource!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Supposedly, he even designed a device that could permanently block hyperlanes, though the project was scrapped due to power limitations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692937" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know anything about Rebus's current project?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692937" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is he doing now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692938" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have no details on his current project, other than a few intelligence reports confirming that it's near completion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rebus sounds like an experienced mass murderer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692940" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's quite a career.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692941" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's unlikely that anyone in the galaxy has more experience in this field than Rebus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692943" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no way one guy could design that many weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692943" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't buy it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692944" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our reports indicate varying levels of participation in each project, though he was a key factor in all of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692946" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once his new project enters the testing phase, we will stand a much better chance of locating Rebus himself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692948" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will report to you as soon as I know more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless you know where he is, I don't want to hear about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692949" id2="17" version="1065353216">No.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh. Very well, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692956" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir? If I may ask, I was wondering about your opinion on Imperial superweapons--devices that can devastate entire fleets or worlds in a single strike. I find them intriguing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692957" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one should have weapons that powerful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Superweapons are horrific.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692958" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is a popular viewpoint, but I cannot understand it. Surely such devices could see worthwhile use in the defense of freedom!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692960" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like the sentiment, but I am interested in the science behind them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692960" id2="17" version="1065353216">The technology is interesting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692961" id2="17" version="1065353216">I feel the same way, sir! Incredible devices, turned to despicable purpose by minds incapable of morality.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692963" id2="17" version="1065353216">A superweapon or two would end this war a lot faster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692963" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish we had some.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692964" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree. These devices may be the product of twisted and sadistic minds, but they're still exceptional pieces of technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given these weapons' capabilities, I've been researching Imperial weapon designers to find a worthy target for Havoc Squad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692968" id2="17" version="1065353216">One name stands out above all others: Colonel Rebus, the head of one of the Empire's top weapons research programs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692969" id2="17" version="1065353216">What have you learned about him, Forex?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Brief me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692970" id2="17" version="1065353216">A brainy colonel sitting in a lab someplace? Easy pickings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692970" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't sound too tough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692971" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll just keep picking harder targets until you're destroyed, won't you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692971" id2="17" version="1065353216">You really are suicidal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Based on the intelligence I've collected, this operation will fall well within our squad's acceptable survival probability at 4,790 to one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692974" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have located no personal information on Colonel Rebus--not even a physical description.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692976" id2="17" version="1065353216">Over the past two weeks, however, mentions of his name on Imperial comm channels have increased in frequency by 15.2 percent. This suggests a project nearing completion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692977" id2="17" version="1065353216">No time to lose, then. Where is he?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692977" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd better act fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692978" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could take out Rebus and his new invention at the same time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like an opportunity!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692979" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is my hope, sir! A truly profound victory for the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe the Imps are chatting about how useless the guy is.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talk could mean anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692982" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would be a stark contrast with all of our available intelligence, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692984" id2="17" version="1065353216">The location of Colonel Rebus's research lab is one of the most closely guarded secrets in the Empire. No information is available as yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692986" id2="17" version="1065353216">As soon as I learn more, I'll inform you right away!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692992" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have excellent news, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Given the rigorous nature of Havoc Squad's missions, my power core has seen extensive use--and its capabilities have increased as a result.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692996" id2="17" version="1065353216">I now have access to far greater energy reserves, significantly improving the quality of my service to the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692997" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must be very proud, Forex.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="692997" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's great!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="692998" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you reached the power core's maximum output?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that the max?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not yet, sadly. But someday!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693003" id2="17" version="1065353216">You need more discipline, not more power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693003" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll just be more reckless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693004" id2="17" version="1065353216">I do not understand your meaning, sir. My designers ensured that I am the most disciplined soldier conceivable by modern science.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693006" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, sir--if I may make a request, let's engage in combat as soon as possible. I'm eager to put my new capabilities to the test!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693012" id2="17" version="1065353216">Target neutralized, sir! Lord Kavos will threaten the innocent people of the galaxy no longer!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693014" id2="17" version="1065353216">As expected, his overconfidence made his defeat all but certain. I simply took my place among the scum hoping to gain his favor, then struck at the first opportunity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693015" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll bet that got you a lot closer than you would have otherwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good thinking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Precisely, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693018" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was it a big crowd?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693018" id2="17" version="1065353216">How many were there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Counting myself, there were fifteen applicants for that Sith fool's &quot;opportunity&quot;.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693021" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised you didn't charge straight in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693021" id2="17" version="1065353216">You didn't just rush him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course not! This was a situation calling for shrewd tactics.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693024" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Kavos decided that a fight to the death would determine his champion--every man for himself. Once the fighting began, I closed in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693026" id2="17" version="1065353216">I started by grabbing a Nikto thug who was making liberal use of a flamethrower. With pinpoint accuracy, I hurled him toward Kavos, whose robes were instantly ignited!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693027" id2="17" version="1065353216">I imagine that kept Kavos's attention pretty well.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693027" id2="17" version="1065353216">A pretty good diversion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693028" id2="17" version="1065353216">It did, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693030" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wish I could've seen the look on Kavos's face.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693030" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hilarious!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693031" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would estimate that he was surprised, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693033" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised Kavos didn't spot the giant, burning Nikto heading his way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693033" id2="17" version="1065353216">That actually worked?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693034" id2="17" version="1065353216">I threw him with considerable speed, sir. Additionally, the sheer volume of flames being produced made evasion or deflection impossible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Although Kavos was thoroughly distracted, I remained cautious, and did not engage him directly. Instead, I targeted a nearby Mandalorian using a jetpack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693038" id2="17" version="1065353216">As soon as his velocity and flight vector were pointed correctly, I opened fire with my cannons, sending him barrelling into Kavos and the Nikto. The explosion did the rest.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693039" id2="17" version="1065353216">It sounds like you carried out your mission with exceptional skill.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very impressive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693040" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you very much, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Was anybody left standing when you were done?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693042" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any survivors?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693043" id2="17" version="1065353216">Negative. All surviving applicants were listed as persons of interest to the SIS, so I elected to remain and subdue them all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693045" id2="17" version="1065353216">You probably shouldn't let this one go to your head, Forex.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693045" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you got lucky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693046" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not sure I understand, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693048" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was a critical victory--our comrades are sure to take heart when they hear that a monster like Kavos has been laid low.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693050" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll begin searching for a new target at once!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693056" id2="17" version="1065353216">Success, sir! Lord Kavos has foolishly given away his position!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693058" id2="17" version="1065353216">To all who excel in the arts of death: be it known that Lord Kavos, master of combat, seeks a lieutenant to serve him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693060" id2="17" version="1065353216">I seek a worthy right hand to carry out my commands across the galaxy--and profit immensely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693062" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those who think themselves suited should present themselves at the coordinates included in this message. Come prepared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693063" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kavos had to know this would be intercepted. He isn't afraid of anything, is he?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693063" id2="17" version="1065353216">This guy's fearless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693064" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry, sir. He'll learn to fear the justice of the Republic soon enough!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693066" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who did Kavos send this message to?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693066" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where did you get this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693067" id2="17" version="1065353216">The message was broadcast freely in many underworld channels, and delivered personally to a number of high-profile bounty hunters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kavos is just trying to lure in his enemies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a trap to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693070" id2="17" version="1065353216">That might be true, sir. But no amount of planning could prepare him to face Havoc Squad!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693072" id2="17" version="1065353216">The coordinates are on Tatooine, sir. I recommend we move quickly, before Kavos can find a suitable lieutenant and move on.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693074" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693076" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll set out as soon as you give the order!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693080" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir! I've discovered the perfect target for our next operation: Lord Kavos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693082" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kavos is a marauding Sith lord responsible for countless deaths: exactly the type of dangerous scum we're uniquely qualified to eliminate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me the full brief, Forex.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693083" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693084" id2="17" version="1065353216">With pleasure, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693086" id2="17" version="1065353216">He sounds like an excellent choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693086" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693087" id2="17" version="1065353216">Going up against a Sith Lord isn't something to look forward to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693087" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're much too excited.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693088" id2="17" version="1065353216">I apologize if I seem overeager, sir. But this bloodthirsty degenerate isn't just an enemy of the Republic--he's an opportunity!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693090" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lord Kavos singlehandedly destroyed a Republic outpost on Brentaal Four, massacring its personnel. He fought and killed two Jedi Knights simultaneously!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693092" id2="17" version="1065353216">According to intelligence reports, this butcher is becoming a hero to the Empire's ravening masses. Neutralizing him will help our cause greatly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693093" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's make this a priority. Tell me as soon as we have a location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693093" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693094" id2="17" version="1065353216">What did you say about him killing two Jedi Knights?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693094" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait, go back a bit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693095" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ayesho and Nil, two renowned Jedi with years of combat experience. Lord Kavos cut them down without suffering a single injury.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693097" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't tell you how much I'm looking forward to facing this threat head-on, sir! I'm going to begin my search right away!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693098" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm still not sure this is a good idea, Forex.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693098" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll think about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693099" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then I've clearly failed to properly express the value of this mission, and I apologize!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693101" id2="17" version="1065353216">This mission will increase Republic morale, decrease Imperial morale, and save countless lives by neutralizing a murderous psychopath.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693103" id2="17" version="1065353216">As soon as I know more, I'll inform you right away, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693109" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir? I'm wondering if you'd be kind enough to share what you know about Force users?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693111" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've only been programmed with a basic knowledge of Jedi and Sith capabilities. What do you think about them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693112" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi and Sith are capable of some pretty amazing things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693112" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force is very powerful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693113" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what my records indicate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693115" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force, Jedi, Sith... they aren't my problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693115" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't think about them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693116" id2="17" version="1065353216">A common sentiment, according to my records. Many see their teachings as nonsensical, and I can't help but agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693118" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi are crazy, and the only people crazier are the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693118" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're all crackpots.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693119" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had noticed that many of their beliefs are illogical with regard to the defense of a state.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693121" id2="17" version="1065353216">I only ask because it is a commonly-held belief that so-called &quot;ordinary&quot; soldiers are no match for Force users in combat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693123" id2="17" version="1065353216">Clearly that belief is false, but it persists. I suggest that I target a notable Sith Lord and neutralize him--publicly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693124" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith are deadly, Forex--let's not take them lightly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693124" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be cautious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693125" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693127" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've always wanted to put those slimeballs in their place.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693127" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693128" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you share my enthusiasm!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693130" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll let you know as soon as I find a suitable target!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693131" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunting down a Sith lord? This is going too far, Forex.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693131" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's too dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693132" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't believe anything is too far for Havoc Squad, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693138" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been reviewing morale surveys and after-action combat effectiveness reports, and I have good news!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693140" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the period following the neutralization of the Ambassador, statistics are up throughout the Republic's armed forces!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693141" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to hear the plan is working.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693141" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's great news!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693142" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did something amazing, of course people are reacting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693142" id2="17" version="1065353216">No surprise there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693143" id2="17" version="1065353216">The plan has worked flawlessly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is there any proof that your mission is the cause?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693145" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's probably a coincidence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Proof? One of the Empire's most public figures was felled in a single stroke! What else could it be?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693148" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am concerned that we might see diminishing returns from future missions unless our targets become even more impressive, though.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693150" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad's new quarry will have to be someone truly savage--a merciless threat to all that's good and decent in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693151" id2="17" version="1065353216">This was all your idea, Forex. Target selection is up to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693151" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's your decision.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693152" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you very much, sir. I won't let you down!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693153" id2="17" version="1065353216">No matter how bad they are, there's no way they're a match for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693153" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go for it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693154" id2="17" version="1065353216">My thoughts exactly!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693156" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can't be sidetracked hunting individual targets, Forex. We have other duties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't take this too far.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693157" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, sir! I will not allow my investigations to interfere with our other operations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693159" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll have this war won in no time, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir! I am pleased to report that the mission was a complete success!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693167" id2="17" version="1065353216">Though the Ambassador had fifteen armed guards in his casino suite, I managed to storm through them all, grab the lying fool, and leap out through the window!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you really took them by surprise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very much so, sir! The enemy never had a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693171" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is the Ambassador still in one piece after that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693171" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did he survive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693174" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a lot of noise for a place that's supposed to be neutral.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds reckless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693175" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need for concern, sir! I checked with the SIS beforehand--there were no external security cams at that altitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693177" id2="17" version="1065353216">Having timed my assault perfectly, the Ambassador and I landed on a passing Ugnaught salvage scow after a mere hundred and thirty meter fall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693179" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once I had made my apologies to the proprietors of the scow, I turned my prisoner over to the SIS, and the toll of liberty rang out across the galaxy!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693180" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excellent work, Forex.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693180" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693181" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wasn't the Ambassador at least injured by that fall?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693181" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised he lived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693182" id2="17" version="1065353216">He suffered only minor injuries. Fifteen fractures, some lacerations and abrasions, and a ruptured spleen. Nothing bacta and a skilled surgical droid can't fix!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693184" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're tough, Forex, but you're going to get pummeled if you keep pulling stunts like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693184" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be more subtle next time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693185" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assure you, sir, I was in no immediate danger. All risks were thoroughly calculated several microseconds beforehand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693187" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that the Ambassador's influence won't be spewing across the galaxy, I suspect we'll see a marked improvement in Republic morale.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693189" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only problem now will be selecting an even more impressive target!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693195" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir! We've had a breakthrough! The Ambassador has been spotted!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693197" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's staying in a suite at the Star Cluster Casino on Nar Shaddaa. If I move quickly, I can take him before he's relocated!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693198" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like a plan, Forex.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693198" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perfect.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693199" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't we cause problems if you assault Imperial personnel on Nar Shaddaa?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693199" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isn't Nar Shaddaa neutral?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693200" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only if I'm caught in the act, sir--and Havoc never fails!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693202" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know if there's time for this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693202" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll see.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693203" id2="17" version="1065353216">The incredibly high risk factors demand a swift operation, sir. I'll be finished in no time!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693205" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693207" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll set out at your command, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693211" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir! I've found our first potential target for the morale improvement initiative: an Imperial propagandist known as the Ambassador.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693213" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've collected a sample of his lies for your review:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693215" id2="17" version="1065353216">Friends--the Ambassador would have you know that you needn't live in fear. You needn't bow to men who are your inferiors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693217" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the Empire, you can live a life of purpose and accomplishment, where only those most fit to rule guide our society. A life of greatness!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693218" id2="17" version="1065353216">Give me our intel on this guy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693218" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do we know about him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693219" id2="17" version="1065353216">The SIS has found no concrete data. He effectively has no personal history before becoming &quot;the Ambassador&quot;--clearly an Imperial cover-up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693221" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surely no one's falling for tripe like this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693221" id2="17" version="1065353216">Does anyone believe that junk?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693222" id2="17" version="1065353216">If it were not effective, even the fools in the Empire wouldn't bother with it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693224" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just a few seconds of that guy talking is enough for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693224" id2="17" version="1065353216">I already want him dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693225" id2="17" version="1065353216">These spurious recordings are broadcast all over the galaxy, filling people with doubts about our noble cause.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693227" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Ambassador is the public face of our enemy. Removing him will boost Republic troops' morale and combat effectiveness.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693228" id2="17" version="1065353216">As soon as you locate the Ambassador, let me know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693228" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's make it happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693229" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be the first person I notify, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693230" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe you can take him out in the middle of a broadcast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693230" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693231" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can only hope we'll be so fortunate, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693233" id2="17" version="1065353216">This guy isn't even a soldier. He's a broadcaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693233" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's not a worthy target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693234" id2="17" version="1065353216">I respectfully disagree, sir. He is a soldier, waging war on the hearts and minds of our people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693236" id2="17" version="1065353216">The SIS is actively searching for the Ambassador, but he's difficult to track down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693238" id2="17" version="1065353216">As soon as I have more information, you'll be the first to know, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693244" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir? If you have a moment, I've developed an initiative to improve morale amongst our fellow soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693246" id2="17" version="1065353216">As we both know, Havoc Squad is the finest military team ever assembled. Our triumphs prove to the public that victory is near!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693248" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, as a team, even we can only accomplish so many victories in a given amount of time. Therefore, I would like to undertake additional assignments on my own time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693249" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of additional assignments?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693249" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you have in mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693250" id2="17" version="1065353216">That isn't a simple request, Forex.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693250" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd have to think about it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693251" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm fully aware, sir! I assure you, I wouldn't ask if I didn't think the work would greatly benefit the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693253" id2="17" version="1065353216">You expect me to authorize you for solo ops?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693253" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you joking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693254" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, sir! And not just normal operations, either.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693256" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd like to coordinate with Command and the SIS to find extra targets--Imperial personnel no one else could challenge--and neutralize them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693257" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some tough wins would really get our troops fired up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693257" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a great idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure these are targets you could handle on your own?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693258" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds risky.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693259" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely, sir! My success is a mathematical and moral certainty!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693261" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc has enough work to do as it is, Forex.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693261" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693262" id2="17" version="1065353216">But sir, I could make a real difference!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693264" id2="17" version="1065353216">My calculations suggest the Republic's forces' morale would increase more than eighteen percent for each &quot;impossible&quot; target I neutralize.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Such incredible victories would demoralize the putrid citizens of the Empire as much as they would encourage our heroic comrades!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693267" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a good plan, Forex. Make it happen.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693267" id2="17" version="1065353216">I agree.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693268" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, Forex. We'll give it a shot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693268" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't hurt, I guess.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693269" id2="17" version="1065353216">It won't do the Republic much good if you get shot to pieces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693269" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could also be destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693270" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's correct, sir. My calculations have shown that the inspirational value of martyrdom is less than sixteen percent, with a maximum duration of only fourteen months.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693272" id2="17" version="1065353216">As always, we are left with no choice but absolute victory!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693274" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll inform you as soon as I locate a suitable target, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693280" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is an amazing thing to know that you are exceptional, sir. I'm sure you know the feeling, given your incredible service record.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693282" id2="17" version="1065353216">My programming, my weaponry, my armor--all state-of-the-art. And my power core--a true marvel!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693284" id2="17" version="1065353216">Other droids may look like me, or have some of my capabilities, but none of them have my power core. I'm very proud to be so unique.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693285" id2="17" version="1065353216">The differences among us are what give the Republic its strength.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693285" id2="17" version="1065353216">Individuality is important.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693286" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly, sir! Billions of unique individuals, coming together to contribute to the greater good. It's truly inspiring.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where did your power core come from, anyway?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693288" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about your power core.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693289" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know anything about its origins. All I know is it gives me the ability to be exceptional!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693291" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you ever stop talking about yourself?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693291" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're really egotistical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693292" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am always happy to discuss the Republic's achievements, and I do feel that I'm an excellent example.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693294" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see Havoc Squad in much the same way. We are set apart from other infantry teams by one thing: you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693296" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to your wise and courageous leadership, Havoc Squad is the finest military unit in the Republic. You are what makes Havoc special.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693297" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's very kind of you to say that, Forex.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693297" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you very much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693298" id2="17" version="1065353216">By analyzing our unit's strengths, we can better utilize them against our depraved enemies!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693300" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just another soldier. Nothing more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693300" id2="17" version="1065353216">I just do my job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693301" id2="17" version="1065353216">The soldiers of the Republic are all very impressive, but surely none of them can compare with you!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Flattery is a waste of time, Forex.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693303" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't suck up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693304" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agreed, sir. That's why I always speak the simple truth!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693306" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's return to the fight, sir--it's already been too long since I saw Imperial soldiers stomped into the muck where they belong!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693312" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir! Allow me to reiterate my pleasure at serving in your command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693314" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since my verbobrain was first activated, I have longed to engage the enemies of freedom directly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693316" id2="17" version="1065353216">Under your noble leadership, I can finally fulfill the mission the Republic's peerless scientists designed me for!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693317" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good that you're so enthusiastic about our mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693317" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you're happy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693318" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't take all of the credit for my enthusiasm, of course. I owe everything to my primary designer--Doctor Boab Deduun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who programmed you, Forex?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693320" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about your designers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693321" id2="17" version="1065353216">My primary systems were designed by one of the greatest scientists in the Republic: Doctor Boab Deduun!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693323" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are Republic war droids normally so eager for violence?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693323" id2="17" version="1065353216">You love killing Imps, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693324" id2="17" version="1065353216">I apologize, sir. I have no love for violence--merely a passion for annihilating all threats to our glorious society.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693326" id2="17" version="1065353216">I assure you, I was designed by one of the foremost minds in the Republic--Doctor Boab Deduun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693328" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks to Doctor Deduun, I can understand the importance of our fight, and the extent of the threats we face. And I can fight harder for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693329" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing better than fighting for a cause you believe in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693329" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to hear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693330" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't agree more, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could you introduce me to Doctor Deduun sometime?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693331" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I meet Deduun?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693332" id2="17" version="1065353216">I would be happy to do so, but Dr. Deduun's lab is highly classified--even I don't know its actual location.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693334" id2="17" version="1065353216">If an opportunity to meet him ever comes, you will be the first person I inform, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693335" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't really &quot;love&quot; the Republic, you're just designed to.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="693335" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's still just programming.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693336" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exactly, sir! And due to the sophistication of my design, my love for the Republic far exceeds what most biological beings are capable of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693338" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I've spoken enough about myself--let us return to our noble mission!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693342" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir! There are matters we should discuss privately, the next time we return to our ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693343" id2="17" version="1065353216">If possible, sir, I'd like to speak with you at our next opportunity!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693344" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need to discuss anything with you at the moment, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="693347" id2="17" version="1065353216">For the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="988644" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will remain vigilant as ever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="988645" id2="17" version="1065353216">As you wish, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="988646" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will follow your lead, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="988647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Death before defeat!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="988649" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must show no hesitation or reservation in our war against the Empire, friend--our enemy certainly won't!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="988650" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir! Allow me to reiterate my pleasure at serving in your command.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="988651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely, sir! My success is a mathematical and moral certainty!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="988652" id2="17" version="1065353216">As always, we are left with no choice but absolute victory!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="988653" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll have this war won in no time, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="988654" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad you share my enthusiasm!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="988655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing is too dangerous for Havoc Squad, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="988656" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fantastic, sir!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="988657" id2="17" version="1065353216">No Imperial will stand in our way! The Republic will triumph!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="988658" id2="17" version="1065353216">We will fight until the last Imperial lies dying at our feet!</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
