<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>208</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/spvp/components.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Laser Cannon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Standard-issue laser cannons made by BlasTech Industries are reliable and effective, if not glamorous. The BlasTech HMC-15 fires quickly and accurately at mid-range, causing moderate damage for a medium power cost.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Light Laser Cannon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Favored by pilots who like to fight at close range, Merr-Sonn's LCL-1 light laser cannons are twin-linked for high damage, and increased power consumption. Gunners should be aware that the LCL-1's damage output drops drastically with distance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Rapid-fire Laser Cannon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="764326" version="1065353216">BlasTech's Spitfire rapid-fire laser cannon is capable of delivering an unparalleled number of bolts per second for a sustained period due to its low power consumption. Its damage fall-off and poor accuracy, however, limit its effectiveness to short-range engagements.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Quad Laser Cannon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The gold standard of laser cannon design, Merr-Sonn's LCQ-4 quad laser cannon fires alternating pairs of bolts from four cannon barrels, dealing considerably more damage than standard laser cannons while maintaining formidable accuracy and rate of fire. Its biggest downside is its power consumption--a drawback Merr-Sonn is keen to downplay.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Cluster Missiles</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Renowned for their quick lock-on time, Czerka's RK-77 cluster missiles are a favorite for close-range dogfights. The missiles' small frames allow pilots to carry more ammunition into battle, though this compact design also sacrifices fuel and payload space, resulting in comparatively low range and damage potential.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Rocket Pods</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Designed to fracture, fuse and atomize enemy infrastructure and other armored objectives, rocket pods can be loaded onto ships in large quantities but lack any guidance systems--they can only be fired straight ahead. As a means of obliterating bunkers, satellites and more, Elsinore-Cordova's &quot;Pulverizers&quot; are one of the most compact and devastating varieties.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Sensor Beacon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Carbanti United Mark Six sensor beacon is an immobile, unarmed drone with long-range sensors and communication rigs. When deployed, it allows the deploying ship's squadron to detect enemies in the beacon's vicinity, and interferes with the systems of nearby hostile ships.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Sabotage Probe</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="764326" version="1065353216">GSI's LOS-0 sabotage probe droid, once launched and attached to a foe, rapidly disables maneuvering thrusters and other ship systems, dealing minor hull damage in the process. Once used primarily by bounty hunters and law enforcement to cripple fleeing ships, these devices are invaluable in the hands of expert starfighter pilots.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Targeting Telemetry</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Alibata-Unyo's advanced sensor system includes custom hardware and software that allow an equipped ship to temporarily boost its sensor range and targeting capabilities. In addition, the system's sensor sweep is so precise that it eliminates any cloaking effects on nearby enemy ships.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Sensor Probe</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The perfect reconnaissance tool for cautious pilots, Carbanti's Mark Three sensor probe can be launched straight ahead to scan unknown territory. Once launched, a probe travels forward while broadcasting the location of any enemies in its vacinity. Although their sensor and communications ranges are good, the active flight and broadcast time of these probes is severely limited.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Koiogran Turn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Utilizing a high-powered array of maneuvering thrusters, the Czerka K-57B engine system allows starfighters to perform the &quot;Koiogran Turn&quot;, a defensive maneuver that quickly turns the ship 180 degrees to face any potential pursuers and return fire without losing speed. This maneuver has the added benefit of evading any missiles that might be locked on.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Barrel Roll</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Combined with high-grade inertial compensators and thrust regulators, the Vokoff-Strood STAR-94 engine system allows pilots to perform a barrel roll that boosts a ship's evasive capabilities--making it difficult to hit with direct-fire weapons and shaking any enemy missile locks. Vokoff-Strood has only recently entered the starfighter market, but its expertise with high-performance land- and airspeeders is serving it well.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Power Dive</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Bold pilots praise Celestial Industries' Powerhouse engine for its ability to support power dive maneuvers, in which the pilot flips his or her vessel and &quot;dives&quot; in order to shake pursuers and evade lock-on missiles. The maneuver has been known to cause lesser pilots to black out, but those purchasing Powerhouses know what they're in for.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Retro Thrusters</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Elsinore-Cordova's Lukaze Four engine and thruster system stands out for its inclusion of retro thrusters, allowing a ship to briefly accelerate in reverse. The maneuvering ship flies straight backwards, boosting its evasion before resuming its original course (and accelerating back to its forward speed). Named for famed Bothan pilot Ne'wha Lukaze, retro thrusters allow a pilot to slip behind pursuers who get too close.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Booster Recharge</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Keizar-Volvec's KV609-B engine battery cells allow a ship to rapidly refill a portion of its engine power reserve. In effect, this allows a pilot to use boosters for an extended period, maintaining particularly impressive speeds.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="287" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Tensor Field</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="288" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Vokoff-Strood's STAR-AE engine system can not only boost an equipped ship's own speed, but the speed of all allied ships in a large radius. This temporary effect is caused by a large-scale tensor field and is invaluable for teamwork-oriented pilots.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="289" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Quick-charge Shield</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="290" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Cygnus PulseScreen quick-recharge shield has limited strength but regenerates quickly. The latest model also includes an emergency boost, allowing a pilot to instantly restore a large portion of the shield's energy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="291" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Distortion Field</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="292" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Colicoid Creation Nest's Membrane defense system augments a low-strength shield with unknown alien technologies, providing a constant boost to a ship's evasion rating. Pilots can activate an additional function of the system to temporarily provide an additional (and enormous) evasion boost.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Directional Shield</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The most versatile shield available on the open market is Prexton's MD-FA directional shield. It has moderate total stopping power but allows a pilot to shift shield strength and regeneration rate between fore and aft shield arcs.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Engine Power Converter</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Cygnus Burner deflector shield is average but unextraordinary in most respects, offering moderate total stopping power against enemy weapons. Where it shines, however, is its engine power converter, allowing a pilot to transfer a portion of shield power to the engine reserves. A &quot;must have&quot; for pilots who value speed above all else.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Koiogran Turn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Utilizing a high-powered array of maneuvering thrusters, the Czerka K-57B engine system allows starfighters to perform the &quot;Koiogran Turn&quot;, a defensive maneuver that quickly turns the ship 180 degrees to face any potential pursuers and return fire without losing speed. This maneuver has the added benefit of evading any missiles that might be locked on.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Barrel Roll</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Combined with high-grade inertial compensators and thrust regulators, the Vokoff-Strood STAR-94 engine system allows pilots to perform a barrel roll that boosts a ship's evasive capabilities--making it difficult to hit with direct-fire weapons and shaking any enemy missile locks. Vokoff-Strood has only recently entered the starfighter market, but its expertise with high-performance land-and-air speeders is serving it well.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Power Dive</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Bold pilots praise Celestial Industries' Powerhouse engine for its ability to support power dive maneuvers, in which the pilot flips his or her vessel and &quot;dives&quot; in order to shake pursuers and evade lock-on missiles. The maneuver has been known to cause lesser pilots to black out, but those purchasing Powerhouses know what they're in for.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Retro Thrusters</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Elsinore-Cordova's Lukaze Four engine and thruster system stands out for its inclusion of retro thrusters, allowing a ship to briefly accelerate in reverse. The maneuvering ship flies straight backwards, boosting its evasion before resuming its original course (and accelerating back to its forward speed). Named for famed Bothan pilot Ne'wha Lukaze, retro thrusters allow a pilot to slip behind pursuers who get too close.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Booster Recharge</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Keizar-Volvec's KV609-B engine battery cells allow a ship to rapidly refill a portion of its engine power reserve. In effect, this allows a pilot to use boosters for an extended period, maintaining particularly impressive speeds.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Tensor Field</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Vokoff-Strood's STAR-AE engine system can not only boost an equipped ship's own speed, but the speed of all allied ships in a large radius. This temporary effect is caused by a large-scale tensor field and is invaluable for teamwork-oriented pilots.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Rotational Thrusters</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Keizar-Volvec KV807-A engine system was built for combat, allowing a pilot to stop all forward momentum and spin to face his or her current target. The maneuver, though risky, has brought about the destruction of many enemies certain of their maneuverability or racing in overconfident pursuit.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Weapon Power Converter</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Designed for pilots in need of extra firepower, Czerka's L-41C weapon power converter enables a pilot to transfer a portion of a ship's engine power to the weapon reserves. As a result, an equipped ship can fire its weapons for a longer sustained period.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Slug Railgun</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Originally designed by Balmorran Arms, HR-0C Slingshot slug railguns are basic magnetic cannons with extraordinary range. The &quot;slug&quot; is a metal projectile that delivers high damage and partially bypasses a target's shield. When fully charged, a slug railgun's damage output can be absolutely devastating.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Ion Railgun</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Balmorran Arms HR-IO4 ion railgun is a ship-mounted magnetic cannon with extraordinary range. It fires ion particles enclosed in a magnetic field which do minimal hull damage but cause severe damage to shields, and drain weapon and engine power.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Plasma Railgun</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Czerka produces an array of exotic weaponry including the Incinerator-class plasma railgun. The Incinerator fires plasma bolts enclosed in magnetic fields, targeting enemies at extraordinary range and causing massive damage when fully charged. Plasma bolts do not pierce enemy shields directly but continue to burn a target after impact, causing significant damage over time to both shields and hull.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Burst Laser Cannon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The starfighter equivalent of a scattergun, the SoroSuub BLC-2 shoots clusters of high-damage bolts in a wide arc but has a slow rate of fire. Capable of annihilating even fast-moving opponents at close range, its damage drops rapidly with greater distance and it consumes large reserves of power.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Heavy Laser Cannon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="328" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The SoroSuub HLC-14 heavy laser cannon has high accuracy, long range and does great damage. Its slow rate of fire and significant power consumption are seen by many pilots as a fair tradeoff. Since SoroSuub's Sullust manufacturing centers were captured by the Empire, both Republic and Imperial navies have scrambled to obtain enough HLC-14s to arm their respective fleets.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Ion Cannon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Santhe Corporation ion cannons (nicknamed &quot;Sparkers&quot; by Republic pilots) do almost no damage to ship hulls but eliminate shields at frightening speed and easily disable enemy systems. They are too inaccurate to be used effectively at long range and have a slow rate of fire, but consume only moderate amounts of energy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Mag Cannon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Manufactured by the Colicoid Creation Nest but of unknown design, the Shrike-class mag cannon rapidly fires a spray of magnetic pellets. Shields are largely ineffective against mag cannons, allowing a significant amount of their damage to apply directly to an enemy's hull. While the cannon is technically no less damaging at longer distances, its inaccuracy makes engagements outside of close range inadvisable.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Concussion Missiles</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Too massive for any ship to carry in large numbers, Balmorran Arms L04 Silent Thunder concussion missiles can lock onto a target within a moderate timeframe and carry enough fuel to travel long distances. Only two L04s are needed to destroy most ships; the missiles are also capable of doing substantial damage to satellites and other mission objectives.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Proton Torpedoes</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Merr-Sonn recently unveiled its latest proton torpedo, the PX-4--a weapon capable of locking onto targets at extreme range and causing massive damage, ignoring armor and shields alike. While its drawbacks include a lengthy lock-on period, a narrow lock-on targeting cone, and the launcher's limited ammunition capacity, the PX-4 is nonetheless ideal for deployment against armored objectives.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Ion Missiles</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Merr-Sonn Mercybringer ion missile does minimal hull damage, but a single hit is enough to down most enemy shields and short out onboard power systems. The Mercybringer locks onto targets within a moderate timeframe and has a long range. Despite its name, the Mercybringer's enfeebled victims are rarely granted a chance to surrender.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Ion Burst</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Built by the Santhe Corporation for use by pilots able to close in on their prey, the I-01 radial burst energizer unleashes a short-range ion wave that causes massive shield damage and drains power from enemies in all directions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Plasma Lance</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="764326" version="1065353216">A vessel armed with Czerka's ZN-1 heavy plasma lance can unleash a cone of superheated plasma directly ahead, powerful enough to instantly consume light starfighters. Czerka officially ceased production of the plasma lance some years ago due to legal concerns, but schematics have found their way to both Republic and Imperial arms manufacturers.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="343" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Hull Charges</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="344" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Originally designed for salvage operations and repurposed by Mid Rim pirates, Borallis Steelbreaker hull charges lock onto enemy vessels like missiles but have a very short range. A hull charge that hits its target magnetically affixes to the enemy ship for a short period before detonating, ignoring shields and causing substantial damage. Due to deficiencies in the launcher, a ship must wait a relatively long time after launching a hull charge before firing another.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="345" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Graviton Charges</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="346" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Borallis's experimental Compressor graviton charges lock onto enemy vessels like missiles but have a very short range. A graviton charge that hits its target magnetically affixes to the enemy ship and generates its own gravitational field, reducing the ship's speed and maneuverability and causing minor hull damage over a short time period. Graviton charge launchers require a lengthy recharge time; charges cannot be launched in rapid succession.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="347" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Seismic Mines</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="348" id2="764326" version="1065353216">GSI's M-S7 seismic mines deliver a powerful explosive payload when triggered by enemies who enter the mines' proximity. Although their explosive radius is small, the mines pierce through shields and cause very heavy damage to ship hulls.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="349" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Seeker Mines</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="350" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Capable of detecting enemies within a wide proximity and automatically maneuvering to intercept nearby hostile ships, GSI's M-L4 seeker mines combine the best features of a mine and a missile. While their payload is powerful, their combined chemical and particle explosions can be absorbed by shields.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="351" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Shield Power Converter</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="352" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Rather than encouraging fancy flying and ostentatious maneuvers, the Celestial Industries Unbreakable engine system allows pilots to transfer a portion of its engine power to the ship's shield power reserves. Its advertising is simple and direct: &quot;Stronger shields mean a better defense&quot;.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="353" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Hyperspace Beacon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="354" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Elsinore-Cordova HY/S84 engine system miniaturizes standard engine components to make room for a deployable hyperspace beacon. The beacon acts as an unarmed, immobile drone that broadcasts its hyperspace coordinates. Ships re-entering the battlefield after defeat can choose to jump directly to the beacon instead of their standard entry point.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="355" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Recall Beacon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="356" id2="764326" version="1065353216">With an attached recall beacon and built-in emergency lightspeed jump capability, the Keizar-Volvec KV707-X engine system allows an equipped ship to deploy an unarmed recall beacon drone at any location, then later jump back to the beacon from anywhere in the star system.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="357" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Sabotage Probe</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="358" id2="764326" version="1065353216">GSI's LOS-0 sabotage probe droid, once launched and attached to a foe, rapidly disables maneuvering thrusters and other ship systems, dealing minor hull damage in the process. Once used primarily by bounty hunters and law enforcement to cripple fleeing ships, these devices are invaluable in the hands of expert starfighter pilots.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="359" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Targeting Telemetry</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="360" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Alibata-Unyo's advanced sensor system includes custom hardware and software that allow an equipped ship to temporarily boost its sensor range. In addition, the system's targeting telemetry is so precise that it eliminates any cloaking effects on nearby enemy ships.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="361" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Sensor Probe</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="362" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Once used primarily by bounty hunters and law enforcement, GSI's LOS-0 slicing devices are designed to launch and attach to a target vessel, where they inflict a number of debilitating effects: the target's location is revealed to the pilot's entire squadron, cloaking is made impossible, maneuvering is impeded, and the ship is far less capable of evading blaster fire overall.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="363" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Primary Weapon Swap</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="364" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Ships equipped with GSI's &quot;X-Change&quot; primary weapon swap system can mount two primary weapons at the cost of an auxiliary system and switch between weapons during combat--an obvious advantage for combat-oriented pilots looking for flexibility.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="365" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Secondary Weapon Swap</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="366" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The GSI &quot;X-Change (Arsenal)&quot; secondary weapon swap system allows a pilot to mount two secondary weapons aboard a ship at the cost of an auxiliary system. The pilot can then switch between the secondaries at any time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="369" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Repair Probes</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="370" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Elsinore-Cordova R-PB6 repair system launches short-range probe droids capable of gradually repairing the ship's hull, or the hulls of nearby allies. The probes can be upgraded to slowly replenish shield power and deliver ammunition, as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="371" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Combat Command</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="372" id2="764326" version="1065353216">When activated, the Czerka OCC-SI (Offensive Combat Command Strategic Intelligence unit) allows a pilot to scan for enemy vulnerabilities and provide a temporary boost to the accuracy and weapon power regeneration rate of nearby allies. The boost fades after a moderate duration. The OCC-SI is derived from the same strategic protocols used by Czerka droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="373" id2="764326" version="1065353216">IFF Mimic</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="374" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The 79X04 IFF mimic allows a ship to broadcast a false identification signature, appearing as an ally on enemy sensors for a short duration. Available primarily through Nar Shaddaa black markets, the 79X04 is rumored to be programmed by the Exchange crime syndicate.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="375" id2="764326" version="1065353216">EMP Field</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="376" id2="764326" version="1065353216">GSI's EMP-X1 field array emits an electromagnetic pulse-wave that disables all hostile drones and ships' system components within its ample radius for a moderate duration. The pulse-wave will obliterate mines, batter drones, and reduce the effectiveness of starship sensors and targeting systems.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="377" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Sensor Shadows</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="378" id2="764326" version="1065353216">A Mirrorshard sensor shadow array allows a ship to appear as multiple vessels flying together on enemy sensors. The Mirrorshard array is manufactured by the Umbaran government, provided to outsiders through treaties and intermediaries.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="379" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Decoy Beacon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="380" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Appropriately equipped ships can deploy Santhe ECHO-X decoy beacons--unarmed but well-shielded and armored drones that, thanks to holograms and faked sensor signatures, appear identical to the deploying vessel. The decoy is capable of breaking missile locks and drawing fire, but after traveling forward a short distance will hold its position until its power is drained after a moderate time span.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="381" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Missile Sentry Drone</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="382" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Elsinore-Cordova Stoic missile sentry is an immobile drone loaded with a standard laser cannon and a long-range concussion missile launcher. The drone is programmed to attack any enemy within range.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="383" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Interdiction Sentry Drone</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="384" id2="764326" version="1065353216">GSI's E-45 interdictor sentry is an immobile drone that generates an interdiction field--essentially, a gravity well that reduces the speed and turning rate of nearby enemy ships. The drone is armed with a standard laser cannon for basic offense.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="385" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Interdiction Mine</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="386" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Balmorran Arms MX-Int interdiction mine creates a powerful gravity well when detonated. The resulting &quot;interdiction field&quot; significantly reduces the speed and turning rate of nearby enemy vessels and directly deals a moderate amount of hull damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="387" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Ion Mine</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="388" id2="764326" version="1065353216">When detonated, the Balmorran Arms MX-I5 ion mine deals massive shield damage and drains weapon and engine power from all nearby foes. As with other ion weapons, it does minimal damage to ship hulls but is highly likely to disable onboard systems.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="389" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Concussion Mine</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="390" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Czerka's G9-M concussion mines are the most widely-used mines in the galaxy. When an enemy ship comes into range the mine detonates, causing significant damage to all enemy ships in a wide radius.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="391" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Quick-Charge Shield</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="392" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Cygnus PulseScreen quick-recharge shield has limited strength but regenerates quickly. The latest model also includes an emergency boost, allowing a pilot to instantly restore a large portion of the shield's energy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="393" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Distortion Field</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="394" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Colicoid Creation Nest's Membrane defense system augments a low-strength shield with unknown alien technologies, providing a constant boost to a ship's evasion rating. Pilots can activate an additional function of the system to temporarily provide an additional (and enormous) evasion boost.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="395" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Directional Shield</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="396" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The most versatile shield available on the open market is Prexton's MD-FA directional shield. It has moderate total stopping power but allows a pilot to shift shield strength and regeneration rate between fore and aft shield arcs.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="397" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Engine Power Converter</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="398" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Cygnus Burner deflector shield is average but unextraordinary in most respects, offering moderate total stopping power against enemy weapons. Where it shines, however, is its engine power converter, allowing a pilot to transfer a portion of shield power to the engine reserves. A &quot;must have&quot; for pilots who value speed above all else.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="399" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Charged Plating</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="400" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Merr-Sonn 00D-A charged plating shield system includes a strong shield with a good regeneration rate; however, approximately half of all damage done to the shield bleeds through to a ship's hull. To compensate for this problem, the pilot may activate the system's charged plating and significantly increase the hull's damage reduction for a short period.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="401" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Shield Projector</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="402" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Sirplex is known for innovation in deflector technology, and the company's KL-44 Commander shield projector is no exception. The KL-44 has low baseline shield strength and a fast regeneration rate, but its projection capability can be activated to increase maximum shield power in all nearby allied ships (including its own) for a moderate duration. The projector does not boost current shield strength--only maximum capacity--and all shield power levels return to their normal range once the duration ends.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="403" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Cloaking Device</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="404" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Rumors abound regarding the origin of GSI's cloaking technologies, but no one can argue about the end result: the GSI Deep Eclipse starfighter cloaking device is among the galaxy's best. Once activated, the Deep Eclipse's cloak has a very long duration and can be toggled on or off outside of combat. If a cloaked ship suffers damage, triggers weapons or activates another ship system, the cloak immediately fails.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="409" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Fortress Shield</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="410" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Prexton LV-F deflector shield has low total stopping power until its &quot;fortress&quot; program is activated. So long as a pilot holds position and maintains zero acceleration, the activated fortress program significantly boosts shield strength. The effect is lost as soon as the ship begins to move.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="411" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Feedback Shield</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="412" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Mandalorian Clan Deshra reverse-engineered the alien technology behind their Retribution feedback shields almost a century ago, and now sell handcrafted Retribution devices to the highest bidder. These shields have only moderate strength, but can be activated with an additional energy charge that delivers significant damage to the next enemy to hit the shield with a primary weapon.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="413" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Overcharged Shield</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="414" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Prexton's HU-OC deflector shield is often tuned beyond its official specifications, offering very strong protection at the cost of a slow regeneration rate. A pilot can temporarily overcharge the shield even further, increasing maximum shield capacity (and boosting current shield strength) for a short period. Extra shielding is lost when the duration expires.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="415" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Shield Projector</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="416" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Sirplex is known for innovation in deflector technology, and the company's KL-44 Commander shield projector is no exception. The KL-44 has low baseline shield strength and a fast regeneration rate, but its projection capability can be activated to increase maximum shield power in all nearby allied ships (including its own) for a moderate duration. The projector does not boost current shield strength--only maximum capacity--and all shield power levels return to their normal range once the duration ends.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="417" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Repair Drone</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="418" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Elsinore-Cordova R-UR4 is an unarmed repair drone capable of gradually repairing the hulls of nearby allies. The repair drone can be upgraded to slowly replenish shield power and deliver ammunition, as well.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="419" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Damage Capacitor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="420" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Designed to boost the energy output--and by extension, the resulting damage--of a ship's primary weapons, the Merr-Sonn TQ-895 capacitor component is favored by pilots who want to hit hard and fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="421" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Frequency Capacitor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="422" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The BlasTech SF-12 capacitor component increases the rate of fire of a ship's primary weapons by feeding energy to both the weapons and augmented cooling systems. It has a reputation for safety and reliability.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="423" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Range Capacitor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="424" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Through enhanced field stabilization technology and precision targeting algorithms, the Czerka KC5 capacitor component increases a ship's primary weapon range.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="425" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Munitions Capacity Extender</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="426" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Elsinore-Cordova's CAR-X4 ordnance magazine component increases the ammunition capacity of a ship's secondary weapons. This feat is accomplished not by adding extra storage space, but by using suppressors and repulsors to render ammunition inert and lightweight while in storage--allowing missiles and other weapons to be packed safely and tightly together.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="427" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Power Pool Extender</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="428" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Merr-Sonn TX-100 weapon power magazine component boosts the ship's maximum weapon power. Popular for use on ships with power-heavy arsenals as well as with pilots who just want an extra edge.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="429" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Regeneration Extender</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="430" id2="764326" version="1065353216">After a lengthy development time, GSI's RAPID weapon power regeneration technology took the arms industry by storm. The RAPID magazine component increases a ship's weapon power regeneration rate by essentially &quot;recycling&quot; extra heat generated by weapon stabilizers.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="431" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Range Sensors</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="432" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Carbanti United's PN-4 sensor component increases a ship's standard sensor range. The sensor uses technology originally used in deep space exploration missions.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="433" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Communication Sensors</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="434" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The GSI Chatterbox sensor component increases a ship's effective communications range, allowing better tactical coordination inside a squadron. While GSI has not traditionally specialized in communications technology, its acquisition of several failed HoloNet companies recently changed things.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="435" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Dampening Sensors</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="436" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Santhe's LE-8 sensor dampeners allow a ship to get closer to enemy vessels before appearing on foes' sensors. This is achieved through a jamming signal that &quot;piggybacks&quot; on a ship's sensor scans.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="437" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Speed Thrusters</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="438" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Vokoff-Strood X/ATM-44 thruster component increases a ship's maximum speed. Originally used in Vokoff-Strood airspeeders, it now works both in and out of planetary atmospheres.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="439" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Turning Thrusters</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="440" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Keizar-Volvec KV457-C thruster component allows precision control over a ship's maneuvering thrusters, resulting in a faster turning rate.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="441" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Power Thrusters</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="442" id2="764326" version="1065353216">By heightening thruster efficiency, the Celestial Industries THR-4B thruster component increases the maximum power available to a ship's engines.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="443" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Regeneration Thrusters</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="444" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Elsinore-Cordova's unusual Dual Stream DS-001 thruster component increases a ship's engine power regeneration rate. It does so by allowing thrusters to intake stray radiation particles, drawing energy for the ship.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="445" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Large Reactor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="446" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Built to boost a ship's maximum shield power, the Sirplex SR-09 fulfills its purpose admirably. The reactor component essentially adds a shield reserve onto the reactor itself.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="447" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Regeneration Reactor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="448" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Prexton AUG-4C reactor component increases a ship's shield power regeneration rate, converting reactor fuel into deflector energies more efficiently.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="449" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Turbo Reactor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="450" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Cygnus Urgent Need reactor component utilizes exotic conductive materials to reduce the time delay that most shield systems require to begin recharging after they've sustained damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="451" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Deflection Armor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="452" id2="764326" version="1065353216">In order to reduce the amount of hull damage sustained whenever a ship is hit, GSI's AR-0B damage reduction armor component generates an ablative energy current through the ship's hull plating.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="453" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Reinforced Armor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="454" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Czerka's HP-S-5 starfighter armor layers additional centimeters of durasteel (along with patented alloys) onto a ship's hull. A ship armored this way can sustain more hull damage and survive longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="455" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Lightweight Armor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="456" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Santhe engineers custom design G-32 evasive armor plating for each class of ship supported. The G-32 components increase a ship's overall maneuverability by accommodating the ship's overall shape, thruster locations, and gravity field generators.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="457" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Remote Slicing</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="458" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Designed by the Anomid Schism Collective and widely copied, a NEEDLE remote slicing unit allows a pilot to wreak havoc on a chosen enemy's electronics--draining power and disabling onboard systems outright.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="459" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Interdiction Drive</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="460" id2="764326" version="1065353216">GSI's Predator interdiction drive is capable of emitting a powerful gravity field for short periods, slowing down all nearby enemy ships--an effect both practical and terrifying.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="461" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Blaster Overcharge</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="462" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Merr-Sonn's LCC-33 Blaster Overcharge system temporarily increases the rate of fire of ship blasters to devastating effect, while simultaneously increasing the primary weapon recharge rate to compensate for the heavier power draw.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="463" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Snap Turn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="464" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The Czerka K-57CE engine's gravity capacitors and maneuvering thrusters have been specially calibrated for the popular &quot;snap turn&quot; defensive maneuver, allowing bold pilots to perform a 180-degree snap turn in a matter of seconds.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="465" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Thermite Torpedo</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="466" id2="764326" version="1065353216">A mainstay of Czerka's explosive ordnance line, LC-9 Thermite Torpedoes can lock on and strike from extreme range. These torpedoes are highly effective at burning through armored starship hulls, and the heat they generate disrupt shields, making them less able to absorb incoming damage. Even hull sections not directly struck are temporarily weakened due to the superheating effect of the thermite detonation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="467" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Railgun Sentry Drone</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="468" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Designed to offer a cheap alternative for buyers who can't afford the cost or upkeep of full-size starfighter gunships, the Merr-Sonn SRG-87 railgun drone provides short-duration, long-range fire against enemy vessels in a convenient, small form-factor package.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="469" id2="764326" version="1065353216">EMP Missile</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="470" id2="764326" version="1065353216">The mid-range EM-03 missile from GSI features a moderate target-lock time and an intense electromagnetic pulse that discharges on impact. Hostile drones and ship auxiliary systems within a large radius are disabled for a moderate duration by the pulse, which carries a charge strong enough to destroy mines, seriously damage drones, and do minor damage directly to the hulls of enemy fighters.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="471" id2="764326" version="1065353216">EMP Beacon</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="472" id2="764326" version="1065353216">GSI's rocket-propelled EM-X1 beacon travels straight forward after it is deployed, emitting an intermittent electromagnetic pulse-wave that disables all hostile drones and ships' auxiliary systems within its ample radius for a short duration. The EMP-X1's pulse-wave is strong enough to obliterate mines and batter drones that it passes close to during its short lifespan.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="475" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Interdiction Missiles</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="476" id2="764326" version="1065353216">GSI's ID-84 interdiction missile can lock onto a target within a moderate timeframe and carry enough fuel to travel intermediate distances. After impact the missile generates an interdiction field--essentially, a gravity well that reduces the speed and turning rate of the target ship. The moderate payload also deals some damage to the target.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="477" id2="764326" version="1065353216">Efficient Targeting</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="478" id2="764326" version="1065353216">GSI's latest and greatest Deadeye v2.7 targeting software is the fastest on the market at reliably and efficiently missile locking targets.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
