<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>80</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/spvp/ships.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="257" id2="764327" version="1065353216">S-12 Blackbolt</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="258" id2="764327" version="1065353216">S-13 Sting</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="259" id2="764327" version="1065353216">S-SC4 Bloodmark</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="260" id2="764327" version="1065353216">NovaDive</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="261" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Flashfire</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="262" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Spearpoint</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="263" id2="764327" version="1065353216">F-T6 Rycer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="264" id2="764327" version="1065353216">F-T2 Quell</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="265" id2="764327" version="1065353216">FT-3C Imperium</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="266" id2="764327" version="1065353216">FT-8 Star Guard</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="267" id2="764327" version="1065353216">FT-6 Pike</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="268" id2="764327" version="1065353216">FT-7B Clarion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="269" id2="764327" version="1065353216">ICA-X Tormentor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="270" id2="764327" version="1065353216">ICA-2B Frostburn</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="271" id2="764327" version="1065353216">ICA-3A - Sable Claw</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="272" id2="764327" version="1065353216">X7-Mirage</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="273" id2="764327" version="1065353216">X5-Whisper</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="274" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Banshee</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="275" id2="764327" version="1065353216">GSS-3 Mangler</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="276" id2="764327" version="1065353216">GSS-5C Dustmaker</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="277" id2="764327" version="1065353216">GSS-4Y Jurgoran</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="278" id2="764327" version="1065353216">SGS-45 Quarrel</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="279" id2="764327" version="1065353216">SGS-41B Comet Breaker</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="280" id2="764327" version="1065353216">SGS-S1 Condor</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="281" id2="764327" version="1065353216">M-7 Razorwire</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="282" id2="764327" version="1065353216">B-5 Decimus</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="283" id2="764327" version="1065353216">B-4D Legion</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="284" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Rampart Mark Four</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="285" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Sledgehammer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="286" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Warcarrier</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="293" id2="764327" version="1065353216">The Imperial Tandankin shipyards produce a small number of elite scout craft used for both reconnaissance and lightning strikes. The S-12 Blackbolt combines extraordinary speed, maneuverability and strafing capacity with powerful sensors and communications rigs. Enemies can be spotted early and their locations relayed to allies--or a Blackbolt pilot can take foes on directly with short- and mid-range laser cannons. Stationary objectives are prime targets for the Blackbolt's rockets. The Blackbolt has only bare-bones defenses, however, with weak shields and a thin, unarmored hull. For that reason, Blackbolt pilots often earn reputations as thrill-seekers or suicidal fools (or sometimes both).</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="294" id2="764327" version="1065353216">The shipyards of Tandankin have served the Imperial war machine for decades, specializing in experimental designs. With its array of laser cannons, ship-to-ship missiles, and hardened armor and shields, the Tandankin-built S-13 Sting barely qualifies as a scout, but it maintains considerable sensor and communications range diminished only in comparison to other scout-class vessels. Its weapons and defenses still don't match those of a full strike fighter, but it can be just as deadly in the right hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="295" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Imperial starfighter squadrons drill relentlessly so that their pilots fly and fight with a single mind. For ultimate coordination, the Tandankin shipyards S-SC4 Bloodmark is practically a necessity. Sacrificing some speed and maneuverability along with ship-to-ship missiles in exchange for some of the galaxy's best sensors and communications technology, the Bloodmark also possesses unique subsystems for improved battlefield awareness. A squadron containing an expert Bloodmark pilot can act with greater efficiency than any other.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="296" id2="764327" version="1065353216">The centerpiece of Corellia StarDrive's scout ship line, the NovaDive is designed to provide the ideal balance of reconnaissance and offensive capabilities. Advanced sensor and communications suites allow NovaDive pilots to quickly spot enemy craft and relay their positions to allies, while mountings for short- and mid-range laser cannons and rocket pods ensure that the craft can hold its own against enemy fighters and even strike at armored objectives. Unfortunately, defensive systems are meager at best; veteran pilots have learned to rely more on the NovaDive's speed and maneuverability than its shields or armor to survive tough engagements.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="297" id2="764327" version="1065353216">When Corellia StarDrive appeared on the verge of losing its military contract, the company refocused on a new scout model--one that would trade away sensor and communications range along with specialized sensor tech in return for more powerful laser cannons, mid-range missiles and stronger defenses across the board. The result is the Flashfire, combining other scouts' speed with deadly offensive capabilities. A Flashfire may not compete head-on against a strike fighter, but its maneuverability may be the edge a skilled pilot needs.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="298" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Outsourcing dozens of components to sensor manufacturers previously focused on the scientific market, Corellia StarDrive managed to assemble the Spearpoint scout ship--a vessel whose sensors and communications equipment outperform practically every other ship on the market, including other scouts. The Spearpoint also possesses auxiliary systems designed to coordinate and support an entire squadron, offering fellow pilots a clear view of the battlefield. These enhancements come at the cost of some of the scout class's traditional maneuverability and speed, however, and also sacrifices some internal storage space.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="299" id2="764327" version="1065353216">The ultimate Imperial dogfighter, the F-T6 Rycer (named for an ace Imperial pilot of the last war) is a product of the Dromund Kalakar shipyards. The Rycer can be fitted with two primary blasters from an arsenal of options, including multiple laser and ion cannons; properly equipped, it can destroy or disable foes at any range. The Rycer is even more maneuverable than most strike fighters, but its defenses are less formidable-a fair trade, according to its pilots.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="300" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Tradition is as important as innovation at the Dromund Kalakar shipyards, and each new design must also honor the past. The F-T2 Quell brings an old name to a fresh exemplar of strike fighter design, possessing speed, maneuverability and good defenses coupled with twin secondary weapon systems that can be switched over mid-combat. This flexibility enables a Quell to carry (for example) both ship-to-ship missiles and torpedoes, allowing it to take on both enemy vessels and stationary objectives.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="301" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Although its design is derived from the FT-2 Quell, the Dromund Kalakar-built FT-3C Imperium lacks some of its counterpart's speed and maneuverability. Instead, the Imperium carries heavy defenses, state-of-the-art sensors and command-and-control systems--it is the pivot around which a squadron turns, bolstering and coordinating allies while under fire. Its secondary weapons are oriented toward eliminating armored objectives instead of dogfighting; Imperium pilots are conquerors first and warriors second.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="302" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Rendili has been producing Republic starfighters for centuries, and the FT-8 Star Guard is the company's latest achievement--a complete redesign of the FT-5A Honor Guard model. The Star Guard carries two primary blasters and gains maneuverability over other strike fighter-class ships at the cost of defensive strength. The Star Guard can support an array of laser and ion cannons that allow it to engage foes at multiple distances, but its lack of heavy ordnance makes it less effective against armored objectives. When it comes to dogfighting, however, there may be no finer ship in the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="303" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Well-armed, well-armored, and with the speed and maneuverability pilots expect from a strike fighter, the Rendili FT-6 Pike carries two sets of secondary weapons along with its primaries, allowing it (when properly equipped) to swap between ship-to-ship missiles and torpedoes mid-combat. This makes the Pike a versatile fighter, able to eliminate enemy ships and armored objectives in the same attack run. Some starfighter pilots are specialists, but Pike pilots are ready for anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="304" id2="764327" version="1065353216">The Rendili FT-7B Clarion lacks the weapon capacity of other strike fighters, instead possessing a powerful array of sensors and command-and-control systems that boost overall squadron effectiveness; if a typical strike fighter is a squadron's fist, the Clarion is a squadron's mind and voice. The Clarion also sacrifices a degree of speed and maneuverability in return for heavier defenses, and its secondary weapons are oriented toward eliminating stationary targets and armored objectives.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="305" id2="764327" version="1065353216">After the Empire's conquest of Sullust, Imperial engineers put several local SoroSuub factories to work creating starfighter parts. The SoroSuub-built GSS-3 Mangler sports two kinds of swappable railguns, strafes relatively rapidly and has an augmented communications range. Its defenses are more than acceptable, while its weaknesses--unimpressive sensors, speed, and turning rate--are standard for the class. Rumor has it that one Mandalorian clan even requested Manglers for payment when the Empire bought its services.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="306" id2="764327" version="1065353216">The G-2A gunship razed whole cities on Sullust when the Empire conquered that planet. Therefore, Sullustan manufacturer SoroSuub was given the honor of designing the G-2A's successor. The GSS-5C Dustmaker gunship carries only a basic railgun but can equip heavy lasers and proton torpedoes to enact devastation from afar. While its defenses are less formidable than those of other gunships, the Dustmaker's unmatched firepower more than makes up for it in the minds of most pilots.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="307" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Despite numerous delays caused by local insurgencies, SoroSuub continues production of the GSS-4Y Jurgoran--a gunship designed for survivability on battlefields where keeping foes at a distance isn't feasible. Along with its basic railgun, the Jurgoran can switch to ship-to-ship missiles in mid-combat and unleash volleys from enhanced close-range laser cannons. Additional speed, maneuverability and equipment options over the GSS-3 Mangler make the Jurgoran ready and able to finish off damaged foes or escape from enemies who may be closing in.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="308" id2="764327" version="1065353216">The Sienar SGS-45 Quarrel carries swappable models of long-range railguns, giving it versatility as well as firepower. Its speed and maneuverability sit at the unimpressive gunship baseline, but it can strafe quickly and it has an impressive communications range. Hotshot dogfighters occasionally sneer at the Quarrel's &quot;workmanlike&quot; build--until they see a skilled gunner devastate an enemy squadron without taking a single hit.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="309" id2="764327" version="1065353216">For pilots who want an armory packed into a starfighter, Sienar offers the SGS-41B Comet Breaker (so named after an accidental weapons discharge during testing). The Comet Breaker lacks the multiple railgun types of the Quarrel, but can equip heavy laser cannons and proton torpedoes to deal extra damage at range. Its defenses are also slightly reduced from the gunship baseline--but for Comet Breaker pilots, worrying about defense misses the whole point.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="310" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Sienar spent a decade perfecting the SGS-S1 Condor before introducing it to the Republic Navy. The result is a gunship with survivability and limited close-combat capability--while its sensor range and ammunition capacity is less than that of similar ships, it can switch its secondary weapon to dogfighting missiles and has access to more powerful short-range laser cannons. The Condor is also faster and more maneuverable than its counterparts and can equip a variety of shields and engines. While it's still not built for prolonged dogfights, it can effectively finish off damaged foes or escape to safety when an enemy squadron closes in.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="311" id2="764327" version="1065353216">The M-7 Razorwire is the ultimate Imperial minelayer, built in the Sernpidal shipyards and loaded with some of the most dangerous ordnance in the galaxy. The Razorwire carries multiple sets of mines and possesses expanded ammunition capacity, allowing it to deploy deadly traps and barricades wherever required. A moderate sensor range and long-range communications systems allow Razorwire pilots to coordinate with allies, but as with other bombers, its dogfighting capability is poor.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="312" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Named for the Sith Lord who commissioned it, the Sernpidal-built B-5 Decimus was banned by the Treaty of Coruscant for its frequent use against civilians. The new B-6 Decimus design was rededicated to combat, and the ship boasts heavy laser cannons, can equip either missiles or torpedoes as secondaries, and has access to a limited selection of auxiliary mines and drones. The Decimus is more maneuverable than other bombers but has a somewhat weaker hull.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="313" id2="764327" version="1065353216">The Sernpidal shipyards' B-4D Legion bomber utilizes drone technology at every turn. The Legion's drones can be used to strike at foes, reinforce and repair allies, and offer new battlefield strategies, turning the bomber into a versatile and devious wildcard. In addition to its basic laser cannons, the Legion can equip either a missile or mine as a secondary weapon, giving it further means of destroying foes.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="314" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Elsinore-Cordova's Rampart Mark Four bomber is a minelayer first and foremost. With extended ammunition caches and two distinct types of mines, the Rampart is capable of laying down barricades any squadron would fear to penetrate. Its defenses and primary weapons match the bomber baseline, while it has a moderate sensor range and excellent communications systems.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="315" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Designed primarily for destroying satellites, bunkers and similar armored or immobile objectives, the Elsinore-Cordova Sledgehammer is more maneuverable than other bombers but possesses a somewhat weaker hull. The Sledgehammer can carry either missiles or torpedoes and can be equipped with mines and drones as auxiliary systems; in addition, it can utilize heavy laser cannons. While not an ideal ship for dogfighting, very few structures can survive a fully armed Sledgehammer bearing down.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="316" id2="764327" version="1065353216">The Elsinore-Cordova Warcarrier is designed to carry and deploy automated drones to strike at enemies, assist allies and reshape the field of battle. Its basic laser cannons can be augmented by secondary missiles or mines, but while it possesses the bomber class's usual resilience, its ship-to-ship combat abilities remain limited. When properly utilized, a Warcarrier can bring a terrifying range of technologies into play, leaving enemies scrambling to adjust.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="317" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Darth Mekhis herself developed the prototype for the ICA-X Tormentor and instructed Chiss engineers on how to bring her fearsome vision to life. This infiltrator-class vessel eschews high-damage secondary weapons in favor of weapons that disable, and it can be equipped with a wide array of technologies designed to baffle foes' sensors. Perhaps most notable is the Tormentor's cloaking field, which can extend to encompass allies--allowing the use of terrifying, otherwise impossible team tactics.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="318" id2="764327" version="1065353216">The Chiss Ascendancy and the Sith Empire co-developed much of their basic stealth technology (without which cloaking devices would be useless), and construction of the ICA-2B Frostburn is performed deep in Chiss space. The Frostburn is the infiltrator against which all others are matched, able to cloak and interfere with enemy sensors, close in on a foe, and eliminate that foe with powerful short-range primary and secondary weapons. A pilot who fails to execute an enemy quickly, however, must be mindful of the vessel's weak shielding.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="319" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Like the ICA-2B, the ICA-3A Sable Claw is built in Chiss space--but unlike other infiltrator-class ships, the Sable Claw is designed to couple stealth tactics with dogfighting techniques. The Sable Claw has improved defenses, carries more versatile primary weapons and can equip a variety of secondaries other infiltrators cannot (including long-range ship-to-ship missiles). What the Sable Claw gains in combat capability, it loses in sensor capacity and maneuverability; its cloak, however, remains the key to victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="320" id2="764327" version="1065353216">The Kuat Drive Yards X7-Mirage is built to cause chaos, using a variety of prototype technologies to wreak havoc on enemy sensors. Its cloaking field is even capable of hiding allies, allowing a Mirage pilot to coordinate a whole squadron executing an ambush. The Mirage's raw damage output is less than that of its peers, however--its secondary weapons are oriented toward disabling, not destroying. Note that officially, the existence of the Mirage is still classified by the Republic Navy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="321" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Rumors suggest extensive collaboration between the Republic SIS and Kuat Drive Yards during the design of the X5-Whisper--a collaboration which supposedly excluded the Republic Navy. But regardless of its origins, the Whisper is a deadly assassin of a starfighter, possessing powerful short-range primary and secondary weapons along with its cloak and sensor interference systems. When used correctly, a Whisper can hunt down isolated targets, eliminate them at point-blank range, then vanish back into stealth.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="322" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Much to the surprise of competitors, Corellia StarDrive recently agreed to co-develop with Kuat Drive Yards a combat-hardened version of the infiltrator class. The Banshee (named for a Corellian bird of prey) carries versatile primary weapons and can equip a wide array of secondaries--including long-range ship-to-ship missiles, rewriting the rules of engagement for infiltrators. Additional defenses help keep Banshees in the fight, but their maneuverability and sensors can't match those of infiltrators such as the X7-Mirage or the X5-Whisper.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="323" id2="764327" version="1065353216">IL-5 Ocula</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="324" id2="764327" version="1065353216">IL-5 Skybolt</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="325" id2="764327" version="1065353216">The Czerka IL-5 Ocula was the company's first entry into the modern scout starfighter field, and utilizes a number of proprietary miniaturization techniques to ensure that nearly all popular internal components can be accommodated. Imperial military officials have shown a particular fondness for the design, ordering thousands of the craft through intermediaries while Czerka executives turn a blind eye. Imperial pilots often employ the craft on long-range reconnaissance missions into territories where their standard scout ships would be quickly recognized.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="326" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Although the Republic military officially passed on Czerka's IL-5 Skybolt in favor of designs from Corellia StarDrive, a number of  regional governors and &quot;flexible&quot; fleet admirals have made the craft a common sight on Republic flight decks nonetheless. Flight crews have a great appreciation for the ease of installing a huge variety of aftermarket components (a rare feature from Czerka), and many pilots have come to favor the design over their standard-issue scout models.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="327" id2="764327" version="1065353216">TZ-24 Gladiator</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="328" id2="764327" version="1065353216">TZ-24 Enforcer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="329" id2="764327" version="1065353216">G-X1 Onslaught</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="330" id2="764327" version="1065353216">G-X1 Firehauler</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="331" id2="764327" version="1065353216">K-52 Demolisher</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="332" id2="764327" version="1065353216">K-52 Strongarm</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="333" id2="764327" version="1065353216">VX-9 Mailoc</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="334" id2="764327" version="1065353216">VX-9 Redeemer</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="335" id2="764327" version="1065353216">As a venerable starfighter design sold to security forces on many of the worlds conquered by the Empire, uncountable thousands of TZ-24 Gladiators have fallen into Imperial hands over the years. Adapted from the larger TZ-2 transport, the Enforcer was designed to serve as a rugged, no-frills combat fighter for long campaigns in remote regions. The Empire has done little to alter the model given its excellent performance record, and regularly fields the Enforcer alongside its standard starfighter complements.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="336" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Designed before the start of the Great Galactic War, the TZ-24 Enforcer remains a highly popular design, and serves as the mainstay of dozens of planetary defense forces throughout the Republic. The ship's designers took great pride in the rugged simplicity of their design, hoping it would provide long years of use even the galaxy's most remote sectors. Given its extended history of service with minimal need for upgrades, the model has surely lived up to its designers (and buyers) expectations.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="337" id2="764327" version="1065353216">A relatively new addition to Imperial starfighter complements, the GSI-produced G-X1 Onslaught is already earning a stellar reputation among first-run pilots. Bulk purchases of military hardware from outside the Empire's own manufacturing centers are incredibly rare, but rumors persist that the Ministry of War plans to make the Onslaught a common sight among Imperial bomber squadrons in years to come, suggesting that the ship is even more capable than its enthusiastic marketing materials suggest.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="338" id2="764327" version="1065353216">A common joke suggests that GSI only produces the Firehauler because it encourages additional sales of their many explosive munitions, but there are very few bomber pilots in the Republic who would turn down the chance to fly one on any given mission. The design has been quick to impress everyone who's taken it for a spin, and GSI's sales projections have only gone up as word of the Firehauler's capabilities has spread among the Republic brass.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="339" id2="764327" version="1065353216">A custom gunship design sold to &quot;discerning customers&quot; all over the galaxy with no questions asked, Hyrotii's K-52 Strongarm was first popularized within the Empire after its purchase by Dark Council member Darth Marr. Many other Sith and military officers soon followed suit, and their impressive combat records in the craft have led to frequent purchases among the Imperial elite.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="340" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Republic forces have increasingly recruited additional support from privateers, mercenaries, and other nonmilitary sources. These &quot;free spirited&quot; individuals often take great pride in their personal craft, with the Hyrotii K-52 Strongarm being one of the most popular. After seeing the gunship in action, Republic officials have been quite impressed, and authorized the ship as a valid alternative for individuals or squadrons that can manage to afford them.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="341" id2="764327" version="1065353216">Although it is no longer fielded as widely as newer designs, the VX-9 Mailoc gunship is still produced at Dromund Kalakar shipyards, and remains a favorite of many veteran Imperial pilots. The ship has certainly distinguished itself in combat against Republic forces - so much so that the SIS carried out a costly covert mission to acquire the ship's design specifications for themselves. Unfazed by the loss, Imperial Mailoc pilots take great pride in targeting the enemy's &quot;knockoff&quot; fighters whenever possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="342" id2="764327" version="1065353216">After Republic pilots first encountered the Empire's VX-9 Mailoc gunship in battle, their first request was that their superiors get them  &quot;a ship like that!&quot; The Strategic Information Service volunteered to do just that, undertaking a lengthy and complex operation to infiltrate the Dromund Kalakar shipyards and acquire the Mailoc's design specifications. The mission was a complete success, and Republic pilots have gladly employed the Redeemer against its original designers in battle ever since.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
