<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>9</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/hoth/heroic_weekly/republic/mission_board.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174045" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leebo Nobim has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Highmount Ridge sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Leebo Nobim may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Grollix has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Starship Graveyard sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Captain Grollix may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sergeant Keloh has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Whiterock Wastes sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Sergeant Keloh may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1174048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Calia has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Glacial Fissure sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Lieutenant Calia may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177347" id2="17" version="1065353216">Kerkarr has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Kerkarr may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177348" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corporal Fabel has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Corporal Fabel may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177349" id2="17" version="1065353216">Neelo Droobas has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Neelo Droobas may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177350" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jaro Dev has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Jaro Dev may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1177351" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maya Drin has outlined the parameters for a high-priority mission in the Clabburn Tundra sector of Hoth. For additional details about the mission, Maya Drin may be contacted in-person. Otherwise, the mission may be initiated from this terminal for your convenience.
 
This mission may require a small group. It may be completed once per week.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
