<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>118</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/republic/the_imperial_blockade/cole_cantarus.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495144" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire won't come back to Corellia. I can promise you that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495146" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got the Senate on vidcom. General Aves is waiting to introduce you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495148" id2="17" version="1065353216">One more fight, and the Legislature's ours. You know what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495150" id2="17" version="1065353216">This war has torn Corellia apart. The council will get what they deserve.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495152" id2="17" version="1065353216">The faster you bring the Ion Wall up, the sooner we can take the Empire down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495154" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good, you're here. We've got trouble. You remember Councillor Belos?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain Cantarus tells me the Republic's on their way here. You can't attack the Legislature yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495158" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's taken control of the Ion Wall, Corellia's most powerful defense system. They're planning to use it against the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495159" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does the Ion Wall do?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495159" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Ion Wall?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495160" id2="17" version="1065353216">It sends out an immense sonic wave that disables ships, security, heavy weaponry--nearly anything that requires power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495162" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this thing hits the Republic, the Empire keeps Corellia for good.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495164" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did the Empire get control of the Ion Wall?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495164" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was quick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495165" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Corellian Council offered it to them. Only we have the codes to operate it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495167" id2="17" version="1065353216">You happen to tell them our position and troop numbers, too?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495169" id2="17" version="1065353216">This would have been nice to know earlier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now you tell us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495170" id2="17" version="1065353216">This thing's news to me, too. Apparently it wasn't something the Council Guard needed to know about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495172" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Ion Wall was only intended to be used during an invasion. It's a weapon of last resort.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495174" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I have the codes. Why not turn it on the Legislature's defenses instead?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495175" id2="17" version="1065353216">Won't the Empire expect a counterattack?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495175" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seems too easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495176" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've been led to believe it's an impossibility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495178" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know the Legislature best. Would this work?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495178" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you think, Cole?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495179" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not sure what the Empire's installed, but it would definitely take out the building's security. What's the catch?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495181" id2="17" version="1065353216">Works for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495182" id2="17" version="1065353216">First, you'll need to point the Ion Wall's emitters at the Legislature. They've been concealed inside statues around Capitol Square.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495184" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once the emitters are realigned, the Ion Wall can be activated. The controls are located inside Intra-Corellian Intelligence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495186" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the catch. Intra-Corellian Intelligence was one of the first places the Empire took over. It'll be crawling with Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495187" id2="17" version="1065353216">Could we sneak inside somehow?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495187" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe there's a shortcut.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495188" id2="17" version="1065353216">No chance. It's an intel bureau--for all we know, the Empire's listening to this comm call right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495190" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some Republic troops or a CorSec squad might even the odds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495190" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have allies, don't we?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495191" id2="17" version="1065353216">You head over with more than you've got, and the Empire will know something's up. Nice and quiet is our best strategy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495193" id2="17" version="1065353216">The more, the better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495194" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials aren't the only danger, I'm afraid. Several members of the Dark Council arrived in Capitol Square a few days ago.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495196" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of them, Darth Acharon, was dispatched to Intra-Corellian Intelligence to keep the Ion Wall safe. You'll have to get past him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495197" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm after the Emperor. The Dark Council can't be much worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495197" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can handle Acharon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495198" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd know best. Me, I wouldn't bet my credits on it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495200" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where are the rest of the Dark Council members?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495200" id2="17" version="1065353216">You mentioned others.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495201" id2="17" version="1065353216">Inside the Legislature. One's protecting the Corellian Council. I feel more like we're being watched.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495203" id2="17" version="1065353216">How does Darth Acharon fight?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495203" id2="17" version="1065353216">It'll take good strategy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495204" id2="17" version="1065353216">I only met him briefly. He has a short temper and a powerful grip. If you can avoid both, you'll live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495206" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where's a Jedi-for-hire when you need one?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495206" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't like my odds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495207" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi have lightsabers for a reason. One good shot is all you need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495209" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never heard of the Dark Council.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495209" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Dark Council?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495210" id2="17" version="1065353216">They govern the Empire according to the Emperor's wishes. Only the most powerful Sith in the galaxy earn a seat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495212" id2="17" version="1065353216">By helping us, you're crossing the Dark Council too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495212" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'd better be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495213" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm well aware. I hope this proves to you that I'm truly on the Republic's side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495215" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should go. There's a secure line from Intra-Corellian Intelligence to my office. Contact me once you've activated the Ion Wall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495217" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Guardhouse is still linked to the Legislature. We can't control their defenses, but we can tell when they go down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495219" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get CorSec and the Republic into position. The minute you activate the Ion Wall, we attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495221" id2="17" version="1065353216">Councillor Belos's assistant is waiting for you. Personally, I'd take my chances with the Empire's droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495223" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Aves knows the status of the neutron emitters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495225" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Republic can't move, neither can CorSec. We have to get those neutron emitters shut down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495227" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gosse is helping her sept settle in. I didn't thank you properly earlier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495228" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a member of the Republic and our ally. It's my duty to protect you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495228" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what Jedi do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495229" id2="17" version="1065353216">Knowing your duty isn't always the same as doing it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495231" id2="17" version="1065353216">I hope neither of you were scarred by Imperial captivity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495231" id2="17" version="1065353216">Glad you're all right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495232" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's turned Coronet City into a battlefield. Spending a few hours as their prisoner was nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495234" id2="17" version="1065353216">You risked your life to help the Republic. I just returned the favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495234" id2="17" version="1065353216">No thanks necessary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495235" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's worth some applause. Not everyone on Corellia does the right thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495237" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rescuing handsome men's a hobby of mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495237" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Flirt] It was a pleasure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495238" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have to make sure to get captured again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495240" id2="17" version="1065353216">You wouldn't be much help from an Imperial cell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495240" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seemed like a smart move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495241" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm betting I wouldn't be very pleasant to be around either.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495243" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we have access to the Selonian tunnels?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495243" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did it pay off?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495244" id2="17" version="1065353216">In the future, try not getting captured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495244" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't get used to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495245" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep that in mind the next time I'm surrounded by armed Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495247" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your actions gained you more than one ally. Gosse had her people confirm the Selonian tunnels ran underneath Coronet Shipping.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495249" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Selonians were forced out of the tunnels by the Empire, but plenty of predators moved in afterwards. You'll have to be careful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495250" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Imperials know about the tunnels, won't they know I'm coming?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495250" id2="17" version="1065353216">The tunnels aren't a secret?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495251" id2="17" version="1065353216">They know they're empty and dangerous. They have no idea where the tunnels actually run.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495253" id2="17" version="1065353216">They won't be a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495254" id2="17" version="1065353216">Exterminating rodents isn't in my job description.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495254" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not here to clean tunnels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495255" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Selonians are trained warriors, but they barely survived an Imperial siege. They're in no condition to fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495257" id2="17" version="1065353216">As long as you're down there, you could clear some of those predators out. The Selonians would like their homes back someday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495259" id2="17" version="1065353216">The tunnels will bypass the shock troops, but their commander, Captain Granta, will be inside. Don't underestimate him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495260" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever Captain Granta has planned, I'll be ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495260" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready for anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495261" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better be. Otherwise this whole plan goes belly up with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Would a man like Captain Granta listen to reason?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495263" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I can negotiate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495264" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shock troops are used for one thing--direct assault. Negotiation's not in their vocabulary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495266" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of tactics are we talking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495266" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any specific reason why?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495267" id2="17" version="1065353216">The neutron emitters, the spaceport patrols, attacking the Selonians--all Captain Granta's ideas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495269" id2="17" version="1065353216">Imperials usually underestimate me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495269" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their mistake, not mine.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495270" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Captain Granta loses a battle, he just starts another one. Don't give him that chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495272" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do I do once I'm inside?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495272" id2="17" version="1065353216">And after I deal with him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495273" id2="17" version="1065353216">If he's as tough as the shock troops I've fought so far, I won't have any problems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="495273" id2="17" version="1065353216">Granta doesn't scare me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495274" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't judge Captain Granta by his troops. The man's captain for a reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495276" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find the neutron emitters outside, somewhere with a clear shot at the tram system. This spike should override any Imperial security.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495278" id2="17" version="1065353216">The neutron emitters will interfere with portable comm transmissions. Once you're inside, contact me through Coronet Shipping's system.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495280" id2="17" version="1065353216">We were starting to wonder if you'd make it back. Glad you didn't bring the Empire with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495282" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Selonians made it to the Red Light Sector. The Imperials were too scattered by your attack to stop them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="495339" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll show the Empire what Corellia really thinks of them.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
