<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>58</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/republic/the_imperial_blockade/deena_behar.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499757" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have your droids. I have other assignments from Councillor Belos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499759" id2="17" version="1065353216">Danison Varik is a genius. You'll need your droids to get past his defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499761" id2="17" version="1065353216">The only way to reach the Empire's droids is by making your own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499764" id2="17" version="1065353216">Deena Behar? I was told you had some information for me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499765" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's talk quickly. Numbers like yours don't escape the Empire's attention for long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to Labor Valley, Master Jedi. I won't waste your time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499769" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major. The Empire has eyes and ears all over Labor Valley, so I'll talk fast.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499771" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been expecting you, Captain. We might not have another chance, so listen closely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499773" id2="17" version="1065353216">You already know the Empire's droids are in a secure laboratory. Its toughest defenses are the prison-grade vault doors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499775" id2="17" version="1065353216">The doors can resist any kind of unauthorized entry--except in an emergency. You'll need disaster relief droids to get inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499776" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you know where I can find these droids?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499776" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I don't have any.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499777" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire wouldn't share this information with just anyone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499777" id2="17" version="1065353216">How did you learn this?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Plenty of Imperials talk when they don't think the Republic is listening.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499780" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm guessing you can't get these droids in a store.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499780" id2="17" version="1065353216">Never heard of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499781" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're only manufactured on Corellia--and they were needed all over the planet when the war came.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499783" id2="17" version="1065353216">What exactly do you do for Councillor Belos again?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499783" id2="17" version="1065353216">You sound like a spy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499784" id2="17" version="1065353216">Councillor Belos is a busy man. I keep him informed on many issues.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499786" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of capabilities do these droids have?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499786" id2="17" version="1065353216">Disaster relief droids?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499787" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're designed to withstand the toughest conditions. They can blast through any door and outlast any turret.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499789" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've broken down plenty of doors on my own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499789" id2="17" version="1065353216">Is that really necessary?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499790" id2="17" version="1065353216">If those other doors were also blasterproof durasteel with triple-fuse locks, be my guest. Otherwise, these droids are your best bet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499792" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Beharen Droid Factory specializes in disaster relief droids. They're here in Labor Valley, but they've been closed since the Empire arrived.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499794" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire shipped out Beharen's inventory before shutting down the factory. You'll need to get it up and running if you want those droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aren't there any Beharen employees who can help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499795" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't the workers do it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killed for resisting, like a lot of Labor Valley's workforce. Most factories here are empty.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499798" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do I reactivate an entire factory?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499798" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like quite a job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499799" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm here to fight the Empire's droids, not do maintenance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499799" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the assistant here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499800" id2="17" version="1065353216">And I was instructed to tell you how to reach them--not do it for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499802" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll need to restore power by reactivating the factory's off-site generators first, and then start up the assembly line.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499804" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are some risks involved. The generators are located in Hellfire, and rebooting the assembly line will activate any unfinished droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499805" id2="17" version="1065353216">What state are these droids actually in?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499805" id2="17" version="1065353216">Define &quot;unfinished.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499806" id2="17" version="1065353216">The droids are missing safety protocols and loyalty programming. They'll fire on you unless they're destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I want to know what Hellfire is?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499808" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hellfire?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Local name for Labor Valley's generators and fuel lines. Half of them are still burning from Republic sabotage and Imperial retaliation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499811" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the risks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499812" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once the assembly line's moving, the factory has to be reconnected to the supply grid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499814" id2="17" version="1065353216">The machines will get their parts, you'll get your droids, and the droids will get you inside the Empire's lab.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Reactivate the generators, turn on the assembly line, hook up the supply grid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's review this first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't forget avoiding the Empire and any hostile droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499818" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds clear enough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499819" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I get to this factory, I better not find an Imperial ambush.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="499819" id2="17" version="1065353216">I still don't trust you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499820" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials will try to stop you, but it won't be because of me, or Councillor Belos.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you've hooked up the supply grid, contact me through the factory comm system. That should let me verify that everything's working.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499824" id2="17" version="1065353216">Until then, it's best we don't speak. Good luck.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="499826" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do I know you?</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
