<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>384</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/republic/the_imperial_blockade/general_aves.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488732" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia's free, and the Empire's on the run. The end of the war's in sight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488734" id2="17" version="1065353216">Supreme Chancellor Saresh, Senators--the Republic's taken the Legislature and the Empire's on their last legs. It's all cleanup from here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488736" id2="17" version="1065353216">The message went out across Corellia, and I'm proud to relay it to you on Coruscant. We will have our victory.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488738" id2="17" version="1065353216">We had plenty of help from our allies, but one squad stood above the rest. We owe our victory to their efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488740" id2="17" version="1065353216">We had plenty of help from our allies, but one man stood above the rest. We owe our victory to his efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488742" id2="17" version="1065353216">We had plenty of help from our allies, but one woman stood above the rest. We owe our victory to her efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488744" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had a feeling I'd see you again, Master Jedi. Few others could win this fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488746" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm pleased to see you again, Major. You've done every man and woman in uniform proud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488748" id2="17" version="1065353216">On behalf of the Senate, I'd like to thank you for your service to the Republic. The general tells us you were indispensable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488749" id2="17" version="1065353216">It took more than firepower to free Corellia from the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488749" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a big job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488750" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Aves and Captain Cantarus gave the orders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488750" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't fight alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488751" id2="17" version="1065353216">We haven't forgotten. They'll both be honored for their leadership.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488753" id2="17" version="1065353216">I expect more than thanks for a fight like that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488753" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where's my medal?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488754" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senate understands the risk you took. You'll be rewarded handsomely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488756" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Corellian Council's decision to join the Empire must be addressed. Councillor Belos will answer for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488758" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you consider us all traitors. But before the Senate condemns us, I'd like a chance to explain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488760" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Corellian Council doubted the Republic's chances of defeating the Empire. We chose to join them rather than be conquered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488762" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some of my fellow councillors still believe this was the right choice. I believe it brought ruin to Corellia and war to the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488763" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coming to us helped reverse some of the damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488763" id2="17" version="1065353216">You did the right thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488764" id2="17" version="1065353216">A few years in jail might change their minds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488764" id2="17" version="1065353216">The council's been punished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488765" id2="17" version="1065353216">My colleagues may never regret their decision. For that, I pity them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488767" id2="17" version="1065353216">Admitting your mistake won't bring back the dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488767" id2="17" version="1065353216">That doesn't excuse you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488768" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know that. Captain Cantarus has been kind enough to show me the casualty lists.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488770" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've done what I can to help the Republic win. With the Senate's permission, I'll spend the rest of my term restoring Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488772" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you expect the Senate to believe that? You gave Corellia to the Empire once. You might do it again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488773" id2="17" version="1065353216">Councillor Belos risked his life to undo the council's decision.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488773" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can trust him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488774" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's true, Chancellor. If it weren't for Councillor Belos, we'd still be sitting in the Red Light Sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488776" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have friends in high places, Councillor. Keep your position, but don't betray their trust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Councillor Belos deserves a pardon, but he can't be trusted.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488778" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make him step down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488779" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've served Corellia for decades. But I suppose my freedom was the best I could hope for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488781" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are other ways to serve Corellia, Councillor. The Senate hopes you'll take advantage of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488783" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senate's heard many rumors about the Imperial invasion of Corellia. Before we continue, we'd like to hear the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488785" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire moved in with the Corellian Council's blessing. We fought their inside knowledge all the way to Capitol Square.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488787" id2="17" version="1065353216">The council showed no remorse for their actions. They've been arrested and removed from office.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488789" id2="17" version="1065353216">The council was loyal to the Republic for years. Why would they abandon us now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488790" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire convinced them that we were weak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488790" id2="17" version="1065353216">They lost faith in us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488791" id2="17" version="1065353216">The council went with the odds. Fortunately for us, they didn't pay off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488793" id2="17" version="1065353216">The council forgot they answered to the people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488793" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too much power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488794" id2="17" version="1065353216">After all the noise we made, I don't think they'll forget again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488796" id2="17" version="1065353216">Those traitors will never control Corellia again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488796" id2="17" version="1065353216">It doesn't matter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488797" id2="17" version="1065353216">With the council in jail, Corellia has no local leadership. There could be riots, crime sprees, further destruction.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488799" id2="17" version="1065353216">After all the damage the Empire's done, the Senate is hesitant to take direct control. Who should lead Corellia through their recovery?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488800" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got a war to fight. CorSec can handle things here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488800" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Corellians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488801" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll hold elections for a new council soon. Should be nice not answering to anyone for a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488803" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia's free, but vulnerable. They'll need our protection.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488803" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488804" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Senate can appoint an interim prime minister. We'll declare martial law until then.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488806" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia is one of our founding planets. There was no warning before they turned. How many more worlds might be on the brink?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488808" id2="17" version="1065353216">You brought Corellia back to the Republic. You have the Senate's attention. How can we prevent other worlds from joining the Empire?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia might look bad now, but all the Empire's destruction can be undone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488809" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't let them lose hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488811" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't our first victory, and it won't be our last. We will have peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488813" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic won't stop fighting until the Empire surrenders. Neither will I.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488814" id2="17" version="1065353216">Inspiring words. The Senate will support your efforts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia joined the Empire, and look what it brought them. War tore this world apart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488816" id2="17" version="1065353216">Remind them of the cost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488818" id2="17" version="1065353216">The council chose badly in a weak moment. Other worlds shouldn't make the same mistake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488820" id2="17" version="1065353216">When you abandon the Republic, you lose our protection. Traitors are on their own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488821" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many worlds have been allowed to rejoin the Republic. Maybe Corellia should be the last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even in times of war, the Republic attracts others seeking freedom from the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488823" id2="17" version="1065353216">Keep your allies happy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488825" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've found our allies in unlikely places, ready and willing to fight for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488827" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make good on your promises. Support all the worlds that came to our aid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488828" id2="17" version="1065353216">After the war is over, our new allies will have whatever they need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488830" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic lost faith in the order after the Battle of Coruscant. The order lost faith in itself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488830" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look to the Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488832" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've learned much since then. The Children of the Emperor can no longer hide from us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488834" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll need our insight to root out any traitors. Recall the Jedi to Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488835" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi have proven their strength. The Senate welcomes their guidance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488837" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've watched countless worlds fall to the Empire. Every time, the Republic has fought and won them back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488837" id2="17" version="1065353216">Believe in the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488839" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire might be willing to sacrifice anything to win, but Republic soldiers are better.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488841" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll never give up, and we'll never surrender. Fight with us, not against us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488842" id2="17" version="1065353216">If any Republic worlds want proof, they need only look to the major's example.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488844" id2="17" version="1065353216">The best soldiers in the galaxy serve the Republic. But you're not using us to our full potential.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488844" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time to get rough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488846" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we keep letting the Empire make the first move, we'll lose more than a few planets.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488848" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go on the offensive. Conquer a few Imperial worlds. No one will call the Republic weak again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488849" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire has no interest in peace. Maybe it's time the Republic stopped trying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellia's free because the people fought back. Their reward is a big pile of rubble they used to call home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488851" id2="17" version="1065353216">Put the people first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488853" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some people call that the cost of war. I call it unfair. The Republic's too focused on the big picture.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take care of the little guys first. You never know when you might need their help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488856" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have the Senate's promise. We'll see Corellia properly restored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488858" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic's got a lot of promise. But it's also got a lot of laws.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488858" id2="17" version="1065353216">Loosen up a little.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some of the galaxy's most brilliant don't play by the rules--but their creativity could be our edge on the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488862" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make the Republic attractive to these--outliers--and the ends will easily justify the means.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488863" id2="17" version="1065353216">An unorthodox approach. But we'll consider your words.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488865" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the politicians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488866" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before you go, we'd like to thank you properly. There's no medal or title that equals what you've accomplished, but this should help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488868" id2="17" version="1065353216">First Class Bloodstripes, Corellia's highest honor. Awarded to those who keep fighting despite the odds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488869" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you, Captain. I'd be proud to fight with CorSec again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488869" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am honored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488870" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'd be proud to have you. But I'm hoping our fighting days are nearly over.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488872" id2="17" version="1065353216">With Corellia free, what's the Republic's next objective?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488872" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not over yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488873" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire will have a hard time recovering from this loss. We hit them now, and we could have a surrender within weeks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488875" id2="17" version="1065353216">I also ended a blockade, beat the Imperial Guard, took on the Dark Council....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488875" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stripes? That's it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488876" id2="17" version="1065353216">When we can fit all that on a medal, we'll contact you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488878" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've freed Corellia from the Empire and set events in motion that may end this war. You deserve more than our thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488880" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our victory today sends a message. The Republic may falter, but we will never fall--as long as we keep fighting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488882" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senators, let your voices be heard. Stand and recognize these heroes of the Republic!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Storming the Legislature will be tricky. Cole Cantarus will know where to start.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488895" id2="17" version="1065353216">With Axial Park under control, Capitol Square is just a tram ride away. We've already started planning our offensive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488897" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Legislature will be our primary target. The Empire's turned it into a fortress. It'll take more than firepower to get inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488898" id2="17" version="1065353216">What is the Legislature, exactly?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488898" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Legislature?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488899" id2="17" version="1065353216">The seat of Corellian government. Imperial officers, the Corellian Council and everyone else who started this little war are holed up inside.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488901" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we have any information about their defenses?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488901" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's pretty vague intel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488902" id2="17" version="1065353216">Councillor Belos might know a few shortcuts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488902" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have an inside man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488903" id2="17" version="1065353216">The councillor's risked his neck for us already. We contact him now, he might lose it altogether.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488905" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cole Cantarus is familiar with the Legislature's security from his days in the Council Guard. He'll be our best starting point.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488907" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll find Captain Cantarus at the Council Guardhouse in Capitol Square. He should be able to brief you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let Cantarus know I'm on my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488908" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll head there next.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488909" id2="17" version="1065353216">What has Captain Cantarus been doing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488909" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's been busy, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488910" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mobilizing our CorSec allies. We'll need them when the time comes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cantarus's information could be wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488912" id2="17" version="1065353216">Things have changed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488913" id2="17" version="1065353216">If that's the case, we'll go to the councillor. But we can't go in blind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488915" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll get back to troop deployment. When we know our next move, my men will be ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488917" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've arrived just in time to witness the final troop deployment into Axial Park.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488919" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's making a last stand. It might get messy, but we can hold our ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Commander Tainor's already been transferred offworld. A lot of people wanted him dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488922" id2="17" version="1065353216">He already lost. There was no reason to kill him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488922" id2="17" version="1065353216">He deserved to live.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some people live for the extra twist of the blade. I'm glad you're not one of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488925" id2="17" version="1065353216">His capture meant more than his death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488925" id2="17" version="1065353216">It sent a message.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488926" id2="17" version="1065353216">It definitely affected the Empire's morale. When they stumbled, we made our move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488928" id2="17" version="1065353216">Helping him fall on his sword didn't appeal to me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488928" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't do executions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488929" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some time in a cell could change his perspective. Maybe he'll stop thinking devotion and start thinking revenge.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488931" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor's probably put a price on his head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488931" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'd be dead if he stayed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488932" id2="17" version="1065353216">A bounty hunter might be preferable to the Emperor's brand of punishment.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488934" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are the Republic's plans for the commander?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488934" id2="17" version="1065353216">What will happen to him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488935" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our most secure detention center and a lot of SIS interrogations. Maybe even his tactical advice, someday.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488937" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperial Guard's been defeated. What's next?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488937" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's no longer a threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488939" id2="17" version="1065353216">I must have called my men at least three times to verify Commander Tainor's death.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488940" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor will have to do better than that to stop me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488940" id2="17" version="1065353216">He didn't have a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488941" id2="17" version="1065353216">Since you're the best we've got against him, here's hoping he can't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488943" id2="17" version="1065353216">He refused to surrender. He was too dangerous to be spared.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488943" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't have a choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488944" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll second that. Wherever he is, the commander's probably thinking of ways he could have won.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488946" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperial Guard had orders to kill me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488946" id2="17" version="1065353216">It became personal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488947" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm surprised it didn't happen sooner. The Empire knows you're our ace in the hole.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488949" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't argue with a man who wants to die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488949" id2="17" version="1065353216">He wanted it that way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not if you hope to win, anyway. The Imperial Guard's code of honor could put the Mandalorians to shame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488952" id2="17" version="1065353216">Winning is what I do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488953" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't have sent you in there if I didn't think you'd make it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488955" id2="17" version="1065353216">The war's not over yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488956" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have to protect our command center. Keep those troops safe until the trenches are done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Checking in, General Aves. Captain Cantarus said you needed me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488960" id2="17" version="1065353216">If we need you anywhere on Corellia, it's here. We're getting close and the Imperials know it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488962" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've been on the march since the blockade ended. When we reached Axial Park, the Empire was waiting.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Axial Park is the gateway to Capitol Square and a monument to Republic history. Failure isn't an option here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488965" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have the Force on our side. Failure isn't a possibility.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488965" id2="17" version="1065353216">It won't come to that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488966" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll trust you on that one. What Jedi are left on Corellia didn't respond to our calls for aid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488968" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can offer you squads from several offworld ambassadors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488968" id2="17" version="1065353216">We do have allies here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488969" id2="17" version="1065353216">Solid thought but we'd never get them here in time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488971" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm ready to fight, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sabotage squads, snipers, you name it--all led by some elite commanders we haven't been able to identify.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488974" id2="17" version="1065353216">No worries, General. Failure isn't even in my vocabulary.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not since I showed up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488975" id2="17" version="1065353216">I had a feeling it wasn't. Or that you wouldn't admit to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488977" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's our battle plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Monuments and history aren't worth dying for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488978" id2="17" version="1065353216">Antiques aren't important.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488979" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic is. And we've let the Empire trample on her for too long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488981" id2="17" version="1065353216">Every time we gain some ground, our troops get ambushed. Between the special forces and the Imperial army, my men are overwhelmed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488983" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're about to start a major offensive into Imperial territory. I need someone on the battlefield dealing with these ambushes as they appear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488984" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever the Empire throws at me, I can handle it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488984" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can count on me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488985" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can I count on any reinforcements or backup?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488987" id2="17" version="1065353216">Will I have any help?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488988" id2="17" version="1065353216">Afraid not. CorSec is holding the rest of Corellia, and my troops will have their hands full with the Imperial army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488990" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's quite a big job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488991" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've got to secure the ground we have. Our engineers are creating a perimeter of trenches around the command center.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488993" id2="17" version="1065353216">The engineers have armed escorts, but the Empire's hit them hard. They'll need your protection until the trenches are stabilized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488994" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell your men to get working. I'll keep the Empire busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488994" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do my best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488995" id2="17" version="1065353216">Move fast and take 'em down hard. There's too much at stake for games.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488997" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll need more than trenches to defeat the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488997" id2="17" version="1065353216">And then what?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488998" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your men will survive if they stay out of my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="488998" id2="17" version="1065353216">No promises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="488999" id2="17" version="1065353216">If things go south, those trenches are our last defense. The men building them are not expendable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489001" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got my scouts working to find special forces before they strike. As reports come in, I'll contact you with your next objective.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489003" id2="17" version="1065353216">Make sure you're prepared before you head out. There's no time to rest on a battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489005" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Empire's droids are the problem, we need to get rid of them. Councillor Belos's assistant will know how.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489007" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's important is we have access to the rocket tram. We're already moving troops and supplies to Republic holdouts across Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489009" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the Empire's not making it easy. Once our reinforcements move from the rocket tram to ground transport, they disappear.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489011" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not sure how the Empire's catching them, but someone contacted us who thinks he does.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489013" id2="17" version="1065353216">Councillor Belos, of the same Corellian Council that voted to join the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489015" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was a mistake. The Republic's trying to free Corellia. I want to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489016" id2="17" version="1065353216">You voted against the Republic. Why would you help us now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489016" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now it's a mistake?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489017" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've broken the Imperial blockade. The Republic wouldn't have had a chance otherwise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nice of you to support us now that the Empire's losing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489021" id2="17" version="1065353216">The council's vote was unanimous. What made you change your mind?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489021" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why help us now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489022" id2="17" version="1065353216">Half of Corellia is in ruins. The Senate's condemned us, the people are rioting... it's bad business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489024" id2="17" version="1065353216">And business would be all you care about, wouldn't it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489026" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're an Imperial now. Everything you say could be a lie.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489026" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can we trust you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489027" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Empire wanted to trick you, they'd use someone you trust.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Puts you out of the running. But I'm still not convinced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489031" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're lucky the Republic even answered your comm call.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489031" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're kidding, right?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489032" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to see Corellia restored. Only the Republic can do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489034" id2="17" version="1065353216">Empire hasn't kept the peace on Corellia like you hoped?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Talk fast, Councillor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489037" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't need a traitor's help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489037" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks, but no thanks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489038" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm risking my life to contact you--the least you could do is hear me out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489040" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're risking our lives every day to undo the council's decision. We don't owe you a thing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489042" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not asking for forgiveness, but your reinforcements will never get through Labor Valley without my help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489044" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your men disappear once they move to speeders. The Empire's using prototype droids that can bring down any short-range vehicle.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489045" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where did the Empire find this technology?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489045" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds advanced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489046" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not found, developed. They've rounded up the best scientists and technicians on Corellia and put them to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489048" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's Labor Valley?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489048" id2="17" version="1065353216">Labor Valley?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489049" id2="17" version="1065353216">The industrial center of Corellia. The galaxy's best fuel yards and factories are there, along with plenty of people fighting for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489051" id2="17" version="1065353216">You could be lying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489052" id2="17" version="1065353216">The council interacts with the heads of the Empire on a daily basis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489054" id2="17" version="1065353216">My assistant, Deena Behar, has been researching the droids. I've instructed her to meet you in Labor Valley. Can she expect you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489055" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll take whatever information your assistant can offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489055" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell her I'll be there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489056" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll trust you for now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489057" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a lot of things, but a liar isn't one of them. I suppose I'll have to prove that to you first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489059" id2="17" version="1065353216">Better not be a trick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489060" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire would do worse. Believe me, I want the Republic to win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489062" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should get back before I'm missed. If I learn anything else that might help, I'll contact you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489064" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this is a trap, we'll find out soon enough. Take the rocket tram to Labor Valley and find this Deena Behar. We need to stop those droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489066" id2="17" version="1065353216">You made it out. We've been busy--Coronet Shipping's still a mess, but the rocket trams are up and running.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489068" id2="17" version="1065353216">The neutron emitters worked perfectly. The Imperials on board didn't even have a chance to attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489070" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell that to the civilians trying to escape the war. They didn't deserve to become casualties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489071" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there had been any way to save them, I would have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489071" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't want them to die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489072" id2="17" version="1065353216">You had a way. It just required the Republic to risk something, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Saving those civilians might have cost the Republic their reinforcements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489074" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look at the big picture here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489075" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are plenty of people willing to fight. The people who died can't be replaced.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489077" id2="17" version="1065353216">In war, every resource counts. The Imperials would have done too much damage.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489077" id2="17" version="1065353216">There was no other option.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489078" id2="17" version="1065353216">I get it--the risk of losing was too high. Can't expect the Republic army to fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489080" id2="17" version="1065353216">They took a chance trying to escape. It turned out bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489080" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one made them sneak a ride.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489081" id2="17" version="1065353216">You might call the sacrifice of a couple of Corellian families bad. Some might call it wrong.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489083" id2="17" version="1065353216">I made my decision. We need to focus on beating the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489083" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's over now, Captain.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489084" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't answer to CorSec.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489085" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no way you could justify it to me anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489087" id2="17" version="1065353216">There were over two dozen civilians on those trams. Thanks to you a lot of them are already offworld.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489089" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd be happier if any of them had stayed to help. We've lost supplies and men all over this sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489090" id2="17" version="1065353216">Innocent people were going to die. I had to do something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489090" id2="17" version="1065353216">Civilians come first, General.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489091" id2="17" version="1065353216">At the Republic's expense. We'll recover, but we might not be so lucky next time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489093" id2="17" version="1065353216">Using the neutron emitters would have made us no better than the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489093" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's the price of honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489094" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose you're right. Victory by any means is their department.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489096" id2="17" version="1065353216">War is part of our job. Civilians shouldn't get caught in the cross fire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489096" id2="17" version="1065353216">Soldiers can take that risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489097" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people of Corellia joined the war when they decided to resist the Empire. We're both fighting to win.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489099" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't kill innocent people. Just a little policy I have.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489099" id2="17" version="1065353216">There were civilians involved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489100" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a difference between innocent and recklessly putting yourself in harm's way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489102" id2="17" version="1065353216">I made my choice. The Republic will have to make do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489102" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's over now, at any rate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489103" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't like my help, don't ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489104" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't think I'm ungrateful. It was your call, and it won't be the last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489106" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is it. Get inside Coronet Shipping and find those neutron emitters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489108" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cantarus has the details on getting inside the Selonian tunnels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489110" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need the Selonians' support. Evacuate those burrows.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489112" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get to that cell block. The Imperials won't hold a CorSec captain and a Selonian leader forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489114" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nearly every place on Corellia has a back door. CorSec thinks some of the Selonian tunnels run right under Coronet Shipping.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489116" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Selonians haven't dealt much with the Republic, so I sent a Corellian to do the negotiating. He should have been back by now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489117" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never heard of the Selonians.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489117" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Selonians?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489118" id2="17" version="1065353216">One of Corellia's native species. They were tunnel dwellers, until the Empire cut off their supplies--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489120" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who is this Corellian, exactly? Can he be trusted?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489120" id2="17" version="1065353216">Bad pick, maybe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cole Cantarus, a former captain in CorSec's Council Guard. The man's impulsive, but he hasn't let me down yet--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489124" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let's not lose our heads yet. The Imperials don't make it easy to move around Corellia--</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489126" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir--Imperials attacked the rendezvous point. Captain Cantarus and the Selonian have been captured.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489128" id2="17" version="1065353216">Someone tipped off the Imperials! Do we know where they're being held?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489130" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a captured CorSec station nearby. It would have the cell blocks and fortifications they'd need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489132" id2="17" version="1065353216">CorSec needs to keep the Red Light Sector secure. You've got to free Captain Cantarus and his Selonian contact.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489133" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they've been interrogated, the Empire might know your plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489133" id2="17" version="1065353216">What if they talked?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489134" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they haven't, we're in the clear. Either way, I don't trust them with the Imperials for long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489136" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm already on my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489137" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we even know if they're still alive?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489137" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a waste of time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489138" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire wouldn't have captured them if they didn't think they were worth something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489140" id2="17" version="1065353216">These CorSec stations have room for plenty more prisoners. Help them if you can, but Cantarus and his contact are your primary concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489142" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll put CorSec on alert and tell my scouts to watch for any sign of them. Get going.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489144" id2="17" version="1065353216">Welcome to the Gilded Descent. CorSec had the intel on the neutron emitters ready and waiting for us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489146" id2="17" version="1065353216">The emitters are at Coronet Shipping. They're a major distributor of starship parts and weapons. Place is built like a fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489148" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, the Empire's using it as shock troop headquarters. That makes a straight assault impossible. Too many defenses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can we bring those defenses down somehow?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489149" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're sure about that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489150" id2="17" version="1065353216">With a few months of careful planning, maybe. But we don't have that kind of time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489152" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do we get inside?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489153" id2="17" version="1065353216">We beat the shock troops around the spaceport, didn't we?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489153" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're such a pessimist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489154" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was just a few patrols. We're talking about a fully staffed and heavily armed HQ.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489156" id2="17" version="1065353216">The minute we see smoke from those supply camps, my men and I will move out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489159" id2="17" version="1065353216">General Aves. I was told you could use some help.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489160" id2="17" version="1065353216">And then some. I'm glad you all appreciate the importance of Corellia.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489162" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi. I know the order's stretched thin, but the Empire's not going to give up easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489164" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major. I was sure other objectives would keep you off the battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489166" id2="17" version="1065353216">Captain. More than one officer has told me you can get things done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489168" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corporal Hartke explained we've lost access to the rocket trams, but he wasn't cleared to know why.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489170" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's gotten their hands on some modified neutron emitters. They're using them to wipe out anyone on board the trams.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489171" id2="17" version="1065353216">Getting access to the tram is useless if we can't ride it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489171" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the trams are working?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489172" id2="17" version="1065353216">The neutron emitters only affect life-forms. The trams themselves are still mechanically sound.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are the Imperials attacking Corellian passengers, too?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Civilians and military both?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489175" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unfortunately, yes. But it hasn't stopped them from trying to escape the more war-torn areas.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489177" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm guessing you discovered that the hard way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489177" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know from experience.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489178" id2="17" version="1065353216">The minute we landed, I sent my best squads ahead on the tram. They were dead before they reached their stop.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489180" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic has allies all over Corellia, but they're no help if we can't reach them. We've got to find those neutron emitters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489182" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've received word that CorSec may have intel on the neutron emitters' location. They've carved out a safe haven in the Red Light Sector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489183" id2="17" version="1065353216">What does CorSec stand for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489183" id2="17" version="1065353216">CorSec? Are they allies?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489184" id2="17" version="1065353216">Corellian Security Force. Local law enforcement and our primary allies against the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489186" id2="17" version="1065353216">Red Light Sectors are usually full of criminals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489186" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure doesn't sound safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489187" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not anymore. Lot of civilians hiding there. Most of the casinos, clubs and cantinas have been shut down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489189" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then why are we here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489190" id2="17" version="1065353216">Without trams, the only way to reach the Red Light Sector is on foot--and Imperial shock troops control what's in between.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489192" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you attack the Empire's supply camps, the shock troops will be distracted. My escort will move to meet up with CorSec as fast as we can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489193" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll keep the shock troops busy until you've gotten through safely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489193" id2="17" version="1065353216">No need to rush.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489194" id2="17" version="1065353216">The path is littered with crashed ships and dead soldiers. I don't plan to linger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489196" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many troops will go to the supply camps, but others might not.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489196" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still, go with caution.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489197" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't worry about us. My men know this is no walk in the park.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489199" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've gotten pretty good at keeping the Imperials busy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489199" id2="17" version="1065353216">Take your time, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489200" id2="17" version="1065353216">That, I don't doubt--you've had the ops to prove it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489202" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make a big mess for the Imperials to clean up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489202" id2="17" version="1065353216">This ought to be fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489203" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't have time for hotshots. Get their attention and get out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489205" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can do that much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489206" id2="17" version="1065353216">You get caught, I might not be there to rescue you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489206" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're on your own.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489207" id2="17" version="1065353216">My men are the Republic's finest. You do your job, and they'll do theirs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489209" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you reach the Red Light Sector, meet me in the Gilded Descent. It's an old casino turned CorSec fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489211" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll let CorSec know we're coming. We'll be right behind you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489213" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Imperials have us trapped here. We've got to get past the blockade.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="489216" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lieutenant Bokete mentioned special forces. Do we know any specifics?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="489216" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not if we're prepared.</text>
		<text bitflag="336" id1="753966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, he's dead.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
