<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>13</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/balmorra/world/siege_of_balmorran_arms/factory_transmissions.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494511" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only a few targets remain airborne--and they've got nowhere to go. But one transport slipped past us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494513" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sending in ground troops--you intercept that ship at the factory's upper landing pad. No one survives this attack!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494514" id2="17" version="1065353216">Attack squadrons engaged! We've downed six Republic transports; I'm calling in additional ground-to-air weaponry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494515" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Darth Lachris. Our ships are closing on the Republic transports--keep destroying those landing pads, and there will be no escape for the enemy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Grand Marshal Cheketta here. I want to talk about sacrifice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494518" id2="17" version="1065353216">My troops and I gave up our homes in the Republic. But the rest of you... you weren't given a choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494520" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your planet was taken from you. You're giving up everything to get it back. That's the real deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494521" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Grand Marshal Cheketta. I've been hearing grumbling lately--people saying the Republic abandoned Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well, I may not be Republic Army anymore, but I'm still a patriot--so don't say it to my face.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494525" id2="17" version="1065353216">The treaty may not've left us much choice, but... the people of the Republic are still behind you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494526" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is Grand Marshal Cheketta to all personnel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Last night was a hell of a fight. Outnumbered ten to one, and we still beat back the Imps.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="494530" id2="17" version="1065353216">Victory's coming, boys. Keep this up, and we can all go home.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
