<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>69</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/corellia/world/republic/concierge/colonel_tott.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466155" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your work freeing those hostages saved a lot of soldiers, too. I'm sorry I lumped you in with the rest of your order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466156" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thanks for your help with the hostages. Getting rid of that artillery saves us a lot of pain on the battlefield.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466157" id2="17" version="1065353216">My forward observers let me know as soon as the last hostage was clear. I'm impressed that you pulled it off.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466159" id2="17" version="1065353216">I may have misjudged you, Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466161" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad I found someone who knows how to follow up talk with action.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now we can call in an air strike and take out that artillery at last.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466164" id2="17" version="1065353216">My concern was getting the hostages out alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466164" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad everyone's safe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mine too. I'm glad we were in agreement on that score.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466167" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone else would do the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466168" id2="17" version="1065353216">I respect humility in a soldier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466170" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't say thanks often--ask my men--but I appreciate what you've done. We'll be a lot safer with that artillery out of the way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466171" id2="17" version="1065353216">Next time, do it yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466172" id2="17" version="1065353216">Trust me, we won't come looking for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466174" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless you can &quot;magic&quot; the rest of those hostages out of the hotel, you'd better be heading back there double-time.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466175" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you're working hard, but there are still hostages inside. We need them all out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get your squad out of artillery range, Simmons! Move it!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466178" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire controls the whole battlefield now. Look for yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466180" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a soldier, I signed up for this, but Jedi... there's a lot of innocent people in the Daoba Hotel that never wanted to be part of your war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466181" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm here to assist, Colonel, but I need to know the situation--not just who to blame.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466181" id2="17" version="1065353216">I want to help them, and you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466182" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's using hostages as shields. That's the situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466184" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire declared war on the whole Republic, not just the Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466184" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't just our war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466185" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everyone knows the Sith attacked to get back at you-- but it's us who suffer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466187" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know you Havoc boys are trained for every situation, but the Daoba Hotel is bad on top of worse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466188" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like a good challenge, Colonel. How bad are we talking?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466188" id2="17" version="1065353216">A bad situation can be fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466189" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's taken a slew of hostages--part of their bold new experiment in civilian shields.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466191" id2="17" version="1065353216">So don't get comfy--the Imps can see us from the Daoba Hotel, and they'll shell here soon.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466192" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you know where the battery is, why not call in an airstrike and take it out?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466192" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shelling can be stopped.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466193" id2="17" version="1065353216">Normally, that's exactly what we'd do--but we can't risk all the civilian casualties.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466195" id2="17" version="1065353216">What would the Empire want with a hotel?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466195" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Daoba Hotel?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466196" id2="17" version="1065353216">Besides being a prime location for their big guns, it's given the Empire a slew of hostages to use against us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466198" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a war, bad stuff happens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466199" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd expect a response like that from a Jedi--all mumbo jumbo and no action. Let me spell it out for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466201" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got a hostage situation and all you can offer is a smart response?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466203" id2="17" version="1065353216">When they took over that hotel, the Empire locked the guests in their rooms and loaded artillery on the roof.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466205" id2="17" version="1065353216">Any bombardment would kill the hostages, and any troop assault gets pounded by the artillery. They've completely tied our hands.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466206" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire won't be expecting one person--I'll get the hostages out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466206" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can free the hostages.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466207" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right. I'll give you a chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466209" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's looking for troops, not a small strike team. We'll get the hostages out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466209" id2="17" version="1065353216">We can free the hostages.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466210" id2="17" version="1065353216">I like your attitude.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466212" id2="17" version="1065353216">My observers will let me know when you get all the hostages clear, then we can take the artillery out with an airstrike.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466214" id2="17" version="1065353216">Surely there's a way to deal with the artillery without endangering the hostages.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466214" id2="17" version="1065353216">There must be other solutions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466215" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got an idea...</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466217" id2="17" version="1065353216">Too bad for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466218" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's where you're wrong, Jedi; as far as I'm concerned this whole war's your fault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466220" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you want to prove me wrong, go into the hotel and get the hostages out so we can end this fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466221" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't have to prove anything to you, but that's no reason for the hostages to suffer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466221" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it for them, not you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466222" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shelling's a problem for all of us, but I've got an idea.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466224" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's expecting a full frontal assault; they won't be looking for someone sneaking in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466226" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can get the hostages free, we can take the artillery out as soon as everyone's clear of the hotel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466227" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have the hostages out as soon as possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466227" id2="17" version="1065353216">They'll be free before sunset.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466228" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just get them out safe, that's more important than speed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466230" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch how easy this is for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466231" id2="17" version="1065353216">Actions impress me, not words. You get everyone out safe and I'll be impressed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466233" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watch yourself once you get inside, the hostages are probably well guarded. I'll see you once it's done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466235" id2="17" version="1065353216">Call in your air strike. A few hostages won't be missed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="466235" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let them die. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466236" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should have guessed that would be your response when I saw you slinking around the rear echelon. Blasted coward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="466238" id2="17" version="1065353216">War's like dejarik; if you control the board, you control the game. Unfortunately, right now they control the board.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
