<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>90</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/coruscant/world/gree_repairing_coruscant/patakk.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Acknowledgment and reverence to you, black bisector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683614" id2="17" version="1065353216">The black bisector returns prosperous, and we form the red parallel, Senator Oranda. The Enclave-Republic bargain evolves achievement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683616" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you succeeded? You really helped all the Gree, uh, &quot;delegates&quot; complete their repairs to the infrastructure?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Eventually, yes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing's left on this planet to threaten these droids, Senator.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683618" id2="17" version="1065353216">Came. Saw. Destroyed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683619" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can put a nice statue of me in the Senate gardens.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683619" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm amazing, aren't I?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683620" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enclave delivers its promised Gree ingenuity, Senator. Coruscant acquires purple equilateral, and the enclave requests Republic reciprocity.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ambassador droid Pat-aK, the Republic has other damaged worlds that could benefit from your &quot;Gree ingenuity.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683624" id2="17" version="1065353216">I propose drafting a formal treaty between the Republic and the Gree enclave. What do you say to that?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683626" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seek a blue parallel with the enclave? I am astonished-gratified-challenged by the prospect. Let us initiate renewed white vertex at once!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683627" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm glad to have aided the formation of this new alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683627" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've done good work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683628" id2="17" version="1065353216">By your actions, we see that Gree technology will be invaluable as we rebuild the rest of the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683630" id2="17" version="1065353216">I see you've finally broken the language barrier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683630" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're communicating!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683631" id2="17" version="1065353216">I swear, sometimes he uses the same phrase to mean completely different things, but I'm getting the hang of it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683633" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe I should leave you two lovebirds alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683633" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's my cue to exit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683634" id2="17" version="1065353216">That would probably be for the best. Somehow I doubt you have much to contribute to political discussions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683636" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time for this soldier to get back to her war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683636" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's my cue to exit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683637" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time for this soldier to get back to his war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683637" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's my cue to exit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683638" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cultivate carefulness, black bisector. Tread toward orange acute, and you will conclude life cycle fulfilled.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't forget my reward.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683641" id2="17" version="1065353216">You honored my delegates, black bisector. Compensation acknowledges your blue obtuse.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683643" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forget these freaks, Senator. We don't need their kind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683643" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't trust outsiders.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683644" id2="17" version="1065353216">Begging your pardon, but the Republic needs all the friends it can get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683646" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have my thanks for all your efforts. I had almost given up on these droids before you came along. That would have been a costly mistake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683648" id2="17" version="1065353216">Acknowledgment and profound tribute, black bisector. This collaboration achieves through you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683654" id2="17" version="1065353216">May you experience blue tangent, black bisector. All depends on your collaboration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683655" id2="17" version="1065353216">Senator, please comprehend. Repairing Coruscant's infrastructure is green obtuse. To form the red parallel, we require a black bisector.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683657" id2="17" version="1065353216">Uh, this is pointless. I can't understand a word you're saying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683659" id2="17" version="1065353216">I use mistaken words and request patience. This will be clearer. The lower levels are alarming and filled with casualties. Active collaborators can solve problems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683661" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse me. Can any of you tell what this ambassador droid is trying to say?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683662" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, I give up. Do you have any idea what this ambassador droid is trying to say?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Aren't ambassadors usually organic?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683663" id2="17" version="1065353216">Ambassador droid?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683664" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is an unusual situation.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683666" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know I'm not a translator?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683667" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know. Even the protocol droids can't decipher these speech patterns. I'm at my wit's end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683669" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't know, don't care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683670" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just listen to the &quot;ambassador&quot; here. I've been down here all week trying to sort this out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683672" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm Senator Oranda. This is Pat-aK, from the Gree enclave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683674" id2="17" version="1065353216">Before you ask, the Gree are a remote people, isolationist. They helped build Coruscant's original infrastructure. We asked for assistance with repairs, they sent the droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683675" id2="17" version="1065353216">What sort of infrastructure needs repairing?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683675" id2="17" version="1065353216">Repairs?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683676" id2="17" version="1065353216">Power, water and waste reprocessing. Things this world needs to survive. The war left a lot of Coruscant in bad shape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you sure you're a Senator?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683678" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isn't this a bit beneath you?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683679" id2="17" version="1065353216">From Agamar. Small agricultural world with no real pull in the Senate, trying to change that by helping get Coruscant running again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683681" id2="17" version="1065353216">We shouldn't need strangers--or their droids--to come fix our problems.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683681" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why call in outsiders?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683682" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whole subsystems of Coruscant were busted in the war, but the tech is so old and weird there's nobody here who understands them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683684" id2="17" version="1065353216">The enclave bargains resources and offers reversal of Coruscant's yellow concave. We commit to white vertex to achieve this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683686" id2="17" version="1065353216">Gree droids seem to speak in Gree patterns. So this gibberish is what I've got to rebuild Coruscant with.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683688" id2="17" version="1065353216">I speak attentively in hopes of comprehension. The bargain encounters great challenges. My delegates suffer assault effecting the maintenance. Fire, damage and fear. Do you follow?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683689" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's something threatening stopping you from doing your job?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683689" id2="17" version="1065353216">Droids are being attacked?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683690" id2="17" version="1065353216">That is an approximate understanding, yes. Your comprehension is high.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683692" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coruscant isn't a safe place. That's not news.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683692" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a dangerous world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683693" id2="17" version="1065353216">My delegates comprehend your terms too well. They reject transit beyond this tower.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683695" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't follow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683696" id2="17" version="1065353216">My exertion to speak attentively has tangibly failed. Should I formulate new statements?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683698" id2="17" version="1065353216">Coruscant needs these repairs to continue functioning. Pat-aK, you have to convince your delegates to brave these dangers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683700" id2="17" version="1065353216">Impossible. My delegates require aid from one accustomed to fire, damage and chaos. A black bisector, you see?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683701" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is dangerous work--Jedi work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683701" id2="17" version="1065353216">I should do this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683702" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi? Ah! Even Gree comprehend this nature. Jedi are black bisector and red equilateral at once.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683704" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very few are accustomed to the things you describe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683704" id2="17" version="1065353216">A rare find, certainly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683705" id2="17" version="1065353216">I sense-soak-perceive you are one of these elite. You radiate experience of green-yellow-white perpendiculars.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683707" id2="17" version="1065353216">People always tell me I look good in black.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683707" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yeah, of course....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683708" id2="17" version="1065353216">From your humanoid face-patterns, I observe you embody deliberate facetiousness, a black bisector survival trait. Exceptional.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fire, damage and chaos are just about my favorite things.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683710" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like fun.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683711" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then potential exists for you to progress us to the red parallel, where all will prosper.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683713" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me help your delegates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683714" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isn't this the sort of thing we pay taxes for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="683714" id2="17" version="1065353216">Can't the Senate do anything?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683715" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm the only member of the Senate who believes the Gree droids can help us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683717" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen, the ambassador droid seems to like you. If you're willing to take on the risk to complete these repairs, it could mean everything to Coruscant.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683719" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will compensate the black bisector with useful and valued items only available from the enclave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683721" id2="17" version="1065353216">My delegates will describe their black spheres for you. These are bold, courageous, mission-callings. Speak to them and learn.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="683724" id2="17" version="1065353216">The white vertex with this Senator evolves as frustration. Your linguistics are primitive-bland-simplistic.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
