<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>12</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/global/mission_console_rep.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1146776" id2="17" version="1065353216">CHAPTER 4: Rise of the Hutt Cartel

***SPOILER WARNING: Due to spoilers contained in this quest chain, you may prefer to complete your class story first.

In a bold act of aggression, the HUTT CARTEL has seized control of wealthy neutral world MAKEB. With the Hutts growing ever more powerful, the Republic seeks to thwart this new threat to galactic security--and to find out what is so valuable about Makeb that the Hutts would risk all-out war to claim it....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1146777" id2="17" version="1065353216">CHAPTER 5: Shadow of Revan

***SPOILER WARNING: Due to spoilers contained in this quest chain, you may prefer to complete your class story as well as &quot;Rise of the Hutt Cartel&quot;, &quot;The Dread War&quot;, and &quot;Forged Alliances&quot; first.

An event too curious to be accidental places the focus on RISHI, a pirate backwater on the fringes of the Outer Rim where many surprises await--and the fate of the galaxy may well be decided....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1146794" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chapter 3 Epilogue: The Ilum Front

The Republic has set its sights on the remote ice world ILUM, where The Empire hopes to recover a rare and powerful resource that could wipe out the Republic for good....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1146801" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chapter 4 Interlude: The Dread War

***SPOILER WARNING: Due to spoilers in this quest chain, you may prefer to complete your class story, &quot;Rise of the Hutt Cartel&quot;, and the Operations &quot;Hutt Hospitality&quot;, &quot;Explosive Conflict&quot;, &quot;Terror from Beyond&quot;, and &quot;Scum and Villainy&quot; first.

In the aftermath of a disastrous fleet assault on ORICON, the Republic sends a team to the Outer Rim moon to crawl through the wreckage, rescue any survivors and confront the terrifying Sith Lords known as the DREAD MASTERS....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1149873" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chapter 5 Prelude: Forged Alliances

***SPOILER WARNING: Due to spoilers in this quest chain, you may prefer to complete your class story first.

The war against the Empire rages on, with a new strategic opportunity offering the chance to strike deep within the heart of the enemy. The droid T3-G2 waits aboard Carrick Station to provide more details....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1153302" id2="17" version="1065353216">Chapter 5 Epilogue: Rise of the Emperor

***SPOILER WARNING: This quest chain takes place after the events of &quot;Forged Alliances&quot; and &quot;Shadow of Revan&quot;.

In the wake of ominous events on Yavin 4, an immortal presence makes itself known on the historic Imperial hub of ZIOST. SIS Agent Theron Shan has placed his life at risk to travel to the hostile world and is hoping to contact his newest ally before it's too late....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1192585" id2="17" version="1065353216">KNIGHTS OF THE FALLEN EMPIRE

***SPOILER WARNING: This quest chain takes place after the events of &quot;Shadow of Revan&quot; and &quot;Rise of the Emperor&quot;.

The immortal Sith Emperor has disappeared after devastating the planet Ziost. Meanwhile, twin conquerors have carved a path of destruction across the Republic and the Sith Empire both. Determined to hunt these enemies down, Darth Marr has enlisted help from both factions, including a stalwart ally from the battle against Revan....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1226893" id2="17" version="1065353216">THE WAR FOR IOKATH

***SPOILER WARNING: Due to spoilers in this quest chain, you may prefer to complete &quot;Knights of the Fallen Empire&quot; and &quot;Knights of the Eternal Throne&quot; first.

The Eternal Empire has fallen. While the galaxy recovers from Vaylin's tyrannical rule, the Eternal Alliance mounts a vital mission to recover a powerful superweapon from the dangerous, unexplored planetary megastructure known as Iokath....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1230288" id2="17" version="1065353216">THE CRISIS ON UMBARA

***SPOILER WARNING: Due to spoilers in this quest, you may prefer to complete &quot;Knights of the Fallen Empire&quot; and &quot;Knights of the Eternal Throne&quot; first.

As the fight for a deadly superweapon rages on Iokath, the Alliance discovers a traitor in their midst. With war threatening to consume the Empire and Republic, the Alliance must act quickly and expose the traitor, before it's too late....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1232874" id2="17" version="1065353216">A TRAITOR AMONG THE CHISS

***SPOILER WARNING: Due to spoilers in this quest, you may prefer to complete &quot;Knights of the Fallen Empire&quot; and &quot;Knights of the Eternal Throne&quot; first.

As the hunt for the traitor to the Alliance stalls, a new ally among the Chiss Ascendency arrives with new intelligence and an offer for everyone's mutual benefit.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1233833" id2="17" version="1065353216">THE NATHEMA CONSPIRACY

***SPOILER WARNING: Due to spoilers in this quest, you may prefer to complete &quot;Knights of the Fallen Empire&quot; and &quot;Knights of the Eternal Throne&quot; first.

The shadowy Order of Zildrog is revealed, but your Alliance knows little yet about their new enemy. Lana Beniko may have more information.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1238532" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi Under Siege

***WARNING: Starting this quest will automatically complete all previous story quests, using default choices where those choices haven't yet been made.

The Alliance is called on upon by old allies in dealing with a conflict between the Sith Empire and a colony of Jedi on the ancient world of Ossus.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
