<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>124</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/jedi_knight/chapter_2/multi/master_satele_shan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go to Belsavis. If the Emperor seeks to destroy other worlds, we'll find them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640420" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's been so long. We thought you were lost forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640421" id2="17" version="1065353216">The mission to seize the Emperor has failed. He's more powerful than we realized. Master Braga, Leeha Narezz and Warren Sedoru are still missing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640423" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor's Wrath helped us escape. He betrayed his master to join our side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640424" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sith serve no one but themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640426" id2="17" version="1065353216">I altered my loyalties to avert a threat to myself--and you. Jedi are not alone in seeing the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640428" id2="17" version="1065353216">Centuries ago, I had a vision of the Emperor destroying the galaxy. Republic, Empire, everything--gone. This Jedi has the power to stop him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640429" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have good reason to believe he's telling the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640429" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should trust him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640430" id2="17" version="1065353216">Extinguishing all life in every star system? No one could do that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640430" id2="17" version="1065353216">How can he destroy everything?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640431" id2="17" version="1065353216">He wields power no Jedi or Sith has dreamed of.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640433" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll fly back to his fortress. You can betray him, and I'll strike the final blow.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640433" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we'll face him now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640434" id2="17" version="1065353216">You aren't strong enough to win that confrontation. Not yet.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640436" id2="17" version="1065353216">The renewed war is merely a diversion to conceal the Emperor's designs. His true plans are already in motion across the galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640438" id2="17" version="1065353216">One by one, every star system will simply die. Trillions will perish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640440" id2="17" version="1065353216">How does that benefit the Emperor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640442" id2="17" version="1065353216">He'll feed on those deaths to become more powerful than all the Jedi and Sith combined. An immortal being of unlimited power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640443" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor defeated my strike team without a fight. He's stronger than we realized.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640443" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's already too powerful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you the only Sith who learned the truth of his plans?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640444" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do the other Sith know?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640445" id2="17" version="1065353216">If others have, they're dead--or serving him without realizing the cost.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640447" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once everyone's dead, who will he rule over?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640447" id2="17" version="1065353216">And Emperor of nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640448" id2="17" version="1065353216">Domination holds no appeal to him. Only power. And this is not the sole galaxy in the universe.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640450" id2="17" version="1065353216">A thousand years ago, the Emperor tricked an entire Sith world into aiding a dark ritual. He promised great power.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640452" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only for himself, of course. The ritual consumed every living thing on the planet. He absorbed those life essences through the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640453" id2="17" version="1065353216">That explains how he's lived so long--and where all his power comes from.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640453" id2="17" version="1065353216">And became stronger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640454" id2="17" version="1065353216">That was merely one world. Imagine what he'll become after consuming millions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640456" id2="17" version="1065353216">He didn't kill all you people. Where did your Empire come from?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640456" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not every Sith died.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640457" id2="17" version="1065353216">The True Sith occupied many worlds at the galaxy's edge. Losing one planet was hardly crippling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640459" id2="17" version="1065353216">One less planet of Sith to worry about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640459" id2="17" version="1065353216">He did us a favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640460" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't speak like that. This is beyond our worst nightmares.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640462" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor has manipulated events for centuries toward one goal: performing an even greater ritual that will destroy this galaxy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640464" id2="17" version="1065353216">But the ritual requires a great sacrifice to begin: billions of simultaneous deaths. He seeks to commit genocide on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640466" id2="17" version="1065353216">That prison world holds the worst filth captured by the Republic. Mass murderers, tyrants--even captured Sith Lords.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640468" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've kept the planet's location secret for decades. If the Emperor has found it....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640470" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once the sacrifice occurs, the Emperor's ritual cannot be stopped. We must save Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640472" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;We&quot;? Your role in this is over, Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640473" id2="17" version="1065353216">Put away your weapon, Master Kaedan. The Sith is cooperating. He'll come with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640473" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's no need for threats.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640474" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele will determine what we do with him. Don't overstep yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640474" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't decide that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640475" id2="17" version="1065353216">I confess, I agree with Master Kaedan. Leaving the Emperor's executioner free is a terrible risk.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640477" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's served his purpose. If we need more information, it'll be easy to get from a prison cell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640477" id2="17" version="1065353216">Lock up the Sith.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640478" id2="17" version="1065353216">Leave me here, and your mission will fail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640480" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know the Emperor's ways. Belsavis is not the only world in danger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640482" id2="17" version="1065353216">We must find the others, and I cannot help you from a prison cell. Like it or not, we need each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640484" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's right. I can feel the truth. Without his help, we are all dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640486" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Council will concentrate on locating other worlds at risk--and finding our missing friends. I'm counting on you to stop the Emperor's plans.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640487" id2="17" version="1065353216">I know this has been hard for you to accept, but it's our best hope. I promise I won't fail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640487" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640488" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll need all the help we can get. There's room on my ship for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640488" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not coming with me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640489" id2="17" version="1065353216">The order needs leadership. This war is stretching us to the limit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Even if Master Braga and the others aren't dead, they're of no use to us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640491" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't waste time on them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640492" id2="17" version="1065353216">If they're alive, we won't leave them in captivity. And they may possess information we need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640494" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contact me when you reach Belsavis--and don't rely too closely on your &quot;ally.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640496" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm disrupting the fabled Jedi calm. I suggest we depart.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640504" id2="17" version="1065353216">May the Force be with you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640506" id2="17" version="1065353216">I brought the sensor logs, Master Satele.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640507" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you have many questions. Master Tol Braga will answer them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640509" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to finally meet you in person. They say you're the greatest Jedi the order has seen in generations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640511" id2="17" version="1065353216">I believe the Force has guided you to me. Together we'll defeat the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640512" id2="17" version="1065353216">Restoring peace to the galaxy is the reason I became a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640512" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's my life's work, Master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640513" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm good with a lightsaber, but that's an awful lot of work.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640513" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just the two of us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640514" id2="17" version="1065353216">If Master Braga has his way, you won't need weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640516" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's about time someone on the Council got serious about this war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640516" id2="17" version="1065353216">Finally, we're going to fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640517" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still impatient as ever. You're sure about this one, Braga?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640519" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm organizing a top secret strike team of our best and brightest. Jedi who don't know the meaning of failure.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640521" id2="17" version="1065353216">Twice you've saved the Jedi Order from destruction. Bengel Morr and Darth Angral were formidable opponents.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640523" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now I ask you to confront the ultimate evil--and help me capture the Sith Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640524" id2="17" version="1065353216">You don't dream small, do you, Master?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640524" id2="17" version="1065353216">A bold plan.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640525" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor is the most powerful Sith. What if we can't capture him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640525" id2="17" version="1065353216">That may not be possible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640526" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then we will do what is necessary to remove him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wouldn't it be easier to kill the Emperor?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640528" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't you mean destroy him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640529" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the opportunity presents itself, we shouldn't hesitate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640531" id2="17" version="1065353216">Killing the Emperor only creates a power vacuum. My plan will end the Sith Empire forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640533" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's an ancient fortress orbiting the Imperial homeworld Dromund Kaas. It's hidden by a powerful cloaking device.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640535" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Emperor rules his people from this cloaked fortress. Not even the highest-ranking Sith can find him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640537" id2="17" version="1065353216">But we're going to locate that fortress, get inside it and seize the Emperor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640538" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there's a way to achieve these goals, we must find it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640538" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then may the Force be with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640539" id2="17" version="1065353216">If even the Sith can't find the Emperor, what hope do we have? We'll just get ourselves killed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640539" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's a suicide mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640540" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let go of your fears. The Force is with us. We will not fail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless you plan to hold the Emperor hostage, leaving will be a bigger problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640542" id2="17" version="1065353216">Getting out is the real trick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640543" id2="17" version="1065353216">Our entire operation will be conducted in secret. The Empire won't know we're there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640545" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've already made great strides toward our objective.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640547" id2="17" version="1065353216">The man you saved on Tatooine scouted the Dromund Kaas system. His sensor logs will help us plan this assault.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640549" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll plot a hyperspace route through the Imperial Navy's defenses. Slip right past them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640551" id2="17" version="1065353216">Other members of my strike team are uncovering ways to pierce the cloaking device and defeat the security around the Emperor's fortress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640553" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could use your expertise on Balmorra. The Empire and Republic are at war there, and the fighting has endangered our mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640554" id2="17" version="1065353216">My ship's ready for departure. Tell your people I'm on my way.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640554" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll leave immediately.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640555" id2="17" version="1065353216">Open war on Balmorra? When did this happen?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640555" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're at war?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640556" id2="17" version="1065353216">The invasion just began. Balmorra belonged to the Republic before the Sith conquered it during the last war. Now, the Republic wants it back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640558" id2="17" version="1065353216">What would I bring to your little strike team?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640558" id2="17" version="1065353216">My expertise?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640559" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're on a mission of peace, but we'll need the Jedi Order's greatest warrior to achieve that goal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640561" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've placed great responsibility on you, but I know you won't fail us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640563" id2="17" version="1065353216">Contact your fellow strike team member, Warren Sedoru, when you reach Balmorra. He'll explain the mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640565" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll give you the holofrequencies of your fellow strike team members. Contact them when you reach Hoth and Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640567" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're going to save the galaxy. May the Force be with us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640570" id2="17" version="1065353216">They could use your particular expertise on Hoth and Balmorra.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Which objective is more pressing, Hoth or Balmorra?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="640571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Where should I go first?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640572" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're both mission-critical. Neither will be easy to accomplish. Do what you feel is right.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="640574" id2="17" version="1065353216">You travel with one of our order's greatest champions. Welcome.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
