<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>70</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/world/imperial/found_in_translation/specialist_nattis.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707879" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once we finish our analysis, we'll find a reliable defense for this new technology. You've done the Empire a great service.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707881" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Esh-kha were ransacking the vault, but I dealt with them. Here are your samples.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707881" id2="17" version="1065353216">I stopped the Esh-kha.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707882" id2="17" version="1065353216">These are even more advanced than I thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707884" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't believe it--Nattis was right. I owe you my thanks for getting involved.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707886" id2="17" version="1065353216">An Esh-kha force armed with these would've been disastrous. Some sort of plasma recharger... Belsavis could've fallen completely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707887" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were right this time, but don't let it go to your head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707887" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just don't get cocky, Nattis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707888" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wise words, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707890" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should be proud of standing by your convictions, Nattis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707890" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes--you stopped a disaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707891" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're kind to say so, but I only did my job.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your narrow vision nearly cost the Empire its foothold. You're lucky to outlive this mistake.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707893" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hayg, you should be hanged.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Thank you for your mercy. I'll respect Specialist Nattis's expertise in the future, I promise.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707896" id2="17" version="1065353216">Well... I'm just glad things worked out in the end.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707898" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take the samples for analysis. Understanding how to defend against this technology is critical.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't forget to bring back samples of the weaponry once you've dealt with the Esh-kha.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707901" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Reclamation Service is mandated to study all dangerous alien technology.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Military decisions are my call!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707905" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord--forgive my tone. Our science officer here thinks he understands troop deployments better than me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707907" id2="17" version="1065353216">Agent--talk some sense into our science officer here, would you? He thinks he understands troop deployments better than me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707909" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hunter. The lone-wolf lifestyle must be nice... no dimwit subordinates. Our science officer here thinks he knows troop deployments better than me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707911" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry about the tone. Our science officer here thinks he understands troop deployments better than me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707913" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm simply concerned. We engaged the Esh-kha yesterday. Two were carrying strange blasters--ancient but highly advanced. What's scary is it felt like a test.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707914" id2="17" version="1065353216">You think they were evaluating the weapons?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707914" id2="17" version="1065353216">What kind of test?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707915" id2="17" version="1065353216">Against Imperial capabilities, yes. They slaughtered several men then just disengaged. These blasters were clearly alien.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707917" id2="17" version="1065353216">Identify yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707918" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, uh... Specialist Nattis, Reclamation Service. My expertise is alien cultures, and these blasters were clearly alien.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707920" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're dangerously close to insubordination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707920" id2="17" version="1065353216">You dare speak out of turn?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707921" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insubordination is a dangerous game. Perhaps even deadly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707921" id2="17" version="1065353216">You dare speak out of turn?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707922" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't think Imperial types took kindly to insubordination.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707922" id2="17" version="1065353216">Challenging your boss, huh?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707923" id2="17" version="1065353216">Insubordination in a combat zone can land you in a shallow grave.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707923" id2="17" version="1065353216">You dare question a superior?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707924" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have no choice. I study alien cultures for the Reclamation Service, and these weapons are clearly a threat to Imperial forces.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707926" id2="17" version="1065353216">Their bolts boil through armor. The medics say the tissue damage is horrific.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707928" id2="17" version="1065353216">I told Nattis--the Republic's our priority, and we're already shorthanded. We just--please excuse me. I have a team reporting in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707930" id2="17" version="1065353216">My lord, I understand his perspective. But if the Esh-kha acquire enough of these weapons, they'll become the biggest threat to Imperial forces on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707931" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's ignoring this fact: Once they've acquired enough of these weapons, the Esh-kha will crush us, Republic or no Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707932" id2="17" version="1065353216">You seem confident they can get their hands on additional weapons.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707932" id2="17" version="1065353216">How would they get more?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707933" id2="17" version="1065353216">Intelligence says the Esh-kha recently cracked an ancient storage vault. I translated the manifest fragments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707935" id2="17" version="1065353216">This isn't my business.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707936" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because Hayg won't get involved. The Esh-kha recently cracked an ancient storage vault. I translated the manifest fragments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707938" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think you're blowing this out of proportion.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707938" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like an exaggeration.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707939" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not. The Esh-kha recently cracked an ancient storage vault. I translated the manifest fragments.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707941" id2="17" version="1065353216">The vault holds large numbers of weapons confiscated by an ancient alien tribunal. Enough to arm the entire Esh-kha population.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707943" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need to stop them and study this technology before we face it again.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707944" id2="17" version="1065353216">I shall slaughter these fools and give you your chance for study.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707944" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once I've dispatched these Esh-kha, you will have ample opportunity for study.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707945" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707946" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can solve your Esh-kha problem. For a price, of course.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707946" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707947" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oh, I see. I think I can convince the Reclamation Service to scrape something together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707949" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll neutralize the Esh-kha threat and give you your chance for research.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707949" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll do it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707950" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, but let's make it quick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707951" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course. I understand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707953" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful of the Esh-kha guarding the vault. They've already figured out those weapons--I doubt we can even find the trigger.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707955" id2="17" version="1065353216">But anything you can bring back... we'll see what we can do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry--I'm with Hayg on this one.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="707957" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't help. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707958" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's... disappointing. I hope I'll find someone willing to do something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="707960" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm afraid I can't talk. I'm waiting for an intelligence report.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
