<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>53</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/world/republic/for_want_of_a_droid/officer_brad_narong.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515095" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's useless! This droid's nothing but a junk heap without replacement parts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515096" id2="17" version="1065353216">With all the droids up and running, we've got a fighting chance against those thugs. Thanks for helping out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515098" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got your motivator coils; are your droids ready?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515099" id2="17" version="1065353216">They're as ready as they can be. I should just be able to drop in the coils, and they'll be running.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515101" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not out of the woods, but at least with the droids to help out, we've got a fighting chance. Glad you made it back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515102" id2="17" version="1065353216">I said I'd bring you the motivator coils; I keep my promises.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515102" id2="17" version="1065353216">I gave you my word.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515103" id2="17" version="1065353216">It wasn't any big deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515104" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was a huge deal for my men. Maybe we'll even survive this riot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515105" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're lucky I was bored.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515106" id2="17" version="1065353216">We did fine on our own until the Empire came down on us. You do your part, we'll do ours.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515108" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is a good start, but I've got more droids than this. Can you get a few more coils?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515109" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still here, huh? Still waiting on those motivator coils.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515111" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sorry, Master Jedi, didn't hear you. Crazy racket those convicts are making.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515113" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can't take it, Major. Between the convicts shooting us and our equipment breaking, it's a wonder we're alive.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515115" id2="17" version="1065353216">You guys should wear a badge or something--for a second I thought another convict got in. They've been shooting at us all day.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515117" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's a hundred screaming crazies out there, all my men are hurt, and the warden droids that are supposed to help us don't function.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515118" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can drive off the prisoners and buy you a little breathing room.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515118" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let me handle the convicts.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515119" id2="17" version="1065353216">It won't help--they'll just come back. If our droids were working, we'd have a chance, but they all need motivator coils.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515121" id2="17" version="1065353216">They don't look that beat up, let me take a look at them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515121" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can help with the droids.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515122" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless you've got a pocket full of new motivator coils, you're not going to be much help--without them, these droids are worthless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515124" id2="17" version="1065353216">The blasted Mandalorians raided our supply depot and ran off with our extra coils, so we've got nothing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515126" id2="17" version="1065353216">Figure out how to deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515127" id2="17" version="1065353216">Easy for you to say--you don't have a mob of blood-crazed prisoners screaming for your head.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515129" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not to mention that the Mandalorians attacked and took all our motivator coils--the one thing that would get our droids working.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515131" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mandos aren't like the other convicts--they're more like a military unit than a gang, even set up their own headquarters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515132" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are Mandalorians doing on Belsavis?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515132" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mandalorians? Here?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515133" id2="17" version="1065353216">They were captured after they wiped out some backwater planet. Real nasty, real resourceful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515135" id2="17" version="1065353216">Have you tried negotiating with them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515135" id2="17" version="1065353216">Maybe they'd make an exchange.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515136" id2="17" version="1065353216">They don't negotiate--they shoot anybody who gets too close to their little base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mandos are no big threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515139" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you've never seen them fight--imagine the rest of these murderers with military training.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515141" id2="17" version="1065353216">They've even scavenged a bunch of old warden droids and turned them into turret defenses. That's why they took the coils.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515143" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to help? Break open those turrets the Mandos built and bring me the motivator coils. With those, these droids will be back online.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515144" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have those coils back in your hands before nightfall.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515144" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course I'll help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stay calm, and stay brave. I'll find the coils.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course I'll help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Neutralize the turrets and &quot;requisition&quot; the motivator coils, check. I'll be right back.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515146" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course I'll help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515147" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sure, I'll get your coils--beats paying for them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515147" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course I'll help you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515148" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you can pull it off, we'll have a chance, but I'll believe it when I see it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515150" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll need to find their base.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515151" id2="17" version="1065353216">The camp's near the remnants of the prison housing--the turrets guard the perimeter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515153" id2="17" version="1065353216">Be careful out there, the Mandos are going to go ballistic if you start breaking their toys.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="515155" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do it yourself. [Refuse quest]</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515156" id2="17" version="1065353216">We managed just fine before you brought the Empire down on us. We'll be okay now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="515158" id2="17" version="1065353216">Another broken down droid--seems like nothing around here works right anymore.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
