<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>60</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/open_worlds/class/imperial_spy/chapter_3/intro/colony_control_computer.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490105" id2="17" version="1065353216">Identifying? Colony Control systems locked down. Enter code! Remote access in progress.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490107" id2="17" version="1065353216">No Hunter, but a lot of really weird tech. Hate to say it, but maybe we should call your bosses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490109" id2="17" version="1065353216">The machinery is a parasite, clinging to the colony controls. If Hunter was here, we think we should call our superiors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490111" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't recognize any of this equipment. If Hunter set it up, we should probably contact headquarters so we don't... I don't know, blow up the colony.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490113" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've never seen technology like this. Some sort of override box connected to the machine... your SIS friend must have set it up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490115" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll have to create a link up to headquarters. I don't fancy electrocuting myself without expert opinions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490118" id2="17" version="1065353216">Isen Four colony to Imperial Intelligence headquarters. Secure routing. This is Cipher Nine--there's some sort of device here....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490119" id2="17" version="1065353216">Cipher Nine? I got your report, but we can barely read you. What's going on?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490120" id2="17" version="1065353216">I haven't found Hunter, but he left his mark on the control center.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="490120" id2="17" version="1065353216">Still looking for our target.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490121" id2="17" version="1065353216">Most of the colonists are dead, and the control center is a wreck. Hunter might be responsible.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="490121" id2="17" version="1065353216">This place is a disaster.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490122" id2="17" version="1065353216">Right now, I need you to focus and help me find Hunter.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="490122" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't ask stupid questions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490123" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm linked into the colony's communications relay. Strange tech interference... Fixers don't recognize it, but I can shut it down....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490125" id2="17" version="1065353216">You followed me. You cut off control. I'm a little put out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490127" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not that it really matters. I'm long gone, I got my massacre and besides--it was for propriety more than anything.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490128" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean? Who ordered the colony destroyed?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="490128" id2="17" version="1065353216">You killed these people?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490129" id2="17" version="1065353216">Were you this obnoxious to Ardun Kothe? Or am I special?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="490129" id2="17" version="1065353216">Arrogant as always.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490130" id2="17" version="1065353216">I tried to behave for the SIS--but for you and me?--let's be bad.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490132" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have unfinished business. Leave the tech behind and face me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="490132" id2="17" version="1065353216">Show yourself in person.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490133" id2="17" version="1065353216">Generous offer, but I'm going to say &quot;no.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490135" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, I don't have anything against that place. But if you want a war to start right, you've got to grease the wheels.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490137" id2="17" version="1065353216">When the Republic hears that the Empire slaughtered thousands of colonists who surrendered? There won't be any more &quot;peaceful resolutions.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490138" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why make this conflict bloodier than it has to be?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="490138" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want more violence.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490139" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm making the war exactly as bloody as it has to be.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490141" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're not doing this for the SIS, and you're not doing it alone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="490141" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me who's behind this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490142" id2="17" version="1065353216">Innocent people are dead. Republic citizens--your people!</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="490142" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're sick.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490143" id2="17" version="1065353216">Touchy, aren't you? Did I hit a nerve?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490145" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time for me to go. And you need to stop coming after me, &quot;Cipher Nine.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490147" id2="17" version="1065353216">Because without anonymity, you won't last long--and I can make your operations very public.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490149" id2="17" version="1065353216">Blast. I couldn't trace him... I'll pull what I can from the machinery, but he's more right than he knows. The survivors are a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490150" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do the survivors pose a threat?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="490150" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you mean?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490151" id2="17" version="1065353216">These people surrendered before, and they're half-dead. They won't be trouble.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="490151" id2="17" version="1065353216">The colonists are harmless.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490152" id2="17" version="1065353216">As soon as word gets out what happened, other worlds we've captured will rebel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490154" id2="17" version="1065353216">Watchers Seven and Nine are... strategizing. They recommend eliminating the survivors on Isen Four so the news of the massacre is contained.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490155" id2="17" version="1065353216">The colonists are a resource we can still exploit. We just need them under control.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="490155" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should make use of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490156" id2="17" version="1065353216">What you're suggesting is unconscionable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="490156" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't kill them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490161" id2="17" version="1065353216">You activated the Eradicators once. This is a chance to save Imperial lives at the cost of Republic ones.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490163" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then our troops will waste time putting down bloody rebellions instead of winning the war.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490165" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, look... I can give you the coordinates of the largest cluster of life-forms. Maybe you can negotiate something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490167" id2="17" version="1065353216">But I need to send in the death squads soon. Your reputation may be secure, but mine isn't.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490169" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one will know what happened on Isen Four until we're ready.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="490169" id2="17" version="1065353216">Very well; they all die.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490170" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want them dead, I'll make them dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="490170" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can get rid of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490171" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir, it's--if they spread word, rebellions will start on half the captured planets. You can... buy us time to prepare.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490173" id2="17" version="1065353216">Oxygen generators at these coordinates; distress beacons here. Eliminate them all, and death squads can take care of anyone left. We'll see you back home.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490175" id2="17" version="1065353216">Systems unavailable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="490176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Life support systems failing. Evacuate the colony immediately.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
