<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>50</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_2/consulting_the_expert/doctor_oggurobb.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1018603" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need more droids--not excuses!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1018605" id2="17" version="1065353216">Perhaps you should have left me some isotope-5. What am I supposed to build your war machines with, durachrome and phobium?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1018607" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am an artist, Toborro--but I require the proper time and materials to produce my masterpieces. Respect my process!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1018609" id2="17" version="1065353216">Liar! The Republic and Empire have united against me, and now you've joined the enemy. I see who stands in your lab!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018610" id2="17" version="1065353216">The chrono's running. You will not escape justice--or this Jedi. Give us what we want, and we'll be merciful.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1018610" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're closing in on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1018611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do you never tire of your own voice?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018613" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're fighting over a dying planet. This madness must end. Let the Jedi help you negotiate peace and end this pointless conflict.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1018613" id2="17" version="1065353216">We come in peace.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1018614" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you are trying to put me to sleep... it is working!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Havoc Squad's coming for you next. Be a good host and prepare snacks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1018616" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't feel left out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1018617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your name may intimidate the Empire, but in Huttese, that word translates as &quot;clumsy half-wit who dies embarrassingly.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018619" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't mind me, I'm just enjoying the show. I never knew how big Hutts' nostrils could flare when they get upset with each other.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1018619" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're cute when you bicker.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1018620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not mock me! I'll grind that pretty face of yours into the dirt!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018622" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic hasn't made friends with the Empire--and the doctor doesn't work for us. Not yet, anyway.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1018622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wrong, Toborro.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1018623" id2="17" version="1065353216">You lie! You're all liars! But I see the truth!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Anyone who isn't with us is on the losing team. I'm sure Doctor Oggurobb is smart enough to see that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1018625" id2="17" version="1065353216">The doctor works for us, now.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1018626" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew it! I will use your liquefied brains to grease my droids, doctor!</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1018628" id2="17" version="1065353216">Listen to reason. Think! It is not too late to cut a deal with the Republic.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1018630" id2="17" version="1065353216">There will be no deal! If you are not with me, you are dead!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018632" id2="17" version="1065353216">Churlish nincompoop! You can see why I was forced to lend my brilliance to your assault. I'm glad you're here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018633" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know why we're here. Millions of innocent people will die if we don't get the fuel for Toborro's ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1018633" id2="17" version="1065353216">We need the isotope-5.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Then you have come to the wrong place. Toborro took every microgram of it--including the ark's fuel rods that I constructed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018636" id2="17" version="1065353216">You helped us defeat your own security grid. I thought your people only spoke in Huttese.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1018636" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're our mysterious friend.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018637" id2="17" version="1065353216">All Hutts can speak your language--we simply choose not to. Given the circumstances, I prefer to avoid linguistic misunderstandings.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unless you want your beautiful mind splattered all over this lab, you'd better cooperate.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1018639" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't cross us. We're violent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please don't waste your time on grisly threats. I submit to your superior position.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018642" id2="17" version="1065353216">We have complementary goals. You want what Toborro possesses, and I wish very much not to die here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018644" id2="17" version="1065353216">Provide me with transport off this doomed planet. I will aid your efforts to recover the isotope-5 fuel rods that power Toborro's ark.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell us where the fuel rods are, and we'll consider your offer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1018645" id2="17" version="1065353216">Share what you know now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018646" id2="17" version="1065353216">What you seek lies within Toborro's private fortress. That part is elementary. Accessing it will require abundant artistry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018648" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're the only halfway-decent Hutt we've met in a while. I suppose that should count for something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1018648" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have a deal.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018649" id2="17" version="1065353216">How fortunate for me, that my brethren have profoundly lowered your expectations.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018651" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm taking everything in your databanks--and anything that isn't nailed down.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1018651" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm looting this place, first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018652" id2="17" version="1065353216">I was going to suggest the same thing. Pity to let all this go to waste when the planet implodes.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018654" id2="17" version="1065353216">I have a personal shuttle here. It's large enough to accommodate us all. Thanks to you, it can now fly.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1018656" id2="17" version="1065353216">We should leave before Toborro sends an army to kill us. Take me to your allies, and I will explain what must be done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1051685" id2="17" version="1065353216">Shall we depart? I'd rather not be here when Toborro sends reinforcements.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1051687" id2="17" version="1065353216">My apologies for the earlier subterfuge--a necessary contrivance. Toborro seized control of my defenses and was watching me closely. But I am no one's prisoner!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1051688" id2="17" version="1065353216">I keep a shuttle nearby that seats six--a tight squeeze, but I'll just fit. I assume you brought your own transportation.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
