<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>26</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/exp/01/makeb/world_arc/republic/hub_2/consulting_the_expert/mysterious_ally.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019311" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's high time you Republic agitators showed up! Toborro and his brutes have this entire facility captive. I was wondering if you'd ever bother liberating it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019925" id2="17" version="1065353216">Toborro's security grid is down. We're entering the main complex.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019926" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once you've eliminated them and disabled any internal defenses, we will evacuate Sanctuary. Your heroics are most appreciated, and we will return the favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019928" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is obvious you came for the illustrious Doctor Oggurobb. We are transmitting his coordinates so that you may quickly find him! Best of luck!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019945" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're not getting a stable image on this end. Who are you, and how do you know us?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1019945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Identify yourself.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019946" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please, call me Lippi. After all you've done to the Cartel, everyone on Makeb knows you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019948" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Republic sent me here to protect its people from a Hutt invasion. The word you're looking for is &quot;defender.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1019948" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm a hero, not an &quot;agitator.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019949" id2="17" version="1065353216">No offense intended. I'm confident you are quite the hero.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019951" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not here to free anyone--unless by &quot;liberate&quot; you mean &quot;throw in binder-cuffs and drag away for questioning.&quot;</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1019951" id2="17" version="1065353216">We're here to capture someone.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019952" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not everyone here serves Toborro willingly. This was an independent research facility before he blundered in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019954" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are many on this mesa being forced to work as slaves. We would be honored to aid your attack.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019956" id2="17" version="1065353216">We possess detailed data on the lethal security grid Toborro installed across the mesa. We'll help you destroy it so you can enter the main complex and we can escape.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019957" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you have information, now's the time to share it. Things are about to get loud.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1019957" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right, start talking.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019958" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you know how everything works and you're on the inside, can't you deactivate the grid from there?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1019958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why can't you do it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019959" id2="17" version="1065353216">Like my peers, I am confined to my laboratory. It required considerable ingenuity just slicing this comm channel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019961" id2="17" version="1065353216">The security grid doesn't matter. I'm after a target--and once I have him, I'm leaving.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="1019961" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't care about you people.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019962" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not only will you find gaining entrance to the complex impossible, escaping with your prize will prove equally challenging. Listen to reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019964" id2="17" version="1065353216">I am transmitting data on several key objectives. Each will provide you ample opportunity to convey your displeasure with Toborro. Stand by....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1019966" id2="17" version="1065353216">Follow those instructions precisely. You'll not only gain access to the main complex, you'll destroy Toborro's security grid. We'll speak again when you breach the main complex entrance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="1026719" id2="17" version="1065353216">Splendiferous! You've eliminated many of that bully's unforgiveably barbaric thugs, but more remain inside the complex.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
