<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>34</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/class/jedi_knight/master_satele_shan.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="493001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Satele, we've arrived at Belsavis. Have you learned anything?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509173" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire just launched a surprise attack there. Dangerous prisoners are free from their cells to wreak havoc down on the surface.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509175" id2="17" version="1065353216">A mere diversion. The Emperor has only one true goal - the annihilation of all life on this world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509176" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just tell me what to do.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509176" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll stop him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509177" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wiping out an entire planet isn't easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509177" id2="17" version="1065353216">What's his plan?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509178" id2="17" version="1065353216">We don't know how the Emperor intends to destroy all life on Belsavis.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509180" id2="17" version="1065353216">If he wants to execute a bunch of sociopathic criminals, I say we let him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509180" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good riddance to bad rubbish.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509181" id2="17" version="1065353216">Jedi respect life. And not all on the world are criminals. The guards and their families live on the surface, too.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509183" id2="17" version="1065353216">The destruction of Belsavis will fuel the Emperor's ritual and make him unstoppable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509185" id2="17" version="1065353216">We do have one lead. Intelligence indicates a high-ranking Imperial named Executor Krannus recently arrived on world.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509187" id2="17" version="1065353216">Krannus is a pure-blooded Sith. Fanatically loyal to the Emperor. Whatever the plan is, he's the one tasked with carrying it out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509188" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do we have any idea where Executor Krannus is now?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509188" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not if I find him first.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509189" id2="17" version="1065353216">What else can you tell me about Executor Krannus?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509189" id2="17" version="1065353216">You know him?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509190" id2="17" version="1065353216">Unlike most of Sith blood, Krannus was not born with an affinity for the Force.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509192" id2="17" version="1065353216">Despite this, he has risen quickly through the ranks of the Emperor's army. It would be a mistake to underestimate him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509194" id2="17" version="1065353216">He can't carry out the plan if he's dead.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509194" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess I'll have to kill him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509195" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enna Tabord, a member of our Order, is already on the surface looking for Krannus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509197" id2="17" version="1065353216">She'll help you find the Executor. But she isn't strong enough to stop him - that task falls on you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509198" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, master.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509199" id2="17" version="1065353216">If these are the most dangerous criminals in the galaxy, should we just leave them on the loose?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509199" id2="17" version="1065353216">And the escaped prisoners?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509200" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the Emperor succeeds in his ritual all life in the galaxy will be extinguished.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509202" id2="17" version="1065353216">What your companion says is true, but Jedi do not turn their backs on those in need.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509204" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do not endanger your mission, but do what you can to help the Republic restore order.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509206" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sometimes I feel like I'm the only Jedi getting anything done.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="509206" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't it always?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509207" id2="17" version="1065353216">We all serve in our own way. You are our greatest warrior... and our best hope.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="509209" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go to the planet's surface and meet Enna at the coordinates I'm sending you now. May the Force be with you.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
