<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>88</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/belsavis/class/jedi_knight/warden_bartaph.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508815" id2="17" version="1065353216">Belsavis owes you a debt it can never repay.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508817" id2="17" version="1065353216">Colonel Bartaph, I was told you wanted to see me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508818" id2="17" version="1065353216">First, let me express my gratitude. Your actions saved many Republic soldiers.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508819" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm always glad to help the Republic Army.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508819" id2="17" version="1065353216">It was my honor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508820" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some of my superiors don't trust your Order. They'll have to revise their opinions after this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508822" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your special forces were invaluable during the battle with Executor Krannus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508822" id2="17" version="1065353216">And they returned the favor.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508823" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make sure their actions are properly recognized. It isn't every day soldiers are praised by a Jedi.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508825" id2="17" version="1065353216">I won't waste your time, but there's something I need you to clear up for me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508827" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's forces were all over Belsavis when I arrived. Someone had to stop them, and your people weren't up to it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508827" id2="17" version="1065353216">They couldn't save themselves.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508828" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your lack of humility aside, my people only just got here. We're doing fine, thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508830" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make the rest of this quick. There's some confusion I need you to clear up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508832" id2="17" version="1065353216">My forces apprehended this man during the riots. He was with a prisoner gang that attacked some guards.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508834" id2="17" version="1065353216">I told you. I was shooting at the gang, not the guards! I'm on your side.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508836" id2="17" version="1065353216">According to his comm logs, you spoke several times. Why were you communicating with one of the galaxy's worst criminals?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508837" id2="17" version="1065353216">His information helped me hunt down Executor Krannus.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508837" id2="17" version="1065353216">He assisted my mission.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508838" id2="17" version="1065353216">That corroborates half of his story. The rest of it is still a problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508840" id2="17" version="1065353216">He said he could help find Executor Krannus, but all I received was some useless data.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508840" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] We hardly spoke.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508841" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's a lie! I helped you find Doctor Gantrell's team! They'll back me up!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508843" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pak is looking for a way off Belsavis. He thought helping me was his ticket out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508843" id2="17" version="1065353216">I think he was using me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508844" id2="17" version="1065353216">I never asked you for anything!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508846" id2="17" version="1065353216">I risked my life for you, and you turned around and stole those weapon prototypes!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508848" id2="17" version="1065353216">The ones Doctor Gantrell's team was developing? You took them?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508849" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Jedi are at war and I'll take every advantage I can get.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508849" id2="17" version="1065353216">I need to stop the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508850" id2="17" version="1065353216">I understand. Would've been nice if you'd asked.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508852" id2="17" version="1065353216">I make dozens of life-and-death choices every day. This was one of them.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508852" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't question my actions.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508853" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll have to report this to my superiors. If they have a problem with your decision, they'll be in touch.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508855" id2="17" version="1065353216">Frankly, I'm starting to wonder if Pak is telling the truth. I'm inclined to believe him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508856" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seriously, Colonel, you shouldn't believe everything that comes out of his mouth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508856" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Lie] He's lying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508857" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're right. I'll put him in a cell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508859" id2="17" version="1065353216">No! That's not fair! You couldn't have saved this planet without me!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Despite his lies about the prototypes, he did help me. He's earned some freedom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508860" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let him go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508861" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't know what's going on between you two, but I have bigger problems right now.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508863" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not a prisoner anymore. The warden made me an honorary guard. It's true!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508865" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no evidence to support your statement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508867" id2="17" version="1065353216">My instinct is to throw Pak into the nearest cell, but there is a chance he's being honest. What do you think?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508868" id2="17" version="1065353216">My forces apprehended this prisoner during the riots. I need to know why one of the galaxy's worst criminals was helping you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508869" id2="17" version="1065353216">There must be some mistake. Pak is not one of the inmates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508869" id2="17" version="1065353216">He's a guard, not a prisoner.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508870" id2="17" version="1065353216">I thought Pak was one of the guards. You're telling me he's one of the inmates?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508870" id2="17" version="1065353216">What are you talking about?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508871" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could sense you were hiding something.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508871" id2="17" version="1065353216">I knew you were a liar, Pak.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508872" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's true. I came here a decade ago as a prisoner, and I deserved it. I did things you don't want to know about.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508874" id2="17" version="1065353216">Being on Belsavis--surrounded by scum just like me--it opened my eyes. Even if I could never leave here, I could still change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508876" id2="17" version="1065353216">It took years, but I did it. The warden made me an honorary guard. Said I earned that.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508877" id2="17" version="1065353216">You worked hard to turn your life around, and he rewarded you for it.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508877" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds like you did.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508878" id2="17" version="1065353216">You kept this a secret from me. You're a liar.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508878" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't believe you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508879" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once a criminal, always a criminal. Sooner or later, you'll fall back to your old ways.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508879" id2="17" version="1065353216">People don't change.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508880" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm trying to make up for the terrible things I've done. The warden gave me that chance.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508882" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you claim. Unfortunately, we have no evidence to support your story.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508884" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's possible the records were destroyed in all the chaos. However, it's also possible you're lying.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Whatever he used to be, he's changed. I couldn't have saved Belsavis without him.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508885" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pak is a good man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508886" id2="17" version="1065353216">What were his crimes? Why is Pak imprisoned for life on Belsavis?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508886" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why was he a prisoner?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508887" id2="17" version="1065353216">Only the most vicious and dangerous criminals end up here. Take the worst crimes you can imagine, and multiply them by a thousand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508889" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not like that anymore. I helped you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508891" id2="17" version="1065353216">He had every chance to tell me the truth about himself. I think he'd say anything to stay out of a cell.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508891" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't believe him, Colonel.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508892" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can help you. I've changed.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508894" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now you see my dilemma. I don't want to imprison someone who doesn't deserve it, but I don't want to set a criminal free.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508895" id2="17" version="1065353216">I couldn't have completed my mission without Pak. He's earned his freedom.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508895" id2="17" version="1065353216">Let him go.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508896" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm not authorized to let Pak leave Belsavis, but I can see that he is restored to his guard status.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508898" id2="17" version="1065353216">This means everything to me. Thank you both.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508900" id2="17" version="1065353216">If the warden made Pak a guard, someone knows about it. Keep him in the holding cell until you find the truth.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508900" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait until you find proof.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508901" id2="17" version="1065353216">That sounds reasonable. Pak, you'll stay here until we get this all straightened out.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508903" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess it's better than going back into genpop....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508905" id2="17" version="1065353216">Criminals don't get special treatment. Lock him up with the rest of the inmates.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="508905" id2="17" version="1065353216">Throw him back in the prison.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508906" id2="17" version="1065353216">No! Do you know what the other prisoners will do to me? You're a disgrace to the Jedi!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508908" id2="17" version="1065353216">Enough! Remove the prisoner at once!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508910" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure you have business elsewhere. Thank you again for everything you did here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="508914" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm trying to bring some order to Belsavis. You'll have to wait.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
