<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>38</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/taris/world/burnoff/kon_yel.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623384" id2="17" version="1065353216">I will be on Taris for some time to come. There are many buildings in fragile condition, all of which must be studied.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623387" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can smell chemicals on you. But I also smell fire and smoke.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623389" id2="17" version="1065353216">Did you complete the burnoff? All the toxins and pollutants have been incinerated?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623390" id2="17" version="1065353216">Absolutely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623391" id2="17" version="1065353216">Just barely.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623392" id2="17" version="1065353216">Nothing could please me more. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623394" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't know why I bothered.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623395" id2="17" version="1065353216">A pity you perceive it this way. I believe you have saved lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623397" id2="17" version="1065353216">The structure will still collapse, but it shall leave no poison in its wake. Perhaps we can rebuild the area after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623399" id2="17" version="1065353216">If there is any way you can destroy the chemicals before their storage building collapses, please--assist us.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623400" id2="17" version="1065353216">What do you think, Kon?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623402" id2="17" version="1065353216">The foundation of the Taris ChemWorks Factory cannot be repaired. I expect total collapse within two weeks.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623404" id2="17" version="1065353216">Once the building falls, the stored chemicals will flood this area. They are... highly toxic to humans. I am sorry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623406" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make sure there are speeders on hand, but we can't just pack up and go. Do what you can.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623408" id2="17" version="1065353216">As always. I will pursue an alternative.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623410" id2="17" version="1065353216">Master Jedi, forgive my inattentiveness. I'm honored by your presence, though I advise you not to stay long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623411" id2="17" version="1065353216">Forgive me, officer--I am aware of your presence, and duly respectful. However, I advise you not to stay long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623412" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse my inattentiveness, mistress--you are with the reconstruction effort? I must advise you not to stay long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623413" id2="17" version="1065353216">Excuse my inattentiveness, master--you are with the reconstruction effort? I advise you not to stay long.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623414" id2="17" version="1065353216">You were talking about evacuation. What's going on?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623414" id2="17" version="1065353216">I overheard that call....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623415" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate the advice, but I could use a reason.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623415" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why shouldn't I stay?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623416" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't need advice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623417" id2="17" version="1065353216">Again, I apologize. Perhaps I can approach this matter differently.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623419" id2="17" version="1065353216">Many of these ruins are unstable. A nearby structure used for chemical storage is on the verge of crumbling.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623421" id2="17" version="1065353216">As I was explaining to my colleague, there is only one way to remove the chemicals before they spill--a burnoff.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623423" id2="17" version="1065353216">A well-armed demolitions team could reach the structure and incinerate the chemical stockpiles. I can provide the incendiaries; unfortunately, no team is available.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623424" id2="17" version="1065353216">You want to plant explosives around a building that's about to collapse?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623424" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sounds dangerous.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623425" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm willing to try.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623426" id2="17" version="1065353216">Your generosity is considerable. You should know, however:</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623428" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't worry. It can't get much worse than this.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="623428" id2="17" version="1065353216">This whole planet's toxic.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623429" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are--apologies--mistaken. These chemicals are known to cause at least seventeen distinct illnesses.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623431" id2="17" version="1065353216">Between the structural instability, the toxicity levels and the incendiary chemicals, the mission does carry substantial risk. It is nonetheless urgent.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623433" id2="17" version="1065353216">You are not a demolitions team--I fully recognize this. But if you could arrange the burnoff, I would humbly welcome your aid.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="623435" id2="17" version="1065353216">Please excuse me. I am studying the latest engineering survey of the ruins....</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
