<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>107</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/location/tatooine/world/republic/forge_the_future/galen_besk.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572940" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tatooine's a safer place, thanks to you. The shadow of Sith won't cross here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572942" id2="17" version="1065353216">Galen. I've done all I can to help the locals.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572943" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's what I keep hearing.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572945" id2="17" version="1065353216">Mayor Airen says her outpost's reopened for trade. She's got visitors from as far as Mos Maran, talking and working together.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572947" id2="17" version="1065353216">There are farmers who aren't afraid of Sand People anymore, militiamen you inspired... you've given Tatooine a reason to fight.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572948" id2="17" version="1065353216">You said if I did this, Tatooine could stop an Imperial takeover.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572948" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about the Empire?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572949" id2="17" version="1065353216">The people who live here did the real work. I just lent a hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572949" id2="17" version="1065353216">I didn't do anything notable.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572950" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's all anyone really needs.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572952" id2="17" version="1065353216">I could be on Coruscant or Alderaan right now. Instead, I've been risking my life for nobodies.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572952" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been helping idiots.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572953" id2="17" version="1065353216">Who would you rather be risking your life for?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572955" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll never be strong enough to beat the Empire, but united, we can convince them we're too much trouble to conquer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572957" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now get out of here before another sandstorm hits. If you can save Tatooine in a day, I imagine the galaxy needs you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572958" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now get out of here before another sandstorm hits. I imagine Darth Angral won't wait much longer.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572959" id2="17" version="1065353216">If I fail at my mission, everything I did here will mean nothing. Tatooine will fall along with many other worlds.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572959" id2="17" version="1065353216">My duties come first, true.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572960" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now get out of here before another sandstorm hits. I imagine those lost Masters you're after can't wait anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572961" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force itself seems troubled by what I face. But I must prevail.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572961" id2="17" version="1065353216">My duties won't be easy.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572962" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll do what the Force requires of you. I can sense that much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572964" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now get out of here before another sandstorm hits. You must be eager to stop those traitors.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572965" id2="17" version="1065353216">I follow my orders and serve the Republic. That's all I ask.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572965" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm just a dutiful soldier.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572966" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force will provide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572968" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now get out of here before another sandstorm hits. The treasure hunt can't wait, can it?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572969" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's time I got a real answer. Who are you, and how do you know about me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572969" id2="17" version="1065353216">All right--who are you really?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572970" id2="17" version="1065353216">I suppose I owe you that much.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572972" id2="17" version="1065353216">Some Jedi boldly save worlds. Others fight empires. And some put their lightsabers aside and help in smaller ways.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572974" id2="17" version="1065353216">No offense, but I barely broke even here. I've got to start turning a profit.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572974" id2="17" version="1065353216">Time to make some money.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572975" id2="17" version="1065353216">You will, someday--but the Force will guide you to interesting places.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wipe that smirk off your face. When you're dead and buried, I'll have the Republic eating out of my hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572977" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go away, old man.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572978" id2="17" version="1065353216">When I'm dead and buried, I'll know I tried my best.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572980" id2="17" version="1065353216">Go on. We won't meet again--and though this planet won't remember you, what you've done will change it forever.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572984" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you don't save that outpost, no one else will.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572989" id2="17" version="1065353216">Get your boy inside. We've got ten minutes before the wind picks up.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572991" id2="17" version="1065353216">What about Chesla?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572993" id2="17" version="1065353216">She's not stupid, she'll be here--just go!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572995" id2="17" version="1065353216">You should get inside, too--there's a sandstorm coming, and the spaceport's a designated shelter. No flights in or out for a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572996" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't get word out to everyone yourself. I'll bring people back--just keep the shelter open.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572996" id2="17" version="1065353216">My duty's to help, not hide.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572997" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Force can be a beacon in a storm. I can help those who're lost find their way here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572997" id2="17" version="1065353216">I volunteer to assist.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572998" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'd expect that from a Jedi. All right, but we lock down in twenty. Move!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="572999" id2="17" version="1065353216">I appreciate the advice, but I don't like sitting around. Let me sweep the town, I'll find anyone left behind.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="572999" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll make sure everyone's in.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573000" id2="17" version="1065353216">Good to see the Republic has a heart. Now move.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573001" id2="17" version="1065353216">Rough flying doesn't scare me. Why don't I grab a speeder, shuttle people back here before the storm hits?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573001" id2="17" version="1065353216">I can lend a hand.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573002" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're a lifesaver, Captain. Just get yourself inside before we lock down!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573007" id2="17" version="1065353216">We've done all we can. Now we wait.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573011" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've been on Tatooine awhile, and I haven't seen any storms.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573011" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are sandstorms common?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573012" id2="17" version="1065353216">They mostly die out crossing the Jundland Wastes, but when they hit, they hit hard.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573014" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll take my chances. My ship is tough.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573014" id2="17" version="1065353216">No way I'm staying here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573015" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not that tough. Besides, hangars are already sealed--you'll have to wait things out like everyone else.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573017" id2="17" version="1065353216">Galen! Dozen more from the farmsteads coming in!</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573019" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess we'll make room. Come on, they'll stay out of your way....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573021" id2="17" version="1065353216">We'll be buried alive in here.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573023" id2="17" version="1065353216">You'll be just fine. Don't worry.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573025" id2="17" version="1065353216">Looks like we got out okay--pretty much everyone did, though we lost three power generators.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573027" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess that's not exciting next to flying around the galaxy, fighting Imperials on Nar Shaddaa and whatnot.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573028" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't compare to fighting--what was it, some Sith Lord causing groundquakes in the desert?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573029" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't compare to tracking down some crazed Jedi Master, I suppose.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573030" id2="17" version="1065353216">Doesn't compare to stopping the &quot;mad bomber of Anchorhead&quot; and his Imperial cronies, but what does?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573031" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not that it compares to the excitement of chasing Jedi and Sith, meeting big-time gangsters....</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573032" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're very well informed, for a--what did you say your job was?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573032" id2="17" version="1065353216">How do you know about me?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573033" id2="17" version="1065353216">Name's Galen. I'm just a man enjoying his retirement, trying to give something back to the community.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573035" id2="17" version="1065353216">I deal with my share of violence, but I don't look down on people who aren't fighting for their lives.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573035" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's not all about excitement.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573036" id2="17" version="1065353216">Not even a little bit?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573038" id2="17" version="1065353216">My business is private.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573039" id2="17" version="1065353216">Of course--I'm pushing my luck keeping you here, I know.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573041" id2="17" version="1065353216">Look, these people have it rough in the best of times, but between pirates and sandstorms and Sand People... we can't take much more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573043" id2="17" version="1065353216">If you leave without finishing the job you started, how long before the Empire claims this planet?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573044" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're asking me to stay--but I've done what I came for.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573044" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;The job I started&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573045" id2="17" version="1065353216">And along the way, you helped out all sorts of people; would it hurt to focus on that, for once?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573047" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tatooine isn't a threat or a strategic asset. I wouldn't worry about the Empire.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573047" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire won't bother you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573048" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Empire's already here! Digging up dirt, testing bombs... they've got a garrison in Mos Ila.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573050" id2="17" version="1065353216">I wouldn't worry. The Empire won't be bothering you anymore.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573050" id2="17" version="1065353216">I took care of the Imperials.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573051" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm grateful for what you did, but we both know they're still out there.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573053" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tatooine isn't part of the Republic, and your fate isn't my concern.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573053" id2="17" version="1065353216">That isn't my problem.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573054" id2="17" version="1065353216">No one's paying me to babysit this planet. What goes on here is up to you.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573054" id2="17" version="1065353216">I don't really care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573055" id2="17" version="1065353216">You've helped us out already--I'm only asking for a day or two more.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573057" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tatooine's only chance is unity--making communities that can stand together against warlords and monsters.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573059" id2="17" version="1065353216">Espelar's our best hope--it's a trading post where farmers, Jawas and leaders from half a dozen towns swap information. The Empire means to burn it to the ground.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573060" id2="17" version="1065353216">How will the Empire &quot;burn it to the ground&quot;?</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573060" id2="17" version="1065353216">Tell me about the threat.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573061" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm sure Espelar is important to Tatooine, but I can't see why the Empire would care.</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573061" id2="17" version="1065353216">Why would one outpost matter?</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573062" id2="17" version="1065353216">With a strong trade outpost, there's strong community and strong resistance. Without....</text>
		<text bitflag="1360" id1="573064" id2="17" version="1065353216">You can't be serious.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573065" id2="17" version="1065353216">I've got pals in the militia, all sorts of places; I'm asking you to trust me.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573067" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sandstorm broke Espelar's defenses, and the Imperials will send in saboteurs. You need to give the people breathing room, help them rebuild.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573069" id2="17" version="1065353216">Stop the Imperials, head into town and help put this planet on the path to being a proud, independent society. Or give up and go--your choice.</text>
		<text bitflag="1345" id1="573073" id2="17" version="1065353216">There's nothing I can do for you, I'm afraid.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
