<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<stb_file>
	<file_info>
		<strs>84</strs>
		<file_name>/resources/en-us/str/cnv/alliance/zakuul/yuun/yuun.stb</file_name>
	</file_info>
	<file_content>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169551" id2="17" version="1065353216">You have returned... and added the extra verses that only you could add.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169552" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm back, as promised.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169553" id2="17" version="1065353216">These objects... reacted to me. Did you know they would do that?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169554" id2="17" version="1065353216">You knew these things would react to me, didn't you? I expect an explanation.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169555" id2="17" version="1065353216">You knew these would react to me and didn't tell me? I demand an explanation.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169556" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun apologizes for any misunderstandings. There is an odd maelstrom swirling about you....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169558" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun suspected, therefore, that only you could walk the path to claim them.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169560" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun apologizes that the exact nature of the link and its larger significance cannot be explained more fully. Yuun lacks the words.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169562" id2="17" version="1065353216">Everything is ready, save for these pieces. Completing the task will take but a moment.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169564" id2="17" version="1065353216">The instrument is complete, and you yourself tuned it earlier.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169566" id2="17" version="1065353216">With sufficient expansion, this device can hide your new base of operations from the long range sensors of the Eternal Fleet.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169567" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's incredible, Yuun. Thank you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169568" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun is humbled by your thanks. In truth, Yuun only found the path--it is you who walked the most critical steps.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169570" id2="17" version="1065353216">You always did manage to work miracles. This will be a huge help to the Alliance.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169571" id2="17" version="1065353216">Are you saying this will keep Arcann's ships from ever finding us?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169572" id2="17" version="1065353216">Now that this device is complete, Yuun shall gladly join you. In truth, Yuun had already seen this joint path approaching.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169574" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun shall make all haste in traveling to Odessen. May our new path lead us to wisdom and justice.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169575" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're making a pretty bold claim. This thing had better work like you say.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169576" id2="17" version="1065353216">There is no call for doubt. It is your own special nature which has guaranteed the device's harmony.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169578" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun eagerly awaits your return, and thanks you again for your help.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169581" id2="17" version="1065353216">You return quickly, as Yuun had hoped. Is it now a more convenient time to assist Yuun?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169582" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yes, let's get to work.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169583" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm still not doing this.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169587" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Wait for his reaction]</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169588" id2="17" version="1065353216">This is not good....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169590" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Yuun urgently checks his breathing equipment]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169591" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey there, Yuun! It's been a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169592" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun's breather is not malfunctioning... you are not a hallucination of atmosphere poisoning....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169594" id2="17" version="1065353216">That's some way to greet an old friend....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169595" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'll admit that I've never understood your creepy Findsman stuff, but that's just rude.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169596" id2="17" version="1065353216">Major! Yuun apologizes greatly, no offense was intended.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169598" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hallucination is a common side effect of atmosphere poisoning in Gand. Yuun feared a breather failure....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169600" id2="17" version="1065353216">Hey there, Yuun! It's been a while.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169601" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir... You... the signs indicated a meeting of great import today but....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169603" id2="17" version="1065353216">Howdy, Bugface. How's the creepy Findsman stuff going?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169604" id2="17" version="1065353216">Sir... You... Apparently not as well as Yuun had thought.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169606" id2="17" version="1065353216">Over a year we searched for you... but no path or trace could be seen. All believed you had not survived the battle.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169608" id2="17" version="1065353216">To find that you are alive shames this Gand as a Findsman, but also instills great joy.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169609" id2="17" version="1065353216">It's good to see you too, Yuun.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169610" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun is happy to hear the feeling is mutual. Still, there must be a greater reason for your visit. You have always acted with purpose, sir.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169611" id2="17" version="1065353216">Guess you can't find everything after all.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169612" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Findsman's path is not a journey to perfection, but understanding. Yuun understands that you have always acted with great purpose, sir--why have you come?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169613" id2="17" version="1065353216">I'm getting the old squad back together, Yuun... and then some. I came here to recruit you.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169614" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pack your gear, soldier! We're moving out.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169615" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun no longer serves in the Republic military, though it is an honor to be sought out regardless. However, the path of Zakuul must be followed to its end before Yuun departs.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169617" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun is gathering parts to assemble a new whole. A poem of technology. Yuun has gathered most of the seventeen pieces already....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169619" id2="17" version="1065353216">If this Gand could humbly impose, your assistance in gathering the remaining parts is required before starting down this new path together.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169620" id2="17" version="1065353216">Always happy to help.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169621" id2="17" version="1065353216">Fine, I'll help. Whatever gets us out of here the quickest.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169622" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun greatly appreciates your patience and help, and provides the locations of the remaining stanzas of the poem.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169624" id2="17" version="1065353216">Do it yourself. I've got better things to do than run errands for you.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169625" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun understands, but this is the path Yuun has seen. Without your assistance, the journey cannot begin.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169626" id2="17" version="1065353216">I said I'm not doing this.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169627" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun understands; you must walk your own path. Yuun will await your return at a more convenient time.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169629" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169630" id2="17" version="1065353216">I take it you're Yuun?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169631" id2="17" version="1065353216">Correct, this Gand is named Yuun.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169633" id2="17" version="1065353216">You, Gand. What is your name?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169634" id2="17" version="1065353216">Greetings. This Gand is named Yuun.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169636" id2="17" version="1065353216">You must be the one Yuun has been expecting.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169637" id2="17" version="1065353216">I represent an Alliance opposing the Eternal Throne. I'm here to convince you to join us.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169638" id2="17" version="1065353216">And thus the signs are made clear. Excellent. Yuun is almost ready to depart.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169639" id2="17" version="1065353216">...Well that was easier than expected.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169640" id2="17" version="1065353216">Pack your things, you're coming with me.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169641" id2="17" version="1065353216">Interesting. You are quite different from how Yuun imagined you would be....</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169642" id2="17" version="1065353216">[Let Yuun Continue]</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169643" id2="17" version="1065353216">Wait... you knew I was coming?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169644" id2="17" version="1065353216">&quot;Knew&quot; is not the correct word. &quot;Felt&quot; is more accurate.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169646" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun has seen the signs of this coming meeting, and thus has been preparing.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169647" id2="17" version="1065353216">Preparing for what?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169648" id2="17" version="1065353216">To join and stand alongside the others who oppose the Eternal Throne.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169649" id2="17" version="1065353216">Great. Let's get going then.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1169650" id2="17" version="1065353216">So you didn't know I was coming, or why I was coming, yet you're already prepared for it....</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169651" id2="17" version="1065353216">Yuun is preparing, not prepared. This Gand apologizes for causing misunderstanding.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169653" id2="17" version="1065353216">The Eternal Empire's technology is a unique new form, and resisting first requires understanding.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169655" id2="17" version="1065353216">We each have our own paths to find.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169779" id2="17" version="1065353216">It is hard to describe, yet somehow in tune with the remaining objects.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169781" id2="17" version="1065353216">Seeing the path and seeing its destination are not always one and the same.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1169784" id2="17" version="1065353216">This device can resonate in perfect harmony with Eternal Empire technology. Thus, it can also resonate in perfect counter to it, each tone negating the other.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188722" id2="17" version="1065353216">You're definitely right about that.</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188723" id2="17" version="1065353216">Skip the philosophy. Are we ready to get to work or not?</text>
		<text bitflag="321" id1="1188724" id2="17" version="1065353216">Don't leave me in the dark again. Ever. Understand?</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1188725" id2="17" version="1065353216">This Gand apologizes further. Full understanding will be cultivated in the future.</text>
		<text bitflag="3393" id1="1188727" id2="17" version="1065353216">At long distances, yes. But it is not a cloaking device. At sufficiently close range, enemy ships may still detect the base. Caution is advisable.</text>
	</file_content>
</stb_file>
